(Lee Hee Jun, Park Hae Soo)
(Kwak Sun Young)
(Song Geon Hee, Suh Ji Hye)
(Yoo Seung Mok, Bek Hyun Jin)
(Heo Jeong Do, Jung Moon Sung)
(Scarecrow)
(This program was supported by the MSIT and KCA.)
(The characters, locations, institutions, groups...)
(in this drama are a work of fiction.)
(Child actors and animals featured...)
(were filmed safely with expert supervision.)
(Central Patriots and Veterans Hall)
The response to the new property law has been overwhelming.
Many are saying it's about time we had a bill that reflects reality.
Even union leaders are welcoming it, saying it's made talks smoother.
Of course. They must have been so frustrated.
Times are changing so fast, but the law just couldn't keep up.
Your approval ratings have been high since the policy took effect, sir.
At this rate, you could consider a presidential run.
Come on, public opinion matters more than the presidency for now.
Hey, our recent interview. Does it air today?
Yes, sir. It's on in ten minutes.
Pull it up.
Suspect in the Kangseong Murders, which terrorized the nation,
has been identified 33 years after the incidents.
Hold on.
Go back. Play that again.
Yes.
In a briefing this morning, police announced...
that following a re-examination by the National Forensic Service,
DNA from evidence collected at three of the crime scenes...
matched that of a current inmate, and an investigation is underway.
The suspect is a man in his 60s, known only as Lee, who is now...
(Scarecrow)
(Episode 5)
Sun Yeong. Hey, are you awake?
- Ji Won... - I'm here.
Why am I here?
You don't remember?
I should be asking you. What happened?
It's...
Someone was chasing me.
I was trying to get away from him and...
Who was it?
I don't know.
Gi Beom. What happened to Gi Beom?
We don't know yet.
- Sun Yeong. Where are you going? - I have to find Gi Beom!
Sun Yeong. You...
Is that the son of a gun?
I found the owner of the handkerchief.
You're saying this is my sister Sun Yeong's?
Sun Yeong embroidered this herself. The only person who'd have one...
just like it is Gi Beom.
So he only covered his face in front of me?
Why?
Detective Kang.
- Well? What happened? - It's just...
We lost him.
Doctor.
How is he?
The surgery was a success. He's stable with no organ damage.
Infection is still a concern, but for now, we'll have to wait.
These are the patient's belongings.
Prosecutor Cha... He went there to give you this...
(Police I.D. Card, Kang Tae Joo)
(Office For Surgery)
You didn't know you were pregnant? You're about three months along.
- Pregnant? - I guess you really didn't know.
What about the baby? Is the baby okay?
Yes. There's nothing to worry about.
Fortunately, you have no signs of a concussion.
We just need to treat the scrapes on your leg, and you'll be fine.
If you feel dizzy or get a headache, come in for an exam.
- Okay. - Thank you, Doctor.
Sun Yeong.
Sun Yeong. Hey, Sun Yeong.
Don't tell my brother. Please. I'll tell him myself.
Okay. Okay, I won't.
Kang Sun Yeong. Who was that guy?
- Tae Joo. - I asked you who did this.
Hey, you!
- Leave her alone. She just woke up. - Answer me!
I don't know. I didn't see him.
- Are you serious? - Why would I lie?
You were with Gi Beom, weren't you?
Why are you bringing up Gi Beom?
Don't tell me you suspect Gi Beom.
Are you out of your mind?
Then what is this? Where's Gi Beom?
Why did something like this happen to you?
I'll explain.
Just let me.
So Gi Beom locked you in a warehouse and just left you there?
He said he'd take care of everything.
I went after him a little later, and someone started following me.
At first, I thought it was the police.
I figured they were tailing me for Gi Beom,
so I tried to lose them.
That's when I fell into the ditch below.
That's it.
I don't remember anything after that.
Kang Sun Yeong.
If you're lying to cover for Gi Beom...
It's all true, Tae Joo.
Are you sure?
What happened to Gi Beom?
We're still after him.
- I stopped Gi Beom's surrender. - What?
What were you thinking? You should've told me!
I was going to.
But you were gone from the station. They said Jeon Kyung Ho might die.
- So what was I supposed to do? - He's not dying. He woke up.
You don't have to worry about that.
Thank goodness.
He's not the problem right now.
Then what is?
(Kangseong Jeil Hospital)
Don't worry about Sun Yeong. I'll stay with her.
I appreciate it.
Doesn't something seem off?
If Gi Beom really is the culprit,
why would he lock Sun Yeong in a warehouse?
Tae Joo, our Gi Beom would never...
Ji Won.
I'm done with the Gi Beom I thought I knew.
It's better for him that way.
Whether he's the culprit or not.
Ji Won, you know why Gi Beom is on the run, don't you?
Please, tell me. What in the world is going on?
Gi Beom is...
He's a suspect in the serial murders case.
What?
I thought you...
were my father's son.
I can't stand having brothers, you see.
Being friends is one thing, though.
Si Yeong! Si Yeong! Hey, Si Yeong! Si Yeong!
What the hell happened here? Si Yeong.
It was you, wasn't it?
You did this, didn't you?
You son of a gun. You finally got to Si Yeong...
If I didn't drink...
Just call Cha Si Yeong's family, you fool.
There's no one at his home.
What do you mean, no one's home?
Si Yeong lives alone in that huge house.
- What about his family? - I think his family lives in Seoul.
Wait, are you interrogating me now?
Let me know when this guy wakes up.
That son of a...
(Judge Nam Sang Jik, Assemblyman Jo Gyeong Mook)
There's no home number.
(Cha Jun Young)
For a mere sergeant's resignation, why involve a commissioner?
A commissioner?
Commissioner Cha Jun Young. How do you not know him?
He's the youngest commissioner ever.
Cha Jun Young.
Cha Si Yeong.
(Public Phone)
Hello?
Is this Commissioner Cha Jun Young?
Speaking.
This is Sergeant Kang Tae Joo from the Kang Seong precinct.
A sergeant?
Why would a sergeant be calling me? Especially this late at night?
I'm calling about Prosecutor Cha Si Yeong.
Prosecutor Cha Si Yeong is in the hospital right now.
The hospital? Why?
He was stabbed during the arrest of a serial killer.
Hold on. So, did you catch the suspect?
- No. - And are you sure he's the killer?
I can't say for certain at this point.
Is that so?
His surgery was successful. I thought you'd be wondering.
I'll hang up now.
Wait. How did you know I'm his brother?
Does he usually go around bragging about me?
I took a lucky guess. From his contacts.
You guessed?
Cha Jun Young, Cha Si Yeong. Anyone could tell they're siblings.
I'm hanging up now.
What the hell is with that guy? He only asks about the suspect.
His own brother gets stabbed, and that's all he asks? Darn it.
So they lost the suspect.
Hey, Kang Sik. It's me, Gi Hwan.
Do you know where my brother, Gi Beom, is?
You don't?
Hey, if you happen to get in touch with Gi Beom,
can you please tell him to call me?
No, it's nothing. Okay, I'll talk to you later.
Who was that calling so early in the morning?
Was that about Gi Beom?
Yes, it was Gi Beom. He said he's safe at his friend's.
- That's a relief. - Where did Gi Beom go?
Let's see, where was it?
Haenam, was it?
He went to help out on a friend's farm there.
Hey, Tae Joo. What brings you here so early?
I ran into him on my way from the market.
Thanks for the ride, Tae Joo. It really helped.
It was nothing. I don't get to visit nearly enough.
How have you been? Everything okay?
- You seem to be in a good mood. - Good mood? Not at all.
Hey, what's with the good mood?
Did you catch Gi Beom? Is that why you're here?
No, dude. It's nothing like that.
Hey, don't even mention Gi Beom to my mom.
I told her he went to visit a friend out of town.
You don't know where he is either? You really have no clue?
I have no idea, the little punk.
He's been out of contact since what happened yesterday.
- How's he doing? - Jeon Kyung Ho?
Don't worry about that piece of trash.
We can wrap it up with a settlement.
What? Are you serious?
That guy isn't exactly innocent himself.
Anyway, we need Gi Beom to draw up the settlement papers.
- When you find him, send him to me. - Okay. Thank you so much, Tae Joo.
I really mean it.
- I'm taking off. - All right.
- Drive safe. - Yes.
Go on.
He's not home? So, where else might he have gone?
It seemed his family had no idea where he was either.
Hey.
How do you know they weren't just putting on an act?
His family thinks he's just wanted for assault.
And his mother didn't even seem to know that much.
Since I let it slip about Jeon Kyung Ho dropping the case,
if Lee Gi Beom isn't the serial killer,
- he's going to react to that news. - So then,
are you saying Lee Gi Beom may not be the culprit?
What kind of crap is that? If it's not Lee Gi Beom, then who?
Your sister was almost attacked where we went to find Lee Gi Beom.
And Prosecutor Cha was attacked.
- It can't be anyone else. - For now, it's all circumstantial.
But it's a mountain of circumstantial evidence.
Chief, we should put out a warrant for Lee Gi Beom's arrest right now.
And we should get a search warrant for his home and the bookstore.
Prosecutor Cha Si Yeong may have seen the culprit.
What if the person he saw wasn't Lee Gi Beom?
Come on, I keep telling you that's impossible.
Let's just wait until Prosecutor Cha wakes up, sir. Okay?
- Chief. - Chief.
Prosecutor Cha will be waking up soon.
We don't have a second to waste.
He's right, Chief. We're really running out of time.
Chief, please.
Quiet! Just be quiet. Let me think for a minute.
- But we're out of time, Chief! - I know!
Yes, Kangseong Police Station.
I'm sorry?
A murder?
Ju Hee, wake up.
Time for breakfast.
Oh my, why are you sleeping in so late?
Come on, get up. Time to eat. You have to get ready for school.
Her mother found her this morning.
It looks like strangulation marks.
Darn it. She's just a kid.
(Crime Scene - Do Not Enter)
This doesn't fit the pattern.
Was the main gate left open?
Apparently, they found it open this morning.
Was the kid home alone last night?
They say her parents were sleeping right in the next room.
This is one sick son of a gun.
Killing a kid with her parents right there...
All under the same roof. This bastard has zero fear.
- What is it? - Come take a look.
Oh, Gosh.
- What's going on? - They're saying a kid was murdered.
- What happened? - What? Is that true?
- A teen was found dead at home. - What happened?
- It's not the serial killer, is it? - Gosh.
What is it?
You remember this place from yesterday, right?
Gotcha.
You son of a gun.
Hey, Do Hyeong Gu.
In my 13 years as a cop, I've never seen you this cool.
- You saw that, didn't you? - It was cool. It was our teamwork.
- I got to take a leak. Back soon. - Just make it quick. Jeez.
Is he a puppy? He's always marking his territory.
Gosh, darn it.
Hey, go do that farther away, you punk. Gosh, honestly.
Hey, where are you going? Hey, grab that bastard!
You son of a gun!
- Hey, follow him, darn it! - Where are you going? That bastard.
That son of a gun!
You son of a gun!
Of all the places...
If that bastard Lee Gi Beom did this...
Shouldn't we tell them what happened yesterday now?
It's making me crazy.
- How is this possible? - This isn't the first time...
- How many victims is that now? - I guess we'll be up all night.
- Does this make any sense? - Oh, my gosh.
Oh, no.
What's all this? Why is our Ju Hee dead?
I was asleep and I didn't hear a thing.
I'm her father,
and I didn't even know my daughter was dying next to me.
I...
was just dead to the world.
What a pathetic bastard.
Hey, don't say that.
Our poor Ju Hee... What are we going to do, honey?
My poor girl. This is all my fault!
I killed her!
- I killed her! - How is this your fault?
It's the fault of the police,
who can't even catch a single killer.
That's right! How many is that now? Is this even a safe place to live?
We can be careful outside, but if they come for us at home?
Exactly. People are dropping like flies!
- Do your jobs properly! - How are we supposed to live?
That's right!
Chief!
Everyone, please calm down.
- Catch the killer already! - Hey, say something!
- Hold on! Just a moment. - Chief.
Please, everyone, settle down.
- I'm okay. Please settle down. - Chief.
I'm the one in charge here.
The fact that our investigation has been lacking...
Yes. I have no excuse.
As chief, I bear the greatest responsibility.
But our detectives and officers have been working around the clock.
Every single one of them is doing their absolute best.
So please, just have a little more faith in us,
and if you can be patient, we will...
Wait for what?
- Just catch him already! - Chief, that's enough. Let's go.
- What are we waiting for? - What about the killer?
I promise you, we will find the killer.
- I promise, we'll find the killer. - Then do your jobs properly!
Where are you going?
- What are you doing? - Do your jobs properly!
- My daughter! What do I do? Ju Hee! - Pull yourself together.
(New Era, New Police)
- Hurry up. - Why?
- Get over here. - You look like hell.
What's going on?
- Commissioner's coming! Line up. - The Commissioner's coming.
- The Commissioner? - The Commissioner.
Put this on first.
Hey, Dae Ho, grab this.
Hey, he's here.
- Just a second. - The Commissioner?
All right, everyone, fall in!
Attention!
Salute!
Welcome, Commissioner.
- Why is he here? - I have no idea.
So, are we supposed to go in too?
(Cha Jun Young)
This was a very difficult decision for the President to make.
He's well aware of all your hard work.
So please, don't take this transfer as a demotion...
Let's just consider it a chance for some well-deserved rest.
(Public Security Status, Kangseong Police Station)
This tea is pretty good.
Get me some water.
Si Yeong? Are you awake?
- I need water. - Water.
Excuse me, Doctor.
Your wound is healing nicely.
But for now, try to keep it dry when you bathe.
- Does that mean I can go home? - Let's see how you are tomorrow.
Alright then.
Thank you, Doctor.
Thank goodness it wasn't any worse.
You wouldn't wake up. I was afraid you wouldn't make it.
The culprit?
They haven't caught him yet.
By the way, while you were out, Kangseong was turned on its head.
In the wake of the serial murders in Kangseong,
Kangseong Police Chief Park Eun Gyu, has been relieved of his duties...
They're replacing the chief in the middle of all this?
And three of the squad leaders too. What the hell is going on?
Appointed as the new chief of the Kangseong Police Station...
is Commissioner Cha Jun Young, the youngest to ever reach the rank.
The sluggish investigation up to this point...
has caused the public's trust in us to hit rock bottom.
We will establish a new task force with a massive injection...
of manpower and plan to put the investigation into high gear.
You said you would speed up the probe.
When can we expect tangible results,
if you had to predict?
An exact timeline is difficult, but if we abandon our passivity...
and take a more proactive stance,
I'm sure we can redeem ourselves from this recent dishonour.
Victims' families have lost faith in the police.
Are you confident you can earn it back?
I will stake the honour of the police force...
- in restoring the public's trust. - Sounds like a big shot's coming.
- We will do our utmost... - In the end, he's just another cop.
You've all worked hard.
Hey, don't look so glum.
This terrible case is happening here, in your hometown.
You must be the ones to catch him. Do it for Kangseong Police's honour.
You have to.
Yes, Chief.
Chief.
Drive safe.
- I'm off. - Yes, sir.
Attention!
Salute the chief!
Thank you for your service, sir.
(Building a Just Society)
Let's head inside.
Where the hell did that bastard Kang Tae Joo go?
After all the chief's done for him. That ungrateful bastard.
Where'd he go?
Hey, what are you doing here?
Were you waiting for me?
What are you grinning about?
Are you that happy to get out of here?
What's not to like? My "demotion" sends me to the coast.
And you know how much I love sea fishing.
Here. Take this.
What's this?
Why do you keep wearing that jacket? You can't get the smell of eggs out.
It bugs me.
- It smells? - Of course it does. Can't you tell?
Geez.
Hey, where'd you get the money for this?
Come on.
I make plenty.
- Hey, isn't this a little big? - That's the size you should be in.
It'll help hide that gut. You're not as skinny as you think.
I don't have a gut, you brat!
Tae Joo.
You're a good detective. But...
Don't do everything on your own. Work with your team.
I have realised something through my career.
That your colleagues are your greatest asset.
Don't you forget it, kid.
Thanks. I'm off.
Always with the nagging.
Take care, Chief.
The autopsy results...
(Investigation Unit 2)
She was sexually assaulted, then strangled to death.
Any leads on the killer?
Yes. At the scene, we found what we believe is the killer's...
body hair and fluids. Once again, the suspect is male, blood type B.
Is that it?
(One: Body Hair, Two: Bodily Fluids)
- Yes, sir. - Gosh.
There's nothing new. This is why the top brass are all getting axed.
- I'm sorry, sir. - Darn it.
Hey, Kang Tae Joo.
- Sir. - What do you think?
Is this another one of the Serial Murders?
I don't believe this is one of the Serial Murders.
Why not?
It's different. A home invasion, not an open attack like the others.
This victim was 14, not the same age group as the others,
and the killer's usual M.O. of tying up the victims...
is missing.
Is that so?
Are you crazy?
What's up with him? Need to take a dump or something?
Yes?
Do you have something to say?
It's... What I am trying to say is...
At around 11pm on the night of the incident,
the suspect Lee Gi Beom was spotted near the victim Ju Hee's home.
We believe he was leaving the house right after the crime.
This is clearly one of the Serial Murders.
Right.
That's all I have.
What a bunch of clowns.
Right?
You kept something that important from us?
Are you out of your mind?
I know, I screwed up big time.
But how was I supposed to know...
that he'd run off and kill again?
Gosh.
Wait, 11pm? That'd be after Prosecutor Cha was attacked.
Exactly.
He escaped the scene and hid in Lee Ju Hee's house.
His movements and the timeline match up perfectly.
Hey, Kang Tae Joo.
You still don't think Lee Gi Beom is the one? Even after this?
This is from His Excellency.
And it's what Father wants too.
Father wants this?
This "democratization" nonsense... The fallout from last year still...
It is going to affect the upcoming by-election.
But you know how important this election is to Father, right?
That's why Father...
wants us to lead this case and solve it together.
- Us brothers? - Yes.
So you're finally acknowledging me as your brother?
Hey.
When were we ever not brothers? We share the same father's blood.
Now you're hurting my feelings.
Get up. Get up!
He'll do better next time.
You know our Si Yeong is a bright boy.
Right?
Father, I was wrong.
Please, just one more chance.
Please, give me 1 more chance. Please? Just 1.
If you want to live in this house as my son,
you have to earn it.
Don't you forget it.
(Report Card, Cha Si Yeong: 2nd Place)
Don't take what Father says lightly.
One wrong move and you're out.
Don't tell me you think you're Father's only illegitimate child.
Gosh. Jeez.
Anyway, get well soon.
Let's do this together.
I'm off.
Goodbye.
Brothers?
There was a time I was dying to hear him say that.
But what can you do?
I'm a little too old to come crying to my big brother anymore.
Commissioner.
I hear they're putting together a new task force.
Has a new chief been assigned yet?
Why would he be curious about that?
You are trying to kiss up to them ahead of time?
No, I couldn't care less about any of that.
Isn't it the position for the person who stands before your people,
whether it's taking the blame or facing the fire?
So, Commissioner, use your influence to get us that kind of person.
Gosh. That arrogant son of a gun...
Hey, hey, how'd you do that?
Here.
What did you say to piss him off like that?
Come on, tell me. I might need to use it someday.
Did you see him?
I saw it. After you told him off, his face just crumpled.
No, the culprit! I'm asking if you saw him.
Gosh, that hurts.
I'm still a patient, you know.
I got stabbed!
Did you see him or not?
- Yes? - I didn't see him.
Why?
Were you expecting me to say a different name?
You're still not convinced...
that Lee Gi Beom is the killer?
You've been like this from the beginning.
Since you brought in Lee Gi Beom as just a person of interest.
You've been way too soft on Lee Gi Beom.
- It's not like that. - Then what is it?
If Lee Gi Beom was the killer on the day you were attacked,
none of his actions or his timeline make any sense.
It's like two different people were in the same place that day.
It's like Gi Beom was one person,
and the culprit of you and Sun Yeong's case was someone else.
- But... - But...
Lee Gi Beom was spotted near the murdered Ju Hee's house.
And it was right after the estimated time of your and Sun Yeong's case.
I was wrong.
Based on the circumstantial evidence, Lee Gi Beom is the killer.
Thanks for saving Sun Yeong.
I haven't told her yet. She's still really shaken up.
I was so sorry.
To you and to Sun Yeong.
I really was.
Sun Yeong, what's wrong?
Did you have a nightmare?
Was it a dream?
Are you worried about Gi Beom?
Ji Won, something's not right.
He just left like that.
And we haven't heard a single word from him since.
It's not like Gi Beom at all.
To be honest, that's been bothering me too.
I'll go check with his family. He might have contacted them.
I'll go with you.
Okay, sure. Let's do that.
Excuse me, hello.
- Hi! - Is Seok Man in?
He just stepped out.
Did my younger brother happen to stop by?
No, I haven't seen him lately. Tell Gi Beom to stop by sometime.
My daughters keep asking for him.
They're driving me crazy asking,
"When's the handsome uncle coming back?"
Okay.
Aren't you getting off here?
- Sorry. - For crying out loud.
Where do you think you're going, you punk?
- Darn it, this little... - Darn it!
Hey! Hey, get back here!
Get back here!
- Darn it! - Gi Beom!
This punk's got a death wish, right?
Hey, go on ahead!
Hey! Are you nuts?
Gosh.
You know that guy, don't you?
What you just saw...
Don't you dare breathe a word of it to anyone.
If you want to live.
Darn it.
Talk, you son of a gun! Talk! You hear me?
You bastard.
Spit it out, you punk!
You piece of trash!
Spit it out! Yes?
You're the one who killed them all, aren't you? Right?
This little bastard.
There's something about this kid...
He seems weirdly familiar.
Hey.
Haven't we met somewhere before?
This son of a...
Hey! Go easy on him.
Don't worry. I didn't mess up his face.
- Still no word on the handkerchief? - Same old story.
He just keeps saying he lost it.
The search warrant just came through.
For real?
Gosh, I'm touched.
Did you come to get me since I'm being discharged?
Here. You handle this.
What's this?
A search warrant?
I'm going to catch the killer.
- As soon as possible. - And how soon is that?
Before the new task force is formed.
Before your brother even has time to unpack.
Hey, I like the sound of that.
I like it a lot.
- Kang Tae Joo got the warrant. - Darn it.
And to think they blew us off when we asked for one.
We got the warrant. That's what counts.
Now what are we going to do with you?
All right, let's go.
Hey!
Spit it out, you punk!
Jeong Sook.
Sun Yeong? What brings you here?
I was just wondering if you'd heard from Gi Beom.
And why would you be asking?
- Didn't you say you two were over? - Ma'am, this is important.
Where is Gi Beom right now?
In Haenam. At his friend's house.
Really? Are you sure about that?
Of course. He even called us saying he was doing fine.
Isn't that right, dear?
Jeong Sook, is that true? Did he really call?
Well, the thing is...
Man, this weather is brutal.
All right, line up.
If you find anything suspicious, confiscate it on the spot. Got it?
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Excuse me, what is this all about? What's going on?
What? Is that really true?
So you haven't heard from Gi Beom? Not even once?
- No. - Why are you just telling me now?
He said you'd worry...
- We're going in. - Hey, what are you doing?
Darn it. This maggot. Darn it.
Honey.
- Gi Hwan. - Detective Jang, what's going on?
Well, there you are.
- Are you Lee Gi Beom's mother? - I am.
This is a search and seizure warrant for Lee Gi Beom.
We'll need your full cooperation.
- All right, tear this place apart. - Yes, sir.
Please, I...
Why? Why are you doing this to us?
- Oh, my gosh. - Mother, Mother.
What do you think you're doing?
Gosh, what are we going to do?
Now, where should I start?
- Hey, tear this place apart. - Yes, sir.
(Take The Lost Items.)
(Das Kapital 1-1)
This bastard... He's a darn commie too?
Wait a second.
Stop right there, you son of a gun.
Gotcha, you little rat.
(Take The Lost Items.)
Hey, just let the other detectives handle it.
You don't need to get involved personally.
Hey! Hey, you fool!
Gosh, he's so stubborn.
Don't we deserve to know why you're doing this?
Move it, or I'll arrest you for obstructing justice.
What could my brother have possibly done so wrong?
You sure ask a lot of questions.
Your brother, Lee Gi Beom, is a serial murder suspect.
What did you just say?
Serial murder? That's ridiculous. Don't make me laugh.
- Tae Joo. - Detective Kang. Why are you late?
- Tae Joo. - Prosecutor.
Tae Joo, you've come at the perfect time.
These men are spouting complete nonsense.
They're calling my Gi Beom a serial killer.
The boy wouldn't even hurt a fly. How could he possibly kill people?
Tae Joo, please, you have to stop them.
Calm his mother down first.
It's true. Gi Beom is a serial murder suspect.
And he's currently on the run.
Have you heard from Gi Beom at all?
We have to find him, Ma'am.
Do you suspect my Gi Beom too?
Come on, answer me.
I asked if you suspect Gi Beom too!
Yes.
He's a suspect, so I have to investigate.
If Gi Beom has been framed, I'll find a way to clear his name.
But if he's guilty, I'll be the one to bring him in.
So, if you truly believe in Gi Beom,
then trust me and cooperate with the investigation.
- Search the suspect's room first. - Why, you...
- You bastard, I ought to... - Mother, Mother! Calm down.
- Let me go! Let go! - Please, calm down.
I said, let me go!
This is all your fault!
If you, as the eldest son, had just made some decent friends,
- none of this would've happened! - That's enough, Mother.
Don't you dare call me Mother.
I cooked for you and your sister when your own mother never did.
I was the one who fed you. Me!
But you? Of all people, you're trying to ruin my son's life?
Oh, dear.
- Ma'am. - Ma'am.
- Ma'am, ma'am. - Ma'am! Ma'am!
Ma'am, are you all right?
- Ma'am, hold on. - Just a moment.
Get your hands off me!
Sun Yeong, you...
Don't tell me...
It's Gi Beom's.
I can't believe you. Hey! Are you out of your mind?
He's a serial killer! How could you have his baby?
Don't say that about him.
It wasn't Gi Beom.
I remember what happened that day.
I clearly remember the man's back who dragged me away that day.
- It wasn't Gi Beom. - That's ridiculous.
Those fields had no street lights. You couldn't see a thing.
The man was limping on one leg, like he was hurt. I swear.
Just stop.
Even if you were telling the truth, I wouldn't believe you.
You'd even twist your own memories to protect Gi Beom.
- Tae Joo... - Sun Yeong, go wait in my car.
No, Ji Won, but...
Nothing you say changes anything. Don't waste your breath. Go wait.
Go.
Go wait.
So you're not going to investigate this properly?
That's what I'm trying to do now. So what?
If I hadn't foolishly trusted him and stalled on this,
things never would have gotten this bad.
That's a laugh.
Don't kid yourself. You're not some sentimental guy.
The only reason you hesitated was because you had no evidence.
Because the pieces didn't fit, and it didn't make sense.
That's the kind of cop you are, Kang Tae Joo.
Darn it.
- What? - Hey, what is it?
Here.
Son of a gun...
Look at this.
Detective Kang.
I had a feeling you and Lee Gi Beom went way back,
but I had no idea you two were this close.
(December 13, 1987)
- Hey, it's been a while. - Tae Joo, you're late.
Yes, work held me up, so I got a late start from Seoul.
- So where's the groom? - He's in the bathroom.
I think he's got an upset stomach.
- He must've accepted every drink. - Tell me about it.
- Hey. - Hey there.
Long time no see.
Hey, everyone's getting hitched. When are you going to?
You are even seeing anyone?
- That's... - Hey, Tae Joo!
What took you so long? The ceremony's already over.
Hey, you should just be glad I showed up at all, you brat.
Here's the gift money.
Thanks!
Tae Joo, let's take a picture. We have to have proof you were here.
A picture? Dressed like this? No way, man.
- I'll take a picture for you guys. - Gi Beom, you have to be in it too.
Hey, Yong Taek, can you take a picture for us?
Yes, sure.
Just one.
Okay, ready? One, two, three.
December 13, 1987.
If you two were this close, shouldn't you have recused yourself?
Hey, Kang Tae Joo.
Look at that son of a gun.
Bolting now that things are getting tough?
Choi In Sook went missing on December 13, 1987.
Estimated time of the crime, 8:30pm.
(Incident: 8:30pm, Dec. 13, 1987)
(December 13, 1987)
Gi Beom was with me then.
How is that possible?
- Who'd have thought to look there? - Tell me about it.
Kang Tae Joo, you're here already.
Sir, we found evidence proving Lee Gi Beom is the killer.
What?
This.
What is this?
Inside this,
we found this.
And this belongs to Park Ae Sook?
Yes.
I just came from confirming it with Ms. Park Ae Sook herself.
She confirmed she lost it on the day she kidnapped.
(ID Card: Park Ae Sook)
I wonder where the prosecutor is.
Probably at the office.
There he is. Got him.
- Hey, I'm going to go report this. - Yes, sir.
Park Ae Sook's handbag, found in the bookstore.
That's evidence pointing to Gi Beom as the killer.
But the photo we found at the house proves Gi Beom's alibi.
The two pieces of evidence are telling different stories.
What's going on?
What on earth am I missing?
Tae Joo. Hey, Tae Joo.
What did you mean by that earlier?
Why are you calling my brother a murderer?
Gi Hwan, not now.
Hey!
When did you start suspecting my brother?
Don't tell me it was since you came to our house.
The settlement was just an excuse,
and you were really there to go after my brother?
Is that it?
- Answer me, you bastard! - How could I not?
What?
We found the victim's belongings at the bookstore,
the victims Yoo Jeong Rin and Kim Min Ji...
were last seen at your bookstore,
and the killer was wearing Gi Beom's handkerchief.
And you expect me not to suspect him?
What was found in the bookstore?
Gi Hwan, look...
None of this makes sense unless Gi Beom is the killer.
If it's not Gi Beom, then who else could...
Besides Gi Beom,
someone who could come and go from the bookstore and the house.
There might...
be another suspect.
Mr. Lee Yong Woo, have you been well?
Where's the other guy?
Professor Kang Tae Joo went back to his actual job.
He has a paper he needs to finish too.
So meeting with me...
is less important than his paper?
That's not it at all...
Lee Yong Woo has clammed up again.
He's gone right back to how he was when we first met.
He's not just hostile. He's being deliberately difficult.
Why on earth did you quit?
Especially after you'd built such a good rapport with him.
That's a job for you active officers now.
And stop trying to work this old man to the bone.
Please, just tell me what to do, sir.
A way to get Lee Yong Woo to talk.
Lee Yong Woo has already made up his mind.
To tell the truth.
So it shouldn't be too hard.
Right.
Lee Yong Woo asked me to give you something.
He called it a gift, or something like that.
A gift?
(Murders: 14, Rapes: 19, Attempts: 15)
What are these numbers?
The truth.
(Scarecrow)
The culprit is identified as Lee, a resident of Kangseong...
Lee Gi Beom just confessed to everything.
Gi Beom, was it really you? Answer me.
Was it really you? So you tried to kill Sun Yeong too?
She's not my family.
- A comment, please! - Just say something!
Are you the real killer in the serial murder case?
Did Lee Gi Beom really say this?
This is all public knowledge, and some parts are just plain wrong.
The illegal arrest, the assault...
If Prosecutor Cha finds out what you've done...