(Lee Hee Jun, Park Hae Soo)
(Kwak Sun Young)
(Song Geon Hee, Suh Ji Hye)
(Yoo Seung Mok, Bek Hyun Jin)
(Heo Jeong Do, Jung Moon Sung)
(The Scarecrow)
(This program was supported by the MSIT and KCA.)
(The characters, locations, institutions, groups...)
(in this drama are a work of fiction.)
(Child actors and animals featured...)
(were filmed safely with expert supervision.)
Did I hear that right?
Aren't you going to sing?
At first, I was just trying to scare them.
But making someone afraid of me felt pretty good, you know?
Like I'd finally become somebody.
And then?
Was there a specific trigger for your first murder?
What is going on today?
It all started...
with a single pebble.
Who's there?
Is anybody there?
If I hadn't been hit by that stone...
If I hadn't gotten caught,
would things have turned out differently?
It may have started by chance,
but maybe it was always my destiny.
Did anyone...
ever find out you were the killer?
Let's see.
If they had found out,
I would've been caught by now, wouldn't I?
Right?
(The Scarecrow)
Here you go. Have some of this.
Thank you.
You're Seok Man's sister-in-law, right?
He's just a boy working for us. But now, we're like family.
I assumed you were family since you're so good to him.
Family is what you make of it. Sharing your lives makes you family.
But still, my heart goes out to that boy, Seok Man.
His family scattered across the nation looking for work,
and he came here when he was only about 18.
By the way, about his leg, when did that happen?
I heard he had polio when he was young.
And he can't run?
Goodness, no. How could he run on that leg?
Even walking is a struggle for him. The poor thing can barely manage.
When we get to the hospital, see the doctor without a fuss.
Don't cause any trouble.
Okay.
(Police)
What is it?
We're from the Prosecutor's Office.
We're here to transfer Lee Gi Beom to the detention center.
What?
We haven't been notified of any such order.
Then feel free to check with your station.
- Why wait? Get him out of there. - Yes, sir.
Hey, wait a minute.
Hey!
Who authorized this?
You can't just barge in here like this.
We've safely transferred Lee Gi Beom to the detention center.
- No visitors are allowed. - Okay, good work.
You can head home straight from there.
Don't worry. I've taken care of everything.
Thank you for handling this for us.
Still, you shouldn't have beaten him up so badly.
When I heard you were attacked,
we got carried away with anger.
I had no idea you detectives cared so much for me.
If that's the case,
then I suppose I'll have to take...
full responsibility for the both of you.
Thank you, sir.
- Get back to work. - Yes, sir. We'll go, Prosecutor.
Thank you.
Hey.
What are you thanking him for? That son of a gun made us do it.
Watch your mouth.
Once we mention Prosecutor Cha, we're both done for.
Don't you forget it.
Okay, Seok Man.
Do you remember the detectives who arrested Gi Beom?
(Investigation Unit)
Yes.
Point them out.
It's these two.
Jang Myeong Do.
Do Hyeong Gu.
You knew Gi Beom's family was looking for him, didn't you?
Why didn't you say anything?
They told me to keep my mouth shut.
These two...
threatened you, right?
Yes.
Seok Man.
Why were you there that day?
Near Lee Ju Hee's house, I mean.
Especially at that time of night.
And with your bad leg.
Well... It's...
I don't really remember why I was there. Is it important?
That's understandable.
It happens.
I tend to be pretty forgetful.
(New Era, New Police)
Thanks for coming in.
It was no problem.
Hey, Seok Man.
What's your take on Gi Beom?
- Gi Beom? - Yes.
He's handsome, kind...
and really popular with the ladies.
But why do you ask?
It just seems like someone's intentionally trying to frame him.
It seems like someone has a grudge against him,
so does anyone come to mind?
There are guys trying to pick fights with him.
Who are they?
They say he hits on girls, or something like that.
He's so popular, so I guess they're just jealous.
Unbelievable.
Just pathetic, right?
I should get going now.
Okay. Sorry I can't give you a ride home.
- It's fine. I'll take the bus. - Okay.
Oh, dear.
What are you doing here?
Your daughter told me before she left...
to make sure you take your medicine.
Couldn't she ask someone else? Fine, whatever. Just take it away.
You don't have to do this anymore. We're nothing to each other now.
Hate me if you want, but please take your medicine.
Everyone's talking ill of Gi Beom. Will you lie here doing nothing?
We have to tell them that's not him, that he's innocent.
If they won't listen, we must shout a hundred, a thousand times.
I can't do this on my own.
Please, you need to get your strength back too.
Here you go.
(Witness Statement)
(Lee Gi Beom was caught by the detectives while resisting arrest.)
This testimony suggests Lee Gi Beom might be innocent.
Please start the internal investigation...
into Jang Myeong Do and Do Hyeong Gu.
An internal investigation? We've not questioned the victim yet.
What do you mean?
Lee Gi Beom was sent to detention. No visitation allowed.
Si Yeong was one step ahead of us.
You can't just go and tip your hand to the enemy like that.
What were you thinking?
Darn it.
So what now?
It's frustrating that he got one over on us.
Want me to tell you his weak spot?
Why would I say no?
Hey, come here. Closer.
I shouldn't do this as his brother,
but I'm telling you because I feel for you.
Si Yeong...
is a complete child.
He's still terrified of Father.
I bet he'd do anything to avoid disappointing his father.
(Kangseong Daily)
Wait, is that for real?
Yes, we have a witness.
They illegally arrested him and had the victim's purse.
If that's true, it means Gi Beom might be innocent.
Lee Gi Beom confessed everything the very day he was arrested.
Was he tortured or something?
I knew it. There's no way Gi Beom is a killer.
We should be the first to break the story.
Think this through.
If Lee Gi Beom is the real killer, we'll face serious backlash.
We have to run it anyway. We're journalists.
Ji Won.
What?
- Someone's here to see you. - Who?
- What did you say? - I have a favour to ask.
For your article,
just add one single sentence for me.
"The investigation headquarters has found another prime suspect."
First of all, is that true?
Who is it?
I can't reveal that yet.
Hey, don't worry. I'm not bluffing.
If you can't go public, why should I write the story?
Gi Beom's locked up in the detention center.
Visitors are not allowed.
- I can't see him. - What?
They silenced him so we can't even begin our investigation.
At this point, Im Seok Man's testimony alone...
- isn't enough to get Gi Beom out. - Those sons of witches.
If word gets out that there's a new suspect,
they can't keep treating him badly like they have been.
They'll start to wonder if he's really the culprit.
So you're saying you haven't even shared anything...
about the new suspect within the police?
The suspect is Im Seok Man, right?
I knew it. Something felt off when you asked if he could run.
First Gi Beom, then Gi Hwan, and now Seok Man?
Are you suspecting Seok Man because of Park Ae Sook's handbag?
There's more.
The place where Gi Beom was arrested...
was in front of Lee Ju Hee's house.
But if Seok Man witnessed it,
that means he was also there at the time of the murder.
- But Seok Man, his leg... - That's why...
- I'm going to check it out myself. - Check what?
- Whether or not that guy can run. - No.
Even if he can't run,
I need to know if he could've still committed the crime.
- The culprit chased me that day. - Did you see the culprit run?
Of course he ran. He had to, to chase me.
- He struck me with a rock. - What if he threw it?
That's a real stretch.
Don't worry. I won't make any rash moves.
I'll conduct a full investigation. Until it is done,
I'll keep the suspect's identity completely under wraps.
Please, write the article.
Even if I can't show my hand, they need to know they might be wrong.
What did Tae Joo say?
Did he tell you not to run the story?
Do you have a ball?
A ball?
Stand right about here, okay?
And when I give the signal, you throw this, all right?
You want me to hit you with this?
- That's going to be hurt. - Let's see you hit me first.
All right.
Ready... Go!
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five! Now!
Ji Won...
Hey. What happened?
Did I get you?
You...
What was that?
So I hit you.
You almost got me.
Oh my...
Is this for real?
Hello.
That's right.
Tell the others to join the Investigation HQ as scheduled.
The investigation headquarters? Why?
The case is pretty much wrapped up. Do we really need to?
Kang Tae Joo's request.
- What? - I thought you two were friends.
I guess you're not that close.
(Culprit arrested... But was it a coerced confession?)
A certain Mr. Lee, prime suspect in Kangseong murders,
was illegally arrested by police, sparking a major controversy.
The actual time of his arrest was confirmed to be...
- five days earlier than reported... - Where's Prosecutor Cha?
- What Mr. Lee endured... - He's not here yet, sir.
Is still unknown.
Mr. Lee confessed after his arrest, but there are claims of assault...
or a coercive investigation during his detainment...
are now being raised.
If his confession was coerced, the fallout will be immense.
Meanwhile, the newly formed Investigation Headquarters...
has reportedly identified another prime suspect,
making the public wonder which of the two is the real killer.
Assemble the internal affairs team.
Right now!
"Another prime suspect."
That punk is holding out, even on me?
Police have announced they will use the latest forensic techniques...
to identify the real killer.
(Kangseong Police Station)
Detective Kang.
- Hello. - A word, please.
A "prime suspect" this prosecutor knows nothing about?
He's not a prime suspect. He's just a person of interest.
Reporter Seo must've heard a rumour and ran with it.
- So why wasn't I briefed? - No physical evidence yet, so...
Don't give me that nonsense. You think I don't know you?
When you get a suspect in sight, you go full steam ahead.
I regret it, and what happened to Gi Beom was my fault.
I actually learn from my mistakes, unlike someone.
Who is the suspect?
I'll tell you when the investigation's over.
Then what's this?
"New forensic methods." What's that about?
- That's also not verified yet... - Are you screwing with me?
What is your angle here?
I don't have an angle.
I said I'd investigate and report, Prosecutor Cha, didn't I?
So just go and wait patiently.
I just need to confirm one thing and it's over.
- Just one thing? - Yes.
Just one.
Then let me confirm one thing with you, too.
When you got stabbed,
did you see anything of the culprit?
- Like a distinctive walk. - I don't know, darn it.
Just one thing?
- Sir. - Hey. Did you find out?
Yes.
It's confirmed, Im Seok Man is Type B.
(Medical record)
(Im Seok Man, Blood Type: B)
- Okay, let's go. - Right.
Since it leaked to the press,
an internal investigation is unavoidable.
Have you made sure the detectives will keep quiet?
You don't have to worry about that.
They won't bring me up.
As it happens,
your mother's condition has worsened.
Take some time off.
And don't get tangled up in this mess.
But...
I'll wrap up the investigation quickly.
You're lucky your brother was here.
How long are you going to keep relying on your brother?
- Are you leaving? - I have to.
I've got a mountain of work to do.
Wait... Mom...
Is she doing that badly?
- Hello. - You're here.
Could you please put these where she can see them?
Your son brought you some beautiful flowers.
I'll go put them in a vase.
Mom.
I'm here.
My baby, you're here?
Si Yeong, where's your report card?
Your grades didn't drop, did they?
You don't have to worry about that anymore.
Si Yeong.
Don't defy your father.
Your father...
is a terrifying man.
He would throw us out in a heartbeat.
Mom. I'm a prosecutor.
A prosecutor in this country.
No one can touch me. Not even my father.
And I'm getting married.
To a woman from a very powerful family.
That's wonderful.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Thank you so much.
So please, just rest easy, Mom.
Don't worry about a thing.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Do you admit to the unlawful arrest of Lee Gi Beom?
Like I told you, it wasn't an illegal arrest.
The prosecutor in charge was injured, so I had no choice!
We had no idea when the prosecutor would even wake up.
If the 48-hour hold had expired, the suspect...
Were we supposed to just let the suspect walk away?
What did you do with him locked up? Did you torture him?
- Torture? I just asked questions. - You verbally abused him, right?
Come on, don't be so harsh. We're both detectives, aren't we?
You know you have to yell and build tension to make them talk.
Unbelievable.
Seok Man, I steamed some potatoes,
so feed the kids and fold the laundry.
Okay, have a good time.
Mommy's heading out, sweeties.
- Bye-bye, Mommy. - Okay, sweetie.
Hey, kids.
Are you guys hungry?
Want some potatoes?
Kyung Jin, I told you not to draw on this.
This belongs to a friend of mine.
- Don't cry. - I hate you!
I'm sorry.
You must be hungry. Should we have some potatoes?
It's hot.
I want to try it.
I want to come up too.
Come on up.
Hey, kids, let's eat the potatoes.
Su Jin!
Su Jin, are you okay? Are you hurt?
I'm okay.
Oh my, you're super fast!
Of course. I'm a great runner.
I told you not to climb on dangerous places, didn't I?
I won't do it again.
Promise.
You need to grow up big and strong, and stay safe.
So you can grow up and marry me, right?
What brings you here?
Seok Man. You're Type B, aren't you?
Yes.
Well, this is awkward.
I'm afraid I have to ask you a pretty awkward favour.
What kind of favour?
I need you to take off your underwear.
What?
Your underwear.
- Get this to Dr. Jo right away. - Yes, sir.
(Unidentified Suspect's Body Hair)
But sir...
How'd you get him to take off his underwear?
You want to know?
I begged and pleaded.
What could you have possibly said to get him to do that?
I told him the brass handed down a quota.
They told us to get pubes from 20 Type B guys each.
I told him, "You have to help me out."
And he just took off his underwear for that?
I told him, "Whoever refuses is the culprit."
No way.
Are you Type B? Do you want to take off your underwear?
Do you want me to get one of your pubes?
Get out of here, you punk!
Hey, and tell Dr. Jo to call me the second the results are in.
- Yes, sir. - Right.
(Investigation Division)
What's this?
Give it to me.
Stop.
"Suspect Un..."
Is his last name Un?
- And four syllables? - For crying out loud.
Who is it? You know who it is, don't you?
- I don't know. - Spit it out, you punk.
- You're with Kang Tae Joo. Tell me. - I really don't know!
Tell me the truth.
- It's a bluff, isn't it? - What do you mean, a bluff?
You know Park Ae Sook's handbag that was found at the bookstore?
He's the one who planted it there.
- What? - Also,
at Lee Ju Hee's murder scene,
he was there too.
Well, I'm off.
Is that true?
Yes, that's what Detective Park said.
The suspect was at Lee Ju Hee's murder scene too?
Yes.
That's impossible.
Detective Do and I combed that area to catch Lee Gi Beom.
We didn't see anyone suspicious. Except for the guy with the limp.
Wait.
A limp?
Yes.
I just need to confirm one thing and it's over.
When you got stabbed, did you see anything of the culprit?
Like a distinctive walk.
And you're just telling me this now?
Who was he? Did you ID him?
You didn't?
He's someone Lee Gi Beom knows, so I just figured...
- He's a friend of Lee Gi Beom? - Yes.
But don't worry. I made sure he kept his mouth...
I'm not asking you to shut him up. Who is he?
(Ministry of Justice)
(Emergency Transport)
(Kangseong District Prosecutors' Office)
About the time you were arrested...
Who was it that saw you?
I heard it was someone you know.
I don't know.
Look, I think you're misunderstanding something.
We've found evidence suggesting he might be the real killer.
- What are you talking... - It was him.
He planted Park Ae Sook's purse in your bookstore.
And you know that purse is the key evidence that framed you, right?
That's why I'm asking you.
So cooperate.
Let's be honest. If he's the killer, that's good for you, isn't it?
His name.
It can't be him.
- What did you say? - I said he's not the killer!
You son of a witch! Show respect when the Prosecutor is speaking!
- That's enough. - I'll handle him.
Stop!
Get a grip.
It was the same back then.
"Just give us the name of one of your fellow protestors."
They said they'd let me go.
They tried sweet-talking, threatening, and they even beat me.
So I talked.
And just like they promised, I was released.
But my friend...
couldn't return.
The school that my friend never returned to...
I couldn't bring myself to go back.
Not again.
I can't lose another friend that way.
I think Detective Kang is barking up the wrong tree this time.
The guy can barely walk.
The real killer's escaped often. How could a guy with a limp...
No!
Are you all blind? Don't you see him?
- Excuse me? - Lee Gi Beom.
If he were the real killer, would he be acting like that?
Is Lee Gi Beom really our man?
Gi Beom.
- Tae Joo. - You can't be here. No visitors.
I'm family.
I just need five minutes.
Five minutes. That's it.
How are you holding up?
I'm getting better.
I'm sorry.
Honestly, I suspected you.
When I heard that you followed Min Ji that day,
I wondered if you only gave her an umbrella.
I doubted you.
You were just doing your job.
I don't hold it against you.
Tae Joo.
I can get out of here, right?
I need to be out before Sun Yeong has the baby.
That will be too late.
Before Sun Yeong starts showing,
you two should have the wedding.
Yes.
(Italian Bakery)
The news must have been quite a shock.
I had no idea Lee Gi Beom was illegally arrested.
As a prosecutor, I'm truly ashamed.
Don't say that.
Prosecutor, you were in the hospital after getting hurt saving me.
No, that's no excuse.
I'm going to conduct a proper investigation now.
So does that mean Gi Beom can get out?
Fortunately, it turns out there's a witness.
He's apparently Gi Beom's friend. If we can just find him...
Gi Beom's friend? Who is it?
I'm not sure of the name. All I know is he has a bad leg...
Im Seok Man?
Seok Man?
Sorry, who?
Investigator.
I need you to look into this guy, Im Seok Man, right away.
See if he has a criminal record, and find out his blood type.
His blood type is Type B.
And he has no prior convictions.
Why don't you two get some coffee somewhere else?
Yes, sir.
What is this?
It's data comparing hair sample found at the crime scene...
to Im Seok Man's.
Are you sure about that?
Yes. Your suspect's hair sample also had high titanium and sodium.
It's a match.
(Radioactive Isotope Analysis Report)
"Radioactive Isotope Analysis?"
This is it?
This is your so-called scientific investigation method?
You wanted to know.
The Nuclear Research Institute? Not the National Forensic Service?
You see that there?
"The culprit is a sweaty labourer,"
"like a welder working with iron."
Im Seok Man fits this description to a T.
And Im Seok Man brought the purse of Park Ae Sook...
to Lee Gi Beom's bookstore.
Come on, you think this is a coincidence?
- I heard he can't run. - He can run.
I saw it with my own two eyes.
This is insane.
Changing the lead suspect before a trial is no big deal.
But once the trial begins,
there's no turning back.
I bet he'd do anything to avoid disappointing his father.
Imagine that the suspect you indict ends up getting acquitted.
And your father's election is just around the corner.
Hey, are you sure you'll be okay with that?
Seok Man's not here. He went out.
Where did he go?
I'm not sure. Hey, did Seok Man go to work today?
He doesn't have any work today. He has no off-site jobs, remember?
He said he was going to meet a friend.
Seok Man.
What are you doing here this late?
Well...
I came to return something to you.
A friend? Who was it?
I don't know. He said he was going to return a friend's handkerchief.
This one?
Hey, this is not yours.
Hey, can I take a look at that?
What is it?
A handkerchief.
A handkerchief?
You mean Gi Beom's handkerchief?
Yes.
Why do you have it?
I think Gi Beom must have left it at my house.
When was that?
- I'm not sure. - Think hard.
How long have you had it?
I can't really remember...
Where is it right now? Is it at your house?
- Yes. - Let's go to your place.
Right now?
- What are you waiting for? Come on. - Okay.
Sun Yeong, wait up. Slow down.
Come on, hurry up. We're running out of time.
Are you mad at me?
Because of the handkerchief?
That's part of it.
I heard you saw Gi Beom get taken away.
Why didn't you say anything?
You knew I was looking for him.
Honestly...
I thought he was the killer.
What?
Why else would the cops have taken him in like that?
How could you even suspect Gi Beom?
- You know him best. - But the way the cops acted...
Are the cops always right?
Is that really what you think?
There are innocent people who get framed.
A lot of them. Gi Beom is one of them.
It's all because of that stupid handkerchief...
You really don't remember how long it's been at your house?
I'm not sure.
Okay, Ji Won was hospitalized the same day I was.
September 7. Was it before that or after?
- I really can't remember... - Stop saying you can't remember.
Try your best to remember.
It might have been before.
Before? Are you sure?
So what does that mean?
What do you mean? It means we can clear his name!
Then, the killer must have had it after Gi Beom lost it.
So, the killer isn't Gi Beom, but whoever had it then...
Sun Yeong.
Stay away from me!
No, it can't be.
The killer...
is you?
What?
Answer me!
How could you even think that?
You trust Gi Beom without question, but you suspect me?
- Sun Yeong! Are you okay? - Get away from me!
Don't come near me!
What is wrong with you? What did I do?
Sun Yeong!
Sun Yeong.
Tae Joo.
- Im Seok Man, you punk! - Sun Yeong.
- Im Seok Man! - Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Hey.
You're under arrest as a suspect for the serial murders.
No, it wasn't me!
I'm telling you it wasn't me!
Please...
It really wasn't me.
Why would I kill anyone? Why would I do that?
Then what's this?
- Why do you have this? - That's...
I don't know.
It's obvious. Gi Beom dropped it. That's just like him.
He says something is precious, but he's always dropping it.
And after Sun Yeong worked so hard to make it, why did he...
There are guys trying to pick fights with him.
They say he hits on girls, or something like that.
He's so popular, so I guess they're just jealous.
Did you...
had a crush on Sun Yeong, didn't you?
Is that why you hated Gi Beom?
- Because Gi Beom liked Sun Yeong? - I liked her first!
What?
I'm the one who liked her first!
- Oh my goodness. - It's just like mine.
It's so pretty.
I made this myself.
- Really? - Yes.
Thank you.
I have something for you too.
You do?
Close your eyes.
He knew I liked her.
But he still confessed his feelings to Sun Yeong.
What kind of friend does that?
Do you have any idea how long they've known each other?
You're the one who butted in.
You planted that purse to frame Gi Beom, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
- It's the truth, Tae Joo. - Don't you dare call me that!
The thought of a piece of trash like you being anywhere...
near Sun Yeong and Gi Beom...
is chilling and disgusting.
Do you have any idea how many people are dead because of you?
You have the nerve to call yourself human?
- Tae Joo. - Call me that one more time.
And I'll rip your mouth off.
The sooner you repent and confess, the better.
Spend the rest of your life atoning for the people you killed.
In the Kangseong serial murders, where seven women were killed...
for the past two years,
the killer has finally been apprehended.
How was the suspect apprehended?
Yes, we found evidence of the crimes at the suspect's home,
and through radioisotope analysis...
by the Korea Atomic Energy Research Institute,
we confirmed that the suspect is indeed the culprit.
So you're saying you're certain you have the real killer this time?
Yes, we are certain.
What is all this?
What's the special occasion?
Ji Won!
Ji Won, you made it.
You can help out too. We've still got a lot of work to do.
You're missing the most important part.
For someone just out of jail, nothing's more important than tofu.
Tofu? On a day like today, he needs meat.
Mother, they say it means you won't go to jail again.
All right, come on, let's get frying.
So when is Gi Beom getting here?
Gi Hwan went to pick him up, so they should be here any minute.
Everyone's at home waiting for you.
Sun Yeong's there too.
Sun Yeong?
Mom gave you two her blessing.
Really?
- Wait, how? - Sun Yeong went to bat for you.
I can't wait to see everyone.
Hey, what's wrong?
I'm just a little hungry.
You scared me.
I guess it makes sense you'd be hungry.
I doubt the food at the detention center was good.
Don't worry, Mom cooked up a storm for you.
Right.
My wife told me to pick up a cake.
You missed your birthday in there.
A cake? Forget it.
Just take me home.
Come on. It'll only take a second.
- Hey. - Yes?
I'm going to get some sleep.
Yes, okay. Go ahead and sleep. Rest up, all right?
I'll wake you up when we get home.
Gi Beom.
Gi Beom, wake up. We're home.
You look so worn out.
You've been through so much.
I thought I'd never see you again.
Don't say that.
I'm so glad you're back safely. I really am.
Sun Yeong.
From now on,
let's live a normal life.
Let's get married like everyone else,
have kids like everyone else,
and just grow old together.
Just like everyone else.
Okay.
Like everyone else.
Just like that.
Hey, Gi Beom. You won't believe it. They had your favourite cake.
You asleep?
Gi Beom.
What's wrong?
Hey, Gi Beom!
Gi Beom, wake up.
Gi Beom!
What's happening?
Hey!
Gi Beom!
(Stop)
(Murderer, leave the village.)
(Condolences)
Look. That's Kang Tae Joo, right?
- He's the one who put Gi Beom away. - Oh, dear.
- The nerve. How dare he come here? - How could he...
Tae Joo.
Where is my Gi Beom?
You killed him.
My Gi Beom.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Bring him back!
My precious boy.
My sweet, wonderful boy.
The apple of my eye.
Bring him back!
- Bring him back! - Ma'am...
Take her to her room.
Gi Hwan.
I need to say something to Gi Beom.
I'm sorry,
but I can't stand to face you anymore.
Please, just go.
Gi Hwan.
Gi Beom's cause of death was sepsis from organ damage.
Apparently, it got pretty serious while he was in detention.
One of the guards even told him to go to a hospital when he got out.
How could they make a healthy man...
just die like that?
I...
I'm the one...
who ruined everything.
I...
made Gi Beom die...
- Tae Joo. - I...
Tae Joo, look at me.
You can't fall apart right now.
You have to make the ones who did this to Gi Beom pay.
Those punks didn't even show up to the funeral.
Not a single one of them has apologised.
How can people be so heartless?
- Where's Cha Si Yeong? - He's at the funeral.
To the funeral?
Did he?
(Condolences)
- Assemblyman. - It's been a while.
Take it easy.
- I saw the policy went through. - Right.
- Hey, there he is. - Go easy on me in the meeting.
Gi Beom.
It's a party in here.
With no guilt,
no sorrow,
they laugh and chatter.
The very people who killed you...
have already...
forgotten you.
So don't you forgive any of them.
I knelt before them...
completely powerless.
Don't forgive me either.
Have you...
ever had someone find out you were the killer?
Let's see.
If I had, I would have been caught earlier, wouldn't I?
Right?
What about Gi Beom?
Did Gi Beom...
not know you were the culprit?
No, he didn't know.
Hey, Gi Beom, I'm going for a cake, so just wait...
Hey, Gi Beom, what's wrong?
Are you hurt? What's wrong?
What's the matter with you?
Gi Hwan.
We're going to the hospital.
Was it you?
What?
To Tae Joo...
Did you tell him I followed Min Ji out?
- What? - But that's not what happened.
You followed Min Ji out.
It's starting to rain.
I'll give her the umbrella and head home.
Lock up and leave. Don't touch this. I'll take care of it tomorrow.
Okay.
You said you'd give her the umbrella...
(Kangseong Bookstore)
and followed her out.
Did I?
You just got it mixed up, right?
Of course.
What other reason could there be?
You need to go to the hospital.
Gi Beom.
Gi Hwan.
Don't hurt Sun Yeong.
Never.
Mark my words.
I have to go buy that cake.
Just wait here.
Gi Beom...
didn't know anything.
So Gi Beom did know.
I told you, he didn't know.
Why don't you believe me?
Whether someone knew or not...
is not something you can know for sure.
It's an assumption.
Lee Gi Hwan.
Sit.
Let's talk some more.
That name...
I haven't heard that in a long time.
There's the Tae Joo I remember.
(The Scarecrow)
- Get out of the way! - Prosecution wants death penalty.
How can you call yourself human? How could you pin that on me?
Seok Man, did you really kill those women?
I'm the one who killed them.
Tae Joo, we shouldn't see each other again.
- Sun Yeong! - Sun Yeong!
I think Sun Yeong is trying to kill herself.
How can we give up? Someone died, and another was framed.
Sun Yeong, it's dangerous!