♫Everything is different when we watch the sky from the sea bottom♫
♫The person I used to be is gone♫
♫I no longer believed a person could save another♫
♫Until when you broke into my world♫
♫Even if the world fell apart into darkness♫
♫We would bloom in the darkness♫
♫The knight and the king♫
♫Like the white sails in night navigation are protecting the ocean♫
♫I see a clear direction♫
♫In which a touch of golden color flickers at the end of the wheat field♫
♫Even if I am the king♫
♫With supreme glory everything is meaningless without you♫
♫All what I did is to make you remember♫
♫The way everything was when it started♫
♫If I am the king♫
♫Who is proud and arrogant like wild and wind weeds♫
♫I only want you to be at my side whatever it takes♫
♫And everything is the way it used to be at the very beginning♫
[Adapted from Jinjiang Literature City novels "Lighter and Princess - Grassy Garden" and "Lighter and Princess - Changming Lamp" written by Twentine (Zhou Aihua)]
[Episode 16]
Oh, thank you so much.
It's nothing.
I've added lots of WeChat accounts.
Come on.
I specially booked crisp pastries.
They taste so good.
They're quite famous in Shanghai.
Come and have a taste.
Everyone can have a taste.
Come on.
Give you this.
Let others taste it. Let others taste it.
Well, come here. Come here.
Is it tasty? How does it taste?
It tastes good.
Yes.
I think this restaurant is good.
There is also one portion. This one.
Take it.
Thank you.
Have a taste.
It tastes good.
It tastes very good.
I entered the final, Li Xun.
Thank you very much this time.
Thank you.
Not at all.
Thank you for giving me advice.
Thank you so much.
It doesn't matter.
Are you Zhu Yun?
I heard from Gao that
you're also the main member of the Nanhu University Base.
May I have your WeChat account?
Let me have your QR code scanned.
Gao showed me the source codes
of your Blue Crown app a few days ago.
The source codes are concise and accurate.
It's a pity that
you don't participate in this competition.
But there're also some problems with this competition.
What do you mean?
Some contestant
has managed to win by devious means,
greatly shocking us.
Do you mean our senior?
He's simply the shame of the School of Information Technology of our university.
It's rumored in the campus that
his tutor and sponsor once cooperated.
Knowing they set up a new studio recently,
his tutor and sponsor got several topics in advance.
When they almost finish them,
they can invite some students to do some tail-in work.
In this case, they can not only profit by patent sales,
but also win some prizes.
They keep the good points of both.
And Fang Zhijing,
who won the Special Attention Award in this competition,
to press the crystal ball with us.
Is he that student
we saw on the stage?
Yes.
It's just him,
Fang Zhijing.
Who are you talking about?
Xu Lina,
why didn't you invite me to dinner?
You're too busy to have dinner with us.
Zhu Yun,
it's really you.
I remember you're at Nanhu University.
Well,
you should have told me
you would come to our university,
so that I could
do the honors.
Can't you
recognize me?
I'm Fang Zhijing.
Long time no see, Fang Zhijing.
You're also here for the competition?
I didn't see your name on the list.
Were you eliminated?
It's funny.
She could design the Blue Crown app,
let alone the final.
You must be Li Xun.
Hello.
I've heard a lot about you.
I'm Fang Zhijing.
Your Blue Crown app
turns out to be a success,
but it's buggy every now and then.
It would be better if it could run smoothly.
It doesn't matter.
You're freshmen,
so it's normal for you to have some weaknesses.
Yes, it's normal.
Its DAUs are ten times more than the expected ones.
So we still need to upgrade the server.
It's a pity that
we can't fight it out
in the competition this time.
Well,
enjoy yourselves.
By the way, Zhu Yun.
Please tell me in advance
before coming to our university next time.
Such a supercilious guy
will invite his destruction sooner or later.
Yeah, I'm here.
Go upstairs directly.
Okay, bye.
Well, Zhu Yun,
do you have something else to talk with me?
If there's nothing, I'll leave first.
See you another day.
Do you still remember Xiaoyan?
Of course.
I went to see her at her cemetery
during the Spring Festival this year.
She has gone for so long.
I wish her well in heaven.
Honey, I'm coming.
Let me introduce to you.
This is my old classmate Zhu Yun.
This is my girlfriend Wu Yuxin.
Hello, Zhu Yun.
Let's go to dinner.
Your teacher is still waiting for you.
Be free.
The competition is a mere formality,
let alone the forum.
What do you mean by that?
I'm not interested
in the forum,
but our project team has cooperated
with the sponsor of this competition.
So they invited me
to the launch ceremony.
I'm leaving.
I'm the first prize winner
of this competition.
All right, just be quiet.
See you, Zhu Yun.
You told her too much.
Don't worry.
She can do nothing to me.
What would you like to eat today?
Zhu Yun,
where did you go?
What's the matter?
Let's go.
Zhu Yun,
we're leaving.
Speak.
Let's join in the competition.
It's a piece of cake for you.
As long as you take it a little seriously,
you can win as easily as winking.
Why do I waste my time
doing such an unimportant thing?
Li Xun,
let's join in the competition.
Why did you change your mind?
I just want to participate in it.
Tell me why.
Won't you join it?
No, I won't.
You're also fed up with him?
Don't laugh at me.
No, no.
It's normal.
Ordinary girls can't stay with him for long.
Well, it's quite normal.
Why?
Li Xun has his own plans for everything.
Let me tell you.
I asked him to help me
design music synthesis software.
He was not available for a month.
Later, I paid him,
and he agreed to do it for me.
He'll start his own company.
He's prone
to suspicion,
so he can't accept their investment easily.
And he needs to save money to start his company himself.
Well,
why must you participate in the competition?
I just don't want that bastard to win.
I can't let him win the first prize.
Who?
Fang Zhijing.
My best friend in high school
was Liu Xiaoyan.
Xiaoyan was very close to a senior
in Senior Two.
She only told me about it.
[Vanilla]
It's melting.
Why don't you put it in the freezer and take it out later?
No one will take it away.
No.
What if someone else takes it?
He loves vanilla ice cream best.
You keep talking about him.
Who is he?
I'm here.
This is for you.
Vanilla ice cream. Thank you.
I haven't finished my homework. I'll leave first.
Bye-bye.
The last one.
It's hard for me to get it.
I told you
we'd better stay together secretly.
It was also on that day that
Liu Xiaoyan and Fang Zhijing's secret relationship
[The puppy love in Senior Three is exposed. Come and have a look!! Come and have a look]
was exposed on the school forum.
[The puppy love in Senior Three is exposed. Come and have a look!! Come and have a look!! [Including a photo]]
What's up?
Someone posted it to the school forum.
I got it.
The IP address
turns out to be our school computer room.
Someone in our school did it.
What a busybody.
Well,
we can say we happened to go home together.
My bike was broken, so...
Our teachers won't believe it.
It's the critical moment
for the selection of "Provincial Merit Student".
If it weren't for you,
there wouldn't have been such a mess.
Fang Zhijing was elected as the "Provincial Merit Student" for two consecutive years.
If he was elected thrice,
he could be recommended to the Information Technology University directly.
But Fang Zhijing was criticized at school
because of the photo.
Unexpectedly,
[Liu Xiaoyan: I've fallen in love with you since last semester...]
Fang Zhijing released his chat information with Xiaoyan out of context
[Liu Xiaoyan: Thank you, darling]
in order to get the recommendation certificate
and shifted all the responsibilities onto Xiaoyan,
making her the target of public criticism.
[More details! More disclosures!]
She's so shameless!
It's just her.
[Real killer moves in silence. She usually looks low-key, but she's such a coquettish girl.]
Good as she looks, she's such a nuisance.
Stop pretending.
Xiaoyan.
Why did you
post some of your QQ chat information with Xiaoyan
and deliberately nip off the information unfavorable to you?
Did you see me do it?
And it's none of your business.
But it's not the truth.
It's you who plague Xiaoyan.
Plague?
Do I plague her?
Xiaoyan is so kind to you,
but you hurt her ruthlessly.
If so,
why can't she sacrifice for me?
Xiaoyan is very sad now.
Go and see her.
It's really inappropriate for us to meet now.
If others find we stay together,
I really can't make it clear.
Then her sacrifice will become meaningless.
Then at least comfort her.
I said
I have no relationship with her.
Don't bother me again.
Fang Zhijing.
Fang Zhijing actually made a statement.
Fang Zhijing refuses her,
but she still plagues him shamelessly.
Xiaoyan seemed to live in darkness since that day.
Fang Zhijing was still a good student in everyone's eyes.
Xiaoyan became silent
until one day...
Zhu Yun, there was something wrong.
Liu Xiaoyan took sleeping pills.
How is she?
I don't know. She is still in the emergency room.
Liu Xiaoyan's family member?
I, I'm her mom.
The patient's central nervous system
has been inhibited by a large number of sleeping pills.
Because of long time of brain hypoxia,
she has brain death.
It's of no use to rescue her again.
How could this happen?
Aunt. Aunt. Aunt.
-Aunt. -Xiaoyan.
Xiaoyan.
My girl.
Fang Zhijing.
What do you want to do?
Shame on you!
You know Xiaoyan is shy.
When she was laughed at by other students,
she still cared about your feelings.
But you
confused right and wrong
and caused her to be slandered by others
for a recommendation certificate.
Do you have a conscience?
I didn't ask her to take the sleeping pills.
It's because she had psychological problems.
Am I to blame?
As soon as I heard about her accident,
I rushed here.
I've done my utmost.
She killed herself because of you.
-It's you who killed her. -Zhu Yun.
It has nothing to do with me.
You can't say that.
The bad guys in the fairy tale world
will never come to a good end.
But we don't live in the fairy tale world.
The bad guy enjoys a good life,
with excellent studies and sweet love.
He feels as if nothing had happened.
He has no sense of guilt.
Why?
A bad thing
never dies.
The result proves everything.
I can't let him stand on the podium.
Never.
Why do you come to me suddenly?
You look serious.
Gao,
I want to participate in the information security competition with you.
Okay.
You said...
I changed my mind.
Okay.
There're many groups in the competition.
To be honest, I'm a little unsure about it.
I thought to find helpers.
Do I need to register?
No.
I can add your name directly.
I'll send you the project progress later.
Okay.
Zhu Yun,
why do you want to join in the competition suddenly?
I want to win the first place.
Good.
I'll go to meet Mr. Lin.
Let's go together.
Let's go.
Look,
you've done a good job.
Keep calm.
Do you think my project can stand the test?
Yes, sure.
This is the printed list of the finalists of various universities.
Have a look.
Mr. Lin, you already read it.
So please help us make an analysis.
I don't have much to say.
Only some common universities
and national defense universities
have real strength in the computer science major.
I don't have much to remind you.
Remember,
it depends on your real strength.
Read it yourself.
There's a strong group in the Information Technology University.
Their project is practical.
It's estimated they can win a prize
and profit by patent sales.
Is their group leader named Fang Zhijing?
What's their competition topic?
Mr. Lin,
it's time to have a meeting.
Okay.
Don't forget to close the door when you leave.
[List of the Finalists of the "Jianguang Electronics Cup" First Nanhu University Students' Information Security Competition]
[Fang Zhijing]
USB Intelligent Encryption Interface.
Is his competition topic
"USB Intelligent Encryption Interface"?
It's very practical.
If he wins by this project and applies for a patent,
I guess lots of enterprises will compete to buy it.
What's the matter?
Don't worry.
Our project is not bad.
If we do it carefully, it's also competitive.
Gao,
let's go and invite Li Xun to join us, okay?
Why do you mention him suddenly?
He isn't interested in the competition.
I'll go and talk with him again.
We two can also make it.
You also want to win the first prize, right?
With him, we can win it for sure.
Are you so unsure of yourself?
No,
but the final is drawing near.
Or are you unsure of me?
That's not what I meant.
Whatever.
Go and ask him yourself.
But don't miss
to defend the ARP spoofing attack.
Such an attack is always disguised as a gateway
or a host in the network.
So you need
to deploy some monitoring points in the network
to monitor the false ARP data packets,
find out
the ARP attack source
according to the false MAC
in the false ARP data
and finally deal with the attack source.
[Interception failed]
[Interception succeeded]
We can't resist the flooding attacks at all.
As long as the attack source is slightly disguised,
it can bypass our defense system.
I'll try again.
I'll go out to take the air.
Can you design
the encryption interface of the USB device?
What?
Can you design
the encryption interface of the USB device?
We work together every day.
What are you thinking about?
I'm serious. Can you design it?
If the encryption interface
is only made for functions,
we can find a single-chip computer as the main processor
and equip it with some interface chips.
I'm not familiar with hardware,
so it may take some time to design it.
It's easy to design the software
as I just need to deal with the interface firmware
and key management.
Is it of high difficulty?
Why do you ask me this?
Princess, do you want to receive an outsourced project for us?
You've improved.
You know to find work for yourself.
I have to remind you.
Don't serve them at a low price.
Charge high for it.
How long will it take you to finish it?
It depends on the offer.
What if you are very, very satisfied with the offer?
Then it depends on the requirements.
I have very, very high requirements.
There're various kinds and degrees of encryption methods
in the world.
Advanced encryption is a process of continuous improvements.
But it won't take long
if it is only to realize the functions
of encryption interface.
What's up?
These are common sense questions.
Why do you ask me?
100,000 yuan.
Not enough.
This is just the deposit.
He's bursting with joy.
I know how much money
you have.
Princess,
I guess there's no one tenth of the deposit
in your card.
How can you pay me?
So I said it's the deposit.
Let me calculate.
I try to transfer 2,000 yuan
to the bank account every month
to repay you the rest of the money.
So I can pay you
10,000 yuan in five months
and 100,000 yuan in fifty months.
You can just wait to collect money later.
What do you think?
Fifty months?
It's so long.
Will you
pay me 100,000 yuan
for the USB encryption?
No.
This is other's competition project.
All the people think he will win.
I want you to join me in the competition
and defeat this project.
As long as you sign, we can make a deal.
After I repay you the deposit,
you can still keep my salary card.
I will work for you for free,
okay?
Are you serious?
Yes.
[Payee: Li Xun]
♫If love has some temperature left♫
♫This dream will automatically exit♫
♫After waking up I will hold you back♫
♫Don't go♫
♫Destiny is not a journey♫
♫Hold me tight and don't get lost♫
♫In the depth of my soul♫
♫You're my everything Take one step back♫
♫What a profound understanding♫
♫I care too much about you♫
[Interception succeeded]
I made it.
I made it. I made it.
Everyone, I made it.
Zhu Yun,
come here. Come now.
I made it.
I've done a lot of tests.
Both flooding attacks and spoofing attacks
[Interception succeeded]
can be detected by the system in real time
and the ARP attack source
[Interception succeeded]
can be automatically isolated,
which doesn't affect
the normal communication between hosts.
Well done, Gao.
Barring accidents,
I think we can at least win a prize this time.
We may also
win the first prize.
Really?
Gao, let me in.
Copy the codes for you.
Why?
I didn't invite you.
This is my project.
Gao,
I told you I would invite him.
We didn't make any progress back then.
Now our project is almost completed.
Zhu Yun,
why didn't you
discuss with me
before making a decision?
Let's talk outside.
He's a strong and excellent programmer,
but I don't need him.
What's going on?
[Interception failed]
Who launched the attack?
Let me check.
No need.
Flooding attacks
generate a large number of false MAC addresses
in the network,
so you
defend against them
by the strategy of configuring switch ports.
Spoofing attacks
will disguise themselves as gateways
or hosts in the network.
You choose to deploy some monitoring points
in the network
to detect false ARP data packets,
find out the ARP attack source
according to the false MAC
in the false ARP data
and finally deal with
the attack source.
The idea is kind of feasible,
but you lack necessary ability.
So this system
is full of loopholes
from architecture design
to code level.
I broke through your defense system
with only less than 20 lines of codes.
I passed the preliminary.
The preliminary stresses understanding of concepts,
while the final stresses real strength.
Working night and day this month,
you designed such a shabby project.
You still have the wild wish of winning the first prize.
The judges will teach you a bitter lesson.
What do you actually want to do?
Help you win the first prize.
I don't need you.
You can win
only if you follow me.
Gao.
He is so arrogant
and changeable.
Mr. Lin,
if I participate in the final myself,
can I win?
Any contestant may win
or fail in a competition.
I mean
you'd better not put too much pressure on yourself.
You're a freshman.
You have lots of chances in the future.
There're all sorts of activities
you can participate in
every semester and every school year.
There're
regional, provincial
and city-level activities.
You have many chances to train yourself.
So Mr. Lin,
I can't win
without his help,
right?
Jianhong,
you...
Let me tell you
about my own experience.
I'm one of the first students
learning this major in our country.
I remember the first time I got a computer,
I was so excited that
I couldn't fall asleep all night.
I came out top in the academic performance
in my class.
I retained to work in our university after graduation.
My classmates envied me
and thought
I got the best chance.
Some of my classmates who weren't given satisfactory jobs
went to Zhongguancun.
After a few years,
they became the IT leaders.
If I'm compared with them now,
whose chances are better?
Who wins?
Who seizes the better resources?
Jianhong,
you have a long life road.
Don't let yourself
be trapped
by temporary wins and losses.
[Are you sure you want to permanently delete this folder?]
One day, I will let you know
I can be better
without his help.
[3,437 items deleted]
Let's lose no time.
Say how to amend the project.
What's your opinion?
If I say,
I think we should rewrite all the codes.
We don't need to rewrite all of them.
Just reconstruct the codes with problems, okay?
We must rewrite all of them.
We're pressed for time.
Your program
is like a swimmer in cotton-padded clothes.
We can't find its bugs in the beginning,
but more bugs will occur with time going.
By then, we can do nothing to improve it.
I deleted the previous program,
so let's rewrite.
Okay.
Gao,
are you alright?
Yes.
Both of us want to win.
It's good that
he can help us to win, isn't it?
I've stayed up late for several days,
so I'm a bit tired.
I'd like to have a rest in the dormitory.
Go back to rest early.
Go to sleep in the dormitory.
I have no time to sleep.
Li Xun,
be kind to Gao later.
Am I unkind to him?
He is still the project leader.
It's still he who will introduce the project
in the competition.
Am I kind enough to him?
What are you doing?
I'm putting up a bed for you.
Sleep on such a bed?
It's a bit like a farewell ceremony.
You may die from overwork
if you keep staying up late.
You stay up late more often than me.
Don't compare with me.
Come here.
Sleep.
Why are you staring at me?
Close your eyes and sleep.
All the lights are on. How can I fall asleep?
Haven't you slept?
I make a plan.
Don't worry about me.
As we're more and more pressed for time,
I should make a detailed plan,
so that we can arrange
every hour and every day effectively.
Li Xun,
be sure to win.
Be sure to win.
Don't worry.
You paid me, so I'll help you win.
You can ask me to do whatever you want
after the competition.
Write it down.
You said I could ask you to do anything I like.
Words alone are no proof.
Just put it down carefully.
But what you said is ambiguous.
You said it yourself.
After the competition,
Li Xun can ask me to do anything he likes.
Zhu Yun.
Why do you return me my bank card?
God knows how long
I can get your pay.
I just want this.
♫I pass by the world♫
♫And pass through the night♫
♫In the crowd in the dim light♫
♫You're over there with the fireworks♫
♫It's the intuition of the dream♫
♫That breaks through the boundary♫
♫The first sight♫
♫Spreads and later it wins the world for me♫
Li Xun,
what I'll say is serious.
♫The clock keeps ticking♫
No matter what you want to do
and what goals you want to complete in the future,
♫I am leaning on your shoulder♫
you can count me in.
♫We won't break up♫
I'm not kidding.
♫Stay with me from the hustle and bustle♫
I'll keep my word.
♫It's the fulcrum of your palm♫
♫That gives me the courage to move forward♫
♫Just like the flame in the night♫
I know.
♫Cause I believe I love you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫I am at your side♫
♫Spending such a long time with you♫
♫Cause I believe I want you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫The hot firework♫
♫Keeps burning for me because of you♫
♫It's the intuition of the dream♫
It's an insult to the fairness of the competition
♫That breaks through the boundary♫
that you can win the special prize for this shabby project.
It's all cut and dried
You're using such unscrupulous means.
♫The first sight♫
You should be responsible for your remarks.
♫Spreads and later it wins the world for me♫
Hi, why did you
do this?
♫The clock keeps ticking♫
Because of love.
♫I also want to stand by your side♫
♫As long as I am brave enough♫
♫Every dream I have♫
♫Will not, will not, will not lose to the time♫
♫Cause I believe I love you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫I am at your side♫
♫Spending such a long time with you♫
♫Cause I believe I want you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫The hot firework♫
♫Keeps burning for me because of you♫
♫Cause I believe I love you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫I am at your side♫
♫Spending such a long time with you♫
♫Cause I believe I want you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫The hot firework♫
♫Keeps burning for me because of you♫