♫Everything is different when we watch the sky from the sea bottom♫
♫The person I used to be is gone♫
♫I no longer believed a person could save another♫
♫Until when you broke into my world♫
♫Even if the world fell apart into darkness♫
♫We would bloom in the darkness♫
♫The knight and the king♫
♫Like the white sails in night navigation are protecting the ocean♫
♫I see a clear direction♫
♫In which a touch of golden color flickers at the end of the wheat field♫
♫Even if I am the king♫
♫With supreme glory everything is meaningless without you♫
♫All what I did is to make you remember♫
♫The way everything was when it started♫
♫If I am the king♫
♫Who is proud and arrogant like wild and wind weeds♫
♫I only want you to be at my side whatever it takes♫
♫And everything is the way it used to be at the very beginning♫
[Adapted from Jinjiang Literature City novels "Lighter and Princess - Grassy Garden" and "Lighter and Princess - Changming Lamp" written by Twentine (Zhou Aihua)]
[Episode 17]
[Xu Lina  Gao Jianhong: Lina, we have arrived. Are you at school?]
Lina.
We have arrived.
[Xu Lina  Gao Jianhong: Lina, we have arrived. Are you at school?]
Are you at school?
Gao.
This is for you.
You bought it?
Last time you treated me to dinner,
so just take it
for a return gift.
You are so polite.
Thank you.
I don't understand.
I chose one that I thought was good.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Don't you open it?
I like everything you give me.
Okay.
Gao, only you come?
Where's Li Xun?
Has he come yet?
Yes.
Where is he?
In the room.
We changed our project
as he said.
I was just looking for him.
Let's go upstairs.
He's sleeping.
He sleeps at this point?
Is he an old man?
He's irritated recently.
Don't bother him.
He scolds people mercilessly.
Really?
Fine.
Then I'll go shopping.
Let me go with you.
I'm free
and want to take a walk.
All right.
This is so cute.
Yeah.
This Macchiato is too sweet.
I'll get fat.
Then give it to me.
I'll buy you a new one later.
This.
Thank you for your coming.
Welcome to the comprehensive oral care brand.
May I help you?
I want to buy a toothbrush for my friend.
Would you recommend some?
Okay.
Then you can take this
marble electric toothbrush.
It sells well.
It can clean teeth effectively.
Really?
There are twelve modes
for you to adjust the intensity by yourself.
Is this for lovers?
Yes, it's for lovers.
It's pretty. Then I'd like to take a pair.
Okay.
Will that be cash
or charge?
Cash.
-Okay. -Wait.
I'll buy it myself.
Card.
Okay.
You are back.
Yeah.
I bought some fruit. Have a taste.
Okay.
How was the discussion today?
Pretty good.
That's good.
Why did you come back so late?
I was stopped on my way back.
Go for the competition.
[Go for the competition. You are always No.1 in my heart. U smile every day.  Xu Lina]
You are always No.1 in my heart.
You smile every day.
Xu Lina.
Let's go to the restaurant we ordered last night.
Several groups eat together.
How many of you are there?
Zhu Yun?
You go first.
Bye-bye.
I remember when you graduated from high school,
you changed the phone number?
It suddenly occurred to me
I forgot to ask your mobile number last time I saw you.
You also come to the competition?
Last time I asked you, but you didn't tell me.
I didn't see your name on the list.
Come on.
Does it need to hide so deeply?
I'll have a group meeting later.
It'll end bout seven o'clock.
Then let's have a meal.
No thanks.
We are old classmates.
I haven't seen you for so long.
How about we have a meal and talk about the past?
Our group has an appointment to have dinner together.
Li Xun also comes?
Of course.
You can keep your own trump deep.
I really want to see
how capable he is.
Then I'll go first. I'll be late.
Wait,
tell me your phone number.
Let me make a note.
I didn't bring my cell phone with me.
I can't remember the number.
That's amazing.
Next time.
Bye, old schoolmate.
Have you submitted it?
Deadline is 12:00.
It's 11:40 now.
What are you doing?
Click submit.
Test it again?
No need. You've packed it.
Test it again.
How many times have you tested it?
What if there is a problem with this platform?
There are only three competition platforms.
Windows,
Linus,
and Unix.
Even pupils won't make any mistake.
But
I'm afraid.
[Uploaded]
Isn't it over?
That's it?
What a hare.
Hello. Hello. Hello.
Here.
Okay.
Hello. Hello.
I'm so sorry.
I had a jam due to heavy rain.
It doesn't matter. I've just arrived.
Is that so?
Well,
I'd like to leave for a while.
Order me a Macchiato.
Okay.
OK.
Waiter.
Hello.
A glass of Macchiato, not too sweet.
Okay.
Thank you, Feng.
How is it?
Isn't this a good place?
You should have avoided suspicion at this time.
But you asked me out alone.
I've invited you to such a far place.
It has avoided suspicion enough.
Fang Zhijing.
What happened on earth?
Isn't that the sponsor of the competition?
Feng.
I heard that
Nanhu University has a pretty good
project recently.
The judges loved it.
You heard about it?
Have you seen their project?
How did you like it?
What's wrong?
Are you scared?
Scared?
Not at all.
Anyway,
you can't be more careful.
By the way, Feng,
can you
discuss with Mr. Chen
and ask him to apply for a star prize with the organizing committee?
There is no such award.
It won't work.
Feng.
Listen to me first.
Think about it.
Haven't we made an agreement?
The contract is ready,
waiting only for signature.
Mr. Chen also
needs to enhance his performance this year,
right?
If something goes wrong here,
the company must treat him as a joke.
How should I persuade Mr. Chen?
How about this?
I can give in three more percent
in the patent transfer fee.
Feng.
Later,
for the annual patent transfer fee,
you will take 30 percent
and me, 70 percent.
Okay.
I'd have a try.
Great.
Thank you, Feng.
I have a meeting this afternoon.
I have to go.
Let me walk you out.
Wait, Feng, take an umbrella.
Thank you for that.
Discuss with Mr. Chen.
Fang Zhijing?
Isn't that one beside Fang Zhijing
from our
competition's sponsor?
You know him?
He was also present in the forum.
What is Fang Zhijing doing with him?
What are you up to?
He must be trying to do something.
During the competition,
meeting with sponsors privately
is against the rules.
Don't be so impulsive.
I'm going to report them to the organizing committee.
Do you have any evidence?
We saw it with our own eyes.
So what?
Did you hear what they said?
It's against the rules to meet privately.
But at most, they will get a notice of criticism.
Can it help?
What a coincidence.
We even came across him.
I didn't expect Fang Zhijing to have such a move.
What happened to Fang Zhijing?
When we had coffee this afternoon,
we met Fang Zhijing.
I've never any mean person like him.
We saw them staying
with someone from the organizing committee.
What happened?
Sorry. I'll answer the phone first.
The competition will start soon.
He met the sponsor
in secret in a far place.
They wouldn't have a normal chat only.
I think they're just discussing
about the direct determination of award winners.
They have determined the result of the finals?
What finals?
They are cheating fools like us.
Why is it so cold?
Has the taxi arrived?
Not yet, but soon.
What would you like for dinner?
Some people
are really mean.
They can do anything for an award.
Being able to sell patents are a kind of ability.
Instead of gossiping here,
some people would better go back and improve
their level.
What level should I improve?
The level of playing tricks and pulling strings?
What bullshit are you talking about?
Whether it's bullshit
is clear to everyone.
Xu Lina.
What right do you have to slander me
playing tricks and pulling strings?
You are just a gifted student of folk dance
who was enrolled by points adding.
Aren't you clear about
your programming level?
Have you no shame
to say this?
Make it clear.
You are clearer than me
how many people you asked for help
to make your shabby system.
You alone can never
enter the finals in your life.
But I've improved
it for at least three times.
Right, Li Xun?
Miss Xu.
Next time, before you criticize someone,
consider whether you have this ability first.
You.
Here we go.
How can there be such a person?
Fang Zhijing.
Is what Xu Lina said true?
Zhu Yun,
why are you so naive now?
Can you ask this directly?
I asked you if it was true.
You participate in this competition
because you really want to compete with me?
What a pity.
I'd love to
compete with your God Li.
But there's no chance.
Maybe next time.
It's all cut and dried
You are scared once Li Xun attends?
You're using such unscrupulous means.
The judges think my stuff is good. So is it called means?
People like Xu Lina are playing tricks.
You saw it too.
They have their resources.
I have my way.
We are the same.
And I don't care about it.
Do you know the essential difference
between them and me?
They can choose to talk nonsense or not.
I can also choose to listen or not.
But whether they talk nonsense or not,
my result will not be changed.
If I choose to listen,
at most, I will be annoyed for a while.
If I choose not to listen,
then I'm the winner.
You're so smart.
You should understand
who is better.
In this world,
heroes are always judged by success.
People always
worship the strong.
Believe it or not.
As long as I keep succeeding,
everyone will forget today's criticism
and become my fanatical followers
and admirers.
Okay, I'm done.
I have to go.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I squeeze so much time out,
not to see you like this.
I'm sorry.
Do you hate Fang Zhijing?
I see.
Don't you ask why?
Yes.
What if the reason doesn't convince you?
It doesn't matter if there's no reason.
Everyone can make decisions based on their emotions.
Do you have a way?
No.
Do not overdo it.
Something has no result originally.
Stop loss in time.
Waste less time.
I'm tired. You can leave.
Hello.
How are you feeling now? Are you nervous?
You know what?
On the day of the competition,
the group leader will get to the stage to explain first
and the judges will score on the spot.
You have only ten minutes to explain.
Then it's the work demonstration.
Zhu Yun.
Class rep.
Mr. Lin.
I mean,
you need to demonstrate it first.
In a short time,
show clearly the work's creativity,
technology roadmap,
and application prospect
to the judges and audience.
This is important.
Got it?
Yeah.
Mr. Li.
that USB encryption project
of the Information Technology University
will be awarded anyway?
Miss. Zhang told me about this.
I also inquired it indirectly.
There is definitely a rumor
saying that
a star prize will be set up.
Don't think so much about it.
This is beyond our control.
Just mind your business.
We learn for ourselves,
right?
I see.
I have other lessons.
I'm waiting for your good news.
Bye-bye.
All right, goodbye, Mr. Lin.
Goodbye, Mr. Lin.
Didn't you listen to Mr. Lin?
They gave them a star prize.
This is good for us.
The biggest competitor left.
It will do us no harm.
We have a better chance.
No chance.
He will still stand on the stage like a success,
saying those acceptance speeches proudly.
No one knows how dirty he is.
No one can tear off
his hypocritical mask either.
In this world,
there is no absolute fairness.
Moreover,
there are countless roads to victory.
Even if one way is blocked by you,
there are still countless ways for him to take.
Where's Li Xun?
Where is he?
He hasn't been back for days.
He didn't answer any call or WeChat massage.
I didn't know he came for competition
or travel.
I'm tired. I'd like to go back to have a rest.
By the way, Feng,
can you discuss with Mr. Chen
and ask him to apply for a star prize with the organizing committee?
Do you really think no one can defeat you?
Li Xun.
Even you block one of his ways,
there are countless other ways he can take.
[Delete]
[Sure]
Do you really think you can do anything?
[The First Nanhu College Information Security Competition]
[Jianguang Electronics Cup Summit]
I think we have no problem.
Princess, have a look again.
Stop that.
Where's Li Xun?
I don't know.
Congratulations.
You know what?
You won the first prize this time.
Really?
And what about you?
I can't compete with you.
I got a star prize.
You don't even have a chance to compete with me.
Are you disappointed?
Where's Li Xun?
He is absent again?
He's busy.
He is really mysterious.
He doesn't leave any chance to others to worship him.
You can get this result in my freshman year.
That's great.
Let's have a chat later.
Bye.
He is really bold-faced.
Next, we are going to issue
the first prize of this competition.
Nanhu University.
LAN ARP Protocol
Attack Defense System Based on Switch.
Winners are Gao Jianhong, Zhu Yun and Li Xun.
Let's go together.
You go.
Thank you.
Great.
Next
is our most important link.
We have a work
that stood out at the competition stage
and got the opportunity to sign the contract in advance.
The purpose of this competition
is to promote exchange and cooperation
between enterprises and universities.
This work has taken the first step for us.
So
we set up a star prize.
The winner is the Information Technology University's
USB intelligent encryption interface.
Participants are Fang Zhijing, Wang Yujun and Zhang Shuo.
Well, we also invite
sponsor of this competition,
leader of Huake Technology Co., Ltd
to present the award to them on stage.
Thank you.
I'll call Mr. Lin.
Can you say something about winning the prize?
Yes, sure.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Fang Zhijing.
Right here.
First of all, I would like to thank the organizing committee
for giving us this star prize.
Secondly,
I want to thank all of you here.
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you.
Get down.
I know
there are a lot of rumors in the school recently,
saying that I cheated
or I stole others' work.
Originally,
a clean hand wants no washing.
As I have never done it,
I don't need to explain too much.
But for the rest of my team,
this is quite unfair.
So right here,
I solemnly clarify to everyone that,
I, Fang Zhijing,
have never done anything that
violated the rules of the competition.
Those irresponsible remarks,,
slanders, or false accusations,
will damage the reputation
of this information contest,
and a great insult to
the fairness and impartiality of this contest.
It's an insult to the fairness of the competition
that you can win a star prize for this shabby project.
Is it Li Xun?
Who is this?
Li Xun.
What's up?
You have been disappearing for days.
Where have you been these days?
I went to do something bad.
What do you mean?
Well, I mean,
your so-called encryption interface
is totally vulnerable
and doesn't deserve this prize.
Li Xun.
You should be responsible for your remarks.
Am I afraid of responsibility
or are you afraid of responsibility?
Yeah. Are you afraid of responsibility?
Yeah. Yeah.
You are afraid?
Afraid?
Okay.
If
he can crack my encrypted USB disk,
I can give up
this patent transfer fee
to him.
But if
you can't break it,
you, need to
apologize to me.
Okay.
It's a deal.
For the sake of fairness,
I'd better use the computer of the organizing committee.
Help yourself.
This competition will be wonderful.
I have confidence in Fang.
[USB encryption]
What are they doing?
Li Xun is cracking Fang Zhijing's encryption USB disk.
I've seen your plan introduction.
Good concept.
Of course.
Or I can't take it.
Within a minute,
I have three ways to crack it.
Okay.
This USB disk contains my personal privacy.
If he can crack it,
I'll show it to you all.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Go ahead.
You're very considerate.
To prevent forgetting the password,
while the USB disk is encrypted,
usually a key is generated.
Indeed.
Our patent
considers that many people forget their passwords.
But you are not skilled enough.
What is generated is a local static key.
This key
can be found
as long as your computer is hacked.
The letter e here
represents the drive letter to be unlocked.
This is the local static key you saved.
Great.
Let me see.
There's no privacy.
You hide them all?
God.
His girlfriend is there.
You didn't hide such private things well?
From the source of the document,
you have another WeChat account.
Your girlfriend knows it?
That's not good.
[102 items deleted]
It's not over yet.
Do you want to see it?
Yes.
Let's continue.
The second way.
Empty disk copying.
Now,
I am about to use Ghost
to copy the disk.
But I have to say
your encryption software is quite secure.
Even in DOS,
it also prohibits the use of Ghost.
Once Ghost is activated,
the USB disk will pop up automatically.
[Sector copy]
Even if you plug it back in,
it cannot be seen in Ghost.
Therefore,
I used
DiskGenius,
a software for direct operation of hard disk.
I insert two USB disks
and make direct copying, and decryption succeeded.
Because this encryption software
is associated with the serial number of the USB disk,
if it enters a new USB disk,
the file will be automatically released.
[Sectors copied]
Great.
You can't delete the file cleanly.
You need to improve your safety awareness.
You don't deserve
the star prize
of the Information Security Network Competition.
Well done, Li Xun!
So cool!
This is too outrageous.
Chairman Peng.
You can't let him do this anymore.
Don't worry.
Isn't he testing your product?
This is not in accordance with the rules of the competition.
It's not appropriate here.
I'll ask you again later.
You just leave in this way?
If you run away,
your patent can't be sold.
Here is a chance for you.
Put a patch.
[USB encryption]
Only five seconds left.
Li Xun.
Can you?
Let's get started.
Li Xun.
Three seconds are left.
Chairman Peng.
Look at him.
What do you mean?
You can't afford to play?
Who can't afford to play?
Look at him.
He can't afford to play.
How is it?
Admit failure?
Do you still need me to explain to you?
The third method
is a physical method.
As long as the flash granule
or the main control chip is replaced,
the original software encryption
will be automatically invalidated.
I don't need to explain
such a simple truth to you, right?
Sorry.
I just delayed you a minute.
But then,
I have to delay you for a little longer.
This is the surveillance video of last Saturday afternoon
from a cafe on Nanchang Road.
What does that mean?
Tian Feng is really my senior.
I admit we should avoid suspicion before the competition.
But I haven't seen him for a long time.
We just met and had coffee. What's wrong?
Any problems?
Really?
By the way, Feng,
can you discuss with Mr. Chen
and ask him to apply for a star prize with the organizing committee?
Think about it.
Haven't we made an agreement?
This is the cafe I went to that day.
The day I saw him.
Mr. Chen also needs to enhance his performance this year,
right?
If something goes wrong in the end,
the company must treat him as a joke.
How should I persuade Mr. Chen?
How about this?
I can give in three more percent
in the patent transfer fee.
Later,
for the annual patent transfer fee,
you will take 30 percent
and me, 70 percent.
Okay.
I'd have a try.
Look what you've done?
Mr. Chen.
Mr. Chen, listen to me.
Li Xun.
I remember you.
This student,
I feel like you're
kind of breaching the rules of the competition.
This will also affect
your performance.
I see.
Then can you tell me
why you did this?
Because of love.
♫Everything is different when we watch the sky from the sea bottom♫
♫The person I used to be is gone♫
♫I no longer believed a person could save another♫
♫Until when you broke into my world♫
♫Even if the world fell apart into darkness♫
♫We would bloom in the darkness♫
Li Xun, I love you!
You are so cool!
♫The knight and the king♫
Li Xun.
♫Both stubborn, are having the same dream♫
♫Wherever I go, I just want to wander with you♫
♫My princess will never be sad again♫
♫If I am the king♫
♫Who is proud and arrogant like wild and wind weeds♫
♫I only want you to be at my side whatever it takes♫
♫And everything is the way it used to be at the very beginning♫
You beat
us jury's face today.
That's good.
You finally supervised
the fairness and justice of our competition.
We will revoke this star prize.
But
you have to be punished.
I know.
By the way,
I have a project in Sanya this summer vacation.
It's still a secret stage.
Would you like to go with me?
Let me think it over.
You are putting on airs.
All right, see you later.
Let's go.
Fang Zhijing.
In fact, you are smart in some ways.
Some of your ideas are also correct.
In this world,
it's true to judge heroes by success.
But it's a pity.
You got the end time wrong.
There's still a long way to go.
It is not
over yet.
Okay.
I'm waiting for it.
Let's go.
Are you happy?
Then give me a smile.
Silly girl.
Are you so happy?
Yeah.
I've never been so happy.
That's good.
Otherwise, I will lose a lot.
Where did you go the other day?
You really think I can decode
Fang Zhijing's encrypted USB
within one minute?
I've been working for several days.
I'm so exhausted.
Li Xun.
What kind of person do you think can be called a princess?
Princess,
first,
must have a pair of lofty eyes.
In addition,
she must have an innocent and fragile heart.
Yes, of course.
If she has
a bit spirit of desperate adventure,
that would be better.
♫I pass by the world♫
You think he and I...
Perfect match.
Slow down.
♫And pass through the night♫
Li Xun.
I want to start a business with you,
♫In the crowd in the dim light♫
just from L&P.
♫You're over there with the fireworks♫
Do whatever you want.
I'm your confidence.
♫You're over there with the fireworks♫
Xun.
♫It's the intuition of the dream♫
I came to see you.
Why are you here?
♫That breaks through the boundary♫
♫The first sight♫
♫Spreads and later it wins the world for me♫
♫The clock keeps ticking♫
♫I am leaning on your shoulder♫
♫We won't break up♫
♫Stay with me from the hustle and bustle♫
♫It's the fulcrum of your palm♫
♫That gives me the courage to move forward♫
♫Just like the flame in the night♫
♫Cause I believe I love you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫I am at your side♫
♫Spending such a long time with you♫
♫Cause I believe I want you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫The hot firework♫
♫Keeps burning for me because of you♫
♫It's the intuition of the dream♫
♫That breaks through the boundary♫
♫The first sight♫
♫Spreads and later it wins the world for me♫
♫The clock keeps ticking♫
♫I also want to stand by your side♫
♫As long as I am brave enough♫
♫Every dream I have♫
♫Will not, will not, will not lose to the time♫
♫Cause I believe I love you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫I am at your side♫
♫Spending such a long time with you♫
♫Cause I believe I want you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫The hot firework♫
♫Keeps burning for me because of you♫
♫Cause I believe I love you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫I am at your side♫
♫Spending such a long time with you♫
♫Cause I believe I want you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫The hot firework♫
♫Keeps burning for me because of you♫