♫Everything is different when we watch the sky from the sea bottom♫
♫The person I used to be is gone♫
♫I no longer believed a person could save another♫
♫Until when you broke into my world♫
♫Even if the world fell apart into darkness♫
♫We would bloom in the darkness♫
♫The knight and the king♫
♫Like the white sails in night navigation are protecting the ocean♫
♫I see a clear direction♫
♫In which a touch of golden color flickers at the end of the wheat field♫
♫Even if I am the king♫
♫With supreme glory everything is meaningless without you♫
♫All what I did is to make you remember♫
♫The way everything was when it started♫
♫If I am the king♫
♫Who is proud and arrogant like wild and wind weeds♫
♫I only want you to be at my side whatever it takes♫
♫And everything is the way it used to be at the very beginning♫
[Adapted from Jinjiang Literature City novels "Lighter and Princess - Grassy Garden" and "Lighter and Princess - Changming Lamp" written by Twentine (Zhou Aihua)]
[Episode 14]
[Dormitory No. 3]
What's wrong?
You're unhappy?
Don't want to leave?
I haven't finished my work yet,
but the app must be submitted tomorrow.
Don't worry.
Li Xun is capable.
It won't be delayed.
Dad,
you also think he is reliable?
How to say?
Sometimes men's hunch
is right.
He is good.
But, dad,
how did you know where the base is?
Mom told it to you?
No wonder you happened to have a meeting there.
Mom really went too far.
However, dad, you must see that
I really worked there.
Yeah.
You were indeed busy at work
and even bought many medicines.
Dad.
Yun, remember.
I caught you in the classroom
for the Party class.
Understand?
Yes.
I want to spend the Spring Festival happily.
Xiuzhu,
I almost can't recognize you.
Long time no see, Zhu Yun.
Your further study abroad isn't in vain.
Long time no see, uncle.
You're mature.
Let me do it.
OK.
Xiuzhu
reassures you.
I'm flattered.
Yun is also excellent.
Aunt.
Yun, hurry up.
You haven't seen Aunt Jiang for four years.
Once she heard that you would come back,
she proposed dining together.
She favors you.
You exaggerated it.
Yun,
your New Year gift.
I still can get a New Year gift as a university student?
Yes.
I specially chose
the intensive wave water flosser of sky love color for you.
It looks good and has a good cleaning function.
Do you like it?
Aunt,
you have a good taste.
My classmate has one,
and I was going to buy one.
Really?
Come for dinner.
All right. Let's go.
OK. Go to have dinner.
Yun,
you sit next to Xiuzhu.
Then you can
have a chat.
OK.
I sit next to you.
Come on. OK.
Thank you.
So many dishes.
Mom.
Thanks for your work!
A dish and a soup haven't been served yet.
Two dishes haven't been served.
Well,
we seemed to send them
to primary school yesterday,
but now they go to university.
Yeah.
It's still vivid in my mind.
Make room for this.
Come on.
Let me serve a soup.
Come on. Move here.
Do you remember?
[Li Xun  Zhu Yun: Are you better? Do you still have a fever?]
Back then, they played at eating chicken wings,
and Yun won at last, right?
[Li Xun  Zhu Yun: Are you better? Do you still have a fever?]
But Yun was almost sent to the hospital,
because she ate too many chicken wings.
[Li Xun  Zhu Yun: Are you better? Do you still have a fever?]
Why didn't he reply on WeChat?
Is he better?
[Li Xun  Zhu Yun: Are you better? Do you still have a fever?]
Do you remember it?
What?
We mentioned that game.
You ate 50-odd chicken wings.
Stop.
I'm ashamed of it.
It's glorious.
You shouldn't feel ashamed.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Toast your return.
Welcome. Welcome back.
What's up?
University affair?
No.
Whose message are you waiting for?
I'm checking my scores.
The final exam results may be released today.
You must be No. 1 again.
[Nanhu University Educational Administration System Score Inquiry]
No.
Our class has a top scorer in the college entrance examination. He is awesome.
The scores of your subjects are all high.
An Introduction to the Fundamental Principles of Marxism.
97.
I don't get a full mark by 3 points.
Only 3 points.
Your score is high enough.
After all, the world isn't perfect, either.
What's his score?
Yun,
you need to learn from Xiuzhu.
His many paintings
are on show around the world.
Yeah.
2 days ago,
a painting was on show in the municipal art gallery.
I went there.
You went there?
Xiuzhu,
you didn't tell me.
We didn't meet each other.
Didn't you say that
you had no time to go, didn't you?
Delicious.
Dad.
She went there today.
After I picked Yun up,
we specially
went to the art gallery
and just saw your...
...large...
Poster.
...poster. Yes.
It's very high. So we indeed went there.
Yes.
Thanks for your support.
Well,
I hope Yun can also
go abroad for further study in the future.
What she majors in is not important.
What's more, she should go abroad to widen her vision, right?
If you have any question about going abroad,
you can ask us about it at any time.
If you really plan to do it, you have to be well-prepared early.
As a freshman, I haven't thought about this yet.
You can ask Xiuzhu
whether further study abroad is good or not.
Xiuzhu,
is the moon really fuller abroad?
The moon
is the same abroad.
However,
foreign food
is definitely worse than that of our hometown,
especially the food you cooked
has surpassed those of Chinese restaurants abroad.
He praises my cooking skill.
He was telling the truth.
I'm flattered.
Your cooking skill is getting better and better.
You must have been cooking at home these years.
I send him message again?
[Automatic test platform
Test progress: 100% completed]
[Li Xun  Zhu Yun: Are you better? Do you still have a fever?]
[Zhu Yun: Have you recovered from cough?]
Have you recovered from cough?
[Zhu Yun: The final exam results have been released.]
The final exam results have been released.
[Zhu Yun: I got 97 in the exam of Marxism.]
I got 97 in the exam of Marxism.
[Xiuzhu]
Did he fall ill?
[Li Xun: Why is your score higher than mine?]
Why is your score higher than mine?
Hello.
This is me.
I know.
Do you feel better?
You fool.
The cold medicines you bought me
treat wind-heat type common cold,
but I got cold due to coldness.
I almost died from your medicines.
I'm sorry.
How did you settle it?
I asked someone to send the medicines to me.
That's good.
Have you had dinner?
Yes.
Who sent you the medicines?
I should thank her.
Liu Sisi.
Liu Sisi?
Didn't she go home?
She came back.
Why?
To send me the medicines.
Well, I'll hang up soon. I have something to do.
Wait. Wait.
She also sent you the dinner?
Hello?
Oh, no.
I shouldn't have underestimated my enemy.
Zhu Yun,
you're so different that
you don't go to the shopping mall
but come here on New Year's Eve.
You hadn't come back for long,
so I lead you here to take a look.
You're interested in this?
It's also a kind of art.
You should have a look.
How much is this?
180 yuan.
Sir,
can you repair it?
It's badly damaged.
How was it damaged?
A car ran over it.
I heard that you have various accessories.
You found the right repairer.
You really want to repair it?
You'll be charged much.
How much?
950 yuan.
It's so high.
Can't you give a discount?
This is an old lighter.
It's hard to find all its parts.
I even need to tear down other antiques in my shop
to collect all the parts for you.
This lighter can't be restored
somewhere else.
Let's go somewhere else.
No problem. I'll pay you 950 yuan.
Repair it.
When can you restore it?
After the Spring Festival.
I'm on holiday.
I'll give you 1,000 yuan
to make it a round figure,
but you must restore it today.
You're domineering.
OK.
I'm on duty for you today.
Take it easy.
I'll wait for you here.
Zhu Yun,
why didn't you bargain
but raised the price for him instead?
You also heard that
only he
can restore
this lighter.
Whose lighter is that?
My classmate's.
Such an important classmate?
An ordinary classmate.
Hello.
Hello, this is me.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I'm calling you to ask
about the app of Blue Crown.
Is it OK?
OK .
Tonight is New Year's Eve.
You're still in the university?
No.
You're at home?
Where are you?
Li Xun, hurry up!
We must get in the bus.
You're with Liu Sisi?
We'll be in the same bus.
Anything else?
You, you...
Bye.
Hello?
OK?
No.
The left side is low.
-The left side is low. -Move it upward.
Like this?
[Moments]
Liu Sisi.
She just shared a photo in the Moments.
Move it upward. Move it upward.
Is he behind her in the photo?
Yes.
Really?
Yes. Yes. Yes.
No. His hair style doesn't look like this.
I feel it's almost horizontal.
You can't help me at all.
Let me go down to have a look.
Yun,
help me.
Dad.
What if I fall down?
We can't have a happy New Year.
-Watch out. -Right?
You only played with your phone.
You should be blamed.
Look.
Is it oblique?
Yes, it is.
Which side is oblique?
This?
A small number of foreigners
[Li Xun]
are still biased against Chinese people.
It doesn't matter.
In foreign countries...
Is that him?
Did he go or not?
Where does he have the Spring Festival?
[Li Xun  Zhu Yun: Did you go? What did the boss of Blue Crown say?]
Right?
He doesn't reply again.
[Li Xun  Zhu Yun: Did you go? What did the boss of Blue Crown say?]
At present,
many students don't go abroad for further study
but for a diploma.
Of course.
Not everyone can do like Xiuzhu.
However,
given Yun's major,
I think she should go abroad
to broaden her international vision.
Am I right?
Don't play with your phone.
Talk about
how you think about going abroad.
It's good to stay in China.
For our major,
practice is very important.
It's also good to work early.
Well,
you're wrong.
If you major in computer abroad,
you may join the major companies such as Microsoft
and Google in the future.
It's better
than studying in China
and then joining a small company.
Right?
Those who have been educated abroad
really have a good taste.
Look at this plate
picked by Xiuzhu today.
Dumplings look superior in it,
right?
You exaggerated it.
He bought it casually
when I waited for the lighter under repair.
It's common.
Why do you have a lighter?
What's more,
a lighter needs, needs to be repaired?
Show it to me.
The Spring Festival Gala will begin soon.
Repair...
Is that him?
Impossible.
I'm going to answer a call of nature.
You answer a call of nature during dinner?
Did I mistake him?
[Li Xun]
Hello.
Happy New Year.
Happy.
Have you and Liu Sisi got home?
Not yet.
You haven't gone home so late?
Who told you I went home with her?
Where are you?
It's snowing.
Li Xun, was that you?
How do you know where my house is?
I have been here before.
Then wait for me.
Yun,
where are you going?
The apples you want have been cut into pieces.
Go eat some.
Well, mom,
I'm going to fetch a parcel.
You stay at home.
I'll go. It's very cold outside.
-No need. -Nonsense.
No deliveryman is on duty on New Year's Eve.
I'm going to see if it's snowing heavily.
It's snowing heavily.
Don't go.
You just had dinner.
How about this?
You eat the apple first.
Let's go to enjoy it after playing cards.
Have some first.
How many your cards are left?
Two.
I win again.
So unlucky.
Yun,
you're so absent-minded that
you haven't won yet.
How can I win with you as my rival?
I agree.
You're the landlord in our family.
Why is he silent?
[Li Xun  Zhu Yun: Did you go? What did the boss of Blue Crown say?]
So you always fight against me?
Come on.
[Li Xun  Zhu Yun: Did you go? What did the boss of Blue Crown say?]
Go on. Go on.
Go on?
[Zhu Yun: Are you still online?]
-No. -Are you still online?
I'm sleepy.
[Zhu Yun: Are you still online?]
I'm, I'm sleepy.
Sleepy?
[Zhu Yun: Are you still online?]
I'm bored.
The Spring Festival is getting more and more boring.
[Zhu Yun: Are you still online?]
Three people
are not even enough for playing mahjong.
[Li Xun: I'm almost frozen to death.]
I'm almost frozen to death.
What's up?
-What's up? -Dad,
mom,
I'm taking out the trash.
Take care.
Hello, I'm out. Where are you?
Girl, it's snowing so heavily,
but you go out until now.
Are you going to dig out my body?
I'm sorry.
You went back?
Do you know where Lihua Hotel is?
The one near our house?
I stay in it. Come if you're free.
What do you mean?
Hello?
Lihua Hotel. He wants me to see him?
Yun,
you've been out for dumping the trash for so long.
Come back now!
OK!
It's freezing.
How can I do this as a girl?
I won't.
Will he
be frightened by my look?
Well,
I'd better wipe it off.
♫I forgot time unconsciously♫
♫Slowly understand you on the long road♫
♫Without you, even joy feels lonely♫
♫Looking at your white shirt♫
♫I feel full warmth and endless love♫
♫The secret I've been hiding♫
♫I really want to be with you♫
♫At a moment, in the autumn of a fairy tale♫
♫The knight and princess are destined to meet♫
♫Let me feel and guard your♫
♫Simple wish♫
♫At a moment, in reversely flying days♫
♫I'm no longer afraid of the big world♫
♫By my side, or on my pillow♫
♫You say every good night♫
♫At a moment, in the autumn of a fairy tale♫
♫The knight and princess are destined to meet♫
[Lihua Hotel]
♫Let me feel and guard your♫
♫Simple wish♫
♫At a moment, in reversely flying days♫
♫I'm no longer afraid of the big world♫
♫By my side, or on my pillow♫
♫You say every good night♫
♫Love circulates♫
AAA plus 6.
Bomb.
What's going on?
She comes for you?
You finally come.
Will we go on?
We can go on?
This girl is pretty.
-Very pretty. -Yeah. -Yeah.
Well, you go on.
OK. You go. You go.
You have a good taste.
Let's go.
Don't stand still. Go in.
Go. Go. Go.
If I leave now,
will you lose face?
You want to leave?
I'm thinking about it.
OK, take your time.
I'm closing the door.
Why are you standing there?
Come and take a seat.
Where should I sit?
Sit here.
This is
a single bed.
I ask you to sit
but not lie here.
You ate spicy hot pot on New Year's Eve?
So?
Where did Liu Sisi go?
Didn't you go home together?
You went through your Moments?
You did it so carefully.
I didn't.
We couldn't go to the station together?
I specially came for you.
Hey.
Yes.
You're leaving?
You don't want the red packet?
Red packet?
Why do you give me a red packet?
I received the advance payment today,
so I'm here to paid for your work.
You'll be satisfied.
So thin.
Stingy.
Open it and have a look.
It'll be your pay card.
Does it have a password?
My birthday.
Narcissist.
Do you like it?
I like this gift very much.
Thank you.
This is not a gift.
It's your pay.
This is your gift.
What is this?
Open it and have a look.
Try it.
Where can I try it?
Is anything wrong?
Don't hold your abdomen in.
You're not fat.
Why are you blushing?
I'm, I'm blushing due to the heating.
I didn't switch on the heating.
This dress looks good.
Princess should
wear a dress.
I'm going to wash my face.
How to give him this?
How will you thank me?
Let's let off fireworks.
OK.
I'm going to buy some.
Well,
almost.
OK.
How much?
Well,
pay me 200 yuan.
200 yuan?
-OK. -OK.
-Thank you. -You can take them away.
I'm going to play cards.
OK.
Zhu Yun.
I've bought some.
What kind of fireworks do you want to see?
Those that
will blow up
in the air.
What?
Those that
will blow up in the air.
Your description is vivid.
Just this.
Wait a minute. I'm going to borrow a lighter.
I have one.
You have a lighter?
Catch it.
What a good repairer.
It must be hard to restore this.
Just so-so.
Princess,
thank you.
I gave you this in return.
Don't mistake my meaning.
Are you ready?
♫I pass by the world♫
♫And pass through the night♫
♫In the crowd in the dim light♫
♫You're over there with the fireworks♫
♫It's the intuition of the dream♫
♫That breaks through the boundary♫
♫The first sight♫
♫Spreads and later it wins the world for me♫
♫Cause I believe I love you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫I am at your side♫
Happy New Year.
♫Spending such a long time with you♫
♫Cause I believe I want you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
Happy New Year, Li Xun!
Happy New Year!
♫The hot firework♫
♫Keeps burning for me because of you♫
Eyelashes are so long.
♫I don't know how you've been♫
♫You don't know how I've been♫
♫Nothing has changed♫
♫Have you ever changed?♫
♫I don't know how you've been♫
What do you want to do?
♫You don't know how I've been♫
Good night.
♫It's been so long ago♫
♫I've been walking so long♫
Yun,
get up.
Why do you still lie in bed?
You didn't stay up late yesterday.
Sleepyhead,
rise and shine.
It's a nice day.
Hurry up.
Get up and get changed.
We're going to pay a New Year call.
[Wechat
You've received a WeChat message]
[Li Xun: I'm going back to the university. See you on campus.]
I'm going back to the university. See you on campus.
[Zhu Yun: See you on campus.]
See you on campus.
[Blue & White Coffee House]
I remember
you liked drinking taro milk tea in the past.
Thank you.
But now I prefer coffee.
Sometimes we like pretending to be mature.
Xiuzhu,
how long can you stay this time?
What's up?
I have a long vacation.
I have more than a month left.
Are you curious about Chinese universities?
How about I show you around my university?
Our university is
one of the leading key universities in China,
and its painting major is even very famous
among art academies.
If you didn't go abroad,
you might not be admitted into it.
Don't say so.
I mustn't be admitted.
I didn't mean that.
It's an honor to invite such an excellent artist
as you to our university.
You're abnormal.
Something must happen.
Nothing.
How about this?
I treat you to a good meal near my university
with my lucky money.
I smell something.
What?
A plot.
Just,
just do me a favor.
OK.
It's rare for you
to treat me.
Well,
when do you want to leave?
I'll help you.
Thank you
for allowing Zhu Yun to go with me.
I'm sorry for bothering you
during the Spring Festival.
Well,
Chinese and foreign universities
are greatly different
in both educational concept
and campus atmosphere.
Yun can show you
around Nanhu University these days.
It's rare for me to have a vacation.
I planned to stay at home for some days.
If I go to the university,
I'll have no time to come back.
It's rare for Xiuzhu to come back.
You go with him
and then preview
your lessons of next semester in the university.
Listen.
You must be self-disciplined in university,
or else you may not be admitted into any foreign college due to your bad grades in the future.
How about Xiuzhu go by himself?
I disagree.
You can take this opportunity
to ask him about some affairs,
such as the channel of publishing articles.
Am I right?
I just want to stay with you for some days.
Your university is not far.
If I miss you, I can go to see you at any time.
Go.
I'm leaving, mom.
Aunt, see you.
Drive slowly.
Master.
You want to go but pretended to be loath.
I learn this from you.
After all, you're good at pretending to be well-behaved
in front of parents.
OK, I can give you a discount on tuition.
I really want to learn
how to please my mother.
However,
it's a gift.
You can't acquire it.
Yeah.
It seems that you have a gift for pleasing my mother.
You two are CP , right?
Well, navigate for me.
Thank you.
Thank you, Xiuzhu.
Can you find a hotel later?
Well,
you ask me to leave now?
If I'm free tomorrow,
I'll definitely show you around.
It's late,
and you must be tired after driving me here.
Zhu Yun,
are you sure you won't use me anymore?
Why don't we have something in the canteen?
You're back.
♫I pass by the world♫
The preliminary of Information Security Competition
will be held in the Information Technology University.
♫And pass through the night♫
Hello,
I'm Xu Lina
from the Computer Science Department of this university.
I'm also a freshman.
♫In the crowd in the dim light♫
♫You're over there with the fireworks♫
Hello, Li Xun.
I've long heard your name.
♫You're over there with the fireworks♫
Sorry, I'm very busy.
♫It's the intuition of the dream♫
...and Fang Zhijing, who won the Special Attention Award in this competition, to come to the stage
♫That breaks through the boundary♫
and press the crystal ball with us.
♫The first sight♫
♫Spreads and later it wins the world for me♫
♫The clock keeps ticking♫
♫I am leaning on your shoulder♫
♫We won't break up♫
♫Stay with me from the hustle and bustle♫
♫It's the fulcrum of your palm♫
♫That gives me the courage to move forward♫
♫Just like the flame in the night♫
♫Cause I believe I love you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫I am at your side♫
♫Spending such a long time with you♫
♫Cause I believe I want you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫The hot firework♫
♫Keeps burning for me because of you♫
♫It's the intuition of the dream♫
♫That breaks through the boundary♫
♫The first sight♫
♫Spreads and later it wins the world for me♫
♫The clock keeps ticking♫
♫I also want to stand by your side♫
♫As long as I am brave enough♫
♫Every dream I have♫
♫Will not, will not, will not lose to the time♫
♫Cause I believe I love you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫I am at your side♫
♫Spending such a long time with you♫
♫Cause I believe I want you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫The hot firework♫
♫Keeps burning for me because of you♫
♫Cause I believe I love you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫I am at your side♫
♫Spending such a long time with you♫
♫Cause I believe I want you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫The hot firework♫
♫Keeps burning for me because of you♫