♫Everything is different when we watch the sky from the sea bottom♫
♫The person I used to be is gone♫
♫I no longer believed a person could save another♫
♫Until when you broke into my world♫
♫Even if the world fell apart into darkness♫
♫We would bloom in the darkness♫
♫The knight and the king♫
♫Like the white sails in night navigation are protecting the ocean♫
♫I see a clear direction♫
♫In which a touch of golden color flickers at the end of the wheat field♫
♫Even if I am the king♫
♫With supreme glory everything is meaningless without you♫
♫All what I did is to make you remember♫
♫The way everything was when it started♫
♫If I am the king♫
♫Who is proud and arrogant like wild and wind weeds♫
♫I only want you to be at my side whatever it takes♫
♫And everything is the way it used to be at the very beginning♫
[Adapted from Jinjiang Literature City novels "Lighter and Princess - Grassy Garden" and "Lighter and Princess - Changming Lamp" written by Twentine (Zhou Aihua)]
[Episode 32]
I can understand your fear.
I was watching
and my legs were shaking that day.
But you were really pushed down.
They've gone too far.
Even if you really ruin our game,
it's just a game.
But that's a game developed you.
Not only me.
It's a result of everyone's work in this company.
You didn't expect
it would cause such a serious consequence, right?
You thought
it would not be a big deal even if you were caught
hacking such a small company.
But even a small company
contains efforts of others.
Don't underestimate others.
Li Xun told me about you.
Would you like to go somewhere with me?
Where is this place?
Go in and have a look.
Have a look.
This room,
and all your stuff
are kept for you.
You've been dawdling for so long.
You don't even leave the downtown,
let along going abroad.
You're just waiting for him to come back to you.
Only he thinks of me as a person.
Li Xun won't leave.
You know him.
We still have something to do.
If you really care about him,
just come to live here by yourself.
[Password]
How is it?
Done.
You're a great political commissar.
You did a good job in persuading people.
What should we do next?
What should we do?
You two always have many ideals.
Don't ask me.
Well, we want to
bind him with a stone to sink him into the sea.
What nonsense are you talking about?
So I asked you what to do.
Let him stay in the company.
Do you accept it?
Well, if you don't keep him by your side,
what if he does something bad again?
And if he escapes from the city,
can you catch him?
It's better to keep him aside.
Didn't you also say that he is strong?
Our company is short of labor.
It's the best if he can help us.
I love that.
You give priority to the company's interests.
But he is a little ugly
and will lower the overall look of our company.
I'm leaving. I'm on vacation.
I'm the boss. Did she ask for leave?
She's always like this?
She is much lovelier when being a little more timid.
She is lovely whatever she does
because she is good looking.
Hou Ning.
The same words.
If you are to leave,
I won't keep you.
But as long as you follow me,
I will let you be an upright person.
I know.
How is Zhu Yun's cooking?
Horrible.
She finally has a disadvantage.
Political Commissar Zhu,
why didn't you get a red background?
This one doesn't look good.
Get down. Be careful.
What are you doing?
You even climb up with an adder.
[You can make money without doing evil]
Mr. Dong, come to have a look.
Mr. Dong.
[You can make money without doing evil]
What is this?
Look over here.
I can't understand wherever I look at it.
Let me explain.
New slogan.
Look.
This is written by our Political Commissar Zhu
YOU means you.
MONEY is money.
You know this as you play games.
Devil.
If you have money, you can be a devil.
Illiteracy.
You can make money without doing evil.
Well said.
Why do you point at me?
Hi.
Hi. Morning.
All is here.
Let me introduce.
This is my friend Hou Ning.
Zhang Fang, Zhao Teng, Guo Shijie.
Welcome.
Hou Ning.
I'll clear up a place for you later.
Zhao Teng, help him install the computer.
I have all the materials ready.
Take a look first.
You can ask
Li Xun if you have any question in work.
I'll get a host for you.
No need.
I've ordered one online.
It will be delivered here in the afternoon.
All right.
Our company's junk
should have been eliminated.
I have a question.
If he gets a good computer,
will he hack into others' computers faster?
Talkative.
You hang it up for me?
You're quite self-aware.
Half the people in our company were once in prison.
And considering Hou Ning's conducting behaviors
and Mr. Dong's amazing way
of solving problems,
I have to remind you guys at any time.
From this day onwards,
I am the president
of the Supervisory Committee of Flying.
I will keep an eye on you for Mr. Lin.
Think twice before you act.
Political Commissar Zhu,
you love being an official.
Not convinced?
Zhang Fang dislikes Hou Ning.
But it may be a good thing for Hou Ning.
If he wants to live
in this society honestly,
he must try to change people's views on him.
He can't escape like before.
But don't worry,
Zhang Fang is warm-hearted albeit his sharp tongue.
He won't really bully Hou Ning.
You'd better worry about Zhang Fang.
What you're looking at?
By rights,
I should stare at you in the company.
I warn you.
If you're not serious
and become a drag on the company.
Besides Mr. Dong
and Li Xun,
I can also teach you a lesson.
Zhang Fang.
The top casino is online.
I, I didn't touch anything.
What's that?
It's not mine.
Fang.
I stored them in the online disk.
I haven't watched it in the company.
Bullshit.
What are you watching?
Take a look. Take a look.
What a shame.
Take a look.
What?
Why are you so mean?
Get to work.
New comer.
You did it?
What do you mean?
Show off your skills here?
I confess
I've watched it.
But I paid for it myself.
I didn't hurt anyone.
How do you explain it?
Zhang Fang. Zhang Fang.
I asked him to do this.
We won't make such a joke any more.
He is a new comer.
Please take care of him.
For your sake.
You know what?
He is just like when you first came here.
What are you doing here?
It's quite noisy.
Are you fighting?
Come here after cleaning up.
I was thinking
our Flying Shelter
has more and more complete staff.
What do you mean?
Are you satirizing me?
No. No.
I dare not.
I dare not. I dare not.
Next week,
the Blind Box of Love, right?
It will have an internal test, right?
If it's delayed by you,
I won't spare you, you know?
Hello.
Dong's Delivery will serve you.
What's your good?
Okay, okay.
I can't take three people.
Wait for me.
-Wait for me! -Go! Go.
Don't delay your business.
How come the number of users has not increased these days?
You know it?
Zhang Fang, let me ask you.
Did you promote it?
Where did the money go?
I say in all honesty.
I typed every promotion articles
word by word.
So you spent no money.
Well, do you know
even good wine is afraid of being sold deep in the alley?
Others invest in promotion
as much as
their development cost.
Ren Di, do me a favor.
The Blind Box of Box has been internally tested for three days.
But the data is not optimistic.
What a shame.
Isn't this project mainly undertaken by Li Xun?
It is said that
he paid for it himself.
This time,
he bets all he has on it.
You can arrange people
to copy this game.
Let's make one by ourselves.
It's worthwhile?
How much will it cost us to make one ourselves?
Don't be too short-sighted.
You just want to leave after earning by making our company listed?
Although L&P has abundant funds,
we don't have enough backbone projects.
The data of many games will decline significantly
three to six months after they are online.
It is not easy to pass the examination and approval of the CSRC.
We also need a masterpiece.
Masterpiece?
You call this a masterpiece?
This game looks simple and straightforward.
But it is easier to be accepted by the market.
It has a large potential user base.
Once it's played,
it will be quite hot.
The disadvantage of Flying is publicity and promotion.
But this is our strong point.
Are we fool if we don't
launch it earlier and squeeze Flying out?
So sure?
Yeah.
I want to ask a question I shouldn't ask.
Is it out of your professional judgment
or personal reason?
Intuition.
This game will be hot.
This market is too big.
There are too many games that will be hot.
Leave it alone.
We make our money.
Why are you staring at this?
You don't want to see Li Xun stand up,
right?
I knew
as long as Li Xun farts,
you would come up and smell it.
I disagree.
L&P can't be led by
your personal gratitude and resentment.
Fang Zhijing.
Did I blind your eye?
Have you forgotten that pain?
Anyway, here is my tip.
Even if we develop one now, it's too late.
And even if you make it now,
we'll be more passive
if Li Xun aims at us.
Leave this alone.
I have my own arrangements.
Gather people first.
Ask Dongliang to gather the backbone of the Development Department.
The Blind Box of Love will go online soon.
There's no time.
Hurry up.
[Harmonic Studio]
Sorry for having kept you waiting so long.
It's okay.
Here you are.
How long has it been since he came to record?
He will come to record today.
He is delayed by a business dinner.
I think he can leave the band
to specialize in having business dinners with others.
Wait a moment.
Liu will be back soon.
Don't tell him I once came.
You can't wait for a while?
Zhu Yun and Li Xun have a project to ask you for help.
You can contact them
for specific content.
I have no friendship with them.
If you want me to help,
sit down and talk.
Their company has launched a new game.
Go on.
Here is the thing.
They want...
Hello, Mr. Zhao.
I must have a taste of your good wine.
OK, OK, OK.
Okay, I'll be there right away.
Are you not recording songs today?
Are you kidding? Mr. Zhao is waiting.
Ren Di.
Don't you want to know who Mr. Zhao is?
Fill up. Fill up.
Mr. Zhao.
Last time we were wrong.
I hope that you will let go of us such nobodies.
Come on. Cheers.
Mr. Zhao is the actual controller of Dongting International.
He strongly advocated signing five albums.
Then you quit Light Red.
He was angry.
How much to compensate?
I'll pay.
Mr. Zhao is not short of money.
He joined up with many record companies,
intending to block you.
Whatever.
After leaving Light Red,
I won't play music anymore.
I know you don't care.
But Liu does.
He always thought you are the soul of Light Red.
Light Red can't develop without you.
Come on. Come on.
Let's drink to our hearts' content.
One more. One more.
-Cheers. -Drink to our hearts' content...
He's been drinking with and socializing
people from record companies these days,
begging them not to block you.
♫You dominate our relationship♫
♫You said it's good to be alone♫
♫With no burden or worry♫
♫You rely on me as if I were your family♫
♫You want me to do this♫
You.
♫You always talk to me after drinking♫
Ren Di.
♫Saying that I'm very important  to you♫
Come back.
Let go.
♫And you laugh while talking♫
Ren Di, don't leave me, okay?
♫You said you can't pay back my kindness♫
♫In fact, I don't ask you to pay back♫
♫As long as I can stay with you♫
♫Nothing else matters♫
♫But tears of sadness♫
♫Are still falling down♫
Just take a picture that doesn't show his face.
Is it necessary to be so grand?
Now you know
how those so-called life photos
were taken.
Every angle is carefully designed.
Every exposed thing
has its intention.
But the band needs exposure.
You don't want to show up.
So he helps.
You do your duties and cooperate tacitly.
It's good.
When it comes to this, I feel angry.
We have to live like a dummy.
But Li Xun reminds that
you needn't mention this game when you pose
microblog with text.
Don't act like advertising.
It's natural for someone to dig for details.
You couple really amaze me.
That's his idea.
It has nothing to do with me.
You both
aim at me.
But think carefully.
When did you leave me alone?
Last time, you came to ask for money.
And this time, he called me
and told me to meet him.
Aren't you busy with activities every day?
He doesn't care about this.
I just left my work and went to meet him.
I don't think he's changed at all.
He is just like when he was a freshman.
We despised each other,
but somewhat,
what's that phrase?
Like knows like.
Yes, exactly.
You know what?
I remember a sentence he said to me before.
He said that affection is diamond cutting diamond
but love is letting go of ourselves.
He said that?
Actually, I really envy you.
You haven't changed for so many years,
Both of you have clear goals
and can let go of yourselves for each other.
When he was just released from the jail,
seeing him looking like a jerk,
I really thought he deserved it.
I hope he would live a miserable life.
But now
I still hope he can succeed.
L&P will be listed soon.
This is the last chance.
Are you still short of money?
Li Xun didn't go out to get investment,
which means he thinks we can survive.
If you earn money easily, you will feel it's boring.
I'm an example.
In the past, when I was poor,
I strived for every opportunity to perform.
But now...
Okay.
The next group will be here soon.
Get ready.
This way, everyone.
Hello, sir I need to make up for you.
I'll finish soon.
Where do I stand?
Pick a place yourself.
I'm standing here.
Pick a place ourselves, and I'm sitting here?
You two stand here.
Come on.
Let's change the position.
He is short.
Wait.
What's wrong, Mr. Dong?
What's wrong?
-I thought you would dole out money. -Stylish.
Let's take a serious picture first.
-Cool picture. -Okay.
I haven't taken pictures for several years.
I think
the two group leaders should take a group picture alone.
One, two, three.
Come on.
It's not natural to wear it.
This one is good for everyone.
What's good? I show half a face.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, just this one.
Why? I show half a face only.
Just take this one.
Just this one.
When you wear this suit,
you look like one of the top 50
on the Forbes list.
Enough. Enough.
This, this, this.
It's like a fool.
It's really good. Why do you belittle yourself?
Yeah. You are not like Guo Xiaojian.
That dress belongs to your father, right?
Why do you dress like a manager in the lobby?
Stop it.
I dress like a private car driver.
Who are you satirizing?
Don't insult the private car driver
What's wrong? I've improved their level...
That's it. That's it.
Look.
Why is this so like that...
Let's just say the wedding photo.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
A good match.
Change the background color to red later.
One, ten, hundred, comma, thousand, ten thousand...
Ten thousand
Three million. I counted correctly?
Is it real?
Our Blind Box of Love has been on line for less than half a month,
and the current income is three million yuan.
[Cumulative Gain 3,000,000]
What does this mean?
It means that in one year and five months, it will be over 100 million yuan.
Yes!
Why are you so vulgar?
You just focus on money.
You know what?
This means,
our business has been successful.
We succeed.
You know what?
Our marketing is well done.
Once it became a keyword,
its search number increased quickly.
But at this moment,
I shrunk its registration number
and released four thousand accounts a day.
I don't care who would play it.
This is called hunger marketing.
I must let them know, being able to play this game
is a special thing to show off.
That's it.
Of course it is
mainly because of Mr. Dong's great leadership
and Li Xun's good plan.
So you have to keep up with the later publicity.
Rest assured.
I'll listen to whatever you say later.
You and Li Xun are the two gods of our company.
Where's Li Xun?
Last night, he updated the patch and stayed up all night.
Now he is sleeping inside.
He works so hard.
If you turn off the light now, he'll wake up.
He doesn't like the dark.
Why?
Because the prison's lights
are on for 24 hours a day.
How is the current income?
You still care about this?
If you keep going like this,
you will collapse.
Hurry home and go to bed.
[Tactical Meeting Room]
Our Development Department has studied the Blind Box of Love.
To make a similar game,
at least half a year is needed.
Does this small game
take so long?
Their game is very strange.
It has many game settings we haven't seen before.
If there is no template,
it's difficult to achieve.
If we make one ourselves,
how long will it take?
At least
four months.
Hou Ning is good at taking care of people.
You can't always stay up.
The company won't go bankrupt without you.
What are you thinking about?
I was thinking.
If I'm not guessing wrong,
Gao Jianhong is already trying to find a way
to copy the codes of the Blind Box of Love.
I see.
Were it before,
you wouldn't pay much efforts on
such games as Blind Box of Love.
You focus on it
because L&P is going to be listed soon
and you need to hurry up
and try your best to push it to the top.
You want to attract Gao Jianhong to plagiarize,
and then sue them for infringement.
Are my things so easy to imitate?
If I don't give him the source code,
it will take them at least half a year
to copy a little of this game.
No wonder when I read
the code of the Blind Box of Love,
I found many strange places.
You used to write code that was very readable.
But this time, you used a lot of complicated structures.
The more unique the code,
the more traps there would be.
But even if they fall into a trap,
are we really going to give them half a year
to make counterfeit goods?
So,
I will give them the source code directly.
I've checked
cases of game infringement in China.
If it's just a simple imitation,
it's hard to win.
Not to mention whether we can afford the lawyer's fees,
the backlog of game copyright lawsuits in China
wouldn't be completed in ten years.
If we really fight a war of attrition with L&P,
we'll go bankrupt first.
Don't worry.
Gao Jianhong is more worried than us.
Who else knows about this plan?
Hou Ning and Dong Siyang.
And you.
How about Zhao Teng and others?
They don't know it.
Remember.
The fewer people know it, the better.
How do you let them get the source code?
Will Gao Jianhong copy it directly?
Don't worry about that.
They are used to taking evil ways.
They wouldn't take what I give them directly.
Gao Jianhong has been copying successful projects.
The reason why they can grow up
is because the game market is too chaotic.
China has a large number of users.
They are highly tolerant
of those fresh games.
But what is empty is empty after all.
People can't be stupid forever.
When users grow up,
these companies without independent R&D capability
will go bankrupt.
But how can users grow up
within just a few months?
L&P will be listed soon.
Will they take this risk?
I'll force him to copy.
Such a small company
is like a clown for us.
Remarketing won't help them.
Its annual income must be less than
our company's monthly income.
Gao.
You must not be led by Li Xun.
My review materials will be submitted soon.
Now is the most critical time.
For the company,
you must bear it.
Mr. Gao.
What's your next goal?
To be No. 1 in the industry.
It's really ambitious.
But considering the industrial giants, like
L&P as your competitors,
their strength...
Strength?
What kind of strength do you think L&P has?
Copy and paste?
Companies like that
are not worthy to be our competitor.
[Exclusive Interview with Li Xun
My Heart Flying Network Company]
Gao.
Even if Li Xun develops eight games like the Blind Box of Love,
he won't be a threat to us.
He's intending to irritate you.
I'll tell you one last time.
Take care of what you should take care of.
Don't tell me what to do.
If you don't want to work,
you can leave.
But I must do this.
Got it.
These people are stubborn.
At first glance, it's from Southeast Asia.
Ancestral.
Implantation of RDBMS,
nothing new.
How about we show weakness
and let Gao Jianhong take the source code away?
We've fought with them once.
With our strength,
if we allow him to take the code away,
would they dare to copy it directly?
Then I'll do my best.
You are not allowed to enter here casually.
What are you doing?
I almost forgot
you can understand it.
What do you think?
What's the hottest thing recently?
This is the background data of the Blind Box of Love?
What are you up to?
If there is anything to learn from?
You want to steal the source code?
In the past, you copy others.
Now you dare to steal the source code?
You're breaking the law, you know?
These hackers are in Malaysia.
They can't find us.
Isn't the company going public?
You really pick the right time.
It's none of my business.
I've said all that I should say and persuade.
You can have a talk.
Why are you like Fang Zhijing?
Do you care about money only?
You deal with Li Xun
in such a dirty way.
That's what you want?
If you want to go to jail, leave me alone.
Let's get divorced.
You want to say
this for a long time, right?
That's what you really want to say.
You don't need so much bedding.
If you want a divorce, just tell me.
Count your losses first.
Don't be a loss leader.
Incurable.
I'm entering it.
This firewall looks like paper.
Let's draw the snake out of the hole.
Then go straight to the nest.
[Loser]
Okay, that's it.
Luna.
This one is just delivered to our store.
Mr. Gao said you would like it.
It suits you.
This diamond is twelve point thirteen carats.
It's just your birthday's number.
Mr. Gao specially made it for you.
Do you like it?
My birthday hasn't arrived yet.
I just wanted to give you a gift.
It doesn't matter what day it is.
Do you still remember?
The first time we ate together
in a restaurant like this.
You and me at that time...
Of course I do.
Lina.
I'm sorry.
When I proposed to you,
I promised
I would never be angry with you.
But I failed.
I was also impulsive that day.
But have you considered
what I said?
Divorce.
We won't talk about this today.
Don't you want to stay in Paris for a while?
I'll go with you.
We can buy a house together.
You apply for another school
to get a master's degree.
Gao.
Actually, you don't have to give me anything.
I just think we haven't
had a meal like this
and talked like this for a long time.
I thought
as long as I succeeded in career,
my family would naturally be better.
But I overlooked the most important thing.
Your feelings.
All relationships
need to be cared.
Lina.
I'm sorry
for ignoring your feelings.
Would you like to give me another chance?
I do especially want
to thank someone.
That's Gao Jianhong, the CEO of L&P.
Mr. Gao.
Are you jealous?
Later, more and more women
will show up around Li Xun.
You'll regret it.
Li Xun.
Do you really think no one can defeat you?
♫That breaks through the boundary♫
♫The first sight♫
♫Spreads and later it wins the world for me♫
♫The clock keeps ticking♫
♫I am leaning on your shoulder♫
♫We won't break up♫
♫Stay with me from the hustle and bustle♫
♫It's the fulcrum of your palm♫
♫That gives me the courage to move forward♫
♫Just like the flame in the night♫
♫Cause I believe I love you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫I am at your side♫
♫Spending such a long time with you♫
♫Cause I believe I want you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫The hot firework♫
♫Keeps burning for me because of you♫
♫It's the intuition of the dream♫
♫That breaks through the boundary♫
♫The first sight♫
♫Spreads and later it wins the world for me♫
♫The clock keeps ticking♫
♫I also want to stand by your side♫
♫As long as I am brave enough♫
♫Every dream I have♫
♫Will not, will not, will not lose to the time♫
♫Cause I believe I love you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫I am at your side♫
♫Spending such a long time with you♫
♫Cause I believe I want you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫The hot firework♫
♫Keeps burning for me because of you♫
♫Cause I believe I love you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫I am at your side♫
♫Spending such a long time with you♫
♫Cause I believe I want you♫
♫True love will take it's course♫
♫The hot firework♫
♫Keeps burning for me because of you♫