(GBRB: Farm Operation - Go Go Farm)
(Lee Kwang Soo)
(Kim Woo Bin)
(Doh Kyung Soo)
(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
(GBRB: Farm Operation - Go Go Farm)
(KKPP versus Farm, Round 2 of yutnori)
The four of us will do...
the morning task tomorrow.
(A game of yutnori with the next morning's work on the line)
(Thanks to Kyung Soo's miraculous performance,)
(KKPP claimed victory in Round 2.)
(Final yutnori result: KKPP treats everyone to lunch.)
(Exempt from the extra task of spreading out garlic peel)
(Day 3 of their technical training, their last day at the dairy farm)
Why don't we divide the work?
(The trainees assign roles among themselves and become more skilled.)
We're working faster than yesterday.
(Just about to take a break after finishing the morning task early)
- Kyung Soo, let's go.
- Okay.
What are they?
- Good job on the morning task.
- Thanks.
You're going to take a rest now.
- Okay.
- But on your way...
Could I ask you a favor?
Sure.
So...
(What favor?)
From the milk our cows produce...
on the farm, we make things like yogurt.
I see.
We supply them at local grocery stores...
- and cafes.
- Okay.
I'd like to ask you to help...
- with the deliveries.
- Delivery?
- Delivery? I see.
- That's right.
- Take a look here.
- Do you supply milk too?
(He opens his bag and looks for something.)
I brought it while I was at the warehouse.
What is it? Is it cheese?
- Thank you.
- It's string cheese.
That's right.
(Excited about the food gift)
- I really love it.
- Get their signature and...
I always buy it whenever I go to the convenience store.
This is the same.
(He couldn't wait and opened it right away.)
Please deliver this to the cafe.
Get their signature...
- and bring half of the page.
- Okay.
This one is simple.
(The CEO and intern are distracted by the cheese.)
And there will be some leftovers.
(He picks one piece of cheese...)
(and takes a bite.)
If you subtract the leftover from 20,
- My goodness.
- it will be...
(Exclaiming)
This is always used...
- It's so good.
- Yes.
So there are 20 each.
We collect back anything that doesn't get sold.
Because the customers should not eat the spoiled one.
(Even the Food Director takes a moment to savor the taste.)
Everything I thought was string cheese until now...
wasn't real string cheese.
(There he goes again.)
How is this so good?
(Delighted by how good it is)
- This would make an amazing pizza.
- Put 20 of them...
(Three people eating, one person working)
Can you give me a bite?
(After completing the takeover, the auditor finally gets a bite.)
Gosh, it's so good.
(After tasting the cheese)
We'll get going now.
(The trainees head out to deliver.)
(Current time: 10am)
(First, they're on their way to deliver to a cafe.)
Sang Hoon, are you really hungry?
I'm running out of energy.
(The trainees have been working since dawn and haven't eaten yet.)
We're on our way...
- to make deliveries.
- Yes.
If we make the deliveries and stop somewhere to eat...
Will we have enough time?
How about this?
Let's make the deliveries first.
I heard there's a brick oven at the farm,
so we could make something there.
Like pizza since we have cheese.
Do you want to make something with cheese at the farm?
(They plan to skip breakfast and make lunch with the brick oven.)
- So...
- As brunch?
Yes.
We can eat lunch at the farm,
but we're a bit hungry now.
Let's stop by a bakery and get some bread.
Let's get some bread.
- That's a great idea.
- So we can eat something.
- We're here.
- The cafe is over there.
That's the cafe. The word "coffee" is written there.
(They arrive at the cafe.)
We're here.
Please get out.
That should be the one with ten.
(Taking the yogurt to deliver)
Okay.
- Hello.
We're here to deliver some yogurt.
- Here you go.
- Okay.
(Delivering yogurt to the cafe)
We have things to collect back, don't we?
Don't we have returns to pick up?
No, there aren't any returns.
We're using all of them,
so there isn't anything to return.
- So we can just go?
- Yes.
- I see. Is that good news?
- Thank you.
- It means they're selling well.
- Exactly.
I see.
We've never had a single return.
(Feeling proud that everything sells out)
- Thank you.
- It gets sold out.
Yesterday,
- we milked the cows ourselves.
- Really?
That's great.
To be more precise,
only the three of us worked yesterday.
Sang Hoon got here late.
- He arrived yesterday afternoon.
- I see.
So the three of us made it.
- Oh, thank you.
- Sure.
(The CEO draws a firm line.)
- We'll get going.
- Goodbye.
- Thank you.
- Have a good day.
Bye.
(They arrive at a grocery store, the second delivery stop.)
Do you know those peanut cream buns they sell...
at the grocery store bakery?
- And mammoth bread?
- Yes.
- Those are delicious.
- I love that bread.
The classic ones.
Which way do we go?
Kwang Soo, there's Tous les Jours bakery.
Right.
(They spot the bakery as soon as they walk in.)
(As if hypnotized, he heads somewhere.)
Let's make the delivery first. He said that we had our own shelf.
Are those vegetable dinner rolls?
Did you know that they disappeared?
We used to have them as kids.
With vegetable bits inside.
I don't know them.
It's a type of dinner roll.
Sweet dinner rolls...
No, there are vegetable dinner rolls.
(The hungry intern can't stop talking about food.)
Delivery?
He said that we had our own shelf.
- Our own shelf?
- Yes.
- Hello.
Excuse me, but where can we find yogurt?
- Yogurt?
- Yes.
Take the escalator. You'll find it on the second floor.
On the second floor? Thank you.
Thank you.
(They head up to the 2nd floor.)
Woo Bin.
If we're going to cook something later,
- Get groceries here?
- we can buy the ingredients here.
That's a good idea.
(They decide to shop for lunch after finishing the delivery.)
What would be good to cook in a brick oven?
Wood-fired pizza.
May I ask you something?
If it's possible,
how about making curry and dipping naan in it?
- Oh, my.
- That sounds good.
I can definitely make...
- curry.
- That sounds so good.
That sounds really good.
(The intern seems confident about making curry.)
- Here they are.
- Right.
(They decide to finish the delivery first.)
We can put them in the back.
Wait, I need to check the inventory.
One, two, three.
(Woo Bin checks the inventory.)
He said that we needed to collect these back.
- We need to collect them back?
- I think we should take them out.
Yes.
Hello.
We're going to pick up the yogurt and restock the shelf.
- Gosh, hello.
- Hello.
- Can we take these?
- Yes.
We'll take the remainder...
- and replace them...
- Yes.
- with new ones.
- We'll restock them.
Please leave what you brought.
- Really?
- Yes.
Okay. We got it.
The ones in the front aren't the same brand, right?
- No, they are not.
- No.
Would it be okay if we moved them?
- That's a good idea.
- To the front...
I'm sorry, but our brand should be placed...
in the front.
(Hoping their products would stand out a little more)
I apologize to the other sellers, but it can't be helped.
It'd be better to create a boundary.
Someone might end up buying another brand instead.
Should I place them like this?
(Hoping their products stand out more)
It'd be nice if we could mist it with a spray.
Like in a commercial.
(Wanting to do anything they could to help)
Looking at the label makes you...
want to buy it.
(After finishing the second delivery with lots of care)
Sang Hoon, please make us curry this time.
What do you think about curry?
I love curry.
- I like it too.
- It's my favorite.
- It just needs rice.
- Right.
(Menu Number 1: Intern Moon's signature curry)
I'll look up how to make naan.
As long as it's not too hard...
- Shall we just try it?
- I'll look it up.
Let's make it work.
That sounds good, Sang Hoon.
(Looking up how to make naan)
If we make naan,
we could top it with tomato sauce and cheese,
- and pop it into the brick oven.
- That's an option.
(Menu Number 2: Wood-fired pizza)
(Before deciding on the menu, they ask the farm seniors.)
- Hello?
- Hello, Mr. Kkalloo.
Hello, Mr. Kkalloo. This is CEO Lee.
I'm sorry?
This is CEO Lee.
Oh, hello.
We're thinking of having...
naan and curry for lunch.
What do you think?
Do whatever works best for you.
What does Mr. Lal think?
Lal would like that too.
Can you make them?
We've never tried, but we'll give it a try.
I see. Okay, CEO Lee.
Did you just laugh at us?
What? No.
Once we finish the deliveries, we'll head back.
- See you soon.
- Bye.
I think I can make it.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Today's chef has found his confidence.)
On top of that, it requires plain yogurt.
- We can use...
- Seriously?
- what we take back.
- You can use this.
(The yogurt is already set.)
I'll walk you through the ingredients.
Two cups of flour, plain yogurt,
warm water, yeast.
We can buy yeast here.
I can stretch it out like this and put it together.
Let's hurry and buy the ingredients.
Okay.
(Grocery shopping begins under Chef Moon's lead.)
What type of flour is it? All-purpose flour?
It must be either bread flour or all-purpose flour.
- All-purpose flour.
- One all-purpose flour.
And yeast.
It should be somewhere around here.
(They quickly grab the yeast.)
Tomato sauce.
Wild arugula.
These look so good.
One pack of chicken thighs and one pack of chicken breast.
There are 2 farm owners and 1 CEO.
All right.
Do we need 1 or 2 of these?
I'll get 1kg.
We're making curry for 12 servings.
I'll use twice as many potatoes as carrots.
(2kg of potatoes)
(Onions)
Is that all?
Carrots, onions, potatoes.
Aren't these enough?
(Lastly, Chef Moon is picking out the curry powder.)
Are two enough?
Two packs and this.
- How about slightly spicy?
- That sounds great.
(The secret is layering the curry flavor.)
So you mix different kinds of curry.
Yes.
Aren't you pretending...
- No.
- like you have your own recipe?
- It seems like it.
- Caramel...
Shall I make caramel onions?
- Caramel onions?
- Caramelized onions.
That sounds good.
Actually, that takes a lot of work.
You're good at cooking, aren't you?
No, I can only make curry. That's my one signature dish.
Instead of making rice...
Let's make rice too.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
First, over medium-low heat,
you keep stirring the onions for about 15 minutes.
They eventually turn brown.
Once they turn brown,
they give the sweetness and flavor.
You keep stir-frying them...
until they reach that brown color.
When the onions turn brown,
you add chopped chicken thighs.
Then you add the curry powder.
(In the end, the full recipe remained a secret.)
We're getting fishcake, right?
(They found a fishcake stand on their way out.)
Let's have some.
Hello.
(They settle for a quick bite.)
Gosh, they look delicious.
Why don't we get two rice cake ones? We can take a bite each.
Let's get two rice cake fishcakes.
(Ordering 2 rice cake fishcakes)
- Two rice cake fishcakes, please.
- Two?
- Could you cut them?
- Yes.
In half.
(2 rice cake fishcakes into 4 pieces)
We'll eat them here.
- Thank you.
Go ahead and eat.
(Their first bite after a long morning without food)
Shall we eat together in the count of three?
One, two, three.
(How is their first bite?)
(The deeply touching first bite)
I'm glad that we didn't get any sauce.
It tastes so good.
- Your fishcakes are excellent.
- I agree.
(They taste even better on an empty stomach.)
(Cleaning up)
This is just a question.
- Is the chili fishcake spicy?
- This is just a question.
How about getting one chili fishcake...
and dividing it in four?
- Into four pieces.
- That sounds great.
- Aren't you curious about it?
- I'm also in.
Okay. Sir, can we get one chili fishcake?
(Curiosity gets the better of them, so they order more.)
It's really delicious.
(1 chili fishcake gets ready in no time.)
One, two, three.
(Eating the 3rd fishcake just like the 1st)
The chili fishcake is better.
- This was it.
- Yes, it tastes better.
- It's the right amount of spicy.
- Nice and spicy.
(Just enough spice to whet the appetite)
Crab sticks are similar to fishcakes, right?
But is a crab stick fishcake different?
(A question conveniently leading to his next target)
Let's just get one more and stop.
All right.
(They're about to order one more.)
It's 10 dollars for 5.
- How many did we eat so far?
- Three.
Should we also get a sesame leaf fishcake?
It's the same price, but you get one extra.
Right.
Then let's get 1 sesame leaf and 1 crab stick.
Please cut them into four pieces each.
On this plate.
I can never resist 5 for 10-dollar deals.
- Thank you.
The crab stick one looks so...
Take the crab stick fishcake.
(Hesitating)
- Have some.
- I'll pick...
- after Woo Bin.
- Just pick one.
Woo Bin, pick one of the crab stick pieces.
Do you like the ends?
Yes.
You should take the bigger piece.
Which one do you want, Sang Hoon?
(The bigger piece)
Go ahead.
(A piece of crab stick fishcake)
One, two, three.
(A piece of sesame leaf fishcake)
- This tastes mild.
- It's good.
It tastes mild.
- Thank you, sir.
- Thank you.
This supermarket is a little dangerous,
don't you think?
We can't seem to walk past anything.
(Was this a sign of things to come?)
Do you agree with him?
When you press bar rice cakes into sesame oil soy sauce,
they get flat and spring back while soaking up the soy sauce.
- I know what you mean.
- The sauce gets absorbed.
Like a sponge when washing dishes...
Yes.
Gosh, it looks like nurungji.
Kwang Soo, let's get this.
It's crispy on the outside and moist on the inside.
Seriously.
Shouldn't we try a croffle too?
- Kwang Soo, let's get it next time.
- Ten of these...
We'll get it next time.
Shouldn't we at least taste it?
One apple croffle, please.
We need to get some walnut balls.
(Their appetite keeps growing endlessly.)
- Hello.
- Aren't we going to Tous les Jours?
We came here originally for bread.
Sang Hoon, aren't we going to Tous les Jours?
Tous les Jours?
Ever since I was a kid, my wish was to eat this as much as I wanted.
Do you want to make that wish come true today?
Did you know that twisted donuts are good with ketchup?
Doesn't it look like a baby's bottom?
- It looks so good.
- You're right.
If it's rich milk bread, we must get it.
- Sesame seed glutinous rice bread.
- This is really good.
- Totally.
I like tearing out the soft inside of this bread,
rolling it into balls, and eating it.
I know what you mean.
- You can do that with toast bread.
- Right.
(Did you make your wish come true?)
Honestly, I don't think these are just food.
They're closer to souvenirs.
Here you go, Sang Hoon.
It's really good.
Honestly, I wanted to stop eating after two pieces of fishcake.
Really?
I wanted to stop you guys,
but even you got pulled in.
I lost control before I even realized it.
(The auditor was slowly won over by the CEO and the intern.)
Look at them.
They're eating even during the interview
(You're a perfect match.)
I'm not sure.
- We just found our rhythm.
- We played a piece of music.
I was improvising in a jam session.
It felt like our chords naturally fell into place.
He's the guide I've been searching for.
He shows me the direction.
I can't open my eyes when I swim.
While I'm swimming with my eyes closed,
CEO Lee seems to guide me in the right direction.
Here's why.
I can't swim, but I can see where I'm going.
I can't see what's ahead, but I know how to swim.
(Their teamwork and chemistry are incredible.)
What's that called?
The upper body is human,
but the legs are a horse.
- A centaur?
- Yes.
If we became a centaur,
I'd gladly give Sang Hoon the upper body.
I'd spend my whole life...
pooping.
I'd let Sang Hoon handle...
eating good food, talking,
and everything else.
My parents gave birth to me,
but CEO Lee is the one who truly understands me.
(GBRB Farm Operation - Go Go Farm)
(Lee Kwang Soo)
(Kim Woo Bin)
(Doh Kyung Soo)
(GBRB Farm Operation - Go Go Farm)
(They return to the farm after getting groceries.)
(After briefly organizing the groceries)
If you marinate this in milk, it gets rid of the gamey smell.
- I mean the chicken.
- In milk?
(Milk is needed for Sang Hoon's chicken curry.)
Milk also works well in curry.
Can we get some milk?
Sir.
Sir, could we get some milk?
- I'll give you some.
- Do you have milk?
- Sang Hoon needs some.
- Milk is what we have.
Right.
It felt strange to buy milk somewhere else.
- We have a lot here.
- Right?
Do you have a lot of milk?
We have plenty of milk that you produced.
Right.
We have a lot of milk. I'll ask them to bring it.
Do you have a lot of milk?
Yes, we do.
(The intern shows a cheesy wordplay.)
- Are you from Chungcheong Province?
- If he pretended not to hear you,
he doesn't get the joke.
He just asked if you were from Chungcheong Province.
- Shall we start?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Sang Hoon, I'll wash these.
They're washed carrots.
(Washing isn't necessary.)
Kyung Soo, what should we do?
- What? You can help Sang Hoon.
- Sang Hoon, what should we do?
Put some milk into that stainless steel container.
- Cut up the chicken breast...
- And potatoes?
and thighs...
and let them soak in it.
Put the chicken in here.
Yes.
(Director Doh's pizza will be revealed in the unaired footage.)
This is my first time cutting chicken like this.
- Mine too.
- Right?
Just doing this feels somewhat satisfying.
It feels like we're cooking.
We feel cool from doing this.
Whenever people eat this meat,
they'll think of us.
How long should we marinate it?
While I make caramelized onions,
ten to twenty minutes will be enough.
(Exclaiming)
By the way, how do you make that caramel thing?
When they turn brown, the moisture evaporates.
With the buttery aroma,
the onions will become sweet.
I'll get the onions started.
While I ask you to keep stirring them,
- I'll try making the naan.
- You have a nice way of speaking.
Like saying "while I ask you."
- I see.
- What I mean is...
It makes me feel like...
- Respected?
- I'm part of the team.
- Right.
- I feel like I'm really cooking.
I'm also part of KKPP.
(The head chef intern starts chopping onions.)
- A little bit...
- Wait a moment.
You cut it so evenly...
- and neatly.
- In a clean way.
Sang Hoon was on a cooking show.
(Former assistant to a famous chef)
The onion...
Who chops it like that?
Sang Hoon.
Actually,
the grain of the onion runs this way.
You're right.
- Then why did you cut it like this?
- "You're right?"
I kept changing directions,
- but I couldn't find the right one.
- Really?
Should we just do it this way today?
With a bit of charm?
Have you ever seen anyone cut onions like this?
You don't know, do you?
I don't.
If you don't know, come over here and cut this.
What are you doing?
Once you cook this with butter,
it'll taste the same anyway.
- Are you putting it in?
- Yes.
- Is this right?
(They pour milk over neatly cut chicken.)
Kwang Soo, we're so cool.
I think we can start doing something with this.
(Letting the chicken sit in the milk for a while)
I feel like I'm doing something with the brick oven next to me.
- Shall I prepare four potatoes?
- Okay.
(He rinses the washed carrots.)
Why don't we add more potatoes?
- Five potatoes?
- CEO Hwang likes potatoes.
That's true.
- He eats potatoes for every meal.
- Right.
Imagine potatoes in a curry...
and cut them how you see fit.
Woo Bin, don't you like chunks of potatoes in your dish?
In a curry, they taste better as big chunks.
Believe it or not, I've made curry a few times.
I'm not like you.
I made curry the day before coming to Jeju Island.
(The competition for last place in cooking skills is fierce.)
(CEO Lee rolls up his sleeves.)
(Caramelizing the onions begins.)
(The director and the auditor)
(They cut potatoes and carrots for the curry.)
(Meanwhile, the intern looks at the recipe for a long time.)
(He starts making dough for the naan.)
I have no idea how much I'm supposed to put in.
Is this right?
(Yeast)
(Sugar)
(He pours some hot water.)
By the way...
What?
(Laughing)
What is it?
It's because...
(Glancing at it again)
What? Why did you laugh?
Sang Hoon, wasn't the amount indicated in the recipe?
- For the water?
- Yes.
Right.
Did I add too much water?
Sang Hoon.
It's still not too late to be honest.
Do you know how to make curry or not?
But this is...
(The doubts start to grow.)
I'm making naan,
- and it's my first time making it.
- In the recipe,
could you check the amount...
- All right.
- before you continue?
Are you feeling pressured...
because you were on a cooking show?
I didn't do anything there except talk.
Chef Choi Kang Rok did all the cooking.
All I did was make comments like "That looks good."
I see.
- Then look it up.
- Okay.
Or call the chef.
Do something about it.
What are you going to do with this?
(Yeast sugar porridge)
It requires only 3g.
How much did you add?
(You just found that out?)
He poured the entire thing.
Sang Hoon, shall I throw it away?
No, I'll add this to the flour.
Shall I throw it away? Would that make you feel better?
- Is this okay to use?
- How many grams of yeast was it?
About...
About 15g.
Why don't we throw it away and start again?
We might as well since the warm water is ready.
I'll wash it for you.
Then...
Can I do this instead?
Why me?
Why would you take over what I'm doing?
- I...
- How low do you want me to go?
(Things aren't working out for you.)
I thought if I suggested something,
Kyung Soo or others would...
lead the rest.
But they left me in charge of everything.
It feels like they're telling me, "You take control!"
That's how I feel.
(The intern is put in charge of such a big project from the start.)
I'll really take the scientific approach.
I'll put 6g of instant yeast.
(Yeast again)
I'll add 260g.
- Two hundred and sixty.
- Yes.
Okay.
- That's perfect.
- That's 260g.
That was perfect.
Next, 10g of sugar.
And 400g of flour.
Next, 6g of salt.
(This time, the intern measures everything precisely.)
Wait for five minutes,
and it might start to bubble up.
What do you mean it might?
I mean, it should.
(He doesn't sound all that reliable.)
What should I do, Sang Hoon?
Throw away the milk...
- and wash it with water.
- Wash it?
And you could maybe grill it here.
(His task is to wash the chicken in water and grill the surface.)
We're in charge of a lot of important tasks.
- I know, right?
- You need to grill it too.
But please check it with Kyung Soo.
- What is it?
- Should I wash this with water?
Wash...
Don't wash it. Use a sieve and...
- You can use this.
- Like this?
(He threw away only the milk and kept the chicken intact.)
- Well...
- How is it?
(Sang Hoon has started to make the dough for naan.)
- It looks pretty legit.
- Right.
Now, cook it over high heat...
to just grill the surface.
I'll be kneading the dough here.
Okay.
Is this right?
Honestly, I've never even made sujebi.
He has never even made sujebi.
I mean, why, from the first place...
Tell me if I'm doing it wrong.
It isn't too late.
We have instant rice too.
- We can grill the rice in the oven.
- Naan...
Why would you grill the instant rice in the oven?
(Their doubt became a certainty.)
(As per the intern's instruction, he adds some oil in the pan.)
(He starts to grill chicken.)
(The intern kneads the dough.)
(Glancing up)
(Glancing up again)
(Something is going very wrong.)
Shall I add more water?
This is how it's supposed to be, right?
It's supposed to be this thick, right?
Nice.
- Water...
- A bit more of it?
It should unstick at least.
I think...
there's too much water.
- Oh, it's the opposite?
- Yes.
There's too much water, I see.
Shall I add more flour, then?
- Good.
- Okay. I'll bring over the flour.
Good.
I took a completely opposite approach.
(The intern is wavering. Will he be okay?)
I think we gave him enough chances.
Actually, this meal preparation itself...
is Sang Hoon's farewell party.
(He is at risk of losing his head chef position.)
Kyung Soo, do you mind if I knead the dough?
Sang Hoon is...
No, Kwang Soo. Just do your onions.
You...
You need to attend to the onions until they turn brown.
But he isn't making the dough right.
(To salvage the dough,)
(he adds some flour.)
Right, this is how it feels.
Yes. Now I can knead it better.
Right. Now I get it.
I'm more confident now.
We shouldn't cook.
Even with three people here,
none of them are of help.
I did kind of have high hopes.
Should I put in all the meat and cook them at once?
- I thought they'd still...
- Not you!
I thought they'd still be able to cook somewhat.
I'm not talking to you.
I was wrong.
- Kyung Soo.
- Yes?
Should I put all the meat in and cook them at once?
- But Sang Hoon...
- The color is changing.
Sang Hoon has his recipe.
And how do we cook that?
I want to try following it...
until the end.
(The director still has faith in the intern.)
- Put all in?
- I want to try his food.
(If you follow Sang Hoon's recipe, you shouldn't put all in.)
- Enough.
- Let's just put all in.
(Cooked meat and uncooked meat have been mixed.)
The curry you were trying...
to make...
is gone now because he put in the whole thing.
- We failed?
- Yes.
- Because Kwang Soo put all in?
- There's a reason...
I put Kwang Soo in charge of stir-frying onions only.
Woo Bin was adding bit by bit.
(Nodding)
He's almost boiling...
You don't cook like this even for a school lunch.
(The CEO, who feels guilty, gets angry at him instead.)
But there's one more...
There's no fire.
No fire, right?
What are you doing?
There's no fire underneath.
- I mean, when we use this, - We didn't light it up yet.
the heat might become really strong.
Shall we ignite this, then?
(The intern's idea has been adopted.)
I should fan it until the fire gets stronger, right?
Yes. I think the fire did light up.
- It's pretty strong.
- Yes.
By boiling it...
(The sound of kids playing)
We could have Ji Woo try a bite too.
We'll make it not spicy.
My younger sibling's sons.
Ye Chan and Yi Chan.
They're running around on the grass field.
I realized now that this has...
a lot more responsibility than cooking for myself...
at home.
When I cook for myself,
I'll just go, "That wasn't nice. I'll do it this way next time."
But thinking about...
how I need to treat the CEO, the boss, Ye Chan, and Yi Chan...
How can you feel the responsibility only now?
Shouldn't you have felt it at the supermarket?
(It's great that he realized it, but the timing is a shame.)
(The cauldron is heated up nicely.)
(Transfer the surface-cooked chicken into the cauldron.)
- Shall I put in the onions too?
- Put in the onions.
(The caramelized onions are added too.)
(They add carrots, potatoes, and raw onions as well.)
- It already...
- What?
- It's turning golden-brown.
- Yes.
- It looks delicious.
- Shall we add some pepper?
Sounds good.
Onions...
He saw the onions turning brown...
and mistook them for the chicken.
The chicken is white.
- With the pepper scent mixed, - Yes.
- it has the Nepal vibe.
- Nice.
All the water is gone.
- Tell me when to stop.
- Okay.
You can pour it all.
Stop.
(Pour water and curry onto the well-cooked ingredients.)
Nice.
This is really thick.
(He adds the tomato paste, the kick to this curry.)
It's getting thicker.
(While the curry is getting ready)
Nobody may acknowledge it,
but you're quietly doing your job away from the spotlight.
I have nothing else to do.
This is the only thing I can do.
(The auditor does the donkey work.)
(Tasting)
(Kwang Soo is amazed.)
- It's so good.
- Really?
It's so good.
It tastes better because of the chicken broth.
- There's a strong chicken smell.
- Right?
You mean...
(It doesn't sound right when you say "chicken smell.")
I mean, it's a good thing. Chicken flavor...
Say chicken broth.
Mr. Lal would love it.
(They each taste the curry.)
- It's good, right?
- Yes.
It already tastes good.
- Is it good?
- Yes, it's already good.
(The curry is more or less done.)
The naan is the problem.
(Taking out the dough which was rested for 30 minutes)
(Make it flat using the rolling pin.)
Let's test it.
(Will it cook well in the oven?)
(The spectators gather round.)
My gosh!
I think it's baking!
- What? No, we just put it in.
- Really?
We put it in just a second ago.
It looks like it's bubbling up.
- No, not yet.
- No?
(The naan dough is exposed to the heat of the oven.)
I think it'll work.
- I think it's cooked properly.
- Really?
Look. Like a tortilla...
It looks like what they sell at restaurants.
It needs to be baked longer,
but it would work.
It's still dough.
- Let's cook it longer.
- It looks like naan.
(They see hope.)
Shall I roll it out bigger?
- Since it's working?
- Yes, you can work on the dough.
(They start to produce the naan.)
Use a lot of dusting flour.
Sang Hoon, it was a great idea to bake naan.
I really hope it tastes good.
I think it will be.
- That...
- Dip it in curry,
- and it tastes amazing.
- Right.
It's done, right?
Yes.
It feels like...
I'm doing something very important.
- Woo Bin.
- Yes?
You're eliminated.
- Why?
- It's too thick here.
Thick parts are tasty.
What about mine?
- This is a pass, right?
- This is...
- This is a pass.
- Right?
(Unhappy)
The fire is weak, so it won't be baked.
- I mean the thick parts.
- Okay.
I should put the whole thing in.
(The naan is placed on a tray and put into the oven.)
Sang Hoon, don't use oil...
and bake it on this heat.
Let's try one.
This might taste better.
Then I'll try one without butter...
and one with butter.
Sounds amazing.
(The director opens the oven.)
This...
- Like this.
- Nice.
- Gosh, what's this?
This is just like what they sell.
(The oven naan is a success!)
We can continue to bake with the oven.
Let's go two-track.
- Sure.
- All we need to do now...
- is to keep it going.
- In that case,
why don't you make the one with butter?
- Okay. My goodness.
- Since he doesn't use butter.
- You're really...
- Hey.
- You're so...
- How is it?
The dignity of the CEO.
Why don't we taste both in one meal?
You're insane.
- Yi Chan can have the buttered one.
- Yes.
The CEO can have the plain, original flavor.
And the seniors can feel the taste of their traditional food...
That's right.
and our own unique style...
- That's right.
- at the same time.
Killing 2 birds with 1 stone.
Let's make Mr. Kkalloo and Mr. Lal cry today.
Yes.
(Thanks to the naan being a success, their teamwork has also improved.)
- Sang Hoon.
- Yes?
Can you check this?
I'm not trying to show off or anything.
See if I'm doing this smartly.
Okay.
How's this?
(Rolling out two at once)
You don't get this kind...
of wisdom of life easily.
I don't know. I'm just...
Have you done this before?
- This...
- No, it's my first time doing it.
Really? And yet you can do this?
I've never even worked part-time at a restaurant.
This is crazy.
(The intern became the parrot to the captain.)
- But somehow, I thought...
- What?
Why does everyone...
- roll out 1 at a time?
- Roll out 1 at a time?
Seriously.
If you do this like this,
you can cut down the time to half.
I had this thought.
(Meanwhile, the director tastes the curry.)
(He wraps the well-cooked chicken with naan.)
I had this thought.
(He lets the CEO taste it first.)
- My gosh.
- You're doing two at once.
- This is...
- Is it good?
We should sell it right now.
It worked?
I'm serious.
Is the naan good? Really?
I'm glad we cooked a lot of chicken.
(The auditor, who worked hard doing the dishes, tastes it too.)
It tastes amazing wrapped in naan.
- Goodness.
- It's good, right?
Isn't it so good?
This tastes exactly like what they sell at restaurants.
I honestly didn't expect it to taste this good.
My gosh.
All of this started from the Jocheon supermarket.
(The birthplace of the innovative taste,)
(the Jocheon supermarket)
- Sang Hoon.
- If Mr. Kkalloo asks...
where we bought this from...
(Impressed)
(It deserves an applause.)
(He scoops up the curry with care.)
This.
It's really like a dessert.
(He prepares the dessert, the grilled rice cake.)
How many of us are there?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Sang Hoon, we need two more.
Coming.
Gosh, when did you come?
Do you want to try one?
Yes.
- I washed my hands.
- Okay.
Try it.
- How is it?
- It's good.
It's good, right?
(Expressing how good the rice cake is with her whole body)
It's very good, right?
(They're almost done with setting the table.)
(Woo Bin's hands are full of something.)
Are you decorating the table with flowers even in your house?
Come on.
(Flowers?)
You must always mind your manners...
to greet the guests.
(Curry and naan)
(Grilled rice cake)
(Gratitude and manners added too)
Camellia flowers which had fallen to the ground.
Nice. The table became brighter.
(A romantic outdoor meal is ready.)
(The guests come over one after another.)
Please have a seat, sir.
- Have a seat.
- Okay.
- Are you sitting here?
- Come here.
- I'll sit here.
- Okay.
This is just curry.
- Yes.
- I heard Mr. Lal liked chicken.
So we cooked a lot of chicken.
- We cooked a lot of chicken.
- Thank you.
And I heard the CEO and his wife...
- liked potatoes, so potatoes too...
- Yes.
- Until the end...
- Please have a seat.
- Okay.
- Take as much as you can eat.
- Sir, let me serve you first.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Don't mix the whole thing at once.
Mix it bit by bit. Salty...
- Okay.
- It could be salty.
- It's okay.
- Please come.
No.
Inside here...
Ye Chan and Yi Chan, can you eat spicy food?
- The taste is familiar to me.
- Curry.
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Enjoy.
Is it good?
(They finally start eating.)
- Does the naan taste good?
- Yes.
(They taste the curry first.)
My gosh.
Mr. Lal, you like it because there's a lot of chicken, right?
We cooked this ourselves.
You take spicy food very well.
(Glancing)
(He keeps checking others' reactions.)
(Mr. Kkalloo next to him...)
(folds the naan nicely.)
(He puts it into his mouth at once.)
(The CEO was eating quietly.)
- Yes.
- We have this too.
(He finally says his first sentence.)
This is totally Nepali cuisine.
- Is it?
- Yes.
It tastes like what I eat at home.
Really?
(He lightens up.)
I mean it.
The spices totally taste Nepalese.
(Thankfully, his food has satisfied the guests.)
Is it similar to Nepalese food?
It's similar.
- It's similar.
- The spicy one...
The ingredients are different, but the flavor is very similar.
It reminds me of Nepal.
(Laughing)
(Everyone is satisfied with the taste.)
- I feel rewarded.
- Me too.
Is it good?
Is the naan good?
You know you've really succeeded when kids like your food.
He finished the whole thing.
(The kids like the savory naan.)
(The trainees, who've cooked the meal, taste the food too.)
Is it because we boiled it for a long time?
The chicken is very tender.
- It is.
- Yes.
But we didn't add any extra spices.
- No.
- So how did it end up like this?
I know, right?
Is it good?
- He's eating so well.
- Is it good?
(Sang Hoon enjoys his meal with a much lighter heart.)
Mr. Lal and Mr. Kkalloo. There's more curry.
- Would you like more?
- You're full?
Would you like a bit more?
Then I'll have a bit more.
- It's so good.
- Okay.
(Yes, please.)
(While he fills up the second bowl...)
(He checks something.)
Do you know what's funny?
Mr. Lal doesn't like potatoes.
(Checking)
(Laughing)
And Mr. Kkalloo doesn't like carrots.
- Really?
- They...
He has this much potatoes left,
- and he has this much carrots left.
- Why won't you eat them?
You haven't eaten any potatoes and carrots.
(At the appearance of the food police,)
(he quickly destroys the evidence.)
You don't like carrots?
I do eat them, but...
You don't like potatoes?
I really like them.
I eat them in soup too.
(For some reason, he continued to explain himself.)
This is warm.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Drink water.
Would you like more, sir?
- I'll help myself, thanks.
- Okay.
- There's rice too.
(The joyful meal continues.)
Why? Is it spicy?
(She eats the grilled rice cake too.)
(Watching her eat makes them feel rewarded.)
We should be treating you.
Don't say that.
We've received a lot more.
We appreciate the sentiment. Thank you.
(A meal with heartwarming exchange)
You want to leave now?
Do you want to go to Mom?
Thank them for the meal first.
Thank you for the food.
- No problem.
Her bottom is soiled. Even that is cute.
(The kids leave after finishing their food.)
Look at how Ji Woo smiles as she runs to you.
- So cute.
- I agree.
Ji Woo, where have you been?
(They thought Ji Woo had left, but she came back.)
Where have you been?
Who likes this?
- Uncle here!
- Me.
(Cheering loudly)
(She leaves after handing him an unknown drawing.)
Who is this?
- You!
- It's me?
(Ji Woo wanted to gift him the drawing of the uncle.)
- Thank you, Ji Woo.
- You're welcome.
(After that, Ji Woo got on a roll.)
There's more?
Who likes this?
- Me!
Me!
(Woo Bin is chosen.)
She drew Woo Bin.
She did. The hair is short.
(To Sang Hoon, who's been waiting)
(Cheering excitedly)
Let me see.
She drew you.
Printing out a photo is cheating, Ji Woo!
- Yi Chan, me too.
- A photo...
Kwang Soo, she drew us all...
differently.
You're right.
Mine has an overwhelmingly big head.
This is really...
She's talented.
(Put together, you can clearly tell what the artist had intended.)
Sang Hoon's is practically a photo.
I like it.
I thought she was running with your ID photo.
This is so funny.
(With that, they finish the meal.)
I wonder what she drew.
(After the feast,)
(they've come for the last task of the training.)
Gogo.
- They're going out, right?
- Yes.
- Their first time?
- Isn't it their first time?
- Yes.
- Gosh.
Their first outing.
(Gogo and Farmfarm's first-ever outing)
- Let's go.
- Oh, my.
- It's running.
- Let's go.
- Someone's excited.
Isn't it its first time walking down here?
(Everyone is excited.)
This way.
- Let's go.
- Do you want to go this way?
- Come here, Farmfarm.
- Let's go.
- This way.
- Good luck.
Come. Walk this way out.
(Farmfarm walks outside first.)
This way.
Farmfarm.
Let's go. It's not that way. Come this way.
This way.
Let's go.
(The outside is new to Farmfarm.)
- Let's go.
It's scared.
- Let's go. It's holding out.
Gogo.
(Hesitating about stepping forward)
Farmfarm.
The first outing...
must've startled them.
- This way.
- Come this way.
- Let's go.
(The trainees help the calves take more steps outside.)
It's... Look!
Let's go.
(Stepping on the grass for the first time)
Isn't it the first time ever to jump around?
Exactly.
Goodness.
It couldn't even stand up properly...
- a couple of days ago.
- I know, right?
(It's the moment they feel proud.)
Let's go.
(Their first outing with the trainees)
- Nice.
- Oh, my.
Jump!
Goodness.
- It must be happy.
- Yes, it must be happy.
Gogo.
(Successfully completed the last task)
(How was the first training?)
It was a new kind of experience.
A new experience mixed with novel feelings.
This training was full of those.
Coming up to me...
- and sticking close to me is...
- I know.
Do cows actually do this?
Where else could we experience this?
(While bidding each other a passionate farewell)
I wondered what it'd be like, but as expected,
cows are angels.
Cows are such kind animals.
Everything was new to me.
Some tasks were tough.
But I found...
tricks along the way.
It was fun.
Personally, that is.
I simply thought it'd be full of labor.
It's strange.
I've become attached to them in just three days.
(Some got attached.)
I have.
Since we worked together...
and I contributed as much,
I couldn't help but think...
I became a team member with them.
Despite being an intern.
(Some felt proud to become a teammate during the 3 days.)
(It's time to go home now.)
The CEO, our boss,
and the seniors were all so kind.
Now that three days have passed,
I feel sad.
Such an experience is rare in people's lives.
That made it fun.
Laughing with a group of people.
I grew fond of them.
Laughing and more.
It's sad.
(Check out the rest of the dairy farm story in the last episode!)
What if you were asked to become an official intern?
I see. So what if I'm asked to become an official intern,
not a full-time worker?
I'm not even sure if I'd accept a full-time job offer,
but an official intern offer? It's not tempting at all.
I'd still appreciate it.
I'd want my own intern.
(Great job during your internship.)
(A week later)
Hi.
- Hi.
(It's the 1st day of the 2nd training.)
Why are you already wearing rubber boots?
I have a bad feeling.
(The production crew's greeting is rough from the start.)
Dirt is already on it.
(While Kyung Soo is becoming more and more anxious)
(One man is running at full speed.)
You've gained weight.
- What?
- You've gained weight.
(Kwang Soo has arrived.)
- Kwang Soo.
- What?
(Cut the talk, and look.)
What?
- What?
- Look at their shoes.
Is that poop on the shoes?
No, it's part of the design.
- Vintage style?
- Yes.
You deliberately smeared poop on them?
(The production crew doesn't even try to hide it now.)
You got tanned.
- Didn't he get fat?
- What have you been up to?
- I got tanned, didn't I?
- What did you do?
(The director has a softer look now.)
Maybe.
Didn't I get tanned?
Tanned and fat.
I was taken aback when I looked in the mirror this morning.
Because you got fat?
No, because I got tanned.
No, rather than being tanned,
the fact that you gained weight is more obvious.
Why do you bring up getting tanned and ignore me...
bringing up...
- that you got fat?
- Just how fat did I get?
(The two bicker as soon as they meet.)
Let's go.
I don't have a beer belly, okay?
(Heading to the training area)
I heard Woo Bin's shoot starts today.
- After a break?
- What?
- After a short break?
- Yes.
(Woo Bin can't join the training due to scheduling conflicts.)
A field was rented out to start the shoot today.
I see.
Is he playing a game?
It's a baseball drama.
Is it?
- I didn't know.
- What did you think...
we were talking about until now?
I knew he was shooting a drama.
He kept talking about renting out a field.
Force yourself to ask me things.
About what you're doing?
Well, you know...
If you're not sure about something,
ask me even if you're forcing yourself.
Why does that upset you?
It's something like,
"What did you eat?"
You may not be curious,
but it's just manners.
I see.
Are you a robot or something for me to explain such things?
(Are you a robot or something?)
You have to explain for me to know.
(Thinking)
What are you working on this time?
- What?
- What are you?
- What do you mean?
- Your upcoming work.
- What I'm doing?
- Yes.
- How many times must I tell you?
- Sorry?
- I know who's in it,
but I'm asking...
what kind of role you're playing.
It didn't seem ordinary.
That mountain looks cool.
What is it?
It's a stone mountain.
(Almost at the ranch as they chatted away)
Should I give them a call first?
(They call before arriving at the ranch.)
CEO Nam Hoon.
(CEO Nam Hoon)
I haven't heard this in a while.
It suits a ranch.
He's not picking up.
Hello?
Hello, sir.
Hi.
We're CEO Lee Kwang Soo...
and Director Doh Kyung Soo of KKPP Food.
Right, hi.
Hi.
We're just around the corner.
- I see.
- Should we head to the ranch?
Or where should we go?
Let's see.
- You should come to the ranch.
- I see.
- Okay.
- Our ranch is 462,810m² in size.
Oh, my.
Even with the address, it's hard to find me...
as the street number...
- doesn't cover the ranch.
- It's 462,810m²?
I see.
I'll send you an exact spot,
so come look for me.
- Got it.
- Okay.
I'm at the top of the ranch,
so I can't go down to pick you up.
- I see.
- I'll send you my exact spot.
- Got it.
- Wait.
You're not willing to come down, are you?
You're currently working, right?
Yes, I'm currently working at the ranch.
I see.
So I'm not willing to go down.
Got it. I asked just in case.
- Right.
- He's the firm type.
- Yes?
- I'll see you in a bit.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
(After the call with the CEO)
- It's here.
(The CEO's exact location has arrived.)
We're here right now.
This is the place.
It even has the route. We can even know the route.
- Let's set this as the destination.
- Route.
(Route)
(Taking the recommended route)
If the CEO moves,
so will his location.
Yes, it'll keep moving.
- It'll change the destination.
- Correct.
Can we take the car to the location?
If we arrive at the gate...
- The setting...
- and change it to "walking,"
it'll tell us how to get there on foot.
(And so, they head to the horse ranch.)
If it's 528,930m²...
- No, if it's 561,980m², - Yes?
how many horses must there be?
The last farm had...
- Wasn't it 120 cows?
- over 100 cows.
The size is sixfold.
There's a speed bump near here.
Don't tell me he has 600 horses.
- Maybe 500...
- But the thing is,
dairy farms...
have to produce milk,
- hence the many cows.
- Right.
- But this ranch...
- You're right.
With horses...
What could you do with horses?
Horses.
What do you do with horses?
(Curious about the horse ranch's profit structure)
Why raise horses?
Aren't horses bigger than cows?
Soon, you should turn left.
From what I remember, horses are taller.
Actually, they're similar in size.
The difference isn't huge.
Have you never ridden a horse?
(Have you never ridden a horse?)
Did you never ride one?
Rather than riding one,
- Leading one?
- my roles were mostly...
leading a horse.
Even so, you'd know.
People like you would be the one who's riding it.
(Getting upset while saying it)
I usually led the horse.
I even learned horseback riding because I was told to.
Really? But you didn't ride one?
But I just led it around.
We're here.
Wait. Gosh.
It's telling you...
- To park nearby.
- to park nearby.
He must be somewhere around here.
There are horses over there.
- Is this the place?
- Yes.
This seems to be the location.
- Let's go.
- This is the gate.
We're here.
(They arrived at the horse ranch.)
He's over here.
(Route)
We could enter through there.
There's a gate right here.
(Finally going into the horse ranch)
It sure is huge.
It's really big.
(As soon as they walk into the ranch,)
How pretty.
(a vast grassland lies before them.)
It's huge. Look over there!
Aren't those real horses?
(And in the middle of the grassland,)
They're running!
(the horses run freely.)
This is so cool.
(A tranquil scene painted by the horses)
Should we give him a call, Kwang Soo?
(However, it's hard...)
We can't find the CEO.
Let's call him.
(to find the CEO on the vast ranch.)
It's like...
- Yes, hello?
- Hi, sir.
- Yes?
- We're at the ranch.
- Are you?
- Yes.
I'll send you my location,
so can you come here?
Okay, please send it to us.
- Okay.
- Great.
(End of the call)
He sounds just like he did earlier.
- Is he an AI?
- Then...
(Questioning if he's an AI)
He's here!
He's over there!
(The new location has arrived.)
- Kwang Soo.
- He must be over there!
(Neighing)
The sound of a horse!
Wait.
It must be him, Kwang Soo.
(A mysterious man is standing with a horse.)
How do we get there?
Sir... Can I shout?
Nope!
(Shouting)
Can you actually shout that loudly?
Nope!
(Shouting)
- Who is he shouting at?
- He must be telling it not to come.
Hi.
- Hi.
- Are you CEO Nam Hoon?
- Yes.
- Hi.
(Kim Nam Hoon, CEO of the ranch)
- Nice to meet you.
What were you doing just now?
Today...
is ipmok day.
- Ipmok?
- Ipmok...
is letting the horses out in the field.
They must be so happy.
The horses look free.
Jacy.
Come here. Good girl. Hurry.
Hurry. Come.
- Good girl.
- She comes when you call her.
- The horse is pregnant.
- She's pregnant.
If you approach from the front, she'll think you're a threat.
- Okay.
- Turn around.
She'll sniff you first. Okay.
(Stretching his arms out to Jacy)
That's it.
(Looking away)
You must not smell nice.
- I just washed my hands.
- We washed our hands.
(Admirable Kyung Soo is anxious.)
I'll give you a sweat scraper.
Try brushing Jacy.
After that, touch her.
- What's her name?
- Jacy.
- Jessie?
- Jacy?
- Yes.
Jacy.
(A nervous first bond with Jacy)
Each horse is different.
(Trying to bond with Jacy again)
- It's so soft.
- It's okay.
Go ahead and give her a hug.
She's so soft.
- It's my first time...
- The texture of a horse's fur...
that I had in mind was kind of rough.
Is that so?
Nice.
It's my first time touching a horse. Never did I think...
I'd get a chance to touch one.
It's warm.
That horse is running in its dream.
(Laughing)
- Is it sleeping right now?
- How cute.
It's really small.
It's not a foal.
It's a Shetland pony.
- So it's a pony.
- It's the smallest breed.
It's only four days old?
Look at it drinking milk.
So it's drinking milk.
It's devouring it.
The mother is staying still.
The mother stays still for it.
Kwang Soo, it's drinking with its eyes closed.
(Sticking out)
(Reaching out)
Stay still, and it'll approach you.
(Who will it go to?)
Who will it choose? Oh, my.
(Hesitating)
(Trainee Kwang Soo has been chosen.)
(Savoring Kwang Soo's finger)
It doesn't have teeth.
No, it has no teeth.
(Brushing after bonding with the ponies)
A gift, Kwang Soo.
Thank...
(Startled)
(A sudden horse poop gift)
- Sir...
- It was horse poop.
Why did you...
(Startled by the unexpected horse poop)
That startled me.
- But...
- Yes?
Try smelling it, Kyung Soo.
It doesn't smell at all.
It has no smell.
You've got poop on your nose.
- It doesn't smell.
- It doesn't, right?
The poop doesn't smell.
(Horse poop is odorless even when it's on his nose.)
Should I try mashing it up?
Here, smell it.
(Shocked)
- Smell of dirt.
- You can only smell grass.
How come?
This is a grazing ranch, so the poop doesn't smell.
See these seeds? Barley seeds.
These seeds...
grow back into grass.
And so, the poop doesn't smell.
But... Look at the director.
Stop enjoying it.
(Scratching)
Take videos of us.
(Indulging his own wishes while working)
How adorable.
- Aren't they?
- Are there any precautions...
we should take...
- around horses?
- Precautions?
Try not to overstimulate the horses.
(While the CEO is explaining the precautions)
Give me a minute.
Yes?
(Taking a call out of the blue)
I can't make deliveries today because I have a prior schedule.
- Deliver what?
- Leave me a message.
It'll be 40 dollars to Daejeong-eup.
- Can someone...
really not care about the cameras like him?
Sorry. Today...
We collect the manure...
and sell it as fertilizer.
- I put it up on Karrot.
- Delivery for fertilizer?
- So you do Karrot.
- Yes.
I sell poop to buy horse feed.
I still need to make money.
Of course.
I was actually curious about that.
Everything is great,
but both the horses and the CEO need food to eat.
You need some sort of profit.
The profit comes from educational programs.
We're a pasture-based eco-livestock farm.
It's the first in Korea to take care...
- of retired racehorses.
- Retired racehorses? Amazing.
- Awesome.
- So...
We give them showers,
lie together on the grassland, and more.
The horses help me make a living.
Why don't you...
- gather the poop today...
- Okay.
- and sell it...
- Gather poop?
on Karrot?
(Looking gloomy at the poop news)
(Disappointed)
- Is it not okay?
- No, it's fine.
Poop...
We cleaned a ton of poop...
last week.
- Poop...
- Is that so?
We only just escaped from cleaning poop for a week!
It was cows last week.
- Really?
- Yes.
Cows? Then...
- Poop...
- Please...
clean the poop off your nose first.
- Do I have poop on my nose? Where?
- You do.
It's from smelling poop earlier.
(Cleaning the horse poop off his nose as if it's nothing)
You know that? I just touched your nose...
Give me a second. Nope!
Achick!
(Running to wherever the horses are)
- What?
- It must be a prohibited place.
Where?
(The CEO is unpredictable.)
(The ranch tour resumes.)
These horses can graze freely.
- I see.
- Right.
That's a Shetland pony. It's cute, isn't it?
It's spotted.
It's...
- How cute.
- It's like a Dalmatian.
Like a wild horse.
They just roam around freely.
(The horses wandering through the pasture like wild horses)
How big is this place?
It's 462,810 m².
- Gosh.
- It's 462,810 m²?
(Exclaiming)
CEO Kim,
how many horses are in this area?
Currently, we have a total of 53 horses.
(They're caring for a total of 53 horses.)
It's really huge.
(Across the vast pasture of 462,810m²,)
This is amazing.
(53 horses run freely.)
It's a paradise for horses.
They're having fun.
They're so beautiful.
Look, that one came running out.
(The horses emerge from the woods at the sound of ma.)
Benny, where were you?
Coco.
What have you guys...
been up to in the woods?
This doesn't feel real.
I know.
It's what you usually say to dogs at home.
"What did you eat?"
He's saying it to horses.
We got here not so long ago, but it's already so relaxing.
- Right?
- Yes.
Let's work today while enjoying the green scenery.
Okay.
- I'm an expert at cleaning up poop.
- Okay.
- Look, Kwang Soo.
- Look over there.
- My gosh.
- Do you see the horses?
This place looks exotic.
It's fascinating.
It's hard to believe there's a place like this in Korea.
(An area for horses visible through the green barley fields)
Horses that were recently rescued,
sick, or abused are protected...
in a special care area.
The first priority is helping them gain weight.
(Gaining weight is the most important for the horses.)
They wear halters and are kept with basic lead ropes.
(They wear halters as part of their special care routine.)
This is how you socialize them.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes, sir.
(They came to meet horses in the special care zone.)
- They're tangerines.
- Jeju Island is famous...
- for tangerines.
- Yes.
This isn't for you.
- Is it for horses?
- It's for horses.
Really?
Arthur.
It's the biggest horse on earth.
(The biggest horse on earth?)
(Gasping)
- What is this?
- It looks amazing.
It's really big.
(A presence unlike any horse they've seen before)
Look how thick his legs are.
His hooves are this big.
Our Arthur weighs one ton.
That's why I told you not to get stepped on by him.
If you get stepped on by him...
Isn't this horse different?
Compared to the tiny horse before...
You can hear a thud every step he takes.
All right, give him a tangerine.
Put it on your palm.
(Licking it off)
If you hold a cup underneath, you can collect the juice.
You'll see the sword of Excalibur here.
This is King Arthur.
The horse's mane looks like it's been permed.
(Arthur's curly mane is his another charming feature.)
It sounds like a blender.
Grab here.
Lift your left leg.
- What?
- One, two, three. Jump.
(Mouth wide open)
Sir, you're making me do this...
(Juicing)
(Sitting on the horse's back)
It's really warm.
- Isn't it very warm?
- Yes.
When will I ever get to ride a horse like this?
Spread out your arms.
Lie down.
- Lie down?
- Yes.
Okay.
(He lies back and rests his back against Arthur.)
It's a horse bed.
It's really comfortable.
- Isn't it very comfortable?
- Yes.
(Patting gently)
Shall I turn off the heater? Isn't it too hot?
Yes, it's very warm.
Sit back up.
(The horse's body heat makes it cozier.)
Straighten your back.
Grab the mane here and pull it.
The other horse is eating them.
Look at him.
(The horse is eating something?)
Let him eat.
(Taking the opportunity to steal some tangerines)
My goodness.
- Kwang Soo, pull the horse.
- Gosh.
- Walk with them.
- But...
Okay, walk with horse.
But... Goodness.
(The King's Equerry)
Shouldn't I be on the horse?
(Somehow, it feels familiar.)
I'm older than him,
and I'm the CEO.
Pull him.
Goodness.
I've always done this even in a drama.
(Feeling triumphant)
Riding a huge horse like this...
makes me feel...
like a king.
(Kwang Soo remains silent.)
I really feel like a servant.
Arthur, here's a tangerine.
(He seems like a royal subject.)
Today's biggest highlight is...
Why does Kyung Soo always get the highlight moment?
Lift your left leg.
One, two, three. Jump.
(My goodness)
Hold onto Kyung Soo's waist.
A horse can carry about 20 percent of its own weight.
Since he weighs about one ton...
It doesn't bother him at all.
(He goes back to eating grass.)
He is so amazing.
Sung Joon.
Should I take it?
Give it to me.
(They're the senior staff at the horse ranch.)
How many employees do you have?
- My employees are Sung Joon...
- Yes.
and Sung Joo.
- I see.
- There are two of them.
For the next three days,
- you'll be working in their place.
- Right.
That's why both of you look so happy.
(Big smiles)
I was wondering why they were smiling.
It's not even a funny situation.
With a tangerine in their hand...
(Smiling)
They kept doing this.
At the thought of taking a break...
Right.
We received a lot of orders.
- What orders?
- Poop orders.
We don't have enough poop.
Do you mean the phone call you got?
We have to collect the manure and load it onto that truck.
- I see.
- All right.
(The horses roam freely throughout the pasture.)
(With such a large pasture, the manure is scattered everywhere.)
Each person grabs a snow shovel...
and scoops it up.
We'll fill the one-ton truck by the end of the day.
- Fill that truck?
- Yes.
We'll take it to the compost area and unload it.
Think of it as picking up fallen leaves.
Yes, sir.
It's hard to tell apart from the rocks.
The manure stopped bothering me at some point.
Why would you get a close shot of this?
Why would you get a close shot of manure?
Why are you filming me after the manure?
(It just happened that way.)
Compared to cow poop, horse poop looks cute.
Cow poop is basically diarrhea, isn't it?
Goodness.
Tell me when you see poop. What's this?
This is poop too.
(Picking up horse manure hidden among the grass)
(Looking around)
You know what? Kwang Soo.
What?
- You know what I feel already?
- Yes.
- Finding nicely shaped ones...
feels satisfying.
Poop makes you feel satisfied?
I wouldn't go that far.
This one is a giant.
(Scraping)
(The trainees focus on picking up horse manure.)
This is a gold mine of poop.
(He hit the horse manure jackpot.)
It's like a rock.
Seriously. Take a look at this.
- Like a pebble?
- Yes, it's like a pebble.
(Kyung Soo picks it up like it's a pebble.)
They only poop around the edge of their territory.
(You keep analyzing poop, aren't you?)
All we do is clean up poop.
I might as well analyze it...
to see how it's different from cow manure.
It was still fun.
You don't get a chance to learn...
how different cow manure and horse manure really are.
It was a new discovery.
I'll try to get closer to the horses.
(He learns something new again.)
You know what?
Whoever loses rock-paper-scissors...
The winner tries to toss it into the loser's mouth from a distance.
I can really do it.
What?
While standing apart like this,
the loser of rock-paper-scissors does this.
(Opening wide)
The winner throws it into the loser's mouth.
He only gets one chance.
- I'm in.
- Just one round.
(They start a feed poop game in the middle of work.)
What CEO Kim touched...
Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors.
- Darn it.
- Okay.
(Kwang Soo wins.)
(Speechless)
(Which one shall I throw?)
This is mostly grass.
Hey, it's a Dubai chewy cookie.
(It looks almost like a Dubai chewy cookie.)
You have to stand next to that container.
You're too close.
- You said that you'd do it there.
- It won't move.
- Do it over there.
- It won't move at all.
- It will.
- It's only grass.
- It will move.
You said that you'd stand next to the red container.
How can I throw it into your mouth from there?
You'll be throwing poop. You must stand at least that far.
I can't move any farther.
Move back a little more.
Also, you can only throw it like this.
Like this?
I won't make it this way. Open up.
(Kyung Soo complains, but still opens his mouth.)
Don't move.
(Getting into position)
Please.
(Waiting like a goalpost)
(Will he make the shot from this far away?)
(The horse chewy cookie is thrown.)
(Please miss.)
(Please go into his mouth.)
(What will happen to the horse chewy cookie?)
(He hits it right away.)
(There you go.)
(I almost had it.)
(It started like basketball, but ended like baseball.)
Nice shot.
(Let's just go back to work.)
The atmosphere is clearly different from the last place we visited.
The last place was nice in its own way,
but this one is more... How shall I put it?
Hey.
Hey!
(Kyung Soo gets mischievous.)
What's the matter?
- This is mine.
- We're working together.
We're loading one ton together.
(Teasing Kwang Soo just like always)
Where are you going? We have to clean up here.
We don't have time. The sun is going down soon.
(Kwang Soo manages to toss it into Kyung Soo's cart.)
My gosh.
(Suddenly, a horse starts to run.)
That looks cool.
That looks cool. I wonder how he feels.
I guess he wants to run.
(He runs, showing his career as a former racehorse.)
He's really fast.
(Glancing)
Shall I give him a tangerine?
(After a good run, he's taking a break.)
(He approaches with a secret weapon.)
(Sneaking up quietly)
(The moment he sees it, he eagerly takes the tangerine.)
It looks like he's feeling better.
You wanted to do something with animals.
It looks like you're already bonding with one.
Kwang Soo, clean up the poop.
Wait.
- He's not feeling so well.
- Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo.
(Using the horse's mood as an excuse to put off work)
They really look like pebbles.
(They really look like pebbles.)
(Kyung Soo picks up the pebbles diligently.)
You have to scratch him hard to make him pleasant.
(Approaching quietly)
You have to scratch him very hard.
(He walks over as if asking for a head scratch.)
Put your mane back.
He seems to like it.
He seems to love it.
It rubs against people like a cat.
Isn't it refreshing?
The horse really likes it.
(Keeping it happily entertained)
Kyung Soo, what are you doing instead of picking up poop?
You should work like Kwang Soo.
(The boss appears.)
Kyung Soo.
Please focus. We aren't here to have fun.
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo is already back at work.)
(Indignant)
(He only just started bonding with a horse.)
Should we load them on the truck?
Gosh, you got a lot there.
Didn't we get quite a lot?
Yes, well done.
This will be enough to earn 40 dollars.
Really?
Do you want to try listing on Karrot?
You never know. You could get a message.
- Sure.
- Can you drive this truck?
- I can drive it.
- I'll teach you.
I'm sorry, Sung Joon. This is your part-time job.
Are you in charge of this?
- Doesn't the poop look different?
- You're right.
- If it's worth 40 dollars...
- It's basically money.
I'll take this side.
Place it on here.
And push it in.
- Hey.
- Oh, no.
- Twenty, thirty dollars.
- We're spilling money.
(The horse manure spills onto the ground.)
(Piles of cash scatter everywhere.)
Watch it, Sung Joon.
We spent one hour collecting this.
(Embarrassed)
I knew it.
A moment ago...
(We can't leave anything behind.)
(While he's at it, he takes photos for the marketplace listing.)
Okay.
Why don't you take a photo with the horse in it?
With Arthur in the frame.
Yes, take a photo with the horse.
(If we're doing it, we might as well do it properly.)
Make sure you get me from behind.
(With meticulous direction)
(Very serious)
Okay.
It came out well.
There's no way this won't sell.
There's no way it won't sell.
First,
bond with the horse...
- you're assigned to...
- Yes.
before we leave.
What's his name?
John Snow.
Before coming to our ranch, Snow had earned...
the most prize money of any horse here.
He won races?
Yes, he was a racehorse.
- I see.
- He won 269,000 dollars.
My gosh.
Even after earning all that money,
he was about to be sent somewhere terrible.
(John Snow was at risk of being euthanized.)
We rescued him...
and brought him here.
John Snow is Kwang Soo's horse.
(Kwang Soo's partner horse is John Snow.)
- So you will take him.
- Okay.
He's a Jeju Halla horse.
He retired from Jeju Racecourse in 2021.
The problem was that he was too tall.
A Jeju Halla horse can't be taller than 137cm.
So they kept trimming down his hooves.
They eventually damaged a nerve.
It made him lame, so he had to retire.
Kyung Soo, you're assigned to Morris.
We prepared these two horses for you.
Watch carefully. When I walk,
the horse matches my stride like this.
Achick.
(The ranch owner demonstrates a leading exercise.)
"Achick."
- You have to say it the same.
- That was nice.
(Imitating the boss's cue)
- "Oh chick." Wasn't that too much?
- If you come across...
- some nice grass, give him some.
- Yes.
- Try it, Kwang Soo.
- Yes, sir.
- Achick.
- All right. Show your back.
(Kwang Soo takes the lead confidently.)
- Say it again.
- Achick.
(He loses control immediately.)
- Turn around. Keep going.
Achick.
Run faster.
(A big match between the giraffe and the horse)
(Trying to take the lead across the vast pasture)
That's good.
This is very exciting.
Achick!
(Exhausted)
(They look like they're in sync.)
Stop.
My goodness.
(Flopping down)
(Bonding or not, Kwang Soo gets ditched.)
(Bonding with a horse isn't easy.)
(Will the trainees be able to build a bond with their partner?)
(He totally ignores me.)
(Kwang Soo in a one-sided love with a horse)
(You're so cute.)
(How are you so cute?)
(Kyung Soo meets his true love.)
(The peaceful ranch life continues.)
(Don't go!)
(No, come this way.)
(They run when they want to run.)
(Why is he lying down all of a sudden?)
(These free-spirited horses lie down when they want to.)
(Compared to cows, horses are much harder to care for.)
(Because of that, the work keeps piling up.)
(Suddenly, I miss Gogo and Farmfarm so much.)
(I feel paralyzed.)
(What happened at the horse ranch that makes him want to run away?)
(That's not an old lady picking bracken, is it?)
(Who is it?)
(A stranger appears at the ranch.)
(She's filming us.)
(Shoving a camera in everyone's face)
(Causing a ruckus at the ranch)
(The atmosphere grows more and more serious.)
(Who is this mysterious stranger that has everyone confused?)
(GBRB: Farm Operation - Go Go Farm)
(Lee Kwang Soo)
(Kim Woo Bin)
(Doh Kyung Soo)
(GBRB: Farm Operation - Go Go Farm)