All these years,
you've been working so hard for us.
for us.
Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
You...
What are you doing? Are you scared? I'm scared.
Look how scared you are.
If I don't cut the sandwich,
without cutting the sandwich?
Come on.
Come on
Let's take a shower. Okay.
Sure.
The bath water is ready.
Okay.
Did you have a nightmare?
Kind of.
What did you dream about? It's not important.
It doesn't matter.
That strawberry meow.
How many times have I told you?
She was the one who put it on me.
Can you stop mentioning it?
As the boss of a company,
do you know how many temptations I've rejected for you?
Do you know?
Can you stop
hold on to such a trivial matter?
Can you trust me a little?
Honey.
What are you talking about?
I mean that strawberry meow has been blocked.
Will it affect the company?
I'm caring about you, honey.
What else do you want me to do?
I take care of your family all day long.
You know my temper.
I have to put up with it anyway.
Let me treat you like a Buddha
like a Bodhisattva.
What else do you want me to do?
A man and a woman.
Didn't we agree on our wedding?
There are many things we agreed on when we got married.
Did you do everything?
Honey.
Sit down.
I'm sorry, okay? I'm sorry.
I'm not human.
It's that strawberry meow.
She seduced me.
I just made a mistake
every man in the world.
You have to trust me.
I only love you in my heart.
Say something, honey.
Say something!
Honey.
Hit you.
It hurts in my heart.
Honey.
I'm fine.
I just don't want you to be sad.
Honey.
I don't know what to do now.
I only love you in my life.
I will never do anything
to you and Xixi.
OK?
Okay.
Honey.
You seem to have changed.
Really?
What happened?
I don't know.
I...
I love you more
than before.
Gather up, guys.
Warm.
You have to give me an explanation today.
Sisters,
Go!
Do you want to save grandpa?
Don't hit Meow.
Don't hit Meow, okay?
It's disgusting to touch someone like you.