[English subtitles are available]
[Cohabitation Agreement]
[Jang Ki-yong, Lee Hye-ri]
[Kang Han-na, Kim Do-wan]
[Bae In-hyuk, Park Gyeong-hye]
[My Roommate is a Gumiho]
You won't remember a thing.
When you wake up,
everything will be over.
You just had a short dream.
As of now,
the contract has ended.
Dam, come on out. Breakfast is ready.
Okay.
-Hey, you need to wake up.
-Come on.
Are you a human or a larva?
Hey, what's for breakfast?
-Chicken porridge.
-Nice.
Chicken porridge.
I'm leaving.
Wash the dishes before you leave.
Okay.
Or at least soak it in water.
Okay, you're nagging a lot today.
This is good.
[Episode 8]
Hey.
-Hi.
-Hi. Doing okay?
-You're going this early?
-Yes.
It's really tiring to go
to the first period after midterms.
I'm tired to death.
Right, have you heard?
-Hear what?
-Listen up.
Engineering Department
just added carbonara to the cafeteria.
-Yes!
-Wow, hey.
We can't pass on the new menu.
-To the Engineering for lunch today.
-Of course.
Whoever gets there first,
orders for everyone.
-Okay.
-Bye.
Hey, wait up!
Then I'll eat lunch with those two.
Then I have a team project for my major.
In the afternoon, the group assignment.
And...
Darn it.
The least he can do is
make me forget everything.
Dam?
What are you doing here?
Hey, are you crying?
What's wrong? Is something going on?
Are you sick?
Just go, please.
How could I leave you here
when you're crying like this?
Let's sit on the bench, okay?
You should sit down and cry.
Get up. I'll take your bag.
Okay. Get up.
Hye-sun.
You know we still have to go on
one more date
for the project, right?
Really? We have to go on another one?
Yes, sadly, we have one more time left.
Let's go on a date this Saturday
if you're free.
Whatever.
If you're annoyed,
do you just want to say
we did it and write the report?
Can we do that?
Yes, if we get the story straight
out of our lips.
We have to make a story through our lips?
Yes, something like that.
Wait, why do we have to do that
over some assignment?
Well.
You have to do it well to get good grades,
then it'll be easy to find a job...
Does it even affect your job search?
All right. I hear getting a job is
the biggest priority for kids these days.
If it's that necessary, then fine.
Let's do it.
What?
Hey, what are you doing?
Are you crazy? Let me go.
Let me go. What's with you?
-No, hey.
-Let me go.
[His purity, jeopardized.
Her pride, ruined.]
What are you doing? Have you gone insane?
How can you strangle my neck
as if you're killing a chicken?
Why did you...
[Right, she isn't good at Korean
because she lived abroad.]
Hye-sun, listen up.
There is this thing
called a figure of speech.
When we say "take out our hands and feet,"
it doesn't mean we use our feet.
It means we should do
everything we can to help.
And "get the story straight
out of our lips" means
we come up with a story
and run with the same story
as we make up stuff.
Are you trying to teach me?
-No.
-I'm not that stupid.
I even memorized 1,000 Chinese characters.
I may not have finished Lesser Learning,
but I got into the collegiate system.
Do you think I didn't know?
[Wait, does she think]
[the book Lesser Learning is
related to college?]
[She's a pretty funny girl.]
I'll see you on Saturday.
Instead of using our lips...
I mean, instead of coming up with a story,
let's just meet up.
I get it. You need to go.
All right. See you on Saturday.
[She wouldn't tell me
why she's crying even if I asked.]
[I can't believe
I'm happy to see her in this situation.]
Hey, what's going on?
Why is she crying next to that Tiger boy?
Wait.
Please excuse me.
You should get to class too.
Hey, wait.
Do you want to meet this weekend?
I mean, that's not what I meant.
I mean, well, it is.
We have to do the assignment.
Don't you want to do it?
I don't want to.
Sir, I'm home.
Why didn't you pick up your phone?
You took the Marble out, didn't you?
I could tell by the way she looks.
Did you see her?
So what if I did?
Why do you care?
You won't be seeing her again.
If you've decided
to strain every drop of energy
from a stranger,
you should've stayed away
from getting attached.
And if you've let her go,
you need to brace yourself
and find the next target.
You don't have time to lose
looking miserable,
and that goes for both of you.
Both of us?
She was crying.
She was? Why?
Why do you ask?
I'm sure it's because of you.
That's impossible.
I erased everything about me
from her memories.
I'm not sure if you're sweet or cruel.
Are you sure your magic worked?
You said it didn't work on her mom.
I'm sure no one will remember a thing.
That girl
and everyone else who saw me.
Please keep an eye on her
and see if she does all right
and stays healthy.
You said you wanted me to keep her safe,
not to pry on her private life.
She's safe now.
From whom?
From me.
So now you're worried
about her private life
instead of her safety?
I thought of her like my family.
Please do that for me.
No, if you want to see her,
you can see her in person.
She won't even recognize you.
What's the problem?
Family, my foot.
No guy makes a face like that
to a girl he thinks of like family.
[What about my face?]
How can I put this?
I mean, you've been smiling,
but you look like you're empty inside.
Whatever.
Are you sure everything is okay?
I'm fine.
[I lied.]
I knew how to take out the Marble
from the beginning.
But I lied to you.
I needed energy to become human,
and you happened to be there.
[Yes, I was just a consumable human]
[who was there to give him my energy.]
[So this is enough.]
[The least I can do is celebrate.
Why am I crying?]
Soo-kyung, are you free today?
Today?
I don't have a lesson at my academy.
And my phone English lesson
isn't today either.
Let's call Jae-jin
and party until the morning.
Midterms are over too.
I'm going to do everything
I couldn't do for a while.
That feels much better.
Chicken and beer
beat any kind of relationship.
Tipsy and delicious,
yet delicious and tipsy.
-I missed this so much.
-Right.
You didn't have to miss it.
You did this every other day.
Tell me about it. Some might think
she hasn't done this for months.
Excuse me, we'll take
one more garlic chicken
and another 3,000cc beer pitcher.
-Sure.
-You're eating more?
Are you going to stop eating chicken
after today?
I know our midterms are over,
but I need to recap
today's lecture and study.
Stop eating. Let's go.
Hey, go where?
My curfew is lifted.
We have to party harder.
You had a curfew?
-I didn't know Dan was that strict.
-Right?
I don't have to avoid them anymore.
-What?
My life is filled with happiness,
and it's killing me.
Hey, let's go to a karaoke room.
Karaoke sounds great.
It's time to bust out
Jae-jin's sentimental songs again.
-Hey.
-Fine.
Hey, I don't want
any of these drowsy slow songs.
Only dance songs.
Dance, dance!
Why is Dam so hyper today?
She's scaring me.
I'm not sure.
She said that she feels lighthearted.
Is it because tests are over?
I don't think she studied so hard
for her to feel that lighthearted.
We have a minute left. Let's go.
Let's not sing a long song
and mope over the time we lost,
-but let's go home with some class.
-Start.
["Apartment"]
What's with this song?
Did her taste in music change?
Well, I guess trot music is
really big these days.
[Seoul]
Now that he took out the Marble,
did he become a human
with the energy I gave him?
Goodness, I don't even care.
But why am I here again?
Old habits die hard.
[She was crying.]
You either sleep late
or suffer from a hangover.
Eat up. It's ox blood hangover soup.
Can you make me bean sprout soup
or dried pollack soup next time?
I don't want to see any blood for a while.
You're very hasty.
I was just asking you to consider that.
[Do you feel better now?]
[Let's go eat something
to help you feel better.]
[Let's meet up even if you don't want to.]
[I know it sounds weird,
but just think of this as an assignment.]
[Just think of this as an assignment.]
[Lee Dam]
What are you up to?
Why are you staring at...
My gosh, you were
getting clingy to a girl?
Are you crazy? Give it back.
No, I won't. Why would I
give back something this hilarious?
Darn it, give it back.
You weren't turned down just once,
but continuously over and over again.
I can't believe you're in this situation
despite your looks.
This is the power of one's personality!
Hey, I'm going to kill you, okay?
[Lee Dam]
-What?
-I sent that message.
You've been turned down anyway,
so keep trying and leave no regrets.
Get turned down 100 times, 101 times,
it's the same.
-Hey.
-Boo-ya.
-Darn it, that brat.
-Gosh.
[Gye Seon-woo,
Let's meet up even if you don't want to.]
Why? Who is it?
-Just a senior at school.
-It doesn't look like he's just a senior.
He's interested in you.
I guess he's not into looks.
You psycho.
[Gye Seon-woo]
Man, he's unbelievably good-looking.
What happened?
Stop talking nonsense.
It's not like that.
He just contacted me for an assignment...
-What are you doing?
-Replying.
-Give me back.
-Give me a moment.
Give it to me now.
-Hey.
-What assignment? He's into you.
Give it back, you psycho.
-Darn it.
-Here.
[I'd love to meet you anytime.]
Hey, it's on.
He's 100 percent into you.
I'm going to kill you!
Wash your hair before you go!
I bid you good luck
with your first boyfriend. You got this.
I can't believe this.
[I'd love to meet you anytime.]
Hey, I won't beat you. Open up.
I don't believe you.
I really won't. I swear on my credit card.
Don't you dare lay a hand on me.
I'll use this hair iron
to straighten your twisted mind.
Look at this.
[Lee Dam, I'd love to meet you anytime.]
What do I say to this?
[I'll call you.]
I should just kill Dan.
[Chats]
[He didn't have to delete the messages.]
[No, don't cry.]
[You were just turned down harshly.]
[You had a crush on him,
had expectations that couldn't be met,]
[then got turned down.]
-My gosh.
-It wasn't supposed to rain today.
[I'm like an actress in a tragic movie.]
[Is this a dream?]
It's suddenly raining.
[Is this really him?]
Where are you headed?
I'll share with you
until your destination.
I'm headed
to the Department of Humanities.
[She doesn't look well.]
[Did something really happen to her?]
[If he ended everything
without making an excuse,]
[it means he was
never going to see me again.]
[In the end,]
[that's how little I meant in his life,]
[like a sudden shower.]
I think I'm good now.
I saw a friend over there.
I see.
Thank you.
[This must be the end.]
Excuse me.
Don't walk in the rain, and take this.
Why should I take your umbrella?
-Soo-kyung!
-Hey, Dam.
-My gosh.
-Where's your umbrella?
How did you find me?
Hey, it stopped raining.
Was that a sun shower?
It was sunny, then it suddenly rained.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
[Her kind voice. Her smile.]
[And playing a baby.]
[All those things were
perhaps a privilege.]
[I have now become]
[a nobody to her.]
Have you heard?
Professor Jung recently took a leave
because of his health,
so we're getting a new professor.
Really?
Why? Are you worried?
Well, in my case, it doesn't matter
who the new guy is.
What's that? What's he doing? Jae-jin.
What are you doing?
My friends, I need agony aunts.
What's wrong?
Our grades aren't in, so I doubt
you're worried about repeating this class.
Well,
Jin-ah has been in contact for a few days.
Why won't you even hear me out?
I mean, she keeps texting me
late at night asking if I'm asleep.
Then she sends old pictures
and asks if I remember.
She wants to meet, so what do I do?
What do you think? She's bored,
so she wants to lead you on.
Just ignore her.
You don't have to be shaken.
-She's not like that.
-Whatever. Be quiet.
-Hey, are you serious?
-Yes, he's going to be here.
-Hey, let's sit in the very front.
-Stop that.
Hey, Yu-ri.
What's going on here?
It's the new professor.
I just saw him, and he's amazing.
Why? How amazing is he?
It's none of your business.
-Look.
-My gosh.
He looks like an actor.
He's really hot.
[Seogwa University]
-Gosh, he's so hot.
-Who is that?
I'm sorry I ran in late on my first day.
-Don't say that.
-It's okay.
-Right.
Dam, I'm thinking of retaking this lecture
for the first time in my life.
No, I'll re, re, re, re,
retake this lecture.
[Why is he here right now?]
[If he can use magic,
is he not a human yet? Wait, no.]
[That's not what's important.]
Then let me call attendance first.
-Okay.
-Yes.
-Jeon Da-young?
Seo Jin.
-Yes.
-Gye Seon-woo.
[-What on earth is going on?]
-Choi Soo-kyung.
-Yes!
-Yes.
[-Is it because of me?]
[Is he here to keep an eye on me?]
Lee Dam.
Yes.
[Is he doing this to keep an eye on me?]
As you have been probably informed,
I'm going to be teaching History 101
starting today.
Then
let's start from page 178.
-Yes, Professor.
I've got to hurry to the next class. Bye.
Bye.
Professor.
Thanks for the lecture.
Hey, Dam. Beef tripe after school?
I have no money.
It's on me. I got my allowance.
-Stop annoying me.
-Come on.
-Go away.
[Professor of History, Shin Woo-yeo]
I'm just watching her for a while.
Just for a while.
All right.
I didn't say anything yet, though.
So you're just watching her for a while.
Then what?
What are you going to do next?
You saw what happened
when one failed to become a human
after living 1,000 years.
Haven't you learned your lesson?
Time is ticking.
Why are you still thinking about her?
-I cared...
-If you cared about her so much,
why did you erase her memories first?
[Because I thought]
[if she wouldn't look at me
the same way as she did,]
[I wouldn't be able to stand it.]
Are you sure you want her
to go back to her normal life?
Is it really okay for you to see her
doing just fine
without you?
Of course.
You know what?
I may lie to other people,
but I would never lie to myself.
I'm buying you a really tasty beef tripe.
I said I'm not interested.
You can't convince me
with 20cm of beef tripe.
I know you want to talk about Jin-ah.
Just move on, you clingy punk.
I'm not being clingy.
I just want to say to her
that I'm not an idiot anymore
so she should stop contacting me.
I just want to talk with you about
how I make it sound
more charismatic and ruthless, my friend.
-Whatever.
-Jae-jin.
Jin-ah, what are you doing here?
I just came by
to see your face.
By the way, Dam,
it looks like you're still single,
seeing that you still
hang out with Jae-jin.
-You little...
-No, Dam. Don't.
My legs hurt.
Jae-jin, will you keep me waiting here?
Let's go somewhere and talk.
You're not talking to anyone. Go away.
Who do you think you are
to tell me to go away?
I know who I am to him.
If you make him cry, I'll be the one
who has to take all his drunken grumbles.
If you're not paying
for the drink, just go.
Jae-jin.
Should I go?
Well...
Sorry, Dam.
She came all the way here.
I can't just let her go like this.
Let's go, Jae-jin.
I saw a nice cafe on my way here.
Let's go.
I'll text you.
What am I going to do with that idiot?
[Jae-jin]
[I'm sorry, Dam.]
[I know I'm being stupid,]
[but seeing her face makes me weak.]
Hi, Seok.
Now?
Professor, what kind of coffee
do you like?
Professor. Please have some snacks.
-Seok, what's this about?
-What's your favorite?
Obviously,
we're welcoming our new professor.
You're the president of the council.
[I wished I didn't have to bump into him.]
What are you doing here though?
You're not even a member of the council.
Do you have to be a member
to greet our new professor?
Professor.
As the top History major junior,
I have a question.
Are you married?
Hey.
Can't you see he's not wearing a ring?
Of course. You look so young
I thought you were one of my seniors.
What a surprise.
Dam, don't you have any questions
to ask him?
How will our grades be calculated?
-Sorry?
-This is my first time
having my professor changed
in the middle of the semester.
They will be calculated
in the same way as before.
Yes, Professor.
I see.
Jae-jin.
You thought I was two-timing too, right?
But if you define my love
using one cheap word like that,
I'll be sad.
I was simply confused
if I liked you or him.
I see.
I think I'm done
organizing my thoughts now.
So I'm thinking of giving you
another chance.
-Another chance?
-Yes.
A chance to make me feel safer
and be nicer to me
so I don't get confused.
To be honest, you haven't been
that good either.
You hung out with Lee Dam all the time.
Jin-ah, Dam is just a friend.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Dam is not even a female friend.
She's just a human friend.
I said I didn't like her.
How many times did I say
I didn't like her?
Fine.
I did see another guy while dating you.
But you weren't nice to me either.
We're both at fault.
Choi Jin-ah. Do you even hear yourself?
Not once have I put her before you.
You have always been my priority,
and I have always done my best
for this relationship.
Don't use Dam as an excuse.
You may not be that good of a person,
but you're not that shameless either.
How could you side with her
in front of me?
I didn't know you were such cold a person.
Hye-sun.
Hi. I didn't expect to see you here.
Who is she?
I'm sorry if I have interrupted.
I'll leave you two alone.
See you on Saturday.
Okay. I'll text you.
Who is she? Why are you texting her?
-Well, she's just...
-What?
She's just someone
I do an assignment with.
It's...
Even if he told you who I am,
you wouldn't know.
What?
So what's the point of asking?
-Hey! What are you?
-Don't...
Jae-jin, meet me on Saturday.
[Seriously? Saturday?]
I can't, Jin-ah. I told you
we had to do an assignment together.
You can do the assignment on Sunday.
I like Saturday.
I must meet Jae-jin on Saturday.
I'm not going to cancel
my appointment for you.
And I'll never see you again.
You haven't answered my question yet.
Who is this woman?
Do you want to know who I am? Why?
I don't care whether you're Jae-jin's ex
or a utility pole.
I just want you to know this one thing.
On Saturday, he's mine.
Maybe I shouldn't have meddled.
It's okay.
Next time, don't be like that.
Don't open your heart to others.
You can't win the game
if you show all the cards in your hand.
I didn't play a game.
I didn't want to win either.
I just...
I just liked her a lot.
[Seogwa University]
Lee Dam.
Yes.
[How could he look so fine?]
Aren't you getting in?
[Job Fair]
Why aren't you asking me
why I didn't call you?
Pardon?
I said I would call you
because we're having dinner together.
Oh, right.
Are you free today?
Today, I can't...
Thanks, Seon-woo.
Let's have the dinner later
when you feel better.
What?
You don't look so well today.
You cried a lot the other day...
Seon-woo, why don't we just do it today?
-What?
-Let's go.
This place is famous
for their salmon steak.
For salad, I'd recommend
avocado salad or Cobb salad.
And for amuse-bouche...
Do you like ceviche?
If you don't want to have flour
in your main dish,
there are whole grain
or tofu noodle options.
What's the matter?
I didn't get any of that.
What's with the muse and bush?
What's Cobb and what's ceviche?
And who doesn't want flour?
Then I'll make orders for you.
Okay.
Excuse me. I'd like to order.
That text message wasn't sent by me.
It was my brother.
He has this crazy idea
that you're interested in me.
I know. I figured it wasn't from you.
I thought you would never
talk so sweetly to me
nor send me such emojis.
In fact, that's the reason
why I hesitated to call you.
I was afraid you would
cancel this thing at all.
Seon-woo, you don't have to do this.
If this is because you feel bad
about the bet--
I do feel bad about it,
but that's not the reason.
Then is it because our deadline is near?
I don't really care about assignments.
Then why...
Dam.
You're just acting like
you don't know, aren't you?
Don't know what?
That I like you.
You're the only one
who doesn't know that I like you.
Literally, you're the only one.
You said even your brother thought so.
But how can you not realize it?
[Is he messing with me again?]
[You call that a love confession?]
[Even if he isn't, this is weird.]
[I wish I could turn back time.]
You see,
you don't have to give me an answer.
I know. I wasn't going to.
That's what I said. You're one cold girl.
I'm doing this not because I feel bad
but because I like you.
I wanted you to know that.
[Now I know it,
but does it change anything?]
[Even if someone has feelings for me,]
[I can't stop]
[but think about him.]
-Professor.
-Hi.
[Then when I see him...]
[Then...]
Seon-woo.
I need to tell you something.
What is it?
I'm sorry.
I like someone else.
[Someone else?]
I knew it.
So why did you follow her
in the first place?
It was nice seeing her.
I resented and hated her a lot,
but we had good memories too.
And I used to really like her.
I know she randomly appeared,
but it was nice seeing her.
It was weird.
I understand.
Emotions are weird like that.
Why do you think she suddenly appeared?
Exactly. Why?
Why did she have to appear and sway me
when I was almost finally over her?
Why sway me?
What are you doing?
Why are you copying me?
I am?
I'm just showing sympathy.
You know what?
I still have this stupid idea
that I might have been
too mean to her at the end.
And I even have this idea
that she might have come
because she missed me.
How pathetic.
[Could he be also...]
[Is it pathetic of me]
[to wish that he misses me too?]
Jin-ah, I really want
to move on this time.
If you show up again,
I'll act like I don't know you.
I'll act like I don't know you!
I wish I could act like I don't know you.
Gosh! Walk on your own!
Hey!
You... No. Don't.
I'm not going to run. Don't you worry.
I'm not going to run. Don't worry.
Let's go have a second round.
-Let's go have a second round.
-What?
Hey, wake up.
I will sell your organs
if you don't wake up now.
Have you lost your mind?
What's going on?
Hye-sun.
What are you doing here?
I didn't know it was your car.
Jae-jin got so drunk, so...
[What were they doing together?]
Dam.
I feel sick
and the ground is too soft. I can't walk.
Hey, wake up.
Come on. Goodness.
Let me help.
It's okay. We can take a taxi.
Right. What do we do about your car?
It must be tough.
What?
Tell him to call me when he sobers up.
I want to talk to the perpetrator.
Let's go have another round. Choo-choo.
Gosh, I'm going to throw you
into the recycling bin.
Another round, my foot.
Do you think you can handle him?
I can drive him home.
It's okay. I can take him to my place.
I live near here.
You don't need to.
We'll drive him home.
Let us do that.
Where does Jae-jin live?
It's really okay. If he goes home now,
his brothers might undress him
and kick him out.
But it's late and dangerous.
You should go home first.
[I want to ask him why he sounds so sweet]
[as if he worries about me.]
[I want to ask him why he's with her]
[and why he's always around me,]
[keeping me from recovering.]
[There are so many things
I want to ask him, but...]
It's really okay.
Hye-sun, I'm sorry.
I'll text you tomorrow.
-Bye.
-Okay. Bye.
I should go.
What?
I'm worried.
But...
[Is the person she likes...]
[Why do I keep...]
[No way.]
[Do I like her in a different way?]
I'll get going.
You can't go by yourself.
-I can...
-Ouch!
See? I said you might fall.
[How dare]
[I...]
[She's so young]
[and young.]
[Since when and how?]
I can take care of him.
You can go, Professor.
Hye-sun must be waiting.
[Why now?]
[You know what?]
I may lie to other people,
but I would never lie to myself.
Are you sure you want this?
[Even if she meets other people,]
[dates others,]
[loves others,]
[and eventually
stays out of your life forever?]
No.
I'm not sure.
[We appreciate Kang Mi-na
for her guest appearance.]
[My Roommate is a Gumiho]
[For the first time since I met her,]
[I felt like I fell from clouds]
[and bumped into reality.]
[I'm going to give a presentation
about Goryeo's Buddhist culture...]
[What kind of fox is so easy to read?]
[if you like her so much,
why don't you hurry]
[and turn into a human
so you can meet her again?]
[I think her memories aren't erased.]
[Is there really something
going on between them?]
[Miss Dam.]
[The soundtrack, "One Step Closer" is
now available on streaming sites.]
[Your memories aren't erased, are they?]