The Taoism Grandmaster
Junior Brother,
do you remember?
Master told us about the seven-star Dou Gui
and the importance of placing it in the medicine cabinet.
I was thirsty at that time.
Seven-star Dou Gui,
seven-side Dou,
is about raising your hand,
raising your head,
and holding half of the medicine cabinet.
The medicine cabinet in Seven-star Dou Gui
is determined by the Dou Po.
Each doctor has different habits.
The order of the medicine cabinet will also be different.
But
the common medicine should be put together.
Yes.
Look,
just like this four-leaf clover,
white tree,
ginseng,
dried grass and fuling,
in theory, they should be put together.
Not common.
Look at the Dou Gui,
Tian Ma,
Ma Huang,
Ma Huang Gen,
why is there a fuling here?
Four-leaf clover.
Hey!
Be careful.
This is
the three thousand medicine cabinet
that Master made with his life.
Actually, Yunxiu and Master were in love at that time.
These medicine cabinets were for her.
Master
tried to kill everything
with the peach blossom powder,
but eventually became a demon.
Senior,
I was wrong.
I hate the wrong person.
I think
you have been more painful
than me these years.
If it were you, what would you do?
I mean
the day when Master was in the fire,
if the sword was in my chest,
what would you do?
I would be like you.
The sword
is used to protect the weak and the weak.
It's not used to help the weak.
It's not used to help the weak and the weak.
In that case,
let us go.
Miss.
Young Master Yan,
Lord Han Dao.
Miss,
how did you get in?
My father brought me here.
These are all
the prescription for treating disease and saving people,
cooling down the heat and removing the plague.
The medicine of many famous people in the Peach Blossom Manor
are all from here.
Your father
tried hard to please my master.
These are the prescription for treating disease and saving people.
I didn't expect
he would give his heart
and get a good husband.
I didn't expect
he locked himself in the room
and didn't die.
He betrayed his father.
My father stole these prescription,
but left the Peach Blossom Manor.
He died in the Peach Blossom Manor.
He died in Britain.
Yes.
In order to escape the Peach Blossom Manor,
my master avenged him.
Everything
in Britain is in the Peach Blossom Manor.
Miss,
why are you here?
I want to see
what the Peach Blossom Manor
that killed my sister,
my father
and my brother
is.
What is it?
Okay.
Let's go and find it together.
I've checked here.
The Peach Blossom Manor is definitely not here.
Could it be
that Hong Xiu is hiding something?
Let's go back.
Let's go.
The Peach Blossom Manor
Miss,
If Lord Han Dao agrees to the case,
these bodies will be taken away.
Otherwise,
the bodies will be destroyed.
Do these things
on your own.
Yes.
I'll go and ask Lord Han Dao now.
Uncle.
Miss.
Do you think Hong Xiu
has achieved his dream?
Young Mistress
and my wife want to marry Young Master.
Now they are both in the imperial family.
Although it's tragic,
it's still a good thing.
Is there really
a good thing in this world?
It's a good thing.
But it's not useless.
I think it's really a good thing
that the broken mirror can be restored.
The broken mirror can be restored.
I didn't find the case file.
I still don't understand
who killed the Princess Consort.
If the Princess Consort was not killed by Hong Xiu,
then our guess
must go back to the origin.
Yunyang
can only be the murderer.
Who has the greatest profit
after Hong Xiu's death?
The King of Gu.
That's right.
The reason why we can
find Hong Xiu so smoothly this time
is not only because of the peach blossom umbrella in the red candle,
but also because of the King of Gu's confession.
The King of Gu has been helping Hong Xiu
manage his business outside the manor.
Once Hong Xiu died,
then these industries
are naturally the King of Gu's.
The King of Gu can help Hong Xiu
manage his business.
Can he also help him kill people?
Hong Xiu wanted to take advantage of the King of Gu
and didn't expect the King of Gu to be so arrogant.
After Hong Xiu died,
he put all the blame on Hong Xiu alone.
In this way,
he just wiped himself clean.
Did He Bo also tell us
that the King of Gu and Hong Xiu had a private affair?
If this is true,
then the King of Gu
has a great suspicion.
Senior,
do you remember
the line from the death of Yu Niang?
Seven years, seven months, the peach blossom festival.
We still don't know
what the so-called peach blossom festival is.
Sir, the King of Gu wants to see you.
Sir,
I came to ask for permission under the order of Miss Da.
If you have no objection to this case,
I will order people
to put the bodies of the soldiers in the cage one by one
to prevent damage.
I have sent people to check the bodies
without any signs of corruption.
Besides, the case still needs to be investigated.
There is still something suspicious.
You have a business relationship with Hong Xiu.
Now Hong Xiu is dead,
you are also suspicious.
I just don't know
if you can afford to investigate.
Sir,
I have said everything I can.
I didn't hide anything.
Really?
Seven years ago,
seven years ago, the peach blossom festival.
What is the peach blossom festival?
Now,
Yu Niang, Yun Xiu and the Princess Consort are all dead.
Do you still want to see more people die in the peach blossom festival?
What does Hong Xiu have to do with the peach blossom festival?
This peach blossom festival
is indeed a tragic event in the mountain village.
Seven years ago, the old village head got serious illness.
He hired many doctors who couldn't treat him well.
But the old village head didn't admit it.
He said that the Yun family came to Changshou on their own.
Even if he got sick,
there was a way to cure him.
So he hired a fake Fang Shi.
Fake Fang Shi.
How is it?
Village head, there is a mountain gate in the northwest.
Please lead me there.
Village head,
the mountain gate is right here.
I'm sorry.
It's dangerous.
I don't know if you want to try it.
As long as I can open the mountain gate,
I'm willing to try everything.
Temple
restored
The festival…
Village head.
The fashion is so good.
Today,
the good men, Yunxiu,
Xie Youzi,
Yunyang,
Yunming
are at the Peach Blossom Pool.
If we don't get the Peach Blossom Formation,
the Peach Blossom Pool
and the Miaoling Women
will be in the heaven and earth
to help the good men, Yunxiu,
to live forever.
Go.
You two,
go.
Ming,
you've seen it before.
How can you be my son?
Go.
Useless bastard.
Father, please calm down.
Let me do it.
Go.
That's my good son.
I'll kill you.
God bless you.
I'll go to heaven
and curse the people of the Peach Blossom Pool
and all the other people.
When the Peach Blossom is in full bloom,
you will die from the Peach Blossom Formation.
Okay, I'll wait for you.
The Peach Blossom Pool
No one knows whether the Peach Blossom Festival is a good thing.
But Young Madam
must have used the rumour of the Peach Blossom Festival
to put the village in this panic
and entrust the death of the old and young masters
to the Peach Blossom Festival.
You knew it long ago.
Why did you tell us now?
I didn't experience it personally.
Besides,
the Peach Blossom Festival is a secret in the village.
I dare not reveal it.
Now that the old and young masters are dead,
the young lady is a good person.
I dare not tell anyone about it.
As for your suspicion of me,
please investigate it carefully.
I will follow your lead.
After the case is over,
I will let you know who is the dead.
Thank you, sir.
Young Master,
I'll go and confirm something.
Wait for me.
The Peach Blossom Festival is a good thing.
But Young Madam
is a good person.
I'm sure you'll find someone who can help you.
I'll go and confirm it.
The years are passing by in the silence.
The frost and snow are gone.
We stand side by side in the battlefield.
I see the stars in the sky.
The peach blossoms are blooming.
The grudge is like a word.
Only true love can't win.