[12 years before this...]
[June 2014, restaurant]
I'll fill you in on where we're headed.
I'm so curious.
Here are your tickets.
- Just check in on your own.
- What's today's date?
- It's today.
- Exactly.
[Peru: snatched right off the bat]
[July 2014, studio]
Guys, you just need to head out.
Wait, now? Like right this second?
[Laos: kidnapped under a promo shoot]
- It's already five, move it. - Hurry up!
What is going on!
Hold on, I'm leaving dressed like this?
For real?
[Iceland: kidnapped in a tuxedo]
But I'm literally dressed like this.
On the plane, though.
[January 2016, Phuket]
One, two, three!
You can head out right now.
[Africa: kidnapped during Reply 1988 trip]
Hold on, what do you mean right now?
Just get in that car.
Going right to the airport.
[And ten years later...]
[February 2026, motel]
Ugh, it's so cold.
Yeah.
Okay, I'm good to go.
Hi, I'm Jung Yumi.
[Park Seo Jun]
Wait, we do this standing up?
Yeah, just stay standing there.
[Choi Woo Shik]
All we knew was
Seo Jun, Yumi, and Woo Shik, together.
- That was literally it.
- That's it.
Nobody's telling us what's happening.
I tried guessing every possibility.
I had zero clue, honestly.
They got me so good.
I really didn't know.
Not at all.
Where does
the scheming even start?
Getting yanked out of a livestream was not
even on my radar.
I could not have predicted
the livestream thing...
The livestream part...
- Hold on, we're going now...
- What?
[A nationwide group effort to kidnap live]
Wait, this was a setup?
Looks like we're leaving right now.
- What's happening?
- So many fans are watching.
- What?
- Wait, this was a setup?
[Coming up shortly]
What the... hang on.
[Three weeks before the decoy live]
All these fans tuning in...
The real plan is...
to fool them into a humble little trip
around Korea.
Yeah.
- So that's the real plan.
- Got it.
Think you can manage an "I have no idea"?
- Just...
- Absolutely.
Then set it up like that, please.
Yes, got it.
[Standby for pre-meeting:
Feb 24, Tue, noon (Egg)]
[The cast will think
it's a regular pre-meeting]
[Everyone's been brought in on it]
[Today's live: 12 to 2 PM]
[The day before the decoy live]
[Something gets posted on Channel Full Moon...]
[One odd live squeezed
between IVE and Kim Dae Myung...]
[Channel Full Moon Live]
["Introducing Our Staff,
Writer Kim Dae Ju Edition"]
[Yumi, Dae Ju, Seo Jun, Woo Shik]
[Kim Dae Ju, who's been with them all along]
[Using a decoy live
about Kim Dae Ju's 20th anniversary]
[Congrats! Kim Dae Ju's
20th anniversary celebration live]
[The goal: casually get them into the studio]
Give me 10 min to drag Park Seo Jun,
Choi Woo Shik, and Jung Yumi down here.
Can't you make it in five?
[The day of the decoy pre-meeting]
[Surprise cameras set up throughout HQ]
[Even up to the 4th floor meeting room]
[All set]
[Egg HQ, parking lot]
[30 minutes before standby]
[A black car suddenly pulls in]
Oh? Yumi's here already.
She's way too early, what do we do?
[Current time: 11:30 AM,
Yumi arrived 30 min early]
- You can stay in the car for now.
- What?
Stay in the car,
the others will be here at 11:50...
- Is it okay if I wait in the car?
- Yeah.
[Just steps away from Yumi right now...]
[The live studio]
[Prep for the decoy live is still going]
There's still time, don't worry.
Yumi's already outside.
[Another car that showed up too early]
[Woo Shik also arrived early]
Hey.
Nice ride!
- What's so great? They're all the same.
- Hey!
What are you even doing this early?
- Move over.
- Why?
[Bickering within three seconds of meeting]
Move, I want to try the seat. Out.
Hold on, did you bring a bagged lunch?
A lunchbox.
Are you going to school right now or what?
Off to school, huh...
[Dressed up: level 5]
Are you going to school?
[Dressed up: level 1]
You're so overdressed.
[As those two bicker over who dressed up more]
Seo Jun, please... just dress casually.
Seo Jun's such a fashion guy.
Come on...
Please...
[The studio door quietly slides shut]
Door's closed, right?
Yeah, the curtain's drawn.
They're still down in the garage, yeah?
Ugh, keeping up this act is so hard.
[Takes a deep breath]
So I know they're here,
but I'm not supposed to know
they came to celebrate me, right?
Right.
[Helper 1, Helper 2, Helper 3]
[Helpers dispatched from Channel Full Moon]
[Here's a brief overview of the day's schedule]
Alright, we'll go live from here at 12.
While we kick off the live,
those three go upstairs
to the 4th floor for "prep."
They're going to be like,
"Where's PD Na Young Seok?"
Just tell them he's doing a quick live
downstairs for Dae Ju's 20th.
[Stalling begins]
Just say he'll be right up.
Yumi actually follows our livestream.
She watches our streams all the time.
She might totally click on it.
[Keep her off her phone]
When someone texts me that
Yumi's talking and off her phone,
that's when I spill everything
in ten minutes flat,
[Off to go grab the cast]
then go up.
Then upstairs I'll be like,
"Come to think of it,
you all have history with Dae Ju."
[Pause for effect]
How about we swing by and congratulate him?
Too suspicious? Does it seem off?
[Weird or not, doesn't matter]
It's not super suspicious or anything...
[Seo Jun has arrived]
[Current time: 11:50 AM]
Please.
Oh? He's wearing jeans.
[Dressed up: level 4]
Hey there.
Is Woo Shik here? Where?
[Yumi and Woo Shik still in the car]
Get out, hurry up.
- I can't get out.
- You can't get out?
- I really can't.
- Why not?
I'm dressed way too down for this.
She looks like she packed for a field trip.
- It's just...
- The slipper bag, casual...
I was told casual. Just look at him.
- What's with the slippers?
- Not slippers!
[Questions about all the bags]
[They were told just come as usual...]
Feels like she got a different memo.
- You're just as clueless.
- Me too.
- We're all in the dark here.
- Seriously, no other top with you?
- I brought a jacket, okay.
- You're acting like you know more.
I don't...
[Livestream room]
[Strolling past casually]
Hello?
- Which floor?
- Go up to four.
The 4th floor?
[On edge at the slightest noise]
Gosh, this is killing my nerves.
Noon on the dot.
Let's do this! Let's roll!
We're live now...
Oh, it started! Look at that!
Three "Wow"s showed up!
[People start flooding in live]
Hey! Welcome, welcome!
Happy 20th writing anniversary!
Thanks so much!
[Opening up with the decoy stream]
Send some congrats, everyone!
[4F: fake meeting]
[1F: live studio]
[All three made it to the 4th floor]
Hey! Oh, long time no see!
Oh, what's going on?
Hello.
- Hold on...
- Do you have other plans?
No...
I'm the only one with a wrong memo.
She's literally on a school day vibe.
That's not it, they said come casual!
Even casual...
after years on TV...
At least look decent for the opening!
- At least I wore makeup.
- What?
- I'm wearing makeup.
- Of course you are!
When did you ever? Since when, huh?
Pull up his first "Summer Vacation" clip.
[His first "Summer Vacation" look...]
- Back on "Summer Vacation"...
- First appearance.
[Footage courtesy of CJ ENM]
- What?
- I look so...
I look so sloppy...
- What's wrong?
- Huh?
You showed up in a cotton tee from home.
[Tables have turned]
My mom gave me so much grief over that.
Where's our captain at?
- He's doing a live right now.
- He'll be up soon.
- He'll be coming up shortly.
- It's Kim Dae Ju's 20th year today.
He'll be coming up shortly.
- It's already been 20 years.
- They're doing the live early today?
[Oh right, she's the subscriber]
[Suspicion creeps into the trio...]
[One hour ago]
Man, those ten minutes are nerve-racking.
- That ten minutes is the worst part.
- Right.
I'm such a terrible liar, so...
I'm so nervous right now.
[Staff shaking with nerves before it began]
- He's doing a livestream first.
- He said he'll be on live first.
Who even tunes into a live right now?
What?
- Lunch break viewers are no joke.
- For sure.
[Crisis averted thanks to Yumi]
The live just kicked off?
It's only like a 10-minute thing.
Oh, he'll be right up then.
[What a relief...]
Yeah.
- Congrats.
- Oh, thanks a lot.
- Thank you.
- Isn't it gorgeous?
20th anniversary, oh man.
The congrats comments are flooding in.
For real, staying at a job 20 years is...
That's no small thing.
Never switching careers for 20 whole years...
I really only have ten minutes here.
- There's a shoot being set up right now.
- Yeah, I heard about that.
[Meanwhile, still hanging on the 4th floor]
Wait, we're not doing a farm thing, right?
I'm so curious I can't stand it.
What the heck is this about?
Why is it only us three from the show...
Right? I'm low-key panicking over here.
Me too.
They're rolling the dice
big time this early on.
Honestly, this lineup is peak snooze fest.
There's going to be so much dead air...
Hey, you okay? How are you holding up?
- I'm running on a messed-up clock...
- Yeah, figures.
[Seo Jun flew back from a US soccer game]
He literally flew in from the US yesterday.
Bro, spill the details on that.
- What do you want me to say?
- There were three goals, yeah?
So how was it?
It was fun.
Really?
That's not how you tell a story.
That's way too brief. Ask him again.
- Try asking one more time.
- I don't even know what to tell you.
So like, when I was in LA...
- It was pretty decent...
- You didn't hit up BCD?
[A crew member quietly grabs his phone]
I didn't have a chance.
- Actually it was way bigger than I thought.
- Oh, for real?
[Head to the live room ASAP]
They just arrived for the pre-meeting, so...
We're all set apparently.
- Got it.
- They're signaling us to hurry it up...
Okay... understood.
Alright, everyone.
So here's the thing.
I need to say sorry to you all.
I'm sorry, everyone who subscribed.
[Chat room losing its mind in real time]
The whole
20th anniversary thing
is fake.
[Huh, come again?] [Wait, WHAT?]
[No way] [Excuse me?]
- It's actually been 22 or 23 years for him.
- Yeah. Totally got played...
[So sorry about that]
Look, I tricked you all into coming
to this livestream and I feel terrible.
The truth is Seo Jun, Woo Shik, and Yumi
really are up there for a pre-meeting.
[Currently 4th floor] [Currently 1st floor]
Right now they're up on the 4th floor.
They don't know what they're filming yet.
They were told they'd find out today.
[Bone-dry]
So the plan today is through this live
to ship those three off somewhere rough.
[Wait, is this a kidnapping?] [Kidnapping?]
[Yeah, it's a kidnapping]
"Aren't they watching the live up there?"
So we kept it real for the first five minutes.
They just signaled us from up there.
Phones are down and filming has started.
Alright, I'm about to explain everything.
Pay close attention, everyone.
Again, my apologies.
- This whole 20th anniversary stream...
- Sorry about all of this.
We promise to make it up to you...
The 20th anniversary? Also a lie.
Even the cake is fake. None of it's real.
[Okay, lies aside, on to business...]
[Wait, this is a live kidnapping stream?]
That's right, live kidnapping confirmed.
[This whole thing is a setup]
Yeah, you're watching a sting operation.
Once I bring them down in a bit,
that's where you all come in to help.
There are four questions,
and the answers are fixed.
Only comment what I say, subscribers!
Only four things. That's it.
I trust you all.
Alright, here's question number one.
"Subscribers, what should these three do?"
When I ask "what should they do" and snap...
When you hear it, that's your cue.
What show should these three be on?
Just spam "travel" over and over.
Keep it going with travel, travel.
- Oh, lots of travel coming in.
- It can't come in that fast though.
Watch your timing on this.
When I say "what should they do," right.
Snap, travel. That's it. Snap, travel.
They are not watching the live upstairs.
Second question coming, here we go.
Should they do a trip in Korea?
Or take an international trip?
The right answer is domestic, people.
[International]
Kick that subscriber out.
One or two overseas answers are okay.
Right, throw some in to sell it better.
Here's question number three.
With meals, a place to stay,
and getting around all covered,
how much pocket money per day sounds right?
100,000 won. 100,000 won per person.
Last question.
If I ask, "When should they leave
for the trip?"
Right now.
- Right this instant.
- Are we good?
- The playbook's up.
- Done, right?
Okay, you guys practice up.
Give me ten min. I'll bring Park Seo Jun,
Choi Woo Shik, and Jung Yumi down.
Any chance you make it five?
- I'll try to hurry back.
- Yeah, quick!
Just sit tight for a bit.
If they catch the script, it's game over.
- Keep at it.
- Sure, go do your thing.
I'm heading in.
Oh, thanks.
Keep the congrats going till they show up.
You know, "well done,"
[All set for the group prank]
"you worked hard," all that.
I came yesterday, right after the game.
[Young Seok arrives]
Oh? He's here.
Hello.
- Hello!
- We had a livestream going...
- Wait, you left your live to come up?
- What?
- You walked out of a live?
- A livestream.
It's Dae Ju's 20th today, so we're live.
Anniversary livestream and all...
Tell him congrats from us.
- Didn't get to see him.
- Can I go say hi?
- Why don't we swing by and say hello?
- Yeah, do that.
[Everyone watching holds their breath]
But wait, if we do that...
- They'll figure out today's plan, right?
- No, it's fine.
No, today we're...
- They knew about this.
- That's okay though?
Know what exactly?
[Help...]
[Nice catch]
They already knew
you guys were meeting up today.
Okay, then no worries.
Tell Dae Ju to come up here.
We all should go down there?
All of us? Seriously?
Just to see Dae Ju?
I'll just text him later.
[Laughter]
Just to see Dae Ju?
I'll just text him later.
[Nothing to say, so just a big laugh]
Gosh. Hold on.
Let me just call the PD real quick.
I mean, I'll call him after.
- Everyone has to go down?
- You're doing a live?
Who's on the live?
[The signal sent up from the 4th floor...]
The teaser dropped on Netflix today.
- It's me.
- So the teaser dropped...
- Yeah.
- Here he is.
- Yu Jin's on the live.
- Right.
Really? Okay, don't mention it to Dae Ju.
Is it cool if they run down and just say hello?
Got it.
Let's just pop in
and say hello before anything else.
Might as well promote our stuff
while we're at it.
- Promote what? We have no idea what this is.
- Right.
We have zero clue what we're doing.
Just say it's a pre-meeting and plug it.
- Take one of those persimmons.
- Wait though...
Tell him to bring his instincts back to life.
- That sounds good.
- That's good.
I actually have to take this.
[The trio with zero variety instincts
heads out...]
One sec. Use the stairs.
Yeah, just go.
Alright, the comment section now...
Flood the comments with "congrats on 20 years."
Alright.
Wait a sec.
Let's keep it a surprise.
Wait right here.
[Scoping things out to be safe]
[Nodding]
[Jung Yumi, Park Seo Jun, Choi Woo Shik]
[Entering now]
Alright, for Kim Dae Ju's 20th anniversary
to celebrate this milestone...
Our celebration crew is here!
Hello!
- No, the star! Come over here!
- Hi, everyone.
Hurry, sit down.
Oh hey, we match! Same color.
- You're right.
- I came here for the live today.
[About 5,000 actors recruited]
We were in a meeting upstairs just now.
[Once they've taken their seats]
[Stream thumbnail changed]
[Unplanned Trip: Limited Edition,
and these three have no idea]
You're right.
- You two look the same.
- I came for the live.
- Already 20 years?
- Say hi here.
Anyway, congrats...
- Congrats!
- Happy anniversary!
May you never run out of good instincts.
- Oh, great present.
- Sure.
Appreciate it.
- Just stay five minutes.
- Only five?
- Have a seat.
- Sit.
I really didn't see this coming.
I swear I didn't know.
They told me it's a 20th anniversary...
I figured they were streaming
for Dae Ju's fans.
How did I not think twice
about the 20th anniversary thing?
Zero suspicion. I completely fell for it.
I do wonder what it was like meeting
for the first time.
So the first time...
- Where did we meet?
- Gili.
Coming from our Gili days...
The second one was Seo Jun.
- Yeah, I hopped on board.
- He joined halfway through.
Where did we meet again?
- "Summer Vacation."
Yes. So with these three
who share such deep ties...
So we're streaming,
and they insisted on popping in.
They dropped by and said their hellos.
Actually, while we're here, you never know...
What kind of show should these three do?
[Operation begins]
Let's get the subscribers' input.
What show should Seo Jun,
Woo Shik, and Yumi do?
What show would you want to see?
[The snap cue is triggered]
Let us know your ideas, folks.
[Q1. What show should they do?]
[A1. Travel]
You guys are prepared, right?
Isn't this part of the plan too?
- Whoa, "travel" is blowing up.
- Travel?
- Travel.
Since we've done shows like Seo Jin's...
People want us to go on trips abroad.
- Travel.
Okay, but trips can be local or overseas.
Local or abroad?
- Domestic.
Busan works, domestic's solid.
Oh man, tons of people are saying domestic.
- How about traveling in Korea?
- A road trip across Korea!
Let me ask one more question.
[Holding back laughter]
If they were to travel around Korea,
how much pocket money do you think
would be reasonable per person?
How much pocket money do you think
- Hold on, is this trip for real?
- Seriously?
- This isn't set up already, right?
- You're doing this here?
- What's a fair amount for pocket money?
- Aren't you planning this on the spot?
A hundred thousand won each, got it.
- About a hundred thousand won?
- What even is this right now?
This seems completely set up.
They blurted out the number right away.
I thought this crew was really in sync.
That's what I thought at the time.
I had absolutely no idea until then.
100,000 won per night, each.
One night, 100,000 won each.
- 100,000 won...
- 100,000 won is flooding the chat.
- It's totally dominating.
- 100,000 won?
- That's the clear winner.
30? I can't believe they're all in sync.
Alright...
one final question here.
- For real...
- Hold on.
If they happened to...
- take a trip around Korea...
- You're not asking AI, right?
If they took off,
when's the best time to leave?
Right now?
- Right now?
- "Let's go."
- Now?
- Right now?
- Right now.
- Right this instant.
I guess that's the people's verdict.
- Hey, Yumi.
- Yes?
- Woo Shik.
- Yeah.
- Seo Jun.
This is as if...
- somebody planned all these answers...
- Why am I suddenly shaking?
What's going on?
- What?
- Maybe...
Judging by all these comments...
- What's going on?
- What?
- Maybe...
- You should probably head out...
- What?
[Unplanned Trip: Limited Edition]
- What? - What?
[Best wishes to Jung Yumi,
Park Seo Jun, Choi Woo Shik]
This was all planned.
- What?
[A banner behind the banner?]
What?
This was all planned.
You should probably leave right now.
- You should probably leave right now.
- What?
[Hahaha]
This was all planned.
[Can't believe their own eyes]
You should probably leave right now.
- What's happening?
- I mean,
with all these people...
- No way.
- This was all planned.
Wait, hold on. What is this?
All these subscribers...
I felt totally blindsided, for real.
"Wait, what's happening?"
The moment that banner came off,
within a fraction of a second...
"How far back was this planned?"
For real...
I never thought a livestream would
turn into a kidnapping.
Not even one percent of me saw it.
I'm genuinely terrified.
So many people, in perfect sync,
- What even is this?
- carrying just 100,000 won,
- are telling us to go right now.
- Hold on.
- You all are such good actors.
- You're all way too good at this.
- Seriously?
- Wait, is this all a lie too?
So the whole anniversary was a lie?
- It's the 22nd, not the 20th.
- Yeah, it's been 22 years.
Are you serious?
That was a lie too?
- You planned this whole thing?
- Gosh.
I'm so scared right now.
No. I'm not going.
I refuse. I'm not going.
I had no idea you were this scary.
I think you should leave right now.
Seo Jun, read this out loud.
I don't want to read it.
Please, just read it for us.
"Best of luck to Jung Yumi,
Park Seo Jun, and Choi Woo Shik?
Wishing a safe trip and safe return.
Unplanned Trip: Limited Edition."
It literally says Limited Edition.
Limited, as in things are capped.
You all are about to have a restricted trip.
For this one, we're going with
Unplanned Trip: Limited Edition.
We'll soak up every bit of this trip,
be back in Seoul by Sunday,
then hop on a livestream to fill you in.
Exactly what you asked for,
we'll do a local trip
on 100,000 won per person,
so catch us again in seven days.
Okay, see you all later!
- See you!
This is insane.
[Live ended]
Man, every single one of you
can really act, for real.
That completely caught me off guard.
Okay, so we're done with the live,
but your part is only kicking off now.
Have a seat, everyone.
The pre-trip briefing happens right here.
- In here? This is the spot?
- That's right.
[At that moment, something massive comes in...]
[Travel Restriction Notice]
Wait, none of this is registering.
The show's called "Unplanned Trip:
Limited Edition," yeah?
- Limited. So restrictions apply here.
- Right.
[They review the notice with five restrictions]
Time to break down each restriction.
Woo Shik, start with the first one.
Every day, you relocate to a new city.
Seoul and Gyeonggi don't count.
Every day?
So we're moving somewhere new starting tonight?
Once I'm done explaining,
you'll be heading somewhere
outside Seoul and Gyeonggi.
Got it.
So after we sleep,
we leave for a different region in the morning?
Morning, afternoon, evening, doesn't matter.
- Anytime?
- Just make sure
you're in a new region before the day's over.
[Reality hits like clockwork]
Sure.
Seo Jun, go ahead and read number two.
Each person is capped at 100,000 won per day.
No dipping into your own wallet.
So it's 100,000 won per head...
That barely covers transportation.
- Does that include everything?
- Every last bit of it.
Are you serious?
So with 300,000 won,
getting around and finding a place to sleep
are the biggest expenses.
What about food?
And gas money?
Sorry, but gas isn't something
you need to stress over.
There's no car.
So it's public transit then...
We're taking public transit?
Starting right now?
You're leaving pretty soon.
So we didn't want you stressing over it.
- You had your cars, right?
- Yeah.
While you were doing the live,
we already sent them off.
So there's nothing left to think about.
So each of you gets 100,000 won
to cover transit, a place to sleep, meals,
socks for Woo Shik tomorrow,
fresh underwear for Seo Jun...
Wait, what does that mean?
Hold on, I'm not following.
- What are you saying?
- Look, the thing is...
Because you're leaving this instant,
Unplanned Trip has always been
- about taking off with nothing...
- Except we're not exactly young anymore.
[At heart, though...]
So "sent them off" means they drove away?
- The cars?
- Right.
They're already gone.
We asked the managers to go
somewhere you would never track down.
- It'll work out somehow.
- Alright.
Okay, Yumi, let's hear number three.
Phone use is restricted during the trip.
You do get one chance to use it per day,
but only at the accommodation.
So it's a chance that's being granted.
- Right.
- Not a guarantee, just an opportunity.
Unplanned Trip: Limited Edition is a trip
where being together is enough,
even without phones
and with barely any money.
Doesn't that sound nice?
I'm Po-po over here.
What's Po-po supposed to mean?
It means 44.
- That's 44 alright.
- Sure is.
Po-po.
Think of this as going back to your roots,
- back to that original spirit.
- Right.
It's just... the stamina part...
Woo Shik, read number four.
A daily morning benefit will be provided.
- But...
- Benefit.
What kind of benefit?
A hundred thousand won a day,
relocating every day,
no phone access...
This could get pretty rough for you all.
- Yeah.
- Just a little.
So every morning,
we'll be handing out a benefit
that takes care of one thing
[Written on three slips, drawn at random]
that's been tough for you.
But what it is
[Benefits revealed next week]
and how you'll receive it,
we'll fill you in on that when the time comes.
That's giving me chills.
What's wrong, Po-po?
I really wish this were a dream.
If only it were...
[And the fifth and final restriction]
Come back here on March 1,
start the live,
and the trip officially wraps up.
Never thought I'd actually be doing this.
I know, I never saw myself
on Unplanned Trip either.
Figured I'd just be stuck doing dishes forever.
So where are we headed?
Domestic travel is coming up a lot.
[Relocating every day]
[Across this vast country of South Korea]
[Hit every spot with fresh air and clean water]
This place is gorgeous.
- Oh, what is this place?
- Gosh.
At least we did make it to the ocean.
[Expect to be running every day...]
I've never done anything like this.
You know...
[Expect to have basically nothing]
There's still Spam here...
- Thank you.
- They don't accept cash.
You have to use the machine.
Looks like there's no blanket.
Adding a car rental will leave us with nothing.
At least we'll be able to afford underwear.
I really need a cup of coffee.
I'm exhausted right now.
Let's grab one.
What do you think?
[Don't expect this to go smoothly]
Nobody's saying anything.
- Did it pass?
- No way.
Is that the one?
- Probably not.
- One just slipped away.
[Like a bus that already left]
We need to get off!
[Like doors that could close any second]
This one.
Oh, no!
[Like a swing that moved faster than expected]
- Closed today.
- This place too?
Let's try calling.
[Like a cold "Closed" sign]
One person died overnight.
The deceased is...
Starting from now...
Not a word...
Night has come around again.
But having the money capped definitely
forces us to do things differently than usual.
There's something fresh about that.
Yeah.
It would've been a totally different experience
doing it solo.
[Nothing is going according to plan]
Oh, hold on a second.
What do we do? Where are we even going?
That's exactly what we need to nail down first.
So...
Actually, I have a question.
So we're capped at 100,000 won, right?
If we save some,
can we just roll it over to the next day?
Of course.
- That part's completely up to you.
- Think we can pull it off?
Only one way to find out.
By the last day,
Woo Shik's beard is going to be like...
And then the live turns on.
Like someone who just got back from Everest.
Toured the whole country
[Allowance and Looks: Inversely Proportional]
and just looking absolutely rough...
So should we start
with the farthest spot first?
Since we're already doing this,
somewhere we've never been sounds right.
Here's my take on it.
We hit the farthest point on day one.
And then we work our way back?
- Exactly.
- That could actually work.
So, Jeju Island?
- Jeju Island?
- Yeah, Jeju.
Then we're not eating anything today?
We've got 300,000 won for the day.
I skipped breakfast this morning.
- It's 300,000 a day.
- We could just ask for gochujang on the plane.
- But...
- Jeju's probably pushing it.
Really?
What's the farthest we can get on the KTX?
Busan or Gwangju?
Yumi, doesn't your family live in Busan?
Oh right, they do.
Let's swing by and say hi to your family.
[I'll pass on that one]
Then let's go to Daegu.
Do you know anyone in Daegu?
Not really.
- Alright, let's hear everyone's thoughts.
- Let's decide quickly.
- So are we going for the farthest spot?
- What time is it right now?
Are we just going to inch our way around?
Or do we go all the way to the end
and work from there?
I mean...
Bam, bam, bam, bam!
[Going way up without any reason...]
[Um... sis...]
Sis, pretty sure that one
just landed in Pyongyang.
[That's a no-go zone]
So it's bam, bam, bam, bam!
- Oh, I get what you're saying now.
- Like this, right?
- So you mean covering big distances at a time?
- Exactly.
- Spread out.
- Hit Chungcheong,
- then Jeolla, then Gyeongsang?
- Right.
That could work too.
- We should at least cross one off first.
- Yeah, cross one off.
[The first destination has everyone
thinking hard...]
So what do we do...
[Sliding over]
Should we start with Chungcheong?
[One person charging at the map
like he's in a trance...]
- So we...
- Yeah.
Let's head over for some Boryeong Gulbi.
What's Boryeong Gulbi?
It's Yeonggwang Gulbi.
Boryeong Gulbi.
[Boryeong is known for mud,
Yeonggwang for dried yellow corvina]
Let's think about what we actually
want for dinner.
So we're going just for that?
- Let's go for it.
- Yeah, let's do it.
Sure.
- Alright then...
- Boryeong Gulbi.
[It's Yeonggwang...]
Boryeong Gulbi.
- Boryeong...
- Which gulbi are we even talking about?
It's from Yeonggwang.
Isn't there one that starts with "Bo?"
- Bori Gulbi.
[Laughing fit]
Bori Gulbi.
[Cringe meter rising]
[Let's see now...]
Let's just go to Yeonggwang.
[Quickly steering toward South Jeolla]
Where's Yeonggwang? Right here.
It takes forever by car though.
I've been out there for a shoot
and it's deep in.
So then...
- Going there would be great, but...
- Right.
Getting there in one shot today
might not be realistic.
- Somewhere, though...
- Oh, the food there is incredible.
Should we just throw something
at the map right here?
- That works.
- Alright, let's go with that.
Yeah, that's not a bad call.
- So what if we did it this way?
- What do you mean?
Woo Shik, close your eyes
and walk over from there.
- Just stab it.
- No, you walk forward first.
[Places mentioned so far]
[Jeju, Busan, Daegu, Gyeongju, Geoje...]
[Too many places everyone wants to visit...]
Are we throwing the cap?
Then let's settle it with rock paper scissors.
- Whoever loses does the throwing.
- Loser throws.
- Rock paper scissors.
[Woo Shik instantly crowned
the star of the show]
Come on, get it right.
[Massive pressure]
[The first destination rests entirely
in Woo Shik's hands!]
We throw it to mark a spot?
[Staggering]
[Absolute tension]
Gosh.
If it lands in Gyeonggi, we're starting over.
That's the rule.
Watch yourself.
[I'm Choi Woo Shik...]
Just point him in the right direction.
[Seven years in variety, he just knows]
You're drifting somewhere else.
We're not heading to North Korea, right?
You can stop now.
[Right away]
Where am I?
[Dizzy]
Just set the direction, that's all.
Here it goes.
[Total chaos]
[Not there...]
Again!
[Second try]
Going for it.
Not that spot...
- Where are you even stabbing?
- One more time, this is the last one.
[Deep ocean]
How are we supposed to go to the sea?
Going.
[Final for real this time]
Here we go.
[Please, can we just go already...]
That's it.
- Hey.
- That's it.
- Where is it?
- Where?
- That's pretty far out.
- Where even is this?
- Gumi. Some mountain in Gumi.
- Gumi.
[The mark landed on Gumi, North Gyeongsang]
Gumi!
Some township!
Might as well check it out.
Alright, should we get things rolling?
So let's say we head out in five minutes.
Five minutes from now?
But I'm freezing right now.
[Completely thrown off]
Phones get collected here in five minutes,
and then we're off.
- Sure.
- What about our bags?
Bags?
- If you brought it...
- If that's your own stuff...
[Carry-on items only]
Seriously? Okay, nice.
[Earlier, when they first arrived]
She looks like she packed for a field trip.
- The slipper bag, casual...
- Well...
[Yumi and Seo Jun arrived with backpacks]
I was told casual.
[And Woo Shik, who had a blast teasing her...]
Just look at him.
What did you bring, Seo Jun?
Just the basics, you know.
Wait, you packed essentials?
[Essentials for a... pre-shoot?]
Just stuff for washing up and things like that.
- Same here.
- Why did you pack those?
I still have to shave, at the very least.
You didn't even know
where you were going today.
It was just a pre-shoot meeting.
Still, even without knowing,
I figured something was up.
You knew, didn't you, Seo Jun?
- You knew, didn't you?
- Come on, you knew, right?
No, I had absolutely no idea.
- That's exactly why you only brought a bag.
- What?
You showed up with just a backpack.
I only packed the bare minimum, just in case.
- Exactly.
- I literally just showed up with a backpack.
- Did you have some kind of feeling?
- Just...
You're lying!
I was thinking something was going on.
Have you been talking to Geon Jun?
[Unfair]
I don't even have his number.
At this point,
I'd say this kind of thing counts
as experience in its own way.
If this had been my first time
working with you all,
I probably would've shown up
without a second thought.
Usually
there's at least some heads-up
about where we're going,
but there was nothing this time.
So I realized the only one
looking out for me was myself.
It's basically like packing a first-aid kit.
Thinking along those lines,
I figured I'd at least pack this much,
even if it gets taken away.
Might as well bring it along first.
[Acting every bit like a variety veteran
two years ahead of Woo Shik]
[Another senior with a sharp nose]
Since nobody was telling us what was happening,
I'm kind of a pack-it-all type by nature,
so I packed what I could,
and there were things just lying around.
I just threw those into the bag.
[Really glad she's a pack-it-all type...]
I'll give you a moment
to search on your phones.
[Still need to look up
the route and how to get there]
- Oh, searching?
- We're searching?
- Let's be quick about it.
- Phones are getting collected in five...
I need to run upstairs real quick.
Your bags are upstairs, right?
- Alright.
- Grab whatever you need right now.
[Time is precious...
the trio splits up to divide and conquer]
Wait, why are you doing this to me...
[Suddenly feeling wronged]
Is this right?
Are you coming along with us, Director?
[A nod]
You knew about this?
[Another nod]
[The only three who didn't know...]
I still have chills from it.
What is this?
How did they pull this off?
What am I supposed to do with this?
Hold on a second.
My clothes, okay, clothes are fine for now.
Just a moment. Wait.
[Just throwing on whatever's in sight]
Thank goodness,
I've got one extra outfit in this bag.
Right in here.
[The pack-it-all type always wins...]
[Meanwhile, the search team is diving
deep into the internet...]
- Looks like we need the subway station.
- Right.
I should write this down.
Writing it down won't help.
Oh, right.
[Scrutinizing the map from every angle]
- There's so much good food in Daegu.
- Totally.
Makchang.
Should we hit the market?
- Oh, I'm completely on board.
- The market.
Oh, Daegu Mungtigi!
[Found it...]
[A reason to go to Daegu...]
[Dinner plans shifted, next stop, Daegu]
That settles it, Daegu Mungtigi is the plan.
We sleep in Daegu tonight and move on tomorrow.
[This is the beauty of a spontaneous trip]
Then we take the KTX
and head to Daegu...
Let's bring it up when Yumi gets back.
Since we're taking the KTX either way,
let's say we head to Daegu first,
closest to Gumi.
Then I'll grab my stuff from my car.
Your car isn't here anymore.
- Wait, really?
- The car is seriously gone.
- Because I really...
- Woo Shik, snap out of it!
- You're stuck in those clothes all day.
- Woo Shik, wake up!
- You're wearing that for the whole week.
- For the whole week.
That's not what I...
[That's actually correct]
So I can actually take my backpack?
Of course, your stuff is yours to bring.
Sounds good.
You had even the slightest feeling, didn't you?
No, it wasn't really a feeling,
but something was clearly going on here.
Because nobody was telling us anything.
This pretty much had to be some kind of ambush.
[A 9-year pro with a nose for patterns]
So you still picked up on the vibe?
Yeah. Because they weren't giving us anything.
Hey, at least grab this much.
Let's get coffee before we leave.
We have to grab coffee on the way out.
[Gulping it down]
[Seo Jun layers up with his hoodie
for one last defense against the cold]
Drink your coffee, Yumi.
No, I'm skipping it.
I'll end up needing the bathroom.
If you ask for coffee today...
No, I'm not drinking coffee.
[Busy keeping tabs on Yumi's coffee
on top of everything]
[What is he up to now...]
[Rummaging around]
[Swiping a hallabong]
- Look at this guy.
- Choi Woo Shik.
[After the hallabong, now sneaking snacks too]
[Stashing any food in sight]
Come on, stop it.
Woo Shik, let's not sink that low.
A bag of shrimp crackers isn't crossing a line.
Okay, I'll give you one minute,
since your parents might start worrying,
so make your calls
before we collect the phones.
Alright, one minute starts now.
I need to reach Mom, quick.
[To Mom]
I'm here
with the crew, so don't worry.
And I won't be in touch for a week.
[Everyone scrambling to make their last texts]
This has really gone sideways.
[This one's too busy eating fruit...]
[Gulping away]
[Storing it all in his mouth for now]
Okay, you guys made your calls?
Geon Jun.
[Handing over the phone]
Now, please hand over your phones to me.
Wait, so it actually works like this?
It's off.
Then I'll turn mine off too.
[Now, about this phone bag...]
[Bag TMI: 1. Secured with magnetic closure]
[2. Phone safety visible at all times
3. Which means you might really miss it]
[The production team will keep them safe]
And here it is, 100,000 won per person,
300,000 won total.
- 30 bills of 10,000 won each.
- Am I holding this?
Right.
Inside here, there's
the Travel Restriction Notice and a map.
Got it.
And you can film as you go.
Woo Shik's into that,
so it's an old analog camcorder.
That's fantastic.
[Introducing the trio's
three travel essentials]
[#1. Cash wallet, 100,000 won per person,
300,000 won total]
[#2. Notebook and map,
a smooth-writing notebook with a national map]
[The Travel Restriction Notice is
inside the notebook too]
[Just in case you forget...]
[#3. Camcorder, pure analog vibes!
Record your memories]
["I'll get a great shot for you!"]
[With their three-item kit in hand,
the trio...]
Let's start by checking the money first.
[That same wallet from earlier]
[Park Seo Jun / treasurer]
How much was it, something and ten thousand?
17,500 won.
Hand over the change.
[The thing Park the treasurer does most]
[Counting cash]
One, two, three, four, five.
Hold on, let me check this.
[Absolutely meticulous with money]
Six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Count it one more time.
[And what Park the treasurer loves most...]
The cheapest option, please.
Do whatever you feel like, Yumi.
[What's the occasion?]
Just nothing too expensive.
- Apparently an Americano's 2,500 won.
- Let's move.
- Somewhere cheaper?
- Exactly.
That's the way to go.
[Keeping it cheap, heading straight there]
[Meanwhile, another bold soul takes the lead]
Just head to the building next door.
A different building? Which direction?
[Jung Yumi / public connector]
- Would it be okay to ask? - Ask what?
Should we just ask how to get there?
Could you let us know
when to get off for Yulpo?
Of course.
[Is anyone there?]
[Lost no more, the human GPS has arrived]
There's a direct bus if you go to the terminal.
Oh, for real?
[Making small talk]
It's been years? Oh my.
- Do you two know each other?
- No.
[From elders to kids]
She's from Daegu.
- You're lovely.
- Thank you.
I feel like I've seen you somewhere before.
- Have some.
- Oh, thank you so much.
Sweet potato.
[With Yumi around,
sweet potatoes appear out of nowhere...]
[This one picks up the camera at any moment...]
[Choi Woo Shik, camcorder director]
Oh, this is nice.
Hold on, MZ shot.
Okay.
[Po-po Sis and the Almost-Forties.mov]
Cross over, please.
[Director Choi's direction
turns everything into a film]
[Charisma]
Hold it.
[Woo Shik CAM]
[May be somewhat experimental,
viewer discretion advised]
Sit lower, lower, even lower.
[Three genuine friends, three different styles]
Alright, good.
- Should I take this off?
- Wait.
[Taking a taste]
Let's save it for the end.
[Just enjoying it]
- Oh, so it's here!
- Over there.
This is the spot.
Alright, we're heading out.
Let's go!
[The trip begins]
Wait, why am I the only one in a coat...
[Egg building, Seoul Station, Daegu]
[How exactly, still unknown]
[Current time: 1:25 pm]
We need to get to Seoul Station first.
- Isn't the closest station Hakdong?
- Sinsa!
Sinsa Station!
Is Sinsa actually closer?
Doesn't this way lead to Hakdong?
But we'd have to transfer.
[Obstacles right from the start]
- From Sinsa Station...
- I don't know the subway map...
So from Sinsa...
[No phone means no searching,
and it's frustrating]
Going off memory here...
[Near the Egg building,
there's Hakdong Station and Sinsa Station...]
[Line 3 Sinsa Station, Egg building,
Line 7 Hakdong Station]
[Sinsa Station 14 min away,
Hakdong Station four min away]
If we walk straight down...
[Hey!]
[Glare]
Should we head to Hakdong?
Go for it!
Hakdong is on Line 7, we'd have to go around.
You should come with us.
[Sharp cut-off]
No, I've got things to do.
[The traitor arrives, a 22-year veteran writer]
Director, oh wait, Writer,
what's the best way to get to Seoul Station?
- By bus?
- Seoul Station?
The bus takes a bit of a detour.
The closest station is Hakdong, right?
Is Hakdong better or Sinsa?
[Sensing the moment, firing off questions]
Hakdong is the closer one.
Oh, really?
- Hakdong's the better call.
- Alright.
- Let's head out.
- Are you filming, Woo Shik?
Yeah.
[Woo Shik CAM, even filming the traitor!]
Have a safe trip.
- We're off.
- Take care.
- Let's head out.
- Let's go.
- Straight this way for now?
- Yeah.
[And they're officially on their way]
Let me take your bag, Yumi.
No, I'm fine, really.
- Just hand it over.
- No, later.
Fine.
- Hand it over later then.
- Got it.
[A gentle lift]
What did you pack all this for, though?
It's just stuff I always carry around.
[Maximalist Girl vs. Minimalist Guy]
We should do a "What's in my bag" later.
What's in my bag!
Hakdong Station is right here.
- Then let's head to Isu.
- Hello there.
Please go watch Number One.
[Note: At the time, Number One
starring Woo Shik was playing in theaters]
Yes, hello. That's right.
We're the Number One crew.
[Shameless? Truly Number One...]
Number One...
- Number One.
- Have you seen it, Yumi?
- Of course I have.
- Did you catch it?
- Haven't seen it yet.
- We should check the subway map.
- What?
[Trying to figure out the exact route]
The subway map.
Go to Isu and transfer straight to Line 4.
Didn't we ride Line 4 back
when we were in school?
- Rode Line 4, yeah.
- Right, exactly.
We went to school together,
or were we even in the same year?
- Same school.
If we're in the same class, I'm forty-four too.
Po-po is off-limits.
Getting a single-use ticket.
[Ticket machine spotted]
A transit card? Oh, a single-use one?
- What is this?
- Seoul Station.
Line 1?
Wait, the only line I know is Line 4.
- Hold on.
- Let's just take the one we know.
[Wants to be certain since it's the first trip]
Is there a subway map nearby?
[Striding right over]
Excuse me.
When we're trying to get to Seoul Station,
is Line 1 faster or Line 4?
You're headed to Seoul Station?
- Go to Isu Station first,
- Isu Station.
- then transfer to Line 4.
- Isu Station, then Line 4.
Thank you so much.
[Subway route: Line 7 Hakdong]
[Transfer to Line 4 at Isu,
Exit at Seoul Station]
[Current location: Hakdong]
[11 stations total, transfer to Line 4 at Isu]
That comes out to 6,750 won.
Got it.
[Expense log, subway fare, -6,750 won,
balance: 293,250 won]
[Splitting up the hard-earned transit cards]
Don't throw these away.
So this is the way we need to go.
[Direction already confirmed in advance]
It's this way.
- Is this the right way?
- It is.
[Made it in without a hitch]
[The trio steps onto the platform]
[Seo Jun heads straight for the subway map]
It's only four stops.
[Let's see here...]
[Woo Shik CAM, full of feeling]
The shot looks great here.
Get one from here too.
[Woo Shik CAM,
a director who actually listens...]
[Filming reflections in the glass door...]
I look so tiny in this.
[Instant youth film, just like that]
[Okay, cut]
But seriously,
- nobody saw the banner reveal coming.
- Yeah.
That part caught me completely off guard.
[Still gives chills just thinking about it]
I seriously got chills back there.
You're going to look so cool
all the way to the end.
[Set to be Mr. Autumn vibes
through the very end...]
- This is the right one?
- It's the right one.
Hold on. Let's find a corner spot.
Over here.
Let's just get on first.
[The older two just boarding without a plan...]
There, right there.
A corner... any corner...
[The youngest,
lost while searching for a corner...]
[Stifling a laugh]
[Woo Shik spotted in a different car]
[Regrouped successfully]
[Awkward; Barely holding it together...]
Hello.
[Exchanging greetings with pleased passengers]
Number One!
The movie Number One!
[Barely holding it...]
[Cringe]
- I'm starving.
- Same, I'm starving.
- Should've eaten that tomato.
- Let's grab udon.
Udon sounds good.
It's pricey though...
It runs about 8,000 won.
Let's just hit a convenience store.
First let's book the train tickets,
check the time and if...
- If there's time left over.
- Yeah.
[Lunch plans hinging on the train schedule]
If it's tight, let's just buy something
and board.
[Nodding... hard to argue with that...]
This stop is Isu Station.
[Pulling into Isu, the transfer station]
[Gathering things]
Watch your step.
[Director Choi scrambling to film something]
[Woo Shik CAM, Isu, doors opening on the right]
[First transfer station insert shot...
can't miss this...]
[Mission complete, exiting at Isu Station]
[Even getting the transfer sign on camera]
Right, I used to get off at this exact end.
[This route was Yumi's commute during college]
Back when I was in school.
It's a bit of a walk, though.
[Just follow me, I know Line 4 well]
[Walking a nostalgic path
for the first time in a while]
[Even the long transfer corridor
feels fun walking together...]
Wait, what's this?
Over here...
- No.
- No, don't spend anything right now.
[Cosmetic shopping: DENIED]
Buying anything right now is off the table.
Don't let it pull you in.
[Thankfully resisting temptation
and reaching the platform]
This honestly feels like being 20 again.
- 20 years old?
- Yeah.
[Memories bubbling up]
I rode this all the time back at 20.
[Line 4 arrives, carrying Yumi's memories]
[Transfer wrapped up without a hitch]
Honestly, Number One has been so good lately.
It's really something
the whole family can enjoy.
Right.
[Number One promotion complete on Line 4 too]
- What is this?
- What is this? What's in there?
- What's that?
- No, this isn't.
[The younger ones curious about Yumi's bag]
These are personal items...
- All of this will do you good.
- Seriously?
- What's that?
- Want some candy?
[Face lighting up]
[See, "do you good" turned into candy...]
I need to save these for now.
Should've held back
from sharing at the shop earlier.
Handed out a whole handful back at the shop.
These are good.
I'd like to share, but...
[Put it away]
Those people over there are all in on it.
[To crew]
Sorry I can't share any with you.
[Sorry, but gotta get the sugar in]
[Now's the time]
[Woo Shik CAM]
[Instantly becoming a youth film lead...]
- With this we could just shoot a...
- Music video.
- Should we film something?
- Let's do it.
[Youth Film by Director Choi]
You're the director, let's make a film.
They said it was supposed to snow today.
- Really?
- It won't snow in Daegu.
It'd be nice if it did snow.
[After taking in the view outside]
This stop is Seoul Station.
Seoul Station.
[Seoul Station already]
Doors opening on the left.
[11 stops later, exiting at Seoul Station]
- The KTX is over here.
- Right.
[Signs clearly marked on the floor too]
[Woo Shik CAM, buzzing with excitement
on the way to the train]
- Looking exhausted already.
- I'm hungry.
Seriously starving.
- You're hungry too, right?
- Yeah.
There's more walking ahead.
[Round two of walking begins]
[Walking side by side, and then some more...]
[Hopping up the stairs]
[Huffing and puffing]
[Running, walking, catching their breath]
[Woo Shik CAM]
[The finish line is right there]
[One last stairway to climb]
- Yes.
- It's the 2:28 train.
- What time is it even?
- Daegu.
- Just go, forget the time.
- Let's move.
[The trio finally enters the station]
Those dumplings look incredible.
Looks so good.
5,500 won.
[The price is tempting...]
[But tickets come first!]
Seo Jun.
[Over here]
Found it.
- Please enter your trip details.
- Daegu.
There's Dongdaegu and there's Daegu.
Dongdaegu.
Because Dongdaegu is the main station...
- Dongdaegu...
- Dongdaegu.
- Search for trains.
- Right.
- Please select a train.
- There are so many.
The 2:33.
[14:58 Seoul to 16:52 Dongdaegu]
There's one at 3:00.
Should we take the 3 o'clock?
- Please select your payment method.
- Cash.
- Wait?
- Cash isn't an option.
Oh no.
[Cash payment not accepted]
Oh my.
[Cash nowhere to be found]
[The trio caught completely off guard...]
Let's get over there fast, over there.
[What Yumi meant by "over there"...]
Cash isn't working here.
[A staffed counter right next to the kiosk]
[Lining up at the counter for now]
Or maybe...
We could just ask that person over there.
Exactly.
[Already heading over]
Is everything here card only?
Only cards work here.
- The cars?
- That's right.
- For cash...
- For cash, you'll need to go to the counter.
[A quick bow]
Understood.
[Hand signal sent to the one right across]
[Signal received]
Only this spot takes it.
[Their turn coming up]
Let's go.
- Hello.
We're heading to Dongdaegu.
- We only have cash.
- Oh, that's fine.
- Okay.
- How many in your group?
Three of us.
- The seats face each other, is that okay?
- That works for us.
That'll be 123,900 won.
- How much?
- 123,900 won.
[Stunned by the amount...]
Excuse me?
That's 130,000 won?
[The allowance nearly
cut in half in an instant...]
- So then this...
- Then give me just 20,000 won.
I'll go pick up some dumplings.
- Keep it under 20,000.
- Yeah, got it.
[She heads out to grab dumplings
before boarding]
- Head to the right.
- Row 245.
Thank you so much.
[Dongdaegu-bound tickets booked at 2:58]
[Huffing and puffing]
[Our girl Po-po has had quite
a lot of running to do today...]
One meat dumpling, please.
And two galbi dumplings.
[One dumpling per person, order placed]
One meat, two galbi, that's right?
Correct.
Sorry, could I also get just one water?
[Expense log, dumpling and water:
-17,500 won, balance: 151,850 won]
- It won't take long, right?
- About a minute.
Thank you.
[The younger crew with tickets
moving in to meet Yumi]
There she is!
[Regrouping after completing their missions]
Thank you!
[Amazing dumplings, ready in just one minute]
Let's go, let's go!
[Dumplings secured with time to spare!]
- Should we eat here too?
- Yeah.
Let's go up there.
[Striding up the stairs]
[Short on time, they settle for the stairs]
Ah, let's sit down for a bit.
[First time sitting down since they left]
Let's eat here real quick.
Did you get a lot?
- I got three.
- Oh.
One pork, two galbi.
Oh, I'll take galbi.
Yeah, that one's pork. This is galbi.
- Galbi?
- Galbi.
- What about you, Yumi?
- Let's share.
- Half and half?
- What are you getting? Up to you.
Oh, we can just share.
Hold this for now.
[Sweet Seo Jun is opening
the pickled radish for them]
[Neatly arranged]
- You got one bottle of water.
- You have it.
We're really pinching pennies,
getting just one bottle of water.
Sorry.
I won't drink.
Let's share it.
Thanks for the food.
[Finally taking a bite of
the legendary dumplings]
Wow, nice and warm.
[So good, they wake you right up]
[Dumpling trade]
Might try the pork too.
[Stuffing two dumplings in at once]
How much do we have left, seriously?
Let's eat first, then think.
[Let's worry about money after we eat...]
We're going to Daegu,
so let's have mungtigi today.
What's that?
- Mungtigi...
- It's kind of like... raw beef!
If you have it with soju,
you won't even get a hangover.
[Woo Shik's favorite pairing: mungtigi]
- We could also look for a classic local spot.
- Yeah.
- Somewhere cheap!
- Oh right, we don't have phones, huh?
[No phone to find a classic local spot]
Huh?
- We don't even have phones.
- Yeah.
Guess we'll look around.
We don't have phones,
so we can't look up good places.
We'll just ask around when we get there.
[Anyway, communication complete]
[Smooth and efficient]
[Gather the trash in one place]
[And clean up neatly]
Not bringing essentials is a big problem.
You two are fine.
I've still got to buy underwear...
- Just wear mine.
- And for a toothbrush...
- How would I wear that?
- I already washed it.
Come on.
Just buy one and keep washing and reusing it.
I need a razor and a toothbrush too...
You're gonna be expensive...
Just use the disposable ones at the motel.
- Use them.
- Ah...
- Yeah, just use them.
- I don't even have a charger.
- We don't need one, we don't even have phones.
- Oh, right. No phones.
Oh yeah. Then we don't need chargers.
Why did I even bring this without a phone?
[Peekaboo]
It's heavy, so just for a sec...
[Just a heavy, useless burden to come]
Do you have a mirror?
- Want one?
- Really?
- It's a cushion compact.
- Oh.
- Wait, I'll wipe it...
- Got any tissues? Nose ones?
- Wait a second.
- Just one for my nose.
No, this is the only one I've got.
- What's going on right now?
- A runny nose!
Just use the toilet paper over there.
There's no tissue.
Just use the bathroom tissue from now on.
We're out.
The train's here!
Oh, let's go.
- Four minutes left.
- Yeah.
Let's go!
[Heading to the train]
Hello! Please watch "Number One."
The movie "Number One."
["Number One" even on the platform]
It's a movie called "Number One."
[Boarding Car No. 13]
The movie "Number One..."
[Finally departing for the first destination]
[Fidgeting]
[The two actors adjusting the angle themselves]
That's the one.
It works, done.
[Yumi's cam ON]
- Huh? This way or that way?
- This way.
- This way?
- Yeah.
Is backward seating okay for you?
We can switch if it's uncomfortable.
[Now heading south]
Give me the cam.
[Camera duty switch for a moment]
Huh? You pressed it, right?
This feels like one of those...
You know, people usually die
filming stuff like this... in accidents.
In "Train to Busan," they're filming like this
before zombies appear.
So your last smiling face ends up on camera.
Hey, how fun is this going to be?
- I'm actually so excited.
- Yeah, right.
[S#1. A brief moment of happiness]
Next scene.
Zombies.
[S#2. Zombie appearance]
The camera falls, glitching on the ground.
[Director Yumi's experimental shot]
And there's a scream inside.
Yumi and I are not supposed
to ride the KTX together.
Zombies show up.
[Yumi and Woo Shik both starred
in the KTX-set film "Train to Busan"]
Right, right.
- Stay still for a second.
- The view outside...
[The view of Woo Shik]
Done!
[Director Yumi is satisfied]
[Woo Shik begins his turn as well]
[Peace sign]
[Intense gaze]
[S#3. Back to a happy moment]
And after this,
in the next scene...
[S#4. Zombies appear again]
Aah! Aah!
[They're reenacting "Train to Busan"]
You're exactly the same.
- What do you mean?
- Your face...
it's just like back then.
[No difference from "Train to Busan,"
10 years ago]
[With no phones, there's nothing to do]
[Rummaging]
[Ta-da]
- Jung Yumi's "What's in My Bag."
- Oh, let me have one.
Let's begin. No, we need to save it.
I have lenses.
- I almost bought lenses.
- I have sunscreen, too.
Oh, thank goodness!
- I have tone-up cream.
- Nice!
- Got it at the makeup shop earlier.
Whoa!
- I'll use some too.
- Yay, nice!
Yay... oh!
- Disposable skincare set.
- Nice!
I brought it back from my trip
and just kept it.
Whoa!
[Fully absorbed in self-content]
Awesome!
Good thing Seo Jun brought everything.
- I'm the only one using it though.
- What?
[So childish]
Writer, I...
I'll take this scarf off for a second.
It's actually clothes!
It's clothes, it's clothes!
[She was wearing a T-shirt like a scarf...]
This is clothing, this is actually clothes!
Woo Shik can wear that.
Can I use that as underwear?
[Yumi can't hear anything now]
That habit comes in handy now.
I usually just wear
this cotton T-shirt like a scarf.
Oh, this could be pajamas!
- Nice.
- Yay!
[Woo Shik's pick: the KTX travel guidebook]
Wow, where is this?
- Namwon, Jeonbuk.
- Jirisan Mountain, further south...
Jirisan Mountain? That sounds nice too.
Wanna go to Namwon?
I know someone who has a house there.
Can I stay there too?
- He owns the entire house.
- Yeah?
So this is Namwon here?
He keeps telling me to go to Namwon with him.
- Let's go! Let's go!
- Here...
Is using a connection okay?
Then I'll call him later
when we get a phone chance.
But does he actually live there?
- He just manages it.
- Let's go, let's go!
I'm shy... might not be able to talk to him.
Then you can sleep somewhere else.
- I'm going there.
- Let's go together.
- Namwon sounds good.
- Let's go to Namwon.
- Let me see.
At the foot of Jirisan Mountain.
So this is the plan?
Today, Daegu.
Then go from here to Namwon.
- And from Namwon...
- We'll have to take a bus.
From Namwon...
Let's plan to go to Namwon
and try contacting him first.
- Let's go with Namwon for now.
- Yeah.
- How much do we have left?
- We've got 150,000 won left in total...
but let's exclude the coins.
- 150,000...
- 151,000 won.
151,000 won.
It'll be hard to cover lodging with this.
Exactly.
Like, if it's a rural guesthouse kind of place,
even just a room and a living room...
But Dongdaegu is basically downtown,
so I wonder if places like that
even exist there.
And we can't even look it up without phones.
Ah, underwear...
[Woo Shik is more worried
about underwear than lodging]
Since Dongdaegu is downtown,
there might be something like that.
Places near the station
might actually be cheap.
- That could be true.
- Let's check it out.
There could be cheap places.
- We'll have to walk around and check.
- Yeah.
- Should we walk around near the station?
[They decide to check places
near the station first]
Woo Shik, I don't think
we'll get to eat mungtigi today.
Yeah, probably not.
- It's expensive.
- No way we can afford it.
At this rate, we'll probably just end up
at some cheap gimbap place in Daegu.
[A future that somehow feels
completely predictable]
If we can even afford that...
But when you travel,
eating good food is the best part.
And we're kind of missing that.
Alright, let's decide this.
Look, we have three things to spend money on.
Transport, accommodation, and food.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Which one do you think is the most important?
- Wait, ask again.
- What's more important, sleep?
- Or eating good food?
- Food!
Food?
[Thinking...]
- For me, sleep.
- Sleep?
Then you and I are really different.
So you'd eat cheap food,
but still want to sleep somewhere nice.
Not necessarily a good place.
- I know.
- Not like a fancy place, I just mean...
- Just somewhere to sleep?
- Yeah.
I want to eat something good too.
So what's your priority?
I choose... food.
Me too.
Same, food.
[Laughing]
Is that really true?
You're not going to grant my wish anyway.
- No, no.
- We will.
You're 44, so we should listen to you.
Oh right, you're "Po-po (44)."
Right, you're the oldest here.
You're in your forties.
"Po-po". Big sis "Po-po."
- Ah, my stomach...
- Who drank this?
- He drank it all.
- I never even opened it.
Is it leaking or something?
[Actually, Woo Shik...]
I'm tired.
[Right after getting on the train,
he gulps once]
I don't think we'll find a guesthouse.
[He gulps even when Seo Jun is worried]
Say you'll drink first, then drink.
Oh right, we were sharing this.
I didn't drink from it directly.
[He actually drank from it]
[Checking remaining water]
[Awkward]
[In the end, the last sip goes to Woo Shik...]
It's 1,000 won per bottle.
[It was basically Woo Shik's water]
What the heck?
- Oh my.
- What is it?
[What unfolds before their eyes right now...]
Whoa...
Wow, where are we?
Hey, isn't this Gumi?
[An unexpected heavy snowfall]
This is more beautiful than midwinter.
- It's snowing right now.
- Yeah, it's snowing.
It's snowing...
Oh my, the mountains are beautiful.
Wow, snow!
Is this real?
[Snow they encountered at the end of February]
Wow...
We're not going north, right?
Did we get on the wrong train?
[As they get closer to Daegu]
[The snowstorm gets stronger]
We've arrived. This is Dongdaegu.
You've got a hat, right?
- In March...
- Whoa, what... it's snowing?
[Not the Daegu they knew]
[They arrived in Daegu,
strangely blanketed in white snow]
Oh, Daegu Station. It's been a while.
- It's really snowing a lot.
- Oh my, oh my.
Oh my.
- Does it usually snow like this here?
- Right?
- Oh, are you from Daegu?
- Yes.
Does it usually snow this much in Daegu?
- No.
- Right?
- It's my first time.
- She is pretty friendly.
It's been years.
- Years?
- Yes.
- Oh my!
- Wow...
- Do you know her?
- No.
- She's from Daegu.
- Oh.
You said it's been a long time
since it snowed like this in Daegu, right?
- Yes.
- Oh my, what do we do?
Wow...
- Wow!
- Wow, wow, wow!
[Finally, time to step out into the world!]
It's kind of...
- What should we do?
- Hey...
What is this?
[What unfolds before their eyes...]
- What is this?
- Oh my.
[Huge snowstorm]
Oh my, oh my.
[Facing it head-on]
- Use this together.
- It's okay, we're fine.
Do you happen to know any cheap places
to stay around here?
- Cheap lodging?
- Yes.
- They're all cheap around here.
- She says they're all cheap.
They're all cheap. Let's go.
I'm... I'm okay, thank you!
Thank you!
Oh, thank you!
- We're good, really.
- Okay, okay.
- Thank you!
- She says they're all cheap.
So... how do we find a place to stay?
City tour... wait.
[They want to look it up,
but they don't have their phones...]
- First of all...
- Should we go to the info desk?
Yeah, we should go to the info desk.
- Am I dreaming since this morning?
- There it is, there it is.
- "Tourist information desk."
- Oh, there it is!
Wow!
[Found the Dongdaegu
Tourist Information Center]
Hey...
This is totally unexpected.
What is this?
What is happening?
My clothes are going to get soaked.
[Of all days, it had to snow today]
Aah!
Should we go in?
[Hesitating at the entrance...]
Okay.
[Let's go]
Oh, it's warm inside.
Hello!
- Hello,
- We... in Daegu...
We're trying to find a place to stay.
- Relatively cheap...
- Oh, I see a hotel here.
Not just relatively cheap,
we're looking for somewhere really affordable.
[Seo Jun stepped up bravely]
Right.
There are several
lodging options in this area.
We've gathered some of the cheaper options.
Hey, should we just go to a jjimjilbang?
A jjimjilbang would be super cheap.
That's in the downtown area, around Banwoldang.
Or there's a place called "Mu*** Inn"
that includes breakfast.
Breakfast is a luxury for us.
They provide free meals.
Meals are included.
- Oh?
- Oh!
That sounds pretty good.
It's right behind there.
- Oh really?
- Oh, there it is!
- There it is!
- Sorry!
- Mu*** Inn.
- There it is!
- Let's go there now.
- Where?
- Right in front of us here.
- There's a big screen there.
Oh, there? Yeah, I see it.
- Let's go!
- Let's go check it out! We're going there.
- But for one room...
- Thank you!
- Thank you.
- Thank you, thank you!
If you're going there,
you can take the escalator down.
- Oh, yes.
- Go down and keep walking to the left.
- That's awesome.
- Oh, like that?
Thank you.
- Happy Lunar New Year!
- Be careful.
- My pants...
- Watch your step, it's slippery.
You be careful too.
Oh, be careful!
Wow, I'm completely soaked.
It's freezing.
Aah!
- Careful!
- Hey, let's stick together.
[Camaraderie blooming in the midst of crisis]
- But...
- Yeah.
- It's not like this was planned or anything.
The accommodation too.
- How did we end up on our way there?
- Exactly.
But it feels like the accommodation
is over 60,000 won per room.
Opening video...
No, we were trying to start off cool
in our opening outfits...
[Ended up looking like snowmen...]
But at least the footage actually
looks pretty good though?
- Right.
- Who knew it would snow in Daegu?
[Ignorance is a sin]
Wow.
Wow, my socks are completely soaked.
We need to buy socks too.
[Arrived at Mu*** Inn]
Please check first,
and if it's okay, we'll come in.
- Is filming allowed here?
- Yes.
Hello.
[Will they be able to find accommodation
in one shot?]
This place is nice though.
It has a good vibe.
[Filming permission secured for now]
I'm nervous.
May I have your name?
Oh, we didn't make a reservation...
- We're fully booked.
- Oh, really?
Ah...
- That's a bust.
- Did you bring it?
Excuse me, are there any inns nearby?
- There's a motel right next door...
- Okay.
but I'm not sure
about the price or availability.
- Okay...
- Okay, thank you!
Should we try next door?
I thought things were finally going our way.
[Moving to the next option]
Oh, it's right next door.
[Second walk-in attempt]
Oh, here's an inn...
Hello.
- Do you have any rooms available?
- Yes!
- You do?
- Yes.
[Finally found an available room]
- We should ask that.
- Oh, by the way, we're currently filming...
- Is it okay if we film here?
- What kind of filming is this?
We're from tvN's "Let's Travel Without Money,"
and we're supposed to travel without money.
- Travel without money?
- Yes.
- Per day...
- We have to keep it cheap.
[For now, they go all in on acting pitiful]
One moment, please...
Wait, aren't you Park Seo Jun?
- That's right.
- Yes, that's right.
How have you been?
[They even start using flirting tactics]
Daegu is like my second hometown.
But I'm not exactly sure
what kind of filming this is.
- Oh, it's just like this.
- This is all we do.
- Rooms, two rooms.
- Two rooms.
- Yes.
- There's also me.
- I'm...
- Ah, Yumi?
- Yes.
- I need a separate room.
- Say hello quickly.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
The thing is,
they will share one room, and I...
- Oh, separately?
- Yes.
Two share one, and one alone.
But the most important thing is the price...
How much is the room?
We don't have much money, so...
Well, the standard room is 60,000 won each.
60,000 won each? Okay...
- 60,000 won and 50,000 won?
- Pardon?
60,000 won, 50,000 won!
Oh, 60,000 won and 50,000 won?
- 60,000 won!
- No, 60,000 won.
60,000 won and 50,000 won!
No, since it's you two, 60,000 won,
and mine is 50,000 won.
Huh? Is that right?
- Did I hear that wrong?
- That's what she said...
- No, it's 60,000 won each.
- 60,000 won, 60,000 won.
- Maybe I can at least knock off 10,000 won...
- At least try saying...
- That won't work. That's not allowed.
- No...
- Well, I'm just an employee, so...
- Okay.
- I'll ask the owner.
- Please just ask once.
Alright, then feel free to ask...
- Sorry.
- Yeah.
I thought it was 60,000 won and 50,000 won.
If it's 60,000 won each, that's 120,000 won,
then we'd have 30,000 won left.
We could each get a bowl
of gukbap at the market.
I want to have codfish soup too...
But getting to the market is also a problem.
- Ah, yes, yes. Sir.
- Oh, thank you!
Did we reach a dramatic agreement?
[Owner's approval granted]
So earlier, she said 60,000 won and 50,000 won?
60,000 won each.
Oh! Could I get your autograph?
Oh dear, I'd do an autograph
for 40,000 won but...
Our autograph fee is usually 40,000 won.
Right.
Sometimes it's even more expensive.
Yeah.
We do sell them, but... yeah.
Here...
- Thank you!
- No problem.
Oh right, ma'am.
Are there any...
nearby markets around here?
There's Pyeonghwa Market's
chicken gizzards alley!
- Chicken gizzards alley?
It's quite famous.
We don't have phones, so we can't look it up...
Do the rooms have computers?
- Yes, they do.
- Oh!
Let's search for it.
We'll greet you again later, thank you!
- Can we go to our rooms now?
- This place is really nice!
Thank you!
- Let's go up first.
- Thank you.
This place is really good!
[Right after the trio secured their lodging...]
Sir!
[The staff also booked the same floor]
Are there more rooms on the 5th floor?
[Cast & crew successfully
secured their first walk-in stay]
Wow!
- Yours is 507.
- Yeah, I'll go check your room first.
Oh, water! Water!
- Water?
- Lots of water!
- 500...
- Room 507!
507 comes first. Let's check here.
Is this your room? Oh, it's mine.
[Checking Yumi's room first]
- Oh, nice, nice!
- Let me put my bag down.
Wow, my room is awesome!
Shall we check room 503?
[Now it's time to check
Seo Jun and Woo Shik's room]
Oh, hey!
This is great!
- Oh!
- Nice!
It's like an internet cafe!
- Hey, what is this?
- We got a good room.
- What a good room!
- This is so nice!
[Point 1: two computers]
[Point 2: spacious and clean]
[Point 3: free water, coffee,
cereal, and toast]
[Point 4: near Dongdaegu Station]
[Overall score: five stars]
I feel like we used up
all our luck at the start.
["We've used up way too much luck
on this place." - Actress Jung Yumi]
I even thought about that.
We got lucky today and ended up
staying somewhere this nice.
If it's like a guesthouse,
two rooms wouldn't even be available.
In that case, even just a room
and a living room...
that would probably be enough for us to stay.
But somehow, I feel like
we'll keep staying at nice places...
[Yumi's confidence has skyrocketed]
- Wow, I'm so relieved.
- This is so nice.
This is great.
- Alright, let's search first.
- Wait, let's sit for a bit first.
- This is amazing.
- Wow, this is awesome.
"Dongdaegu Station food spots!"
"Nearby good restaurants."
Try searching "good restaurants." Nearby spots.
We can just go nearby, right?
But we can't really go to nice restaurants...
we only have 30,000 won.
Hey, we said we'd go to the market.
- Pyeonghwa Market... where was that?
- But...
- Pyeonghwa Market. Chicken gizzards alley.
- It's here.
So it's from here to here.
- We can walk there, right?
- Yeah.
- It's close.
- Then, the market... what time is it now?
But everything here is...
basically chicken gizzards.
Yeah, that's what this place is famous for.
[About 10 minutes later]
- We should go to an old local spot.
- Yeah, a proper old restaurant.
- There's beef gukbap for 4,500 won.
- Where?
At Pyeonghwa Market,
there are still places selling
- beef gukbap for 5,000 won...
- Oh.
You even get change back
- from a 5,000 won bill...
- Wow!
- This looks good.
It's perfect for a hangover...
really hits the spot.
The menu's diverse too, so I ordered
tteokbokki, sundae, and dakgangjeong.
Especially the dakgangjeong...
Oh, this place looks good.
- Okay, let's go to "Jang*** Mukbang."
- "Jang*** Mukbang."
- Yumi, we looked it up.
- Yeah.
- There's a place called "Jang*** Mukbang."
- Let's go.
- Beef gukbap is 4,500 won.
- They have ramyeon too.
Let's go. Let's eat everything, even ramyeon.
Let's go!
[Time to dive back into a world
without the internet]
- Oh my gosh!
- Wow, it's snowing more!
- Hey, put your hat on.
- Okay.
[To make matters worse...]
[The snowstorm gets stronger]
[Snow is falling so heavily
it's hard to see ahead...]
[Can they really find their way
without phones?]
- We need to go that way.
- Yeah.
[Departure]
- That's an uphill slope, Seo Jun.
- That's a steep climb.
Let's go this way.
Hey, Dubai chewy cookie!
I'm more mint chocolate though...
That's some Dubai chewy cookie outfit.
Because of the brown...
[Dubai chewy cookie #1
pulls out the camcorder again]
Oh, oh... Where's Woo Shik?
I thought Woo Shik was over there.
[A chaotic move through the snowstorm]
- But it is really cold.
- Right? Your legs must be freezing.
Pa** Hospital!
Oh, there it is.
They said to turn left there.
Crunch.
I never thought we'd end up
walking on snow here...
What is going on right now?
[Info: Filming was on Feb 24,
spring weather until the day before]
This scene is hilarious.
I mean...
Oh no, our shoes are getting soaked.
- These are our only shoes.
- Yeah.
[Obvious]
[Yumi drained again]
Be careful.
Let's stick together.
- Huh?
- Stay close, it's slippery.
- Constantly...
- If one person slips, we're all...
[Laughing]
- we're all going down together.
- Yeah, all of us.
I can't feel my toes.
Me too, my toes...
Does it usually snow like this in Daegu?
- No way, right?
- This is insane...
- My feet are sinking in!
- This is crazy.
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Hey!
Hey, don't! If you fall, we're all in trouble.
I thought...
this was going to be a cool, stylish trip.
Me too...
It's all slushy.
- "The god of gukbap."
- Where is it?
Wow, that looks seriously delicious.
Look at that.
- Where?
- Here, the picture.
Wow.
[They swallow their saliva,
eyeing the food they can't have...]
But going to the market was a good idea.
Yeah.
I mean, if it's only 4,500 won,
we've gotta try it.
- Oh, it was 4,500 won?
- Yeah.
Feels like we're almost there.
- Oh, is it here?
- Oh!
No, wait. They said to turn
when we see the ENT clinic.
It's the entrance, the entrance!
- This is chicken gizzards alley, Woo Shik.
- Let's go in here.
[Finally entering Pyeonghwa Market]
Chicken gizzards alley.
Where exactly are we going?
Yumi, come this way.
It's not closed, right?
If not, we can just go somewhere like this.
Wow!
Oh, watch your step!
- Wow, this place is... kind of a mess.
- Watch your step.
Oh, no!
[Through an unbelievably muddy path]
Let's turn this way!
- Huh?
- Left.
Where is it?
[About 15 minutes into walking...]
- Here it is!
- Here it is! This is it!
[Finally found a restaurant]
Oh!
[Target spotted]
- Hello?
Would it be okay if we just film while eating?
Sure.
- Is that okay?
- Oh, yes.
Let's go, let's go in.
[Owner: But... who are you?]
"Youn's Kitchen!"
[Youn's Kitchen? / Actress]
- Hello.
- Sit here.
- Yeah.
- Whoa!
- Hello.
What are you eating?
- What's good here?
- Tteokbokki and sundae.
- Yeah.
They said the gukbap here is cheap...
The gukbap is really good.
- Do you come here often?
- Yes.
- Wow.
- Beef gukbap?
I guess we could eat a lot here.
Hey, didn't that fried squid
look really good earlier?
Yeah, everything looks good.
[Rising anticipation over the menu lineup]
Let's start with two beef gukbaps...
- Two?
- Yeah.
Two beef gukbaps,
and one fried dish.
- The sundae liver looks good.
- Ah, I want tteokbokki too... and sundae.
Let's just get the full set,
tteokbokki, fried dish, and sundae.
- That combo is 10,000 won.
- Oh.
- Then that's 20,000 total.
- And...
- How much do we have left?
- 11,000 won left.
- Then we should get some soju too.
- Let's get one.
Shall we just order that for now?
Excuse me.
Two beef gukbaps, one tteokbokki, fried dish,
a sundae combo, and one soju.
[Order complete]
It's really cheap though.
How did you even find this place?
- Well... we just searched online.
- We just searched online.
- So you just looked for cheap places?
- A good value...
- A good value spot.
- A good value spot?
Oh!
- Wow!
- But we're bad with spicy food.
- I'm not.
- Oh, really?
[Director Choi prepares insert shot]
- Wow!
- This plus the fried dish is 10,000 won.
- Let's eat.
- Try it!
- Thank you for the meal.
Thank you for the meal.
It looks spicy.
[The "this is really good" frown
immediately appears]
Is it?
It's good!
Yum, it's delicious!
Wow, I was so hungry,
so I was even using my chopsticks like this.
[Jeez...]
[The fried dishes arrive shortly after]
[Immediately grabbing a piece]
[Dipping it deep into the tteokbokki sauce]
[Yum]
- Oh, this is good. The fried chili.
- Is it good?
Should we drink the soju now?
Do we have to go get it ourselves?
[The quick-to-act youngest immediately gets up]
Excuse me.
About the soju we ordered earlier...
should we just grab it ourselves?
Oh, I'll bring it right away...
Alright, let's drink Chamiseul.
[Daegu's local soju, "Chamiseul"]
"A fresh, clean morning,
with such wonderful people."
- That's totally about us.
- Right.
[Self-praise]
Two here, please.
[Gyeongsang-style beef gukbap
with a rich, spicy broth]
Wow, this is 5,000 won?
- Just a little over 5,000...
- Wow, this is 5,000 won. 5,000!
[Incredible value for money]
Yes, thank you!
- I haven't used this.
- Yeah, just give me a little, really.
- That's enough, that's enough.
- Is this enough?
I only want a little radish.
- I mistook that for radish.
- It's too much, really. That's enough.
Did you get some meat?
It's fine, it's fine.
[Aah, yum!]
[It is so good that it makes you
open the lid on your own...]
This is so good!
[Ladies first]
[No, you go first]
- You're 44, so you should go first.
- We're just having soju, why bring up age?
Po-po, you go first.
Don't say that.
It's hot.
For a safe...
and exciting journey.
- Cheers!
Wow!
[Then everyone takes a spoonful of broth]
The underwear, and...
- Wow!
- And the toothbrush and all that...
- Oh, sir, we're just...
- No, it's okay, it's okay.
- We're just...
- It's okay, it's okay.
Oh, my...
[Simple, homey gimbap glistening with oil]
Thanks to PD Na Young Seok...
- Oh...
- Oh!
I'm not very familiar with...
- Wow.
- Wow...
younger people.
I watched "2 Days & 1 Night" a lot.
- Wow...
- Wow!
[Jealous...]
Just turn the camera that way.
Make it last.
- Wow...
- Wow!
- Thank you for the meal!
- Younger folks...
- I know you're big stars, but...
- Thank you!
- Thank you for the meal!
- Honestly, I don't really know.
[Production team: ha ha ha]
[Thanks to you, we get to enjoy this gimbap]
- Wow.
- Looks delicious!
- It's just plain gimbap, but it's good.
- Right.
- The rice is nice and sticky.
- Yeah.
Today...
we really picked the right place today.
[Hurry and eat up]
Go ahead, eat.
We're leaving right after we eat,
so hurry up and eat.
[Heart flutter]
We won't wait.
Can I just eat it?
[All staff put their cameras down]
[As if bound by fate,
they start eating together]
These days, something for 5,000 won...
Look at him.
[Fidgeting...]
[A real top star caught eating]
[Yum...]
[Since everyone's eating well, cheers]
It's really...
[A deep sigh from the core]
[A finishing sip of broth is a must]
This is good.
- Should we order just one more bottle?
- Let's get one more.
- Sir, we'll grab another bottle of soju.
- I'm curious what tomorrow's benefit will be.
- I'll get it for you.
- Okay.
[Now they're down to just 4,750 won]
Yeah.
Thank you. It's so delicious.
Tomorrow morning,
you'll get a fresh allowance anyway.
And there will probably be
your first benefit draw.
- In the morning?
- Yes.
- Oh.
- Not sure what it'll be, but in the morning...
- You're not going to take things away, right?
- No, nothing like that.
You'll be getting a new allowance,
so it'll just be added to what you have today.
Oh, I need to buy some underwear.
Seo Jun, how many did you bring?
I don't know, I need to check.
When I went to the US,
they had a washing machine there.
So I washed everything
and brought it back as is.
Oh, so they're not new, huh?
What, you expect brand new ones?
- What color are they?
- We'll buy you some tomorrow.
Various colors.
Honestly, yesterday...
- I got a perm yesterday.
- Right.
So the stylist told me, today and tomorrow...
- Not to wash your hair?
- She told me not to wash until I come back.
So I didn't shower.
Which means my underwear right now is...
[Shocking confession]
This is annoying...
[So ridiculous... can't help but laugh]
Until tomorrow...
- Until tomorrow...
- Hey, stop it!
That's a bit much for me.
[Same underwear since yesterday]
That's... because you didn't shower.
- Yeah.
- You didn't change?
Hey, you should change it!
- Why would I change if I didn't shower?
- That's...
that's totally different!
Anyway, the important thing is
I need a fresh pair right now.
Just wear his for today.
Just for today. Let's just buy it tomorrow...
- when we have money.
- Ugh, I don't want to hear this.
Do you have black ones?
Hey, how much are the ones
at convenience stores? That's...
I can't look it up right now, so I don't know.
- Stop by one on the way.
- Yeah, I'll check one.
How much do we have left?
- 4... 4,750 won.
- Nice!
- You handle it with this.
But what if the underwear costs
exactly 5,000 won?
Then I'll have to do a talent show right there.
[Underwear more precious than human dignity]
- You can't bargain there.
- Huh?
You can't haggle.
Then I'll just busk on the street,
what else can I do?
Shall we go?
- Let's go!
- This is 3,500 won.
- You guys can have the rest.
- No, let's take it with us.
- Take it with us?
- They said to take it.
- This...
[Carefully saving the leftover soju]
Let's take it.
We'd like to pay, please.
- It's 88,000 won.
- What? No, just ours, please.
- Just the three of us.
- Oh, just this table?
- Yes.
- Oh, we can't pay for them.
Oh, dear.
- We were almost in trouble.
- Sorry.
- 27,000 won, yes that's right.
- 27,000 won, right.
- Yes, that's correct.
- Of course, it is.
Thank you!
Can we pack up the leftovers?
Hang on, I'll pack it so you can eat it later.
Just give us a plastic bag,
then we'll pack it ourselves.
- You never know, we might want it later.
- Alright.
- Let's go!
- Goodbye.
- Thank you!
- We enjoyed the meal!
Goodbye.
Was there a convenience store on the way?
If we go this way, I think there might be.
- Alright.
- Yeah, let's go this way.
Hey, there's a Thai massage place...
- go get a few from there.
- A few of what?
Oh, underwear?
- When you get a massage...
- You know, those clothes you change into.
[The journey has started
for Woo Shik's underwear]
Wait, what?
Excuse me, do you have underwear here?
No underwear?
Don't they sell underwear at saunas?
You don't sell men's underwear here, right?
Oh?
[They go anywhere for Woo Shik's underwear]
I feel like they would sell...
- But...
- Yeah.
But if it's like 7,000 won...
if we hadn't had that extra soju...
[Why is it that bad feelings are never wrong?]
Hey, I don't think this will work.
[The shocking price of underwear
leaves them speechless]
[XXXX won]
Come on, at least for underwear,
they should help us out a bit.
At this rate, I'm gonna get sick.
[The beginning of misfortune
caused by underwear, COMING SOON]
[Next week]
Now, there are benefits inside these pockets.
You'll draw them randomly.
- No way.
- Come on, no way.
[Only the most useful items,
carefully selected]
Oh...
I need this the most right now!
There are exactly three.
You can only choose one.
Please!
[Thrilling]
[What will be the result of
the first benefit draw?]
- Seo Jun, Yumi!
- Yes?
Where are we heading now?
- Namwon!
Namwon!
- Oh, is this Ojakgyo Bridge?
- Yeah.
It looks really cute.
- Oh, I like it.
- Yeah, it's great.
Hey, places like this usually have great food.
- Hungry? Let's go!
- Let's go.
Shall we come back here tonight?
It's so delicious!
[Strangers who met by chance]
[Getting swept up in the music]
- Hey, there's a swing over there.
- What?
[Getting lost in childlike wonder]
Let's go!
[As they fully enjoy Namwon and have fun]
[Collapse]
Ugh...
Why is this so exhausting?
Is it because of our age?
[But there's still one big problem left]
- But I don't think there's any lodging.
- There aren't any...
- He picked up!
- Hey!
I'll ask quickly,
- can we rent your house in Namwon?
- Yeah.
- Address, address...
- Yeah, send me the address.
- Do we just go straight down now?
- Yeah.
Okay!
By the way, Seo Jun,
this is the right way, right?
Did we really walk this far earlier?
- Seo Jun, this is right, huh?
- Feels like we're going somewhere weird.
Why is the road like this?
Huh? What? This is a dead end.
[Will they be able to get to the house safely?]