=Stop! Young Castellan=
=Episode 14=
(Wufengzhai)
(Funeral)
Young Castellan.
You're back.
Condolences, Young Castellan.
(Tablet of the Benevolent Father)
My father...
Young Castellan.
You're finally back.
(Funeral)
Young Castellan.
Here.
Father...
(Funeral)
(Chatelain's Mansion: Guest Room)
Stop!
Who are you?
I've come to deliver food.
Enter.
Put it down and get out quickly.
Song...
Shh.
How are you?
Come here.
You've suffered.
It just looks intimidating.
It's nothing serious.
Just to be safe,
eat this.
Deliverer guy! Hurry up!
Alright. I'll be right out.
Rest and recover.
Wait for us.
You should be careful.
Take care.
Here I am.
Young Castellan,
our men are waiting for you.
Uncle Chen,
I'm back too late.
I couldn't save my father in time.
I'm an unfilial daughter.
Young Castellan,
you must pull yourself together.
Let's go.
Greetings, Castellan.
Song Lian...
I don't have a father anymore.
I still arrived too late...
Wu Baobao,
you did your best.
There's nothing wrong with that.
The guards at Qin's imprisonment
are not very tight.
We have a chance to rescue him.
Let's go now then.
Get some rest first.
We'll talk about it tomorrow.
Lie down now.
Here.
Slowly.
Don't worry,
I'll always protect you.
Sleep early.
The intelligence has been verified.
Really?
Chatelain, you won't worry anymore
if we get the descendant
of the witch physician.
Wonderful.
Have you thought
of a way to capture him?
Once a person has a weakness,
they become vulnerable.
If we capture Wu Baobao,
he'll surely surrender willingly.
Okay.
Using Qin Yuntian as bait,
we'll wait for them
to fall into our trap.
You're wise!
They must think
we'll rescue him at night,
but people are most vulnerable
in the early morning.
I feel like something's not right.
What's wrong?
I just think
it's too quiet.
Who cares? Success or death, we'll see.
Don't move.
I'll go rescue him.
You provide backup.
Why are you pulling me?
You promised to listen to me later.
Alright then.
Be careful.