=Stop! Young Castellan=
=Episode 6=
(Brewmaster's Abode)
Good liquor!
You could have dodged it easily.
Hey, sir!
If you don't sell,
why are you splashing us?
You're being persistent
and refusing to leave.
Sir,
we truly want this liquor.
What are your requirements?
I will
do whatever it takes.
Just don't let me see you again.
Wait a second!
Lady Wu!
Lady Wu,
are you okay?
(I'm fine.)
(It's up to you now.)
Lady Wu is weak,
and she fainted because of you.
I'm afraid we can't leave now.
We may have to trouble you
and stay here tonight.
Are you trying to scam me?
Alright, just for tonight.
Get out of here early tomorrow.
Thank you.
And
don't go near the main house
and disturb my wife.
Stop pretending.
Wake up.
Lady Wu seems to be asleep.
Has she been tired lately?
Let me carry her inside.
I will carry her.
Bamboo Leaf Green.
Luofu Spring.
Dukang.
This one is...
This is called Suhexiang.
A medicinal liquor from the palace.
How do you...
Shh.
You're just a wandering physician,
so how do you know
this is from the palace?
Well,
I've tasted once.
Back in the day,
I happened to save His Majesty
who was traveling incognito.
You guys...
What are you doing?
Let me explain.
She tried to steal the liquor.
Lady Wu...
No way.
We should take it openly,
not steal it.
Well,
come with me and confess to the old man.
We'll ask for the liquor with sincerity.
Are you insane?
What do you want me to confess?
I'm sorry.
Is this your sincerity?
Taking without asking is stealing!
Are you bandits?
Sir, I'm sorry.
Me too.
I'm used to being a bandit.
Now I realize my mistake.
Yes.
You...
All of you
get out of here!
I can't have you here.
Just leave now!
Sir, what's wrong?
Hey!
Sir!
Are you okay?
Sir, wake up!
He has Qi and blood deficiency,
and weak spleen and stomach.
Qin,
prepare
this medicine and boil it.
Okay.
I'll do it right away.
Take care of him.
Help him sit up.
During the day,
he said not to disturb his wife.
His wife...
(Memorial Spirit Tablet)
Young Castellan,
what are you thinking about here?
I've never known who my mother is.
I don't know what she looks like.
Nor do I know...
If she's alive or dead.
Isn't it amazing?
When I was young,
I thought I was born by my father.
Father,
they say I was born by my mother.
They're lying.
I was clearly born by you alone.
That's right.
Alright, stop crying.
Bao,
do you want a mother?
I'm content with just my father.
I'll take care of you too in the future.
Silly girl.
Not just my father,
no one in the village
has ever mentioned my mother.
I guess,
she must have done
something wrong to my father
and ran away.
So I never mention her too.
This bracelet is made of agarwood.
Although it can't replace the bracelet
your mother left you,
it can still calm the mind
and promote sleep.
When did you make this?
Lian, you're being overly
kind for no reason.
Aren't you into me?
I...
No...
How could I be?
You're thinking too much.
Your eyes are dark and puffy.
So I have good intentions.
You're just thinking of nonsense.
Why is there a red string tied to it?
I noticed
you seem to like red a lot.
Red strings ward off evil.
Perfect for you, Young Castellan.
Nice craftsmanship.
It fits perfectly.
I'm sleepy.
I'm going to sleep.
Lady Wu,
Young Master Qin and Young Master Song,
which one do you like better?
What?