=Stop! Young Castellan=
=Episode 3=
Cut the crap!
If you want to kill, then come.
Don't move.
Please forgive me, Chatelain.
I will definitely capture that thief
and bring them to justice.
Go ahead.
Don't keep me waiting too long.
(What kind of Ace Constable are you?)
(Unable to catch even a mere woman?)
(I am the one Chatelain truly needs.)
Zicheng.
Chatelain,
what exactly was stolen from the mansion
that requires such a massive effort?
It's just an ordinary bronze mirror.
Then why...
Young Castellan Wu seems
very interested in my family.
As I haven't found the descendant
of the witch physician yet,
I don't want her to complicate things.
She seems quite obsessed with Wuying.
You might use that to your advantage.
She's just a novice girl after all.
It's that wandering physician before
who might be useful.
Alright.
I'll send someone to investigate.
You should rest and recover
from your injuries.
Here.
Sit down.
How are you feeling?
Why did you come to rescue me?
I told someone to lock you up.
Oh...
Well...
That person didn't lock the door.
Fortunately, he didn't lock the door,
so I could rescue you.
Come on.
Drink some water.
You're weak,
so rest for a while first.
Drink it.
Why am I so sleepy?
If you're sleepy, just sleep.
You'll feel better when you wake up.
Young Castellan?
(How dare you drink
a physician's water?)
(See if you dare bully me again.)
Where did you put it?
(Is this woman a hamster?)
(Hoarding all these useless things.)
The bronze mirror!
You are indeed here for the Wuying.
Speak!
What exactly do you want?
(Such a formidable constitution.)
(Not even afraid of my potions.)
Well,
I understand Wuying better.
So I'm here to help you.
After all,
even with Wu Ying,
you need a physician to refine it.
But you keep wanting to lock me up.
It's
a last resort.
I'll see how you're going
to help me find the treasure.
If you're useless or lying to me,
I can crush you with just one finger.
Yes.
I'll do whatever you say,
Young Castellan.
But
you went through so much trouble
to find clues from Madam Rou,
only to find an ordinary bronze mirror.
It should be useless, right?
Impossible.
For this bronze mirror,
Ouyang Jin sent many people
to capture me.
There must be a mystery.
You're right.
I was just saying that.
Whatever you say
is right.
Song Lian, look!
What kind of nonsense symbols are these?
Only a ghost can understand, right?
I know someone who can decipher it.
But we need to go to a place.
Where?
Let's go.
Where are you taking me?
You'll know when we get there.
What kind of mysterious place is this?
We're here.
What?
What kind of creepy place is this?
Welcome to
the "Dark Market",
where everything you desire
can be found.
Why are they all staring at me?
Try your luck with the rings!
Treasures and curiosities!
Ten taels of silver for one try!
Read horoscopes and fortune-telling
about past and present lives.
Don't be fooled by that.
I'll take you to buy good things.
I want that pear wood birdcage.
I know everything under the sun.
I've found the seller for you.
A millennia-old Guqin is for those
with a special connection.
What are you staring at?
If you're not buying, get lost.
Sir, what kind of meat is this?
Just tell me whose meat you want.
I'll cut it for you right now.
No, thanks.
Let's find the person we need.
Since we're here, there's no rush.
Later,
I'll take you to find something fun.
Let's go.
Check it out over there.
You've traveled far and wide.
Have you heard of Yi Zhihong?
Also known as
the one who takes by telekinesis
with ease.
The Red-Clad Heroic Thief
of unparalleled beauty.
Such a renowned name,
how could I not know it?
Young Castellan,
why are you
looking at me like that?