CURTAIN CALL
Hey, you know what?
I'm feeling anxious.
About what?
A lot of people are coming today,
and I'll be publicly introduced
as Grandma's grandson from the North.
My God.
I mean,
the situation is blowing up.
Still, if we just get through this,
maybe we won't have to run into people.
You're right.
Plus, it's Grandma's last event.
Let's stay alert and try not to slip up.
-Okay.
-Okay?
Let's go.
Link arms.
EPISODE 7
Se-yeon!
You both look really great.
Thank you. It must be these fancy clothes.
-You look beautiful, Se-yeon.
-You look pretty.
Thank you.
Se-yeon, where is Grandma?
She's in the waiting room
but will be out once the banquet starts.
I understand.
Wow. There are so many people here.
-Right?
-Thank you for coming.
-Thank you for having me.
-Welcome.
Good day.
She must be very nervous.
Jin-suk, are you okay? What's up?
What's wrong?
-It's nothing.
-What is it?
-What's wrong?
-Hey, Se-yeon!
Hyo-jin!
You look so beautiful.
-Hey, what's up?
-Someone I know is here.
-What?
-Remember the cousin I told you about?
Right. Your cousin from North Korea?
-I will introduce him to you.
-Okay, great.
Moon-seong!
Moon-seong.
-What do we do?
-Quiet. Let me think.
Is that him?
Yeah. He's acting strange.
Come here.
Moon-seong.
Someone I know is here.
Who is it?
Moon-seong.
What's wrong?
Hang on to me.
-What's with him?
-Hey.
Moon-seong!
Moon-seong, are you okay? Moon-seong.
Tell them to back away.
-Oh, okay.
-Moon-seong!
Hello? Someone help!
Someone help him!
Lift him and put him on my back.
Come on.
To the medic.
To the medic! Open the door!
This way.
-What's wrong?
-Oh, no. It's no big deal.
He's just really nervous. He'll be fine.
Hey, she's gone. She's gone.
Stop it. She's gone.
She left. That's enough.
Damn it.
What happened out there?
Someone I know is here.
Someone you know?
A former client.
I think she knows Se-yeon.
Who is she exactly? Give me details, kid.
Wait, Mr. Jeong.
I feel nauseous.
Stay unconscious.
Take off your shoes and everything.
Keep up the act.
I'll be right back.
-What now?
-Where are you going?
We just caused a ruckus.
I need to handle the aftermath.
Let go of this. Let go.
Close your eyes.
I'll be back.
I thought we were through, for real.
My hands are still shaking.
Hey.
Be honest.
Honestly, I was pretty good, huh?
You agree?
Oh, yeah.
You did some pretty quick thinking.
The acting I just did,
it doesn't come from thinking.
It's an actor's instinct
that gushes out from the spine.
Whatever.
Hey, forget about me.
-What was up with you?
-What?
I obviously had a familiar face there.
But why were you anxious?
Someone's coming. Lie down.
Someone could, I mean.
Hey, my shoes.
-Why can't you take them off?
-My tie, my tie.
You for real?
-You're not actually sick, you know.
-I'm unconscious, remember?
Mr. Jeong, are we ready to go?
How are the guests? Can I go out now?
Chairwoman, there's been…
What's happened?
How can someone unconscious
have a high heart rate?
Wow. He must be really nervous.
What…
do you mean by that?
If he's nervous, he can't be unconscious.
In other words, he's…
pretending.
Would you mind explaining
what this is about?
Hey, buddy. Hey.
Isn't it harder
to pretend to be unconscious?
It has to be.
Doctor, I have something to tell you.
Oh, my. How is Moon-seong? How is he?
No need to worry.
It looks like a simple panic attack.
He'll recover with a little rest.
-Does he have some kind of illness?
-Well, that's…
I'm not sure, ma'am.
You said he's from North Korea, right?
-Yes, yes.
-First, he's in an unfamiliar place.
His environment and identity
have completely shifted.
Besides, he's at this
well-attended formal event.
Even normal people will find
such situations stressful.
So is he really okay?
Well, anxiety disorders are
as common as insomnia.
In my professional opinion,
he just needs a few hours of rest.
I guess he's okay.
-Yeah.
-Let's go home together after this, okay?
But I must at least go see his face
if he's passed out.
You should listen to her.
You grandson will best benefit
from some rest.
I was too blinded by my excitement
that I didn't consider how the kids felt
and just pushed them too hard.
Let's go, Grandma.
Letting him rest is what's best for him.
-Right?
-Exactly right.
Chairwoman, you have to go now.
Everyone is waiting for you.
Moon-seong will be all right?
Don't worry. Let's go.
No worries, indeed.
What recovery? He isn't even sick.
I'm so sorry, Doctor.
What are you doing, exactly?
It's all for the chairwoman.
I just staked my profession on a lie.
As for me,
I staked my entire life.
Everyone will find out eventually.
But for now,
could you keep this to yourself?
As a doctor, this is like…
thinking about the afterlife.
Sorry?
Just because you want to know
if there is an afterlife
doesn't mean you should die early.
Thank you.
Right, then.
What's wrong? You really sick?
I'm lying down because I'm sick.
Now that I think about it,
I think I really might be sick.
Yoo Jae-heon, get it together.
Am I Ri Moon-seong or Yoo Jae-heon?
It's getting confusing.
You're some Method actor, huh?
I thought about the difference
between Yoo Jae-heon and Ri Moon-seong.
About life and theater…
Aren't they one and the same?
Isn't life some sort of play?
Just a thought.
Who says we're special?
People all live the same.
Hyo-jin.
Se-yeon. Is he okay?
He's fine.
I was looking forward to meeting
a North Korean.
I'll introduce you to him next time.
Hi, Hyo-jin.
You were invited too?
Of course. I work here.
-One extra ticket, thanks to her.
-Oh, I see.
Let's go sit.
Dong-jae.
Hyo-jin, it's been a while.
-I'm not late, am I?
-No. We're about to start.
What is this random entrance?
Are you back together?
It's good to see everyone.
Since we're all here,
let's make this official.
What is he saying?
-We're getting married.
-What? For real?
Now that you know,
spread the word to all our acquaintances.
-Is this true?
-No.
Right. You scared me. She says no.
Why are you scaring people?
I'm for real.
The chairwoman has arrived.
I'd like to express how grateful I am
that you all managed to attend
despite your busy schedules.
I gather everyone in attendance
is here by invitation.
I asked that those invitations be extended
with special care.
I believe the recipients will have felt
the pressure to attend.
You can't ignore an invitation like that,
can you?
I'm in my 90s now,
so you probably wondered
what kind of event this might be about.
As you read on the invitation,
this is a farewell party.
Yes, that's right.
It's a farewell party
for you to give me a send-off.
My doctor says
I have three months to live, at best.
No need to be surprised.
I'm over 90 years old.
My limbs are fine. My mind is clear.
What a way to pass.
I've stared death in the face
for a long time now.
Very few of my friends remain alive.
I've fulfilled my last wish too.
I have nothing else to desire from life.
Leading up to my death,
I believe it is a heavenly blessing
that I got to have fellowship
with you tonight.
So instead of a funeral,
I prepared this farewell party.
Even if you attend my funeral,
it will mean nothing to me.
Don't you agree?
So instead of having a funeral
or a mourning period,
I'm going to spend my last days quietly
with my family.
I want my grandchildren
to take note of this.
And so,
today will be the last time
you and I
will meet.
Please
send me off with a smile.
Chairwoman.
You're Se-jun's guests?
Thank you for coming.
This is Attorney Oh.
She's leading our M&A operations.
Hello, Chairwoman.
I've heard so much about you.
You probably didn't hear
good things about me, then.
No, I've only heard good things.
You're even more wonderful in person.
You're quite amazing, Chairwoman.
Well, thank you.
These gentlemen are from Bilton,
on the receiving end of the M&A of--
Hello.
I told you to invite
your ten closest acquaintances,
and you bring only business partners?
What about your friends?
Don't you have any other acquaintances?
These are the people
who I'm closest to now.
Seung-do, why are you just standing there?
Sorry?
Yes, ma'am.
Se-gyu.
Oh, you're all Se-gyu's friends.
Hello, Grandma.
Grandma, you remember Wook-hyeong?
Of course I do. He's your best friend.
In elementary school, you were asked
to write your best friend's name,
and he wrote yours,
and you wrote his, right?
Grandma, you are amazing. Applause!
All right. You all be well.
Yes, ma'am. Sit down, sit down.
Chairwoman.
Oh, my. Good to see you.
Look who it is.
Is your father well?
Yes. He wanted to come,
but he has a business trip overseas.
That's all right.
Please tell him I said hello.
I'll be waiting up there.
But tell him to take his time
and do everything he has to do.
Sorry?
I'm joking, girl.
Oh, you startled me.
Chairwoman.
Oh, Dong-jae. How have you been?
I'm glad to see you looking healthy.
I may look healthy.
But you heard me. I have three months.
But you must see Se-yeon get married.
We'll get to preparing.
Is that what's happening?
No, Grandma.
-She says no.
-She will.
-He says you will.
-I said no.
Se-yeon, if it makes you happy,
I'm fine with it.
Do what you want.
No, Grandma.
So you won't object if she's fine with it?
Of course not.
Then why did you object before?
Because she told me
she didn't want you back then.
Chairwoman, the other guests are waiting.
Shall we?
Of course. See you in a bit.
Mr. Jeong, it's been a while.
Yes, it has.
Enjoy your time here.
Is Moon-seong okay?
Yes. Don't worry too much.
Mom!
Jae-heon.
Moon-seong.
Are you all right?
Grandma.
Oh, thank heavens.
Thank heavens you're okay.
Oh, goodness.
Oh, what a relief.
I'm holding your soft hands.
Grandma, I'm fine.
Thank heavens. I thank the heavens.
Thank you, Moon-seong.
Thank you.
Moon-seong.
Today was your greatest hurdle.
Good job. You both did great.
There won't be anything like this again,
so don't worry too much.
Let's keep it going.
Actually,
I'd like to stop here.
You say that now? Why?
The thing is,
the more I become Ri Moon-seong,
the more I feel like
I'm doing something wrong.
I feel the same.
This feels wrong.
Do you feel like
you're doing something wrong?
You've done nothing wrong.
We're on a contractual agreement,
and you did as I asked.
If what we're doing is wrong,
then it's all on me.
Do you really think this play of ours…
is making Grandma a little happier?
The chairwoman I know
is as tough as they come.
I've never seen her swayed by emotions.
But these days, the chairwoman
is laughing and crying.
Isn't that good enough?
I guess… that is good enough.
I don't know for how much longer
I can keep up the act,
but as long as I play her grandson…
I hope…
Grandma…
can laugh a little more.
Yes.
Of course she should.
Come on out.
Are we okay?
Stop being a wimp and come out, you punk.
Thank you.
I would be dead if it weren't for you.
Don't worry about that.
This is just part of the transaction.
Since I've done you a favor,
you can do me one, yes?
Of course.
Ri Moon-seong-- Where is he now?
GENERAL MANAGER PARK SE-YEON
Se-yeon.
Oh! When did you install this?
I'm quick to pick up on convenience.
I'm trying to adjust
to the South Korean ways.
Yeah. That's the attitude.
How do you feel?
Se-yeon, I have a favor to ask.
Why are we here?
I wanted to come here with you.
I wasn't ever going to revisit this place.
Grandma!
Grandma, I'm floating on water!
Hey.
Do you see that?
What?
That over there. That.
-Oh, the boat?
-Yeah. Do you see it?
Yeah. I see it clearly.
Grandma!
It's Moon-seong!
Grandma, I'm here!
Oh, it's Moon-seong--
Is it really him?
Surprise!
You knew?
He begged me to bring you here.
Oh, my goodness.
Hey, hey. Be careful!
Grandma!
Grandma, I'm here!
It's your grandson, Moon-seong!
YOUNG RANG
Grandma!
Hey, be careful.
My goodness.
Oh, my.
At this rate,
I'll die from you shocking me.
Grandma, were you surprised?
Grandma, I told you I'd be back, didn't I?
Grandma, we just met.
How can we part ways?
I'll never let you go.
All right, all right. That's enough.
You sweet thing.
He's all sunshine and rainbows.
I wonder who he takes after.
Is this Attorney Kang?
It's me.
I need you to come see me.
Mr. Kang.
-What brings you here?
-I spoke to the chairwoman.
What for?
Well, it's…
Oh, good. Se-jun, have a seat.
Tell everyone to gather.
Yes, ma'am.
I know it's been quite hectic recently
for a lot of reasons.
I should have done this earlier.
This is long overdue.
What is it now?
-Attorney Kang.
-Yes, Chairwoman.
It seems all the inheritors are here.
The chairwoman has revised her will today.
Grandma, what's this about?
I cannot reveal the details,
but I can inform you
that a new inheritor
has been added to the will.
That's right.
Grandma, does that mean--
He's my family and my grandson,
whom I've sought all my life.
What I'm saying is,
they obviously have a right
to my inheritance.
Moon-seong.
-Yes?
-Jin-suk.
This is great for you.
Is that so?
So, why-- How is this going to work?
Yoon-hee, Grandma changed her will.
None of this would have happened
if we hadn't come here, right?
Right.
Wow. We just changed the course
of this family's future.
Right? This is like Interstellar.
Mr. Jeong, to be honest,
I want to go warn my past self.
You know what I'd say?
"Make him stay! Don't let me leave!"
Stop that.
Let's think.
Our contract ends when Grandma passes.
The will takes effect after she dies.
Yeah.
Since we aren't actually related,
the inheritance won't be our problem.
I don't know much about that stuff,
but rewriting the will,
isn't that a problem in itself?
-That's true.
-What the hell?
But we're like freelancers
bound to a contract.
Free-- Yeah.
Which means
it's the employer's responsibility
to tackle all work-related incidents.
Legally, we won't be held responsible
for any of it.
Director Park Se-jun offered ten times
the current stock price
with the condition
of acquiring Ilseong Partners.
Ignore him.
-But it's ten times.
-Don't make me repeat myself.
Yes, sir.
Did Se-yeon make any offers?
Not yet.
You may go.
Buying stocks from Dong-jae
is proving to be a challenge.
Offer him 20 times the price.
He says there's no chance of negotiation
even if you offer 100 times the price.
Do we need to overexert ourselves
to buy Dong-jae's shares?
-What do you mean?
-As far as Se-yeon is concerned,
she loves this hotel more than anything.
-So what?
-The reason she broke off her engagement
was because his family,
the owners of Woosang Group,
said something about
a gukbap restaurant owner lucking out
and becoming a lowly innkeeper
shooting for the Woosang Group.
It's all gibberish, really.
So what?
Do you really think Se-yeon would
reconsider marrying him?
It's true that Se-yeon loves the hotel,
which is why it's a problem for us.
What do you mean by that?
She will do anything to save the hotel.
If marrying Dong-jae is her last resort
to save the hotel…
she would marry him without hesitation.
But would she really go that far?
It's best to eliminate
any potential threats.
We must buy all the shares we can.
Yes. I understand.
It's time for me to shake things up.
If we add your shares
with Ilseong Partners' shares
and top it off with the shares from
our new share-riding Prince Charming--
This can work.
Since the shares will be redivided,
Se-gyu and Se-jun will get fewer shares.
We can win this one, right?
You're totally safe.
-Miss Hong.
-Yes, Miss Park?
Our hotel and position will remain safe
for the foreseeable future,
so let us do our due diligence
and align our command and discipline.
Mr. Bae, Director Park Se-jun is here.
Okay.
Why the visit?
Let's talk.
Whiskey?
No, I'm good.
You're boring.
Is this about the Nakwon shares?
The 4% I own in Ilseong Partners--
Let me save you the trouble.
Go someplace else.
No, I'm here because of Se-yeon.
Do you have to go to such extremes
to marry Se-yeon?
How dishonest.
You are here because of the shares.
Gluing together pieces of a broken glass
won't mend everything.
Why do you obsess over her
when you want for nothing?
This is why we can't converse.
That glass you speak of--
What if that's the only one I have?
I should do what I can
to make it whole, no?
I guess you would just throw it away,
since yours is already broken.
Let me ask you this.
Why are you so obsessed
with selling the Nakwon Group?
-Now is the optimum time--
-Se-jun.
500 billion or a trillion won--
Is there a significant difference?
No, right?
You can't use it all up anyway.
Going to take the cash to your grave?
Is Nakwon Group your broken glass?
Good shot!
You hit pretty far!
Thank you.
You came because of the M&A deal, no?
You're interested in my shares.
You're sharp.
You sure are a rising young entrepreneur.
Unafraid to speak your mind.
I want the deal to go through.
I'm not into long-term investment.
I want fast cash.
Plus, the conditions look good.
Good shot!
You're quite decisive as well.
I don't like it when things drag out.
Nice one!
-Do you like golf?
-It's fun.
Why do you think that is?
What do you mean by that?
We walk hundreds of yards each time
just to hit the ball.
Then when we make a successful putt,
we feel satisfaction.
Isn't that what's fun about it?
If we could make it in one shot,
why would people become so invested?
Don't you think?
You're right.
You could join me in taking each step
until Nakwon becomes the greatest.
I think that would be fun to watch.
Would it?
I'll consider it.
Whether I'll need that sort of fun
or whether it really will be fun.
As far as fun goes,
hotel management ranks fourth on the list.
Fourth?
Raising dogs, raising cats,
playing golf, and then…
If you said it came in first,
I wouldn't have thought twice about this.
I think I can trust you.
Our reviews are improving quite a lot,
because our general manager
is quite sensible
when it comes to managing the hotel.
We look forward
to your affirmative answer.
She looks happy enough.
She liked what she heard.
What?
Then what?
He wants Moon-seong's medical records.
Se-jun said that?
Yes. I told him I didn't do any paperwork
because I conducted
a simple diagnosis at the hotel.
I also said medical records are private.
Even to family.
Thank you.
You still won't tell me
what this is about?
Shouldn't I be aware to a certain extent
as to what I'm getting into?
Let's sweep this under the rug for now.
It's better that you don't know,
so that when it hits the fan,
you can say you didn't know.
Se-yeon is meeting the shareholders
in favor of the deal to persuade them.
-Was she successful?
-She finds their vulnerabilities easily.
-So she has information?
-Information?
Se-yeon's right-hand woman.
Yes, Ra-kyung.
She's a manager at the planning office.
Her work relationship with Se-yeon
is like mine with you.
Get rid of her.
Sorry?
Who has the authority
to get her transferred?
That would be me.
From now on, it's an all-out war.
Let's see if Se-yeon can puppeteer
without her arms and legs.
You really are something.
Your experience speaks for itself.
Ra-kyung, what about this person?
Ra-kyung?
-Yes, Miss Park?
-Is something wrong?
I was going to tell you
when things were final.
As of today,
I'm moving to Nakwon's Jeju location.
What?
Was it Mr. Kim?
So he's going to play dirty.
He can't do this. It makes no sense.
-I'll speak to the chairwoman--
-Se-yeon.
I wasn't fired. I'll be transferred.
-Ra-kyung.
-That's the kind of fight this is.
Se-yeon.
Don't ever give in, okay?
Please tell Mr. Bae I said thank you.
Well, this is a surprise.
How can you just barge in like that?
Have you no manners?
How dare you mention manners to me.
You may go.
What I did was within my power.
I took the required steps
to transfer an employee.
You took my person
without even mentioning it to me.
I fully understand your intention.
I'm glad you understand.
You're glad?
Mr. Kim.
Yes?
Don't get too comfortable.
I suggest you stay on your toes.
Watch and see what I'm able to do.
Mother.
Mother!
Father!
Stop this!
Moon-seong, I'm glad you're here.
Let's go see Grandma.
We can take a boat to see Grandma.
Stop it!
I have to leave you in Grandma's hands,
so I can rest easy, you understand?
Poor thing.
Moon-seong, I've done nothing for you.
Your grandfather and your mother
died so early. How will you live?
How will you live, Moon-seong?
Mother.
After we left you, my heart…
My heart was so broken, Mother.
I really wanted to embrace you, Mother.
To be in your arms.
To cry with you.
To tell you I'd been living
with a heartache.
Father, don't wait for her here.
Grandma's not here.
Father.
Father!
JILIN PROVINCE, CHINA
Look, I smuggled him into South Korea.
What? Did he tell you to bring him back?
Your boss is quite vicious.
He wanted to get meat for the kids.
So he took a few coins.
Does he want to capture him that bad?
Whose boss are we talking about?
The kid wouldn't have survived
here anyway.
I had to help him leave.
How did he leave?
Someone picked him up from the South.
Who?
I don't know.
I just needed to deliver him and get paid.
Hey, Moon-seong.
If you want to go, tell me. I'll help you.
I need identification…
with my name, Ri Moon-seong, on it.
I need something
that can prove
that I'm me.
Call.
Wow.
That's a good card. You're a pro.
I'm a natural.
Nine.
Were you shot in the head?
I'm choosing to hand it to you. Let's go.
All right. Let's go.
Let it all out. All right, all right.
What just happened?
You can't even take what's handed to you.
You son of a bitch. I'll kill you.
Think carefully.
What guarantees are there in gambling?
It's all luck.
I just don't understand gamblers.
Don't you agree,
Comrade Ri Moon-seong?
-Honestly, I can't figure it out.
-What?
That's why I came all the way here.
Tell me,
Ri Moon-seong.
Who the hell are you?
LIFE BEGINS AT 90
GRANDMA NOW STARTING TO WALK
It's you, Se-yeon.
Grandma.
What? You can't sleep?
Se-yeon.
Did I upset you too?
No. Don't say that.
I want Moon-seong
to stay with us for life.
He's also your grandson.
Yes. Thank you.
It seems only you understand
how I really feel.
What is it? Something happen?
Is it the hotel?
No, it's…
Ra-kyung has been transferred
to Jeju Island.
She was a great source of strength to me.
But seeing her unfairly transferred…
just really upsets me.
Mr. Kim took the swing,
but Se-jun's behind this.
So, he really wants to sell the hotel?
I thought it was because
he had a lot on his mind
and because he was upset with you.
But now, something's off.
It's as if he's being chased.
Se-jun wouldn't be so brutal like this.
I'm going to stop him.
Se-yeon.
Ra-kyung may have been
like a sister to you,
but Se-jun is really your brother.
I'm glad you want to protect your people,
but you can't lose your real family.
I prioritized the hotel over everything
and lost everything in the process.
That must not happen to you.
You understand?
Grandma.
-This is it.
-What do you mean, "This is it"?
I was thinking about a promotional event
for the new hotel.
This is it.
Moon-seong's talent can be put to use.
JIN-HYUK, JI-YOUNG,
OUR BEAUTIFUL FUTURE AHEAD…
I got the idea when I saw
the picture you sent Grandma.
So, Se-yeon,
does the event need to be so big?
You can make mistakes. Don't be nervous.
I'm rooting for you.
You'll do well.
Excuse me.
Could you do that for us?
Yes. Of course.
Hello.
I should have said that earlier.
I'm the calligrapher.
What phrase would you like?
How would you like it?
SPRING HAS ARRIVED
BECAUSE OF YOUR WARMTH
EVERYTHING COMES TO AN END
TAKE THE FLOWERED PATH
FROM NOW ON IN LIFE
THE SUNSHINE WELCOMES US
LET'S MEET IN HEALTH…
YOU WILL BLOOM
INTO A BEAUTIFUL FLOWER
I think I'm finished.
That's so pretty. Wow.
It makes me feel good that you like them.
Sorry, but can you take a picture for us?
A picture? Sure.
Okay, so…
Like this?
No, just us two.
We want a picture of us two.
With this.
-You two?
-Yes.
Okay, here we go.
One, two, three. Here we go.
-Thank you.
-That's a good one.
-Wow.
-So cute.
-Thank you.
This isn't so bad.
This isn't so bad at all.
EVENTUALLY,
YOU WILL SHINE UP THERE
Can I ask for one as well?
Yes, of course.
What phrase would you like…
Do you work part-time here, Jae-heon?
CURTAIN CALL
I can't believe I'm meeting you here.
It must be destiny.
Ri Moon-seong, you can fight, can you?
-You going to go all the way?
-Do what you can.
I know I won't lose.
If we went back to the old days,
do you think we could do better?
I think we could.
-Chairwoman Ja Geum-sun?
-That's my grandmother.
Should we run?
Seeing Grandma dying before us,
I feel so guilty.