Let me run to the next level
Snow falls as I turn around
I'll go through ups and downs
Hold my hand and I'll live for love
As the song of the sky
The Long Ballad
Episode 16
Isn't it He Yan?
No, Instructor Chen
Brother He is the first place
The first place is great, right?
Do what you should do
What's the rush?
I tell you
The number of people who can win the game
is measured by the overall score
It's just one of the rounds
They are not good at it
Yes
Come, drink
Drink
You just want to join 97th Battalion?
Only if I join 97th Battalion
can I make contributions
and be a general
You are so anxious
and you are so shameless
I don't have a family
What I want to do
is just to prove myself
Lei Hou is your defeated general
Huai Xin chooses him over you
That's his loss
Drink
Come, drink
Come
Today is the Mid-Autumn Festival.
Let's get married.
I want to get drunk and rest.
Here.
I'm happy today. Let's drink.
Sit and eat.
Xiaoju, you're too much!
What did you call me?
Xiaoju.
Are you stupid?
You don't even know your own name.
Xiaoju, do you know who I am?
Who are you?
Me?
My attitude has improved.
I don't change!
Me?
I'm the No. 1all in this state!
he wants to approach me
Just give me the wine
He wants away
Go
How much did they drink?
You should hurry back
Wine
B Sylvanas
You're going back?
You haven't told me
why you didn't choose me to join the nine-legged battalion.
I'm the best in the whole of Yezhou.
I'm a good person.
You
have no taste.
Actually, I know why you didn't choose me to join the nine-legged battalion.
That's because you suspect that
there's a spy.
But you've tried so many times to find out.
You know I'm not...
Lei Hou.
It's Lei Hou.
How is it?
Am I smart?
You're smart indeed.
But smart people
usually don't have good results.
How come?
I'm telling you.
One day, Yan and I
will be on the top of the list.
Yayou.
He Yan.
Put it back.
He Yan, put it back.
Su Long,
don't be mad at me.
I'll show you my sword.
Slaughter her.
Yes.
Shう.
I know it's my fault.
I don't really have to…
Xiaojue, do you like me?
Brother Fei Nu, you are...
I'm going to send the dinner to Du Du.
What about you?
The banquet is not over yet.
Why are you here?
I just got selected into the Nine Seasons Camp.
I wanted to thank Du Du in person.
But I didn't expect Du Du to...
I didn't expect that he would be so kind.
I'm sorry.
Du Du...
You must not like me.
Otherwise,
why didn't you let me join the Nine Seasons Camp?
Let go.
You are too much.
You are so ungrateful.
You are so disappointing.
Tell me.
In terms of appearance,
in terms of body,
in terms of height,
what's wrong with me?
Tell me.
What's wrong with me?
Do you have height?
Even if it's about the relationship between you and me,
shouldn't you
increase the number of people?
What relationship between you and me?
You are just a bad omen.
I...
I want to prove it to you.
Again.
Let go.
Good.
You...
My lord.
If you don't increase the number of people,
I'll...
What are you going to do?
Your Majesty, lend me your hands.
Alright.
Train me.
Keep me waiting.
He...
I think
Brother He
you're sleepingzzo
not bad
Duoduo's tent
correct
To hide the truth
HuanJin
went to me last night
What's wrong?
Do you remember anything?
Dad.
It seems that you remember it.
Did the governor say how to deal with me?
No.
But he doesn't look very good.
Oh, no.
Don't talk about going to the nine-man camp.
I'm afraid I can't stay in the Yezhou camp.
What should I do?
That's not necessarily.
Look.
You used his most real sword
to cut his favorite sword.
And he didn't cut you.
He even let you sleep on the bed.
Think about it.
Why does he treat you so well?
He must have seen
that you are very special.
Very...
Very special?
Did I expose your true identity?
Did I expose my true identity?
You are an indispensable talent.
That's why he is so proud of you.
Am I wrong?
Come on.
Xiaoju.
Do you know who I am?
I am the No.1 in Yezhou.
I'm a very good person.
You...
You have no taste.
Duoduo.
Don't be angry.
I...
I'll show you.
I should apologize to Duoduo
for my misbehavior.
He is not a man of light feet.
He must be a man of great power.
Bring the city's
holy water.
Yes.
Duoduo.
You can't take the wine as the truth.
Or you'll be in trouble.
It's a big deal.
Duoduo.
Or I'll use my three years of military service
to compensate your love.
You have a lot of money.
Can you let me join the wine and drink?
Brother He.
Why are you here alone?
I'm afraid you want to practice more.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
Kneel on this?
Yezhou is so big.
Thank you, brother.
If I go alone,
I'm afraid I'll get lost.
Miss.
Don't be a Hejiang woman in your next life.
It's him.
Brother He.
Did you choose the weapon?
I've not even had a chance.
I don't even know how can I face such an Queen.
Brother.
Just now,
who was with you just now?
They are from the thief,
to give our Duoduo the Juping butter.
Thank you.
vial of swarming with並es.
What do you want to do?
Yezhou Commandery is short of provisions and provisions.
I'm afraid that
I'll invite Yezhou Commandery's
Commander Xiao Jue to come here
to discuss this matter.
I also heard that
Cheng Lisu is in Yezhou Commandery.
I haven't seen Cheng Xianzhi for many years.
I'm worried about him.
I hope that Commander will go with Cheng Xianzhi
to Sun Xiangfu, the county magistrate of Yezhou.
I asked you to come here to discuss official affairs.
Why did you invite me?
We don't need to go there.
You really don't remember?
Sun Xiangfu?
When I entered the capital,
his wife made the marriage arrangement for you.
Oh no.
He asked me to go there
and then he tied me down
and sent me back to the capital to get married.
This...
Huai Xin.
Uncle.
You have to save me.
You can't just
look at your best friend
and your lovely nephew
and jump into the fire pit.
Is it that exaggerated?
Very exaggerated.
You know that
I have a crush on that Song's daughter.
She always
does something strange.
I will be treated as a test subject
and then die slowly.
Instead,
I'd rather die now.
Wait.
Uncle.
I knew you wouldn't just die.
We're so close.
What...
What are you doing?
Yin Qiu's blood is like mud.
I'll lend it to you.
You...
You must be kidding.
Uncle.
You're not really
going to die, are you?
Didn't you say you'd end it?
I...
I was just kidding.
Mr. Cheng.
I heard someone
sent a invitation to Duoduo.
Brother He.
Don't be so stingy.
Remember to
give me more money.
Mr. Cheng, what's wrong with you?
I'm going to be a guest
with Huai Jin
at the county magistrate's house.
That's a tiger's den.
Tiger's den?
You're not going to be a guest?
I'm not going to be a guest.
I'm going to be a guest.
You're not going to be a guest.
I'm not going to be a guest.
Tiger's den?
Why are you afraid of Duoduo?
Is there anyone
more powerful
in the county magistrate's house?
Sun Xiangfu is more scary than a tiger.
Her wife is the matchmaker who set me up.
I'm afraid
Xiao Jue can't even protect me this time.
So Duoduo went to Yezhou
to talk about marriage with you.
No.
Huai Jin went to talk about official affairs.
I'm the only one who wants to go through this.
Duoduo went to talk about official affairs?
What's the matter?
Yezhou's county magistrate
wants Duoduo to go to see him personally.
He's so shameless.
No.
Huai Jin went to talk about military provisions and expenses.
I was...
No, Brother He.
Why do you always mention Huai Jin?
I'm the one who's unlucky.
Not him.
Childe Cheng.
I'm thinking that Duoduo is very capable.
Since I can't count on him,
I'll help you figure out a way.
Let's go.
Let me help you figure it out.
Duoduo.
About military provisions and expenses,
Sun Xiangfu has been trying to find a reason to push it away.
But at this critical moment,
he suddenly wants to go there.
There must be a trap.
I think it's obviously a red-lake banquet.
How about we go there?
I'm not going.
They won't give up.
It's hard to prevent a case if you're well-known.
It's better to take the initiative.
Besides,
Sun Xiangfu still owes me
military provisions for Yezhou.
Duoduo.
I just received the news.
It said that
Chuzhao, the military inspector, is coming to Yezhou.
You should know him.
He's the 19th general of Qingyuan.
He's the favorite student of Xu Jingfu.
He's been working for Xu Jingfu all these years.
According to the investigation,
he just came back from Que City.
What's the time?
Your reputation is damaged in the battle of Que City.
I don't know if it's related to him.
I don't know what he'll do
in Yezhou this time.
I've dealt with Chuzhao.
He was not doing well in Chu's family in the early years.
Until he got the title of official,
the Chu family changed his mind about him.
Now he's under the influence of Xu Jingfu.
He must be
trying to take advantage of Xu Jingfu's situation.
No matter what he's up to,
he's working for Xu Jingfu.
It's so coincidental that he came back from Que City.
The rumor should be related to him.
You should be careful
when you go to Yezhou this time.
Yes.
Duoduo.
The situation is so bad.
Mr. Cheng doesn't know martial arts.
I'm afraid it's not appropriate for him to go with us.
He Yan is the only one who will go to the city.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Duoduo, don't you suspect He Yan's identity?
Why do you want to take him with you?
I'm worried about him.
Since he's so active,
let him go.
He's good at martial arts.
Then we can have a competition
at the red gate banquet.
Sun Xiangfu has been holding
the military expenses of Yezhou Commandery.
But he suddenly invited Xiao Jue to the mansion for a talk.
He Rufei must be planning something
with Sun Xiangfu.
And Yezhou Commandery is the problem.
Even Xiao Jue...
I must figure it out
whether it's for the sake of
Yezhou Commandery, Xiao Jue or myself.
Duoduo.
What's the matter?
I was drunk last night and offended you.
It's my fault.
But Duoduo,
you don't have to look at me like that.
I've already figured out a way
to atone for my sin.
So you decided to go to Yezhou for Cheng Lisu
to atone for your sin?
Actually, it's not the whole thing.
Besides worrying about you,
I also want to atone for my sin.
I'm afraid I can't help you.
Besides worrying about you,
I also want to atone for myself.
For yourself?
I want to enter the Jiuxi Camp
to make a contribution.
If this trip
can make Duoduo
change her mind about me,
next time,
I will definitely be the one
who enters the Jiuxi Camp.
Such a good opportunity is in front of me.
I will definitely take it.
Okay.
We'll wait and see.
Let's see how you make me change my mind.
And at last,
I can go to the Jiuxi Camp
to make a lot of dirty fits.
So I think
you should be on good gallOP.
Mr. Cheng,
Hello.
I'm a friend of Engine.
I have been waiting for you.
Duoduo,
get everybody ready.
Get ready.
Hurry up.
Good morning.
I am Cheng Lisu.
I am from the capital.
I like eating chicken with sesame seeds.
I hate eating rice porridge.
I can't eat peanuts.
It's the most joyful time.
I have to take a bath every day.
Not bad.
You are well-trained.
You are really a man who relies on clothes and horses.
This suits you better.
Brother He,
your style today
is almost like me.
You flatter me.
Duoduo, how about it?
Do I look
elegant and beautiful
in this dress?
You are
even more beautiful than Cheng Lisu.
Who said that?
It's almost the same.
When are you leaving?
Go away.
Young Master,
Ding Yi and Sun Xiangfu
have already met.
They have invited Xiao Jue
to the invitation letter from Yezhou.
It should have been handed over to Xiao Jue.
Okay.
Where is the Sun family?
They are all here.
What did you find out?
They have already
sent a man to kill Sun Xiangfu
as you ordered.
Sun Ling is a good-looking man.
He is unable to do anything
in Yezhou City
because of his father.
The people in Yezhou City
are too bold to say anything.
What's the matter with Sun Xiangfu's position in the mountain?
He is a father.
He will be implicated by his son.
Young Master,
if so,
shouldn't we
go to Sun Mansion?
The stage is set.
The performers
should be here soon.
We will leave when they arrive.
If we miss them,
it will be a pity.
Sirs,
this way, please.
Come on.
Sir, please.
Duoduo.
Uncle,
why don't we go to Sun Mansion?
No hurry.
Sir,
how many rooms do you want?
I want a room with a good view.
A room with a good view?
How many rooms do we want?
Three.
Two.
You and I will live in one room.
Why should I live in one room with you?
Because...
Uncle,
I am your nephew.
You won't even
pay more for a room, will you?
Three.
Okay.
You...
You are not allowed to leave the room tonight.
Huo Jin.
Coming.
Do you have
Koumo fat chicken?
Yes.
Give me one.
Uncle, you know that
I like Koumo fat chicken the most.
One Koumo fat chicken,
one Ba Bao wild duck,
one vegetable, one soup,
and six steamed buns.
Okay.
Isn't it just a room with a good view
and a dish?
Why do you look at me like that?
It's so stingy.
Wait.
I want one
spicy toast with sesame rolls,
shredded chicken with cucumber,
five-flavor steamed gluten,
five-spice
and five-flavor steamed dumplings.
Okay.
Enjoy.
Since it's all your favorite,
I will definitely satisfy you.
But I have taught you
to be simple and simple.
Don't waste it.
Your
I'm so full.
I'm sleepy after eating.
Why is my bed so comfortable?
I'll definitely have a good sleep later.
It's really delicious.
I'm so full.
If you still have energy,
play with me.
No!
It's time for chess,
but I...
It's so crowded here in Yezhou.
No news.
Get your lights of thenight at the Palace doing the hide-and-seek.
I want to have a look at the
Lu您
You.
Where is He Yi passar by?
I'm sorry.
Flying in the sky,
there's always hope.
I'll fight against all the wounds
to find the light.
The wind in the starry sky,
untie me and point me to you.
The courage to fight back,
is the power of existence.
The wind in the starry sky,
untie me and point me to you.
The courage to fight back,
is the power of existence.
The wind in the starry sky,
untie me and point me to you.
The courage to fight back,
is the power of existence.
The wind in the starry sky,