♪Shrugging off past burdens♪
♪Beneath the mask, who am I?♪
♪Release and find wider shores♪
♪Love's a riddle, and rain pours heavy♪
♪Crossed paths, now downward fall♪
♪From dust arises starlight's spark♪
♪Tearing through
the night's dense blockade♪
♪Heart's flame illuminates all solitude♪
♪Let time's sails drift endlessly♪
♪Through wandering exile♪
♪Breaking free from the cocoon,
I start anew♪
♪Moon as song, life as flame♪
♪Nameless heart clings fiercely♪
♪Let me♪
♪Charge toward the next raging river♪
♪Moon darts, snow falls♪
♪We tread rugged paths to reunite♪
♪Hands held tight♪
♪We forever live for love's sake♪
♪Shadow's spear burns fiercely♪
=Legend of The Female General=
(Xianchang Academy)
Today
(Year 14 of Qingyuan, Wei, Xianchang Academy)
marks your first enrollment.
I know
you come from privileged families
and have lived in comfort till now.
But at Xianchang Academy,
you must study diligently
day and night
to refine your talents
through perseverance
and serve our nation well.
(Master Wei,
Scholar of Xianchang Academy)
Young man,
what's your name?
Why do you keep wearing a mask?
Constantly hiding your true appearance
is rather rude, don't you think?
Master,
I am He Rufei.
My visage is unsightly,
and I fear startling others.
So I cannot remove this mask.
He's the Xiaos' second son?
His exceptionalness lives up
to his reputation!
Indeed.
I, Xiao Jue, apologize for being late.
Please forgive me.
=Episode 2=
(Cheng Lisu,
Imperial Medical Bureau's Top Disciple)
The army doesn't tolerate
flashy things,
including you.
I traveled so far to join you.
You treat me like this?
You can go back
for your arranged marriage.
If I could beat you,
I'd have...
beaten you senseless.
Feinu, escort Mr. Cheng out.
Understood.
Would you really
abandon your friend
in need?
Avoiding marriage
won't kill you.
At worst, they'll maim you.
Xiao Jue.
Commander.
Uncle.
We're about the same age.
But you're still my maternal uncle.
Please let me stay.
Okay?
Thank you.
(If you enlist as a woman,)
(it will remain a liability.)
(So I have prepared)
(for you)
(male identity papers)
(of He Yan.)
(He Yan's Household Register)
You're He Yan, right?
(Two names are different)
(in one character.)
(Master's foresight is thoughtful.)
To the left tent for screening.
Then to the right tent if you pass
to register
for uniforms and money.
Thank you.
Next.
Commander, what's screening?
Don't know what screening is?
It's simple.
Strip naked for the medic's exam.
If you're healthy,
you'll pass.
- Thanks.
- Next.
The Gaoxia horse struggles
with the climate.
It hasn't eaten.
Examine it.
See what ails it.
What?
I, a future imperial physician,
am treating a horse?
As a healer,
shouldn't you treat all lives equally?
Besides, Yezhou Garrison
keeps no idlers.
If you want to stay,
be useful.
Fortunately, this is a mare.
Helping it is acceptable.
I'd have declined
if it were a stallion.
Xiao Jue, watch closely.
I can both heal
and tame horses.
Look!
It's spooked!
It's coming!
Make way!
Move aside! Move!
Move aside!
That man's way of taming
is unique to the Fuyue Army.
He's He Rufei's man?
(No, I accidentally gave myself away.)
(Xiao Jue noticed it.)
Not bad.
He resembles my heroics in the past.
That move he just pulled
is way beyond your skills.
(Oh no.)
(Xiao Jue knows Fuyue Army's moves.)
(He definitely recognized it.)
(Yet he didn't react.)
(He took me)
(as He Rufei's man)
(and planned to act against me?)
Come on.
Let's continue.
Gather around!
Impressive.
You're small.
But you're quite good.
You flatter me.
My taming skills could
never match yours, Instructor.
Well...
The army needs
talents like you.
But
I haven't been screened yet.
Forget about it.
If you can tame such a horse,
your physique must be good.
I'll secure the horse.
Then let's handle the documents. Wait.
- Go.
- Thank you.
So naughty.
Turn and slash!
Since you suspect him,
why not kill him directly
for good?
If he's truly a spy sent
by the ill-intended one,
killing one will
only bring replacements.
Rather than endless trouble,
it's better to keep him
to potentially lure out the mastermind.
I wonder
whether the mastermind is He Rufei
or Xu Jingfu.
You said
before your father's campaign,
he impeached the prime minister.
Within days,
he fell into an ambush
at Mingshui.
He Rufei's troops
were a hundred li away,
but arrived only
on day seven after your father
sent the letter.
It was intentional.
I think
they are birds of a feather.
But we lack concrete evidence.
We can't prove
the defeat at Mingshui
relates to Xu Jingfu and He Rufei.
Nor can we prove
their collusion.
Now the Xiao Army is weakened
and disliked by His Majesty.
We can only investigate covertly.
With troop shortages here
and low funds,
building a competent new army
is highly challenging.
Investigate that man thoroughly.
I want to know
whose pawn he is.
Understood.
(Xu Mansion)
(Chu Zhao, Disciple of Xu Jingfu)
Master.
Regarding the Que City mission,
you've worked hard.
As ordered,
I monitored Xiao Jue in Que City.
The battle was unwinnable,
yet no one anticipated
his ruthless tactic
of flooding Que City
to force a reversal.
Pity
those countless lost souls.
Zilan,
ensure that Xiao Jue's
flooding of Que City
and mass slaughter of tens of thousands
are publicly exposed
to expose his infamy to the world.
His Majesty's wariness
toward him will grow even deeper.
Though victorious,
he was promoted in name
but demoted in reality.
He was sent to Yezhou Garrison.
Even with his conscription rights
restored,
that desolate wasteland
could never yield decent soldiers.
Moreover,
I discovered in Que City
a fish that slipped through the net.
I've positioned him as a hidden pawn
in our strategy.
Given time,
he'll become an unstoppable vanguard.
Great.
Focus on recovering these coming days.
Soon,
you'll be entrusted
with greater tasks.
Understood.
Chu Zhao.
(Xu Pingting, Daughter of Xu Jingfu)
You're back! Did you bring me a gift?
Your impudence grows by the day.
Father.
I'd never forget.
What fragrance is this?
Try it to find out.
Try it with me.
Go ahead.
Then I'll graciously accept.
Let's go.
What's wrong with this tinderbox?
Let me try.
Stop it.
Light it with the candle.
Burn him! Burn him!
(Burn him!)
Let me see.
You're injured.
Are you okay?
It's nothing.
Just got burned.
My grip slipped.
Young Master,
your injury...
(Yingxiang, Chu Zhao's maid)
I know you wounded your left arm
intentionally.
But...
I've failed my duties.
And I was also injured by refugees.
I feel ashamed, Master.
You're being too harsh with yourself.
To earn Master's favor,
sacrifices must be made.
(A bandit?)
(Wang Ba, Yezhou Garrison recruit)
Move!
(Zheng Xuan, Yezhou Garrison recruit)
(Face-tattooing punishment?)
(He was a convict)
(and a rogue.)
Boss, your tea.
Well-mannered.
It's tiring.
(Jiang Jiao, Yezhou Garrison recruit)
(Escort Agency)
(Former escort agency member?)
(He must be skilled.)
Look away!
Pretty boy.
(Paler than me.)
(How dare he judge me?)
I used to think
(Mai, Yezhou Garrison recruit)
I was the shortest one here
in the camp.
But now
you're almost as short as me.
Alright.
We together eat more
to grow taller.
By the way, what's your name?
He Yan.
Then I'll call you He.
Agreed.
I'm Mai.
I was a farmer.
Sleep here.
(Huang Xiong, Yezhou Garrison recruit)
(This one was a hunter.)
(A killer wearing prayer beads.)
(Interesting.)
Thanks.
He,
you'll sleep here tonight.
- Okay.
- Let me help.
No need.
You claim hostility with Xiao Jue,
yet you know
the Que City battle
left his reputation in ruins.
Aren't you afraid
to be implicated by him
or slandered?
Master,
I don't believe
Xiao Jue would flood Que City
just for an easy victory.
Nor would he
sacrifice all the people of Que City
as stepping stones
to pave his path to military glory.
Most importantly,
the Xiao Army urgently needs
new recruits right now.
This way I can stand out quicker
and prove myself.
(The snoring chorus is impressive.)
(I last heard this long ago.)
He,
you're up so early.
Nature called.
Mr. Shen.
- Mr. Shen.
(Shen Han,
Head Instructor of Yezhou Garrison)
What guy...
Mr. Shen.
Good morning, Commander.
- Good morning.
Good morning.
Up already?
He woke up
from nature's call, Commander.
Everyone!
Gather at the training field
and have ten weighted laps
around the barracks!
Not a single lap less.
Wait, ten...
Ten laps?
Why?
It was all because of you!
You had to be an early riser
with no team spirit!
- Selfish worm!
- Yes, selfish.
Go home if you want to sleep in.
We're in the army.
You...
Boss! Boss!
If you don't get out now,
you'll be punished harder.
Don't be mad.
Stay calm.
He,
I'm afraid I won't
keep up with the training.
Don't worry.
Recruit training
is always gradual.
Day One will be simple.
I can't go on.
I can't go on. I really can't.
On your feet!
Five more laps!
Come on, He.
I'll count to three.
Two, three!
Watch it.
One, two, three.
Let's go.
(I didn't know)
(how Xiao Jue trained his men.)
(I have finally seen it now.)
(It starts so intense right away.)
(Xiao Jue)
(has such a pretty face,)
(but he's truly vicious,)
(just like before.)
(I thought I could earn merits)
(and rise quickly.)
(But Xiao Jue)
(is hard on others)
(and harder on himself.)
(It seems serving under him won't)
(let me rise)
(as easily as I hoped.)
(Severely injured and then poisoned,)
(in bed for a month.)
(It nearly drained all my strength.)
(I can't go on like this.)
Commander, it's only the first day.
Aren't you pushing them too hard?
Mr. Shen,
these recruits
are either country folk
or bandits and thugs.
Like with that horse,
the Commander's harsh methods
aren't about
breaking their spirit.
He's testing their potential.
Mr. Cheng, you know
our Commander well.
Isn't he the horse-taming prodigy
from yesterday?
Why is everyone else
on their seventh lap
while he started his fourth?
In my opinion,
he's lacking in potential.
Don't speak
of my savior that way.
So what if he is?
He could still
make a good army cook.
Army cook?
You underestimate him.
I actually think
he's perfect
scout material.
Now we'll learn to use various weapons.
I can barely stand.
He,
why is your sword so short?
It's not even arm's length.
It's twin blades.
Not a sword,
but a pair.
W-What twin blades?
Real men use this.
So flashy.
Exactly.
Sounds like useless decoration.
- Good.
- Not bad.
He's got skills.
That should be one technique.
That's sad.
He can't fight properly.
I'm exhausted. Need a break.
He's decent.
- Good!
(Lei Hou, Yezhou Garrison recruit)
Impressive!
- Good!
That's real skill.
A-Are you staring or fighting?
Move back. My turn first.
Impressive!
- Amazing!
Your turn.
Hurry up.
We're on the clock here.
Draw it back.
Come on.
No need.
I can't pull
this bow.
His stance looked decent.
This bow requires real strength.
We can't blame He Yan.
He,
he excels at everything.
We need to work harder.
Block!
Retract!
Again.
Strike!
Thrust!
Block!
Retract!
Again.
Strike!
Thrust!
Block!
What's funny?
Pick it up. Keep going.
A pretty face with nothing.
All show, no skill.
Retract!
Regardless,
he picked up the spear.
That's commendable.
What did you find about He Yan?
He's from a gatekeeper's family
in Jiazhou.
No prior military history.
No suspicious family connections.
Currently,
his background checks out.
Yet he's skilled in horsemanship
and knows military routines well.
He's clearly a seasoned
soldier.
But during drills,
he performs pathetically.
I'm quite curious.
Is he faking it
or truly useless?
The others?
Commander,
recruits have diverse backgrounds.
Some have
dubious pasts.
But the only one who faked it
is this person.
Send two teams from Mingshui.
One to Jiazhou
and one to Que City.
Investigate this impostor thoroughly.
The rest
continue investigating in Mingshui.
As you command.
(Longevity of Cranes and Pines)
(Song Wan, Xiao Jue's Mother)
What's that smell?
It seems to be
from the mountain pass.
The smell of sulfur?
A hot spring?
(But, Sister,)
(the achievements you have today)
are entirely due to
your identity
as the He family's legitimate heir.
(Even with the name He Rufei,)
as a woman,
how could you
(achieve such accomplishments
and reputation?)
(Those were all earned)
(through my pain, blood, and tears.)
(The He family's heir)
(are just empty words.)
(What's mine)
(can't be taken away.)
Only months have passed.
But it feels like a lifetime ago.
In my past life, I hid in shadows.
Only the moon saw my true face.
In this life,
I can finally
fight with honor.
(With this hot spring)
(and proper training,)
(I should recover completely)
(in a few days.)
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
♪Who cares about this boundless void♪
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
♪Stubbornly fighting with my life♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪