♪Shrugging off past burdens♪
♪Beneath the mask, who am I?♪
♪Release and find wider shores♪
♪Love's a riddle, and rain pours heavy♪
♪Crossed paths, now downward fall♪
♪From dust arises starlight's spark♪
♪Tearing through
the night's dense blockade♪
♪Heart's flame illuminates all solitude♪
♪Let time's sails drift endlessly♪
♪Through wandering exile♪
♪Breaking free from the cocoon,
I start anew♪
♪Moon as song, life as flame♪
♪Nameless heart clings fiercely♪
♪Let me♪
♪Charge toward the next raging river♪
♪Moon darts, snow falls♪
♪We tread rugged paths to reunite♪
♪Hands held tight♪
♪We forever live for love's sake♪
♪Shadow's spear burns fiercely♪
=Legend of The Female General=
=Episode 9=
Mr. Chu.
Mr. Sun want to see
you in the reception hall.
Attend to your duties, Mr. Chu.
Rest well.
Commander Xiao.
Mr. Sun.
Might I know why you're here?
This courtyard
is particularly elegant,
so I took a stroll.
But I lost my way.
I'm sorry
I haven't been a better host
and shown you
around the premises.
Since the sunshine today
is mild,
shall we have tea in the pavilion?
This way.
Have some tea.
Young Master.
The account records
are in Sun Ling's secret room.
Earlier,
I concealed myself and was waiting,
but observed
Xiao Jue stealthily entering the study.
Young Master,
could he also be
after account records?
He couldn't have found
Sun Xiangfu's dealings
with Master.
He's likely
after Yezhou Garrison's tax ledgers.
But if he obtains them first,
we'll lose
the initiative.
Yingxiang,
watch
Xiao Jue's every move.
Yes.
Commander Xiao, have some tea.
This smells like
the Junshan Yinzhen tea.
Excellent quality indeed.
Mr. Sun,
your generosity knows no bounds.
A gift from my friend.
Otherwise,
with my meager official salary,
I couldn't afford such fine tea.
Knowing
our men in Yezhou Garrison
still lack military pay,
I feel really uneasy
drinking such fine tea.
Commander Xiao,
your words ring true.
Military life is arduous.
I share their hardships in spirit.
But Yezhou suffers yearly calamities
and poor harvests,
making provisions and pay impossible.
Previously,
border trade supplemented our funds,
but now,
constant clashes with Wutuo
have halted all commerce.
Thus
revenues vanished.
No income means
people can't pay taxes.
Without taxes,
how can I procure military funds?
Forgive my frankness,
as Yezhou's magistrate,
when I think of soldiers
enduring hunger,
my heart aches.
If selling myself
could raise funds,
I'd gladly trade myself
for military funds
to support our troops.
Your words
are truly moving.
Were it not for our garrison
going unpaid for a long time,
I might believe what you said.
Master.
Mr. Chu has arrived at the hall.
Mr. Chu has arrived?
Yes.
Commander, should we...?
Perhaps...
Okay.
I understand your meaning.
Do as you please.
I'll return shortly.
Why does it hurt so much?
(This thing must be poisonous.)
(He hasn't gone far)
(and is still secretly watching me.)
(This poison...)
(He doesn't just want to kill me.)
(And Xiao Jue, too.)
What's up?
Let go.
Someone placed a poisonous ball on me.
Another wasted effort.
He...
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
What are you doing?
Why not smile?
Why smile?
How can you smile?
Not smiling.
Not smiling? Why not?
Why smile?
Get lost.
They fell into the water.
They'll wash up
thoroughly.
That scented ball became useless.
Falling into the water
right after we replaced
his scented ball.
This is too much of a coincidence.
He must be faking blindness.
That young man
is truly unnatural.
Slippery as a loach,
he's impossible to grasp.
My belt!
Belt! Where's my belt?
Where's my belt?
Belt.
Uncle!
I can't find my belt.
Could you fetch it for me?
Here.
You're so good to me.
You called me uncle, after all.
Uncle,
what about my allowance?
Where is it?
It's not worth being your nephew.
You're unlucky to have
a heartless uncle.
Who said that?
You're clearly warm-hearted
and magnanimous.
General Fengyun,
as good
as your reputation.
Earlier,
you really went all out.
I couldn't let you get involved.
Fortunately,
that scented ball
is now useless.
There were many methods,
but you chose the most foolish one.
It indeed required suffering,
but
it was also undoubtedly the fastest way.
Cold?
Put on your clothes.
If you catch a cold,
I won't care.
Ding Yi
is clearly targeting Xiao Jue.
I'll investigate this thoroughly.
You want to kill Cheng Lisu,
but General Feihong
clearly ordered you to take
Xiao Jue's life.
He keeps sabotaging things.
Killing him
would eliminate
Xiao Jue's right-hand man.
Then
matters would become much simpler.
This isn't a bad approach.
I just worry that Xiao Jue...
(It was indeed He Rufei.)
(But why would He Rufei
want to kill Xiao Jue?)
Guards!
Assassin!
Assassin! Hurry!
Over here!
Hurry!
Over here.
Hurry.
Go on.
This way.
Hurry.
(Hide in the Commander's room.)
(Why is he bathing at this moment?)
Did I enter the wrong room?
This...
Where am I?
Take off your stealth outfit
before playing these tricks.
Commander Xiao? Are you sleeping?
Trespassing into my room.
Is this
how you treat your guests?
Sorry, Commander Xiao. A thief entered.
I feared it would disturb you,
so I came to investigate.
You should thoroughly
check every inch
of this room.
You are skilled in martial arts.
Why would you fear a thief?
But
Mr. Cheng lacks skills in martial arts.
When I visited his room,
he wasn't present.
My nephew
has a fondness
for the pastries
from Shiyunju in Yezhou,
so my man took him there.
Is there
a problem with that?
My apologies.
Thank you.
It's lucky
that you bathe daily.
The servants
deliver water every day.
Why was Ding Yi after you?
Why were you wearing
a stealth outfit?
That black-clad figure earlier
was you, right?
Why ask questions
you know the answers to?
Why pretend to be blind?
Not pretending.
It's just
that I'm blessed,
so I can recover
slightly faster than others.
Significantly faster.
But I was
truly blind
for your sake.
Don't be ungrateful.
He Yan.
Get out.
(Why would He Rufei send someone)
(to assassinate Xiao Jue?)
(What is he truly after?)
(No.)
(I can't just wait.)
You want to kill Cheng Lisu,
but General Feihong
clearly ordered you to take
Xiao Jue's life.
He keeps sabotaging things.
Killing him
would cut off
Xiao Jue's right-hand man.
Then
matters would become much simpler.
(Sun Xiangfu's servant)
(is actually He Rufei's man?)
(The delay in rescue at Mingshui,)
(the political betrayal in court,)
(and the assassination in Yezhou.)
(He Rufei,)
(in my memory,)
(you weren't this treacherous.)
(What corrupted you so?)
(Or did I misjudge you from the start?)
(Was this your true nature?)
(Besides,)
(what role)
(does she play in this?)
Young Master,
someone was eavesdropping
on Sun Xiangfu and Ding Yi's talk.
Ding Yi chased him
to Xiao Jue's room.
Xiao Jue happened
to be bathing at the time.
Perfect timing.
Yeah, perfect timing.
Xiao Jue must already know by now
He Rufei sent Ding Yi
to kill him.
Let him know.
After all, He Rufei
is the one who did it.
Young Master,
you've been reading so long.
Have a rest
and have some soup.
This goji and fish soup is
good for the eyes.
Alright.
Who's there?
Trying to act mysterious?
Today, I'll send you to the grave.
Let me be the one to send you off.
In your next life,
don't collude with wicked people again.
(That voice belongs to Cheng Lisu.)
What?
Can't you recognize me?
Who exactly are you?
You're not Cheng Lisu.
He has no martial skills.
Who do you think
I am?
No matter who you are,
today, you'll be killed.
You've really chosen
a fine burial spot for yourself.
This place is used by the Sun family
to suppress vengeful souls.
Each Buddha statue
represents a vengeful soul.
Soon,
you'll become one of them,
being trapped for eternity.
I'm a vengeful ghost crawling out
from the Netherworld.
I care nothing for reincarnation.
Besides,
if I can come and go freely,
these paper charms and clay statues
are just worthless objects.
They mean nothing.
Don't close it.
Let me watch
how this storm
will wash over the world.
Let's make Sun Mansion
descend into chaos.
The more chaos, the better for you.
I wonder what role
Mr. He will play
in this game.
Does your master He Rufei
know about your incompetence?
Ding Yi.
I won't fall for
the same person twice.
Today,
it's my turn to send you to the grave.
Let's see if you can earn rebirth.
Who exactly are you?
You once killed
a blind woman.
Who do you think I am?
He Yan.
But
if you tell me
why He Rufei wants Xiao Jue dead,
I'll make your death quick.
Do you care about Xiao Jue that much?
We are companions
who've survived
life-and-death situations.
Of course I care.
Even if I die,
I'll never betray
my general.
Since you won't talk,
go tell the God of Death.
I'm a ghost of the one you murdered.
I clawed my way out of the Netherworld,
and came here to claim your life.
Who exactly are you?
Commander.
What do you mean by that?
I have pretended
to be Cheng Lisu for a few days.
Don't you recognize me?
I'm He Yan.
What did you mean
by "I'm a ghost of the one
you murdered"?
I was just trying to scare Ding Yi.
Still refusing to tell the truth?
Miss He.
You're clearly a woman,
yet registered under a male identity
to join Yezhou Garrison.
May I ask you
what your intentions are?
Commander.
When did you find out?
I thought
you were a spy sent by He Rufei.
But you just killed his man.
So why exactly
did you hide your identity
to join Yezhou Garrison?
If you tell the truth,
I'll consider letting you
join the battalion.
(A trap?)
(I don't buy it.)
Commander.
Are you serious?
My registration
is true.
But when my mother
was pregnant with me,
she met a wise seer.
The seer said
if she bore a son,
he'd be a military prodigy.
But if it were a girl,
she would die early.
That's why since birth,
I've been raised as a boy.
So the registry
listed me as male.
By that logic,
the Fuyue Army moves
you demonstrated while taming horses
were also taught to you
by this seer in your dreams?
Not exactly.
Living as a boy,
I naturally aspired
to become a general
and make my mark.
Just like you, Commander.
After joining the Fuyue Army,
I achieved some success.
Unfortunately,
my squad leader discovered my identity.
Luckily, he was kind
and didn't expose me.
But
he feared implication,
so he made me
claim injury to retire
and return home.
(Exsoldier in the Fuyue Army, He Yan
retired after injuries half a year ago.)
(Thankfully, Master forged)
(my registry thoroughly.)
Commander.
Well,
I've answered all.
Don't you think
I'm now qualified
to join the battalion?
If your identity was exposed before,
why enlist again?
What if the past repeats?
I want to be a general
and protect my country.
Moreover, I trust
the Xiao Army
won't dwell on trivialities,
but value true talent
and give me a fair chance.
Keep up.
The corpse...
Let Feinu handle it.
Commander.
Why walk so fast?
Waiting to get caught?
Commander.
Help me apply medicine.
I can't reach it.
You're playing a man,
but not a real man.
You're a noble man,
so I trust you completely.
Commander.
Could you be gentler?
I'm made of flesh and blood.
Now you feel pain?
Weren't you tough earlier?
Different circumstances.
On the battlefield,
as a soldier,
even with my last breath,
I'd fight to the end.
Now, during peace,
I should properly recuperate.
Your reading paid off.
Though I'm a woman,
my military tactics and martial skills
rival any man's.
I believe
you've witnessed it firsthand.
Why did you
fight with
He Rufei's man?
It was all for you, Commander.
For me?
Exactly.
I overheard someone plotting
to kill you.
As your subordinate,
it's my duty
to eliminate all threats to you.
So I decided
to investigate covertly.
But someone spotted me.
He tried to silence me.
Every strike was lethal.
I couldn't hold back.
After all,
I need to keep myself alive
to serve you.
Commander,
do you still not believe
what I'm saying?
My loyalty to you
is truer than gold.
Every word comes from my heart.
I swear it.
Stay still. I'm not done.
Commander,
can I join the battalion now?
Why are you
so fixated on
joining the battalion?
Obviously,
it's because I admire you.
I want to achieve greatness
under your command.
Commander,
everyone in your battalion
earned their place
through genuine skills.
You value merit above all.
That's why
I sought to join your ranks,
to prove
no matter one's status
or gender,
anyone can achieve greatness
and serve the nation.
Where there is
a will,
there's a way.
Someday,
I'll become a renowned general.
Your speech
was flawless
and quite convincing.
But
do you think I'll believe that?
If you don't tell the truth,
then leave Yezhou Garrison.
You can't go back
on your word!
If you're not honest,
don't demand honesty from others.
If you expel me,
you'll regret it.
Regret?
I admit
you have talent,
but the Nine Banners Battalion
is full of talented people.
I can't even stay
in Yezhou Garrison much longer.
In short,
if you drive me away,
I'll spread rumors
that you have a sweetheart.
After all,
everyone knows you avoid
romantic entanglements.
Go ahead. Who'd believe such nonsense?
Words aren't convincing,
but I have evidence.
Commander,
I happen to know
you have a red mole
an inch above your waist.
Only an intimate partner
would know
such private details.
Nonsense.
It's not nonsense.
Commander,
your looks are exceptional,
and even that charming mole
is perfectly placed
and cute.
It makes people
hard to forget.
- You...
- Commander.
There's something.
Mr. Feinu,
come in.
What is it?
This is my room.
What is it you want to tell me?
Commander.
As you instructed,
I buried the body in the shrine
and left clues
to see Sun Xiangfu's reaction.
But while burying the body,
I discovered something there.
Commander.
Perhaps you should go see it.
Look here.
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
♪Who cares about this boundless void♪
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
♪Stubbornly fighting with my life♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪