♪Shrugging off past burdens♪
♪Beneath the mask, who am I?♪
♪Release and find wider shores♪
♪Love's a riddle, and rain pours heavy♪
♪Crossed paths, now downward fall♪
♪From dust arises starlight's spark♪
♪Tearing through
the night's dense blockade♪
♪Heart's flame illuminates all solitude♪
♪Let time's sails drift endlessly♪
♪Through wandering exile♪
♪Breaking free from the cocoon,
I start anew♪
♪Moon as song, life as flame♪
♪Nameless heart clings fiercely♪
♪Let me♪
♪Charge toward the next raging river♪
♪Moon darts, snow falls♪
♪We tread rugged paths to reunite♪
♪Hands held tight♪
♪We forever live for love's sake♪
♪Shadow's spear burns fiercely♪
=Legend of The Female General=
=Episode 21=
Here comes our female general!
- Welcome.
- Come on.
- Have a seat.
Come on, sit.
- Come on.
- Take a seat.
- Alright, let's sit.
- Over here.
Sit here.
Thank you.
Now that I've seen you,
I can boast to my friends.
I didn't know
I had become so popular.
This is nothing.
People on the street
will shower you with flowers.
Nowadays in Jiyang,
the one most admired
is Her Highness,
and the second
would be you.
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
But Her Highness is above us,
while you're among us,
which makes us believe
that women can achieve greatness, too.
You ladies
are no less capable than men.
You may not have fought
on the frontline, but your deeds
boosted our morale tremendously.
We simply did small things
under the protection
of frontline warriors like you.
It's nothing.
No deed is too small.
Everyone has their strengths.
As long as we act with benevolence
and righteousness,
we all deserve respect.
Besides,
women enjoy
a higher status in Jiyang
thanks to Her Highness.
You ladies must
showcase your talents even more.
You're right.
I've always wanted
to take the imperial exam.
But I never took the exam,
for fear of being judged.
Next year, I'll give it a try
to leave no regrets.
I wish you success in the exams.
A general and a scholar.
I admire you.
Meanwhile, I only
want to do business.
Most look down on merchants,
but merchants can
sustain themselves.
Exquisite embroidery.
That's Min'er's starting fund.
That's why she did her best.
Don't listen to her.
Miss Wang is getting married.
We're making small items for her.
However,
the groom's embroidered pouch
is hers to make.
Every stitch carries her affection.
We mustn't do it for her.
Miss Yan,
I want to make a pouch too.
Would you teach me?
It's for General Fengyun, isn't it?
Let's teach our general.
- Yeah.
- Let's teach her.
- Come on.
- Let me show you.
Insert the needle from below upwards.
Like this.
Done.
Let's see.
Needlework takes practice.
- Yeah.
- I can teach you
step by step.
Yeah.
What about this?
Well...
If it's not working,
we can try something else.
How about cooking?
General Fengyun would be deeply moved
if you cooked for him in person.
But
I've never cooked before.
I can't just make plain porridge.
Make some plain noodles.
That's the easiest.
Yeah, plain noodles.
We can teach you
all the recipes.
Give it a try.
Yeah.
- You got this.
- Try it.
- Come on.
Yeah.
Commander.
You've been sorting out
Jiyang's military affairs for days.
You must have been tired.
I can't starve you.
Commander, look.
I made the noodles myself.
Commander, please do me a favor
and try it.
Please.
Why did you want to cook?
I just wanted to do something for you.
(How much salt did you put in this?)
Commander.
Is it good?
Yeah.
Seems like I have
some talent in cooking, more or less.
Seeing you enjoy it so much,
I'm getting hungry.
Let me...
You were saying...?
No...
Nothing.
If you like it so much,
I'll make more tomorrow.
What's wrong?
I'm checking for holes.
If there are any,
I can mend them.
I don't think it's torn anywhere.
Commander, I'll head back.
Rest early.
Commander.
Did you hear
a tearing sound?
No.
No?
How did my sleeve get torn?
Yeah, it's torn.
Hurry and take it off.
Come on.
What...?
Is it necessary?
It's fine. Take it off.
No need, seriously.
Take it off.
Do you think
he misunderstood something?
Why is he so flustered?
What's the rush?
Is something wrong?
Commander.
Chai Anxi woke up.
Mr. Chai.
When Wutuo attacked Jiyang,
you could've fled amid the chaos,
yet you stayed,
showing a resolve to protect the people.
But why
did you betray my father
and Wei?
I didn't betray Wei.
I never betrayed Wei.
I didn't expect it.
I just wanted Xiao Zhongwu dead.
I wanted him dead.
My father treated you well.
Why did you do that?
Is there something we don't know?
Feel free to speak.
We'll plead your case
before His Majesty.
He treated me well?
That's because he felt guilty.
He killed my son.
My son had just reached adulthood.
As far as I know,
your son
died on the battlefield.
As a soldier, you should know
that war is merciless.
When soldiers march to war,
they embrace death without regrets.
Why would you think
that General Xiao
killed your son?
If Xiao Zhongwu hadn't been warlike,
my son
wouldn't have died.
If he truly died in battle,
as his father,
I'd be immensely proud.
But he died
under Xiao Zhongwu's
petty schemes.
You were supposed to
lead the vanguard at Yanshan.
Why was my son
sent as the vanguard in the end?
He never returned,
yet you built your fame.
You earned your glory by stepping
on my son's corpse.
I remember that battle.
A total of 216
Xiao Army soldiers
died on the battlefield.
Even though they knew
before setting out
that this battle
would likely be fatal,
they still volunteered to fight.
Your son,
Captain Chai Qian,
was one of them.
Do you know
we encountered Wutuo cavalry
on the way to Yanshan?
With 1,000 soldiers,
we fought against 5,000 enemies.
I couldn't reach Yanshan in time.
Your son volunteered
to lead the remaining
215 Xiao Army troops
to Yanshan,
sacrificing themselves to turn the tide.
You're lying.
Mr. Chai.
As a deputy general,
how could you distrust the commander
who had fought
alongside you for years?
And as a father,
why did you underestimate
the son you raised yourself?
Here is the petition
signed by
all 216 Xiao Army soldiers.
(Petition)
Qian,
you volunteered to fight?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I wronged General Xiao.
I wronged all the soldiers
of the Xiao Army.
General Chai.
You already regret it.
Then tell us the truth.
In the Mingshui Battle,
the commander died,
and 30,000 soldiers perished.
Was it fate
or a setup?
Beware of He Rufei.
He told me to hold back
General Xiao's plea for help
for a few days.
Beware of whom?
He Rufei.
Mr. Chai.
Was anyone else involved?
I only had contact with He Rufei.
But I'm sure
someone in the capital was involved.
He sounded like
someone highly influential.
Who could be
more influential than Xu Jingfu
in the court?
Congratulations
(Li Kuang, Eight Warriors of Fuyue Army)
on being entitled General Feihong.
He Rufei.
It's you.
In the Mingshui Battle,
you made me hold back
General Xiao's plea for help,
killing General Xiao
and 30,000 Xiao Army soldiers.
No, I'm not He Rufei.
You're not He Rufei?
Are you He Yan
or He Rufei?
(Beware of He Rufei.)
(He made me hold back)
(General Xiao's plea for help)
(for a few days.)
(The "He Rufei" Chai Anxi mentioned)
(should be me.)
(But I never)
(saw him in private.)
(The one who contacted him)
(must have been the real He Rufei.)
(Therefore,)
(He Rufei must have)
(colluded with Xu Jingfu long ago.)
(But why did he
scheme against the Xiao Army?)
(Was my death)
(also part of the scheme?)
(No wonder Xiao Jue)
(took the Qinglang Sword)
(and was quite)
(defensive against me)
(at Yezhou Garrison,)
(suspecting)
(that I was a spy.)
(But he didn't know)
(that the He Rufei he knew)
(was not the He Rufei)
(who contacted Chai Anxi.)
(Anyway,)
(I must uncover the truth.)
(Huaijin deserves)
(an explanation.)
Young Master, you're back.
What did Chai Anxi say?
Is Chancellor Xu
involved in the Mingshui defeat?
Since you've obtained an answer,
I'll kill Chai Anxi now
to complete the mission.
No.
He can't die yet.
Where's Xiao Jue?
Went to see Her Highness.
In that case,
we should bid her farewell.
I didn't expect
that you're also leaving Jiyang.
Unfortunately,
we're going different ways.
We're bound to meet
in the imperial court again.
Commander's right.
Why did you
ask to speak in private,
even without He Yan?
I need
your help with something.
What is it?
He Yan
joined my ranks
disguised as a man.
You know best
what restrictions women face.
He Yan is patriotic
and has military prowess.
But her true identity
brings unnecessary complications.
Therefore,
she disguised herself as a man
to serve in the army.
We do need to
address this issue.
But it's not time yet.
So please help
keep her secret.
General Fengyun, rest assured.
You saved Jiyang.
We Jiyang people
won't let our saviors face any trouble.
Thank you.
Xiao Jue.
He Yan is Buwang's only disciple.
Though jade needs grinding to glow,
I won't allow
any man to bully or hurt her.
Jiyang will always be her maiden home.
Don't worry.
I'll keep your secret
even after I go back to the capital.
Thank you, Mr. Chu.
What a pity that you can't
take credit for this.
As long as Jiyang's safe.
Mr. Chu.
Let's stop here.
I was in the army.
Night walks don't scare me.
Actually,
I just wanted to walk with you.
You still call me "Mr. Chu."
That eases my mind.
I didn't know that Commander Xiao would
suspect my master.
By the way,
Yingxiang is holding
the mermaid-silk gown you gave me.
She will take it to your room.
Thank you.
Mr. Chu.
As Xu Jingfu's prized disciple,
you must know
more than you claim
about his dealings.
The real question is
how involved you were.
But you stood with Jiyang in crisis.
I believe
that you would never commit treason.
I hope you'll stop working
for the villain.
Master is a loyal man.
How can I believe
that he'd frame patriots
for no reason?
But Chai Anxi's detailed account
sowed doubts in me...
Never mind.
No matter what lies ahead,
I seek only to act
without regret or guilt.
Then I wish you
a safe journey.
Miss He,
you truly stand apart from other women.
They
lack your resilience.
What they desire
is merely to find a match
for marital bliss and peaceful living.
Mr. Chu, your words
sound rather condescending.
How come?
Men can study literature,
join the military,
or become physicians and merchants.
Yet from birth,
women are expected
to be virtuous and demure,
learn needlework and etiquette,
all for marital servitude
and child-rearing.
Whether they want it matters not.
Because all this
is deemed natural and rightful.
I was small-minded.
Miss He,
as a woman,
you empathize
with women's plight.
You dare to pioneer paths
others dare not tread.
I truly admire you.
You find me different
because I've studied,
ventured out,
and even defied conventions
by joining the military,
as others might call it.
Yet how many women
share my experiences?
If they too
could witness
Yezhou's snows,
Jiyang's waters,
desert moons,
and mountain ranges,
tell me,
would they still tolerate
being confined to petty
domestic squabbles?
Would they still wallow in melancholy
and self-pity?
I wish to blaze
a different trail for you.
What do you think
of this proposal?
I need no one
to blaze a trail
on my behalf.
What I truly desire
is someone who'll walk beside me
to blaze a trail together.
Then who do you think
could
blaze a trail with you?
Could it be
Commander Xiao?
Commander.
You came back alone
just to bid him farewell?
Commander.
Chai Anxi
is dead.
We maintained
complete perimeter security
without lapse.
After nightfall,
some cleaners passed through
and suddenly attacked.
We fought fiercely
but failed to stop them.
Commander.
I've failed my duty.
Please punish me.
You did your best.
Cheng Lisu and Song Taotao
must be treating the injured.
Seek their medical aid.
Understood.
Commander, look.
This token bears Wutuo's lion emblem.
These assassins
could be Wutuo soldiers.
Wutuo soldiers?
Haven't they retreated after the defeat?
Mr. Chu,
you don't know anything about it?
Commander Xiao.
What do you mean?
Haven't I been
with you the whole time?
Chu Zhao is Xu Jingfu's prized disciple.
Are you suspecting him?
The role he has played in this
remains unclear.
But mobilizing Wutuo troops
is beyond his current capabilities.
Commander.
Come in.
I'm back.
Commander.
I've been thinking.
We can't just let it slide.
Shall we rush
to the capital to confront Xu Jingfu?
How can we confront him
without
our key witness?
But
we have some other leads.
At least, we've confirmed
that He Rufei
was indeed involved.
Xu Jingfu is a cunning old fox.
Then let's
look into He Rufei.
Find out how those two
were connected
before Mingshui.
Understood.
No wonder Mr. Cheng
keeps calling
He Rufei ungrateful.
General Xiao treated him so well
and gifted him the Qinglang Sword.
But in the end,
he betrayed us.
Anything else?
If not,
I'll take my leave.
Young Master.
Who sent those assassins?
Master, naturally.
I delayed taking action.
Master ran out of patience
and sent assassins.
All I had to do
was to stay out of it.
So I went to see Her Highness
to establish an alibi.
(But the truth must also surface.)
So I left behind evidence
to guide Xiao Jue.
Just like that,
Xiao Jue will suspect Chancellor Xu.
But he is in the capital.
Wouldn't Xiao Jue suspect
that you did it
on behalf of the Chancellor?
No, he wouldn't.
Xiao Jue knows full well
that Master would never
hand me evidence of colluding
with Wutuo people.
So, I couldn't possibly
mobilize Wutuo troops.
Even without Chai Anxi's testimony,
Xiao Jue will find other means
to fight Master
and He Rufei to the end.
A pity indeed for Chai Anxi,
once a valiant warrior,
now brought to such an end.
Young Master.
Chai Anxi was killed by Wutuo soldiers.
Will Chancellor Xu blame you
for failing his orders?
Gain and loss must balance.
Only thus endures.
Had I followed his orders,
we'd miss the secrets.
These secrets
and Sun Xiangfu's ledger
prove that Master has betrayed Wei.
(Cui Mansion)
Commander Xiao, Miss He.
Mr. Cheng, Miss Song.
Take care.
I don't know
when we'll meet again.
You repelled the Wutuo army
and saved us.
We appreciate it.
(Great Virtue)
Yan.
We'll pass through Chonghuai.
Shall we make a stop
and have fun for a few days?
(Wangjiang House)
Passing through Chonghuai,
I finally get to see
the renowned Wangjiang House.
Did you bring
enough money?
You wanted to come.
So, you're paying.
I suggested this trip to lift spirits
because Mr. He seemed troubled.
Once He cheers up,
Huaijin
will be happy too.
This place looks pricey.
Thank you, Mr. Cheng.
No problem.
Besides,
we can all chip in
if my money runs short.
Just like back at Ruyun House.
Right, Huaijin?
Leave me out of this.
The famous Ruyun House in the capital?
Why did you visit
without me?
Why would we take you?
You were just a kid.
How old were you?
(Guys,)
have you heard of Ruyun House?
Yaojing's biggest brothel.
I've been there.
It's overrated.
Young Master Yan is so experienced.
Of course.
You've been there?
No.
I lied.
Huaijin.
You woke up?
I heard Ruyun House
has a new songstress
named Hua Youxian.
Her stunning look
and heavenly voice
made her the top performer in a month.
Let's go hear her sing
after class.
Do you dare?
It's your turn now.
Tell you what...
Forget about Yan He.
He will brag about it
either way.
Let's go.
Only cowards back out.
He Rufei, you hear me?
Me too?
Let's go.
With the top student
Xiao Huaijin with us,
we won't be punished too harshly
even if we get caught.
Let's go.
Come on.
How do we sneak out?
He Rufei.
Keep up.
Don't be a coward.
Climb over here.
Careful.
- Thanks.
- Let's go.
Someone's missing.
Where's He Rufei?
I'm here.
Pathetic.
Thank you.
You can't even
climb the wall?
I didn't want to come.
Yan He
dragged me along.
Also,
aren't you, the top student,
also sneaking off to the brothel?
What's wrong?
Ruyun House
has long intrigued me.
Yan.
You don't look well.
Didn't you sleep well?
It's fine.
It's just some memories resurfacing.
Is it about Mr. Liu?
I-I'll stop.
Ruyun House is fascinating.
Huaijin.
Remember our old friends?
(Wangjiang House)
Cheng Lisu.
This is...?
Huaijin.
You remember Yang Mingzhi?
(Yang Mingzhi, Magistrate of Chonghuai)
I'm Yang Mingzhi.
Greetings, General Fengyun.
Mingzhi now serves
as Chonghuai's Magistrate.
We were classmates.
So I invited him here to catch up.
Are they enemies or something?
Back at Xianchang Academy,
they were close friends.
Yang Mingzhi
is the only son
of the current Minister of War.
He passed the exams years ago,
yet somehow ended up
as a lowly magistrate in Chonghuai.
Why are they acting
like strangers now?
I'm also curious.
Gentlemen,
fate brought us together
at the academy.
Cleared up your misunderstandings.
Cheng Lisu,
you may not know.
There is no misunderstanding
between us.
Huaijin.
Rest assured.
I'll convince my father
to plead for General Xiao
and urge His Majesty
to find out the truth.
As the Minister of War,
my father
has certain influence.
Mingzhi.
Thank you.
Xiao Zhongwu, as the commander-in-chief,
was reckless,
leading our troops into an ambush.
He was too proud
to seek prompt rescue,
which caused huge casualties.
Xiao Zhongwu
is a sinner to Wei.
(Xiao Mansion)
Huaijin.
I broke my promise.
Sorry.
I forced this burden on you.
No need to apologize.
I heard you volunteered
to go to Que City.
Word travels fast, it seems.
Are you insane?
I know you want to
restore honor to your father
and the Xiao Army.
But it's too risky.
I've made up my mind.
Don't try to dissuade me.
Huaijin.
Have you ever thought
that perhaps
there's no hidden truth?
Maybe General Xiao...
Yang Mingzhi.
From now on,
stay out of my sight.
(Xiao Mansion)
Yeah.
No misunderstandings.
In the end,
I'm nothing
but an oath-breaker.
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪I've seen the mountains♪
♪And trodden through ice♪
♪Day after day, I venture alone♪
♪Destiny is my creed♪
♪Ideals surge beneath the surface♪
♪Igniting the flame against the winds♪
♪A restless yearning in my soul♪
♪Gazing through the mire♪
♪Who cares about this boundless void♪
♪Charge ahead with blazing fervor♪
♪Stubbornly fighting with my life♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪
♪Soaring across the world's expanse♪
♪There must always be a longing♪
♪Disregard the wounds to seek the light♪
♪Light shines upon my heart♪
♪Unveiling scars,
I choose to swim upstream♪
♪The resonance of courage
rings loud and clear♪
♪It's the boldness
that defines existence♪
♪Chasing the light within my heart♪
♪Burying frailty,
embracing life through death♪
♪You'll meet gazes where storms brew♪
♪With our unwavering true love,
brave the world with me♪