(Rated 18+ Content suitable for
audiences 18 years and older.)
(There may be images, sound or
content that requires viewing discretion.)
(Viewers underage of 18
should be advised.)
(This series is fictional not
related to real person, place or event.)
What are you doing?
Breakfast.
Want some?
Uh... Akin, are you free tomorrow?
I was thinking of asking you to
go see the new house with me.
The brochure is on the table.
Ahhh.
Is it good?
Can I have more?
Of course.
The brochure is on the table.
I'll bring it to you.
Let me see.
What do you think?
It's nice.
Let's do it.
Then
I'll go ahead and set
an appointment for tomorrow.
Mmm-hmm.
It's really delicious.
Did you see the news
about Judy last night?
Yeah, I saw it.
It's all over the news.
And that crazy page admin…
No idea what's wrong with them.
Whether they date or break up,
it's their personal business.
I feel kind of bad for Judy.
Yeah, me too.
She always gets treated like this.
And whoever dates her
gets called “Judy Boy” too.
People, huh?
Don't they have
anything better to do?
That they go around giving
people nicknames like that.
And what about you, Akin—
do you want to have one too?
Huh?
“Akin Boy”.
But I'll only be
that for one person.
So cheesy.
Can I have a bite?
Pretty tasty, eating like this
Next time, I won't
bother bringing a fork.
Do you want to eat more?
Why did you move away?
These are all the photos
that sasaeng fan
managed to take.
The reason I called you here today…
is because I want you
to help spread the news.
Let's take a picture first.
Sure.
Thank you.
Tired?
A little bit.
The team really liked you today.
Really?
They said it'll probably
sell out for sure.
- That's good.
- Touch, we'd like to borrow Jin
for a quick magazine shoot.
- Oh, of course.
- Thank you.
Let me say hi to the fans first.
Sure.
Johnny, come stand
a little closer to your friend.
Akin, we'd like you
to say a few words
to greet the magazine's fans,
and invite them
to check out this issue.
You'll see all four of us featured…
in this month's issue
of N-ASH magazine.
Alright, let's gather
over at that corner.
Let me quickly check the pictures.
Sure.
Jin, are you tired?
Just a little. Are you tired?
Have you seen the leaked photos?
What leaked photos?
The leaked photos of Akin.
Hang in there, Akin.
Let's go to the bathroom.
What happened, Touch?
Let's go over there first.
Let's go for a massage.
Have you seen the leaked photos?
It's so scandalous. Who do
you think the other person is?
Yeah, who is that?
(Wait is this really Akin)
(Netizens suspect they're the #1 shipper )
(We need answers ASAP.)
(Why does it always come back to Akin?)
(Word on the street is this top actor's
been real busy around town)
(Sigma Entertainment would like to state the following...)
(We denied Jin were involved)
(We would like to cancelled...)
(any current or future project
(involving Akin and Jin)
(Sigma really is not playing)
(Really looking forward to legend of Gemini)
(Waitttt... If it is akin then the other person is Jin?)
(Careful now Sigma just... threaten to sue any false accusation)
I'm sorry.
For...
The sequel project of
"The Legend of Gemini"
and everything...
that you had to go
through because of me.
I'm really sorry.
Let's put aside the "Legend
of Gemini" project for now.
But even so,
please don't cancel this project.
Let Jin
stay in this project.
Right now, it's not
just affecting you anymore.
Jin is also getting
dragged into this mess.
They were smart to blur your face.
It's making it impossible
for us to file a lawsuit right away.
Another thing is,
if you go file a lawsuit now,
it's basically admitting that
you are the person
in those leaked photos.
So...
Does that mean...
Sigma wasn't behind this, right?
Otherwise,
why would they release those photos?
Why would they risk their
own talent becoming the target?
Why would they make
their own talent the target?
But I think the opposite.
They quickly clarified
the other person wasn't Jin.
It's like forcing you to go out
and confirm yourself
and help them confirm
that the other person is not Jin.
What that means is
they planned it
for me to protect Jin, right?
And if you don't
go help them confirm,
or if Jin comes out
and admits it directly
that the person in
the photo is Jin and you,
they're ready to release
even more intense photos
to condemn you both.
And they're also ready to
cut Jin out of the industry too.
But I think Sigma knows well
that someone like
you wouldn't let this happen.
I also made a mistake by
letting the photo leak like this.
Let's put the "Legend of Gemini"
project aside for now.
I'll try to find a way to fix this.
As for you, don't
do anything for now.
Just be extra careful
for the time being.
Not just for yourself,
but for Jin too.
Do you like eating
when you're stressed?
You must be really stressed, huh?
That photo was pretty scandalous.
And that was just one picture.
The engagement
was already that high.
If the full set got released...
What would happen, I wonder?
It was you, wasn't it?
You're the one
who leaked those photos.
Where did you even get them from?
Can't spill the tea on that one.
Oh, so now you can't talk, huh?
But when it came to my business,
you spread it all over social media.
Oh.
Well, the engagement
was too good to pass up.
Would've been
a waste not to post it.
Pathetic, isn't it?
Selling out someone's personal
life for a few scraps of money.
If it's leaked photos
of two “sexiest” guys,
the engagement must be sky-high.
Maybe high enough that I could quit
profiting off other people's misery, right?
Are you trying to threaten me?
Sigma would never
let you get away with that.
You're right.
They wouldn't
want me to do something like that.
But if I “accidentally” hit post...
I'd just get sued.
Worst case? I lose some money.
But you and
that rising star actor...
You'll be left with nothing.
What do you actually want?
But if you, Akin,
are willing to trade me
something spicier than this photo…
my finger might not
"accidentally" slip,
and post a picture showing
your boyfriend's face, for example.
You already know what I want.
Think it over.
I'll come back for your answer.
Jin,
what are your thoughts on
working with Judy again?
First of all, I'd like to thank
the higher-ups for trusting me.
And lately, I've really
been enjoying my work a lot.
Also, I want to tell
everyone in advance—
This drama—
I promise it won't
disappoint anyone.
Please stay tuned.
We hope you'll watch it!
Thank you.
It's not just affecting you anymore.
Jin is also being
dragged into suspicion.
Be more careful these days.
Not just for your own sake…
but for Jin's too.
(Telephone)
(No profile information.
Add to your favorites list.)
(Jun)
Hello, Jun?
Kin...
Why didn't you answer when I called?
Sorry.
Calling you out this late...
I called you so many times.
Do you know how worried I was?
I saw the news.
But you're not alone in this.
Let's face this problem together.
I'll be by your side.
Don't disappear on me again.
Let's break up.
Huh?
What kind of joke is that?
Do I look like I'm joking?
Do you really want
to break up with me?
If not today,
then one day...
we'd have to break up anyway.
I never intended to be serious
with you in the first place.
Kin, stop lying.
Tell me the truth.
What are you hiding?
Why?
Just because I said
I want to break up,
you can't accept it?
Kin, I said stop lying.
We made a promise.
You, too...
Stop lying to yourself.
For the last time...
Tonight...
I'll stay with you.
Let's just get it over with.
You act like you don't really want this.
Did I mean so little to you?
You were never supposed
to mean anything at all.
Fine.
What's up?
I accept your offer.
But you…
You must not release any more
photos. Absolutely not.
Okay.
See you in two weeks.
Goodbye, Jin.
Goodbye, Jun.
♪Oh, you got me infatuated♪
♪Just by the way that you move♪
♪That you move♪
♪No, nothing else could make me feel the♪
♪Way that your body ever could♪
♪Ever could♪
♪Oh, you got me infatuated♪
♪Just by the way that you move♪
♪That you move♪
♪No, nothing else could make me feel the♪
♪Way that your body ever could♪
♪Ever could♪
I'll give you one more chance.
I won't let you down.
Isn't this a bit too easy?
Prove yourself.
Prove that you deserve
the chance I'm giving you.
Okay.
I'll prove it to you.
That I won't disappoint you.
Very good. Passed, you passed.
Good. Now let's
go bring out the props.
You did great, Jin.
Thank you.
You're really good at this.
You were amazing too, Judy.
Aw, if I didn't have Jin…
I wouldn't have gotten
into character this much.
Hello, Ford?
Do you have a minute to talk?
Jin and Judy's pairing…
Their chemistry is amazing.
They totally
killed it on set just now.
Seriously.
The photographer even
pinched his own leg…
Almost left a bruise.
Hey—
How did you end up in my room?
This is my room, idiot.
You came in here, dragged me into
drinking and acting like a mess…
Now look at the state
of my workspace.
Don't you remember?
Ye dafty!
Your room was already messy anyway.
But you look better than I expected.
I thought you'd be crying
your eyes out or something.
Crying about what?
I'm a grown-up, you know.
It's just a small thing.
Yeah.
Hey—
About the "Legend
of Gemini" project...
Is it still going?
Yeah, there's still
a chance it'll continue.
But I still haven't found
someone to replace you.
But now that page has
gotten a ton of photos.
There must be one that
shows Jin's face for sure.
And even now, they still
haven't released anything.
Did you make some
kind of deal with them?
No.
Heh.
I just said...
That I'd give them
something juicier instead.
Are you out of your mind, Akin?
It's fine, really.
At most...
I might
not be the lead actor anymore.
But I've got nothing to lose anyway.
With skills like mine...
I can still get work easily.
As for that page owner...
At most...
He'll just...
Maybe just shoot some nudes.
And what if he does that to you?
I want to know.
Are you prepared for what's coming?
Go ahead.
Do it.
Come on then.
Go ahead.
With you shaking like that, I don't
think I can go through with it.
You idiot.
This is such a serious issue and you're
still trying to solve it all by yourself?
Why didn't you
just tell Jin the truth?
Jin's future is
looking really bright.
I don't want him to get
dragged into something like this.
And what about your future?
Mine's over, bro.
I'm done.
But Jin...
He's just getting started.
You feel the same, don't you?
Does love really make people blind?
You talk like...
You've actually been in love before.
That's my business.
But you...
With all the dumb stuff
you've done up till now,
I've never stopped you.
Just this one thing—please.
Your time is not over.
Trust me.
Want something to eat?
Good evening, Master Akin.
Do you have a few moments...
just to talk to a lowlife like me?
Just five minutes?
Being this close to me...
You better watch out people might
saying we're sleeping together.
Honestly, I wouldn't mind.
Just afraid...
That the real one
will come punch me.
It's Jin, isn't it?
Yeah, it is, isn't it?
The guy who wants it...
But doesn't know the right time.
How many guys like that
do you think there are?
I'm only saying this because...
I care about you, Akin.
Someone I love
and respect, that's all.
I get it—desire...
It's hard to control.
But try to keep it in check, okay?
Don't worry.
From now on...
There won't be any
more of those photos.
What do you mean?
Because he and I...
will never see each other again.
Can you really do that?
Hey.
Worry about yourself instead.
This Akin...
Isn't that weak, you know.
Ouch.
What was that for?
Acting all tough, huh?
Hey.
You and Master Akin—
what's going on between you two?
None of your business.
So you really broke up, huh?
Guess it's finally my turn then.
I said stay out of it.
Is your car here
to pick you up, Jin?
Yes.
Did you change your perfume?
Do you like it?
I'm so jealous of that couple.
Your perfume smells nice too, Judy.
Hey, Narude.
You knew about them too?
There's nothing good on TV lately.
I'll prove it to you—
That I won't let you down.
Seriously, nothing worth watching.
Hey, why'd you turn off the TV?
Jin and Judy's drama
was getting good!
Akin, time to eat!
So tasty!
Hey, Akin.
Eat as much as you want.
Lyn really took her time
marinating the pork today.
She even boiled it herself.
Thank you.
Eat a lot, okay?
You know...
Wait a sec.
You eat like a kid—
Made a mess all over your face.
Still as tender as ever.
Oh, stop exaggerating.
Seriously, you're all messy now.
Akin, why do you look so down?
Did Sine usually wear a ring?
I've never seen him wear one before.
He tends to lose things a lot.
So when he goes out...
he usually takes the ring
off to keep it safe.
It's a wedding ring, after all.
Wouldn't be worth it if it got lost.
There's only one in the world.
That's true.
Even if you make a new one...
the feeling of wearing it—
it just wouldn't be the same.
Wait, what?
Why are you suddenly so
interested in wedding rings?
Are you planning to
marry someone already?
No, it's not like that.
I just...
was curious, that's all.
Oh, really?
I've been wondering…
what kind of person truly
captures your heart?
Ever since I've known you—
I've never seen you
show interest in anyone.
I'm still enjoying
my career in the industry.
And right now...
there's no one I'm serious about.
Probably won't be for a while.
Oh, please.
Back then, I was still enjoying
my career in the industry too.
But now...
I think I made the right decision.
You could say...
I was preparing my heart.
Preparing your heart?
Wearing this ring—
It's not just to show others that
we're married.
It's also to remind ourselves
that from now on...
our lives will be filled with
both joy and hardship—
together with this one person,
for the rest of our lives.
That's how I wear this ring.
Hey, Akin...
Love isn't
just about the pretty side.
Today might be
filled with happiness,
but tomorrow could bring sorrow.
Still, no matter what problems come,
we have to face them together.
Not let one person
carry the burden alone.
Mom.
Want some snacks, sweetie?
No.
Already full?
Thanks a lot, Sine.
Nana, you strangling me!
Nana!
Are you teasing mommy?
(Don't forget our date,
I'm picking you up tomorrow)
Anyway, I'll be
counting on you, Judy.
Of course.
But I want a reward...
Do you have a shoot today?
No.
I'm running an errand.
What about you, Judy?
Jin and I have a live
interview together today.
Then I'll take my reward in advance.
You really think
I'd do something, huh?
I... I...
Welcome to Midnight Matter tonight!
We're live right now, folks.
And tonight—at this very moment—
- Are you nervous?
- No one's hotter than this pair.
- Yes.
- As our special guests today!
- It's my turn now!
- Let's enjoy this live broadcast together!
Without further ado...
Please welcome Jin and Judy!
- Hello.
- Hello!
Please, have a seat.
Such a gentleman!
Thank you so much...
for honoring our show.
- It's our pleasure.
- We're glad to be here.
Jin has been on
the show once before.
And Judy — well, I feel
like we meet all the time!
(I made it to the front already.)
(I hope you
haven't forgotten our deal.)
You're in the front, right?
I'm starting to wonder...
maybe this couple isn't
just "fan-shipped" anymore?
We saw Jin wearing
a ring on his pinky finger.
So what's the deal with that?
Whoa, kicking things
off with the spicy question?
Well, our show is
known for being bold.
And tonight's
no different — brace yourselves!
You heard that,
everyone watching at home.
Send us your juiciest questions!
Let's take a peek at a few,
shall we?
We'll go with a rapid-fire round.
Quick questions,
quick answers. Ready?
Are you two actually a couple?
No, we're not.
But who knows what the future holds?
Smooth answer.
So charming.
I feel pretty just hearing that!
Alright viewers,
keep the questions coming!
Let's take a look
at a few more, shall we?
You idiot...
Even now, you're still trying to fix
this whole mess by yourself?
Let me read this next
comment out loud...
Jin and Judy are 100% cake!
Jin probably acts this way
with everyone he works with.
Just look at Jin and Akin…
They used to seem super close!
Jin seemed really close to Akin.
But after Akin's scandal,
they don't seem as close anymore.
Mr. Akin,
don't keep me waiting too long.
Or that photo will be
out before you know it.
I don't have time, bro.
Wait—
How long are you planning to carry
this burden all by yourself, Akin?
I said I don't have time!
Is this about
the leaked photo of Akin?
Because I was just
about to clear that up.
There's been
a huge misunderstanding.
Actually, the person in that photo…
wasn't Akin.
The person in that photo
it was me.
Wait—hold on.
Are you saying...
the leaked photo...
the one where people were
getting handsy—that was you?
So then... who were
you with in that photo?
You wanted to talk to me, Jin?
Yes, I'll get straight to the point.
You know who
leaked Akin's photo, don't you?
Jade told me...
that you might be able to help.
Why do you want to know this, Jin?
Even if you find out,
it won't change anything.
What if...
you and I work together?
But it's risky.
What do you have
to offer in return, Jin?
So... who was Jin with in the photo?
It was me—Judy.
Huh?
Wait, what?
But it was just
a scene from a drama.
Yeah, it was from
a drama we were filming.
You don't have to carry
this burden alone anymore.
(Come on, hurry up!)
(Are you even listening?)
- Take a look at both these photos.
- (It's from a drama!!)
It's a scene from a drama.
Just looked at all the details.
Okay, all netizens show's over,
please disperse!
What a shame.
Why did it turn out like this?
Your kid messed everything up.
My page got mass-reported
and removed completely.
Are you done talking?
Come here.
If I were you,
I'd keep my mouth shut.
Because you're not in a position
to bargain with me about anything.
These days…
Don't forget...
You only have what you
have now because of me.
I'm sorry, Judy,
for dragging you into this mess.
Getting the chance to have a ship with
the "Sexiest Man of the Year"?
If I didn't grab
that chance, I'd be a fool.
If the day ever comes when you want
to wear that ring again for real…
Just let me know.
I'll be waiting.
You don't have to wait anymore.
Kin.
Let's go home, Jun.
Hey!
(Jun)