Bobby, Bobby, listen carefully.
Glen killed the seller
of pimple patches.
He's the mastermind.
You made me this way!
Because of you!
I don't have a son
who kills people!
You really don't know
all the things I've done
for you!
You should be thanking me!
I don't have a son
who's a demon!
You're an animal!
Dad, you need to drink this.
- Take it.
- Give that...
Crawl.
- Goodbye, Dad.
- Hidalgo Street?
- That's right near here.
- Bobby?
They've been looking for you
at the party for some time now.
Something happened to daddy.
Let's take him
to the hospital, quick!
Father...
Fight, Father!
Glen, what happened?
We were just talking,
then he suddenly had an attack.
What are you doing here?
You're not part of the family,
go away!
What are you doing here?
Boss, the Mayor was rushed
to the hospital.
Why? What happened?
I heard he had a stroke.
Tonyo, it's father...
Glen, what happened?
You need to fix this, Cecilia.
What do you mean?
My dad saw me
kill someone earlier.
What?
That's probably
why he was stressed,
then he suddenly had an attack.
But I have,
I have a plan.
Listen, Cecilia.
If the doctors can revive him,
Cecilia, listen to me.
I need you to do
something for me.
Are you seriously
asking me this?
We're talking about your father.
Wait a minute,
why do you suddenly
have a conscience?
I was fine destroying
Victor Santiago's reputation
for you,
but this...
Cecilia, you don't understand.
If my dad lives, I'm dead.
So please do this for me.
Please.
Cecilia...
Cecilia!
Tonyo, it's father.
What's the update, Doc?
I'm sorry.
We did everything.
The Mayor is dead.
What?
No, no!
No, Doc!
Not yet, no, no!
Not yet, Doc!
Doc, no.
Mom?
No, Doc!
Your daddy!
It's not true!
Dad!
Daddy!
It's going be okay,
it's going be okay,
it's going be okay.
No!
Why? What happened?
It's not true! Your daddy!
No!
Joaquin!
Mommy ...
Daddy...
- Joaquin...
- Daddy...
Joaquin!
Daddy!
Joaquin, don't, I can't.
Joaquin, how are you feeling?
I'm okay, Sophia.
I'm just grateful
that I'm still alive.
I'm sorry.
I should have listened to you.
Oh, don't go, Joaquin!
Didn't I promise to help you
with the campaign?
So what can I be of service?
Hi!
Hi! See you in the upcoming
elections!
No, Joaquin!
Thank you, Glen.
I'm proud of you.
You are my partner
in taking care of Calabari.
I got to hand it to you, Son.
You're already learning
the ropes.
For sure, you have a good
impression with the press.
Go ahead.
Your father is waiting for you.
Father...
Father?
Is what I heard true?
You called me "Father"?
From now on,
I accept that I have a father.
Thank you very much, my child.
What are you doing here?
Can't you just let our family
grieve?
Get out! Get out!
Get out of here!
Get out!
You're not our family!
Joaquin...
I think Bobby knows where he is.
Bobby? Why Bobby?
Well, earlier, I heard Bobby
talking to the Mayor
on the phone.
Then look now,
she's not here, right?
She left.
What was the last thing
you and my husband talked about?
- Ma'am...
- And why didn't you tell anyone
you were going to see him?
Ma'am, I don't know,
he just called me.
When I got there,
he and Glen were together.
Why are you involving Glen here?
You know, honestly,
just go away!
I don't want to see you here!
Don't come near us!
You're unlucky!
Ma'am, please excuse me!
I know you're all hurting
because of the Mayor's loss,
but let's not blame others.
It's not Bobby's fault here.
You know, you too!
You two leave here!
We don't want to see you!
You're the jinx in our lives!
Go away!
Mom, Mom, that's enough,
that's enough, please.
Go away!
Don't show yourself to us!
You're not part of our family!
You're such a thick-faced!
What? Are you going
to piss me off again?
Have you heard?
What's that again?
The Mayor is dead.
What?
What a shame,
he's my idol.
Oh my...
Oh my, he's my idol too.
That's terrible, isn't it?
It's shocking.
What happened?
I think he had a stroke,
it seems like that.
Cecilia, how are you?
Oh, what's the news
about the Mayor?
Eric, let's just catch up
next time, okay?
Oh, okay.
We received
some sad news tonight.
Our beloved mayor,
Joaquin "El Hepe" Guerrero,
has passed away after being
rushed to the hospital
due to a severe stroke
that resulted
in a brain hemorrhage.
According to the doctors,
he arrived at the hospital
with a weak pulse,
but his condition
did not improve.
He was declared dead,
at around nine twenty-four
in the evening.
Mayor Joaquin was known
as a seasoned actor
before he entered politics.
As a politician,
he is known
for suppressing criminality
throughout Calabari.
For now, the city is expressing
its condolences
to the Guerrero family.
His friends and town folks
are expected to flock
to the funeral
that will be held.
Have you called Bobby yet?
Cap, we can't contact her.
Me too, Cap.
I've been trying to call her,
but she's not answering.
This must be very painful
for Bobby,
for my grandchild.
Stop crying, Captain.
Today, is set to be taken
to his final resting place,
the beloved mayor of Calabari,
Mayor Joaquin "El Hepe"
Guerrero.
All of the Mayor's fellow
citizens are mourning
because of his sudden passing.
It is remembered
that El Hepe just won
the last election with his son,
Vice Mayor Glen Guerrero,
who is expected to replace him
as the new mayor of Calabari.
Bobby, are you sure
you really want to drink?
You don't really drink.
Do you regret...
not going to your father's
funeral earlier?
I don't want to cause trouble.
You know Ma'am Sophia
is mad at me, right?
I'll just pray for father.
You know, Bobby,
I find it weird.
Why?
Why are the Mayor and Vice Mayor
together in that place?
We know it's secluded.
What do you care, Abdul?
Bobby said it,
the father and son
had a heart-to-heart talk.
Heart-to-heart, and then
he suddenly had a stroke.
- What was that, right?
- Right?
What now, girl?
Are you still going to visit
your siblings
with Mayor Joaquin?
Not anymore.
You know, the mother of
my siblings is allergic to me.
What about the youngest girl?
Aren't you close to her?
And she treat you like a sister.
Bobby.
Oh, Sir Tonyo, you're here.
Move over.
Thank you.
How are you?
I'm okay.
I just don't want to be alone.
But tomorrow, I'm going to work.
You're going to work right away?
Bobby, you need to rest.
Believe me,
I've been through that.
I know that.
I've been through that too,
haven't I with godmother.
So I know the feeling too.
T hat break doesn't affect me.
Sorry.
I'm sorry too.
Well, if you need someone
to talk to,
just call me anytime.
It's mine, I need it.
Sorry, Dad.
You shouldn't have died...
but it's your fault too.
I wish you hadn't bothered.
I wish you'd just kept
your mouth shut
if you knew anything about me.
I'm not a bad kid,
but I won't let you
ruin all my dreams either.
I'll apologize to you
next time...
when we meet in hell.
Sergeant Enriquez?
Your grandmother said
you were here.
By the way,
I'm Attorney Noel Cariaga,
the Mayor's family attorney.
Oh, Attorney, what do you need?
I would like to invite you
to our office.
Attorney, we can start now.
Ma'am, can we wait a moment?
We're still waiting for someone.
Who?
Sergeant Enriquez.
Oh, sit down, sit down.
Oh, here.
Attorney, what's that woman
doing here?
Sergeant Enriquez is here
because she's one
of Mayor Joaquin's inheritors.
What?
That's absurd!
- Are you kidding me?
- Mom, mom.
Please sit down,
calm down, please.
That's enough.
Okay...
I just want to know what kind
of nonsense this is.
What was bequeathed to her?
I want proof.
Here are the documents,
Ma'am Sophia.
Here's your copy.
This is your copy.
There.
As you can see,
most of the properties
and assets
were equally divided
among the three of you.
And the only thing left
to bequeath to Miss Enriquez
is the rest house in Batangas
and the ten million in cash.
This is not possible!
And I don't care
if he bequeaths
even one property to her!
Because in the first place,
she shouldn't be bequeathed!
I want that rest house!
Mommy, you never liked
that place, remember?
You and daddy even fought
because you were so angry
when he bought you
that rest house
as a gift for your birthday,
remember?
Exactly!
It was a gift for me!
So it doesn't matter
if I like it or not!
Mom, please stop it.
It's embarrassing
for the Attorney.
It's embarrassing?
Yes.
Isn't it more embarrassing
for this illegitimate child
to be meddling
in the family inheritance?
If you have any dignity
or decency left
in the bones of your body,
you will disclaim
your inheritance...
Mom! Please stop it!
This is dad's last will.
Are we going to deny him that?
Let's just give it to him.
Let's give Bobby
what dad wants to give him.
Please...
Let's do it for dad.
A resort and ten million pesos?
Yes,
but she's thinking about
what he's going to do
with that inheritance.
Oh, Captain, well...
let's go on vacation.
I will wearing my two-piece!
Me, my one-piece!
That's a shame.
Stop it!
Let's just wait and see
what Bobby decides.
Okay.
If you really don't want to go
on vacation,
why don't we just split
the ten million pesos?
And let's get a facelift.
I'll get something done...
I'll get a nose job,
and then my hips,
they're a bit big.
- Perfect!
- So I need to reduce her.
- Isn't it?
- Stop it.
The ten million isn't enough
for your facelift.
- Oh my...
- You're really bad, Captain.
- You're insulting us.
- That's right.
Hey, Captain, where's Bobby?
She went home.
She said he wanted to be alone.
I'll go home first.
I'll cook him a delicious meal.
- You stay there.
- Captain,
set aside some food for us.
I hope Captain's cooking
is delicious.
- It's Zondra!
- Oh, why?
- She was killed!
- Killed?
Yes, and they're asking
for donations.
Oh no, I feel like
this is a hate crime.
What makes you say that, Mar?
They're killing
all the beautiful gays.
Oh no, I got nervous.
- What do I do?
- That's why.
- Yes.
- Don't be nervous.
Poor Zondra.
That's why.
There, oh.
Zondra!
Zondra, don't leave me!
Mother!
She said she's the victim's
daughter.
What's going on
in the world right now?
But, Bok, I don't know
what it feels like
to lose a loved one.
Oh, when you're put
in that situation,
you really don't know
what to do.
It seems like nothing
can prepare you
for the kind of pain
you're going to feel.
We don't even have a picture
of the two of us together,
Father.
It took a while
before I accepted you.
I was so fussy!
Grandchild...
I know you're sad.
Bobby, we're just here...
if you need someone to talk to.
And don't forget
we were close friends
before you got rich.
That's right, Bobby.
But if you don't want
the ten million,
then you can give it
to Mar and me.
We're okay with that...
What's with you?
What ten million
are you talking about?
What are you thinking,
granddaughter?
I'm just sorry, Grandmother.
I only got to spend
a little time with father.
I still have so much
to tell him.
I hope he'll show himself to me,
even if it's just in a dream.
Oh, Bobby, we know someone,
a psychic.
Right, Mar?
Oh, yes!
It's like the soul
of the departed enters her body,
and then you can talk to him.
Right?
You two are something else,
what are you talking about?
Psychic?
That's a scam.
Oh, Grandmother, that's true,
isn't it?
Yes, the one we know,
she's good!
It's Madam Alma.
Are you ready, Mother?
We need to take a deep breath.
Another one.
Hold my hands.
Let's close our eyes
together, okay?
One...
Two...
Three...
Don't open your eyes.
I was just asking her for help
to find out
who killed my mother,
And then I found out
she was just acting!
Hey, what acting?
What acting
are you talking about?
Do you have proof?
I saw something!
Icepick!
- Icepick?
- I saw it, yes!
I can't believe it.
The details she gave
are exactly the same.
How would Alma know
about Zondra's files?
It's only been days
since nilibing si daddy.
We have different means
of coping up.
Yours is so different.
Because out of the three of us,
You seem to be the one
who is least affected
by daddy's loss.
You have a visitor.
- Who?
- There, oh.
- Bobby.
- Tonyo.