I'm the one Will asked to sub
for him during your operation.
Corporal Allen Matibag.
I can't do it, I can't do it.
Anika?
There's Anika.
Who's the guy with her?
Come with me if you don't want
to get hurt.
Wait, Bro.
We can't catch up with them.
- There! Take that one.
- Let's go.
Hey, that's our bike! Hey!
It depends on whether you
tell me who your supplier is.
It's Jhem.
Tell her to meet you
at Malindang Park.
Enriquez, just leave the search
for Mando to them.
Here are the pictures
of the four prisoners
who escaped from Calabari
Prison.
Operation Manhunt starts now.
Just assign Mando to me.
I'll take care of him.
Bro, this is their car.
Yes, that's the one.
Guys, I need your help.
You need to get
to Malindang Park right now.
Why did you choose Mando?
We know that Sir Tonyo
is Mando's target, right?
Right now, he can't do anything
because he knows there are a lot
of police officers
at the hospital.
But I won't wait for that, Sir.
I'll move now.
The prisoners can't escape
just like that.
I think they have a proper
connection.
I think we have a new enemy.
Go hide. Your face
is all over the news.
Boss, this is Mando.
I will work on that.
I just need to finish this.
I don't know.
It happened so fast.
He pointed a gun at me,
and then I couldn't do anything.
How much was stolen?
It was about three
thousand pesos,
and the item he took costs
one thousand five hundred pesos.
What item was that?
It looks like this.
Teddy bear, one of the things
we sell.
He took the pink teddy bear.
Good thing it was caught
on CCTV.
Oh my!
Please don't!
I know him.
That's Rodell Pacheco.
He has multiple theft cases.
I remember him
from the news earlier.
He's from Sta. Lucia,
boundary of Calabari
and our town.
It's just near here.
Miss, stop crying.
We'll make sure to catch
that thief.
I'll hold on to that,
Sir, Ma'am.
Let's go.
Anika!
Jhem.
What happened?
Have you and Vic talked yet?
And why did we meet here?
Sorry, Jhem,
I don't have a choice.
I'm really sorry, Jhem.
I don't really have a choice.
I'm sorry.
What are you saying?
Jhem...
Anika, what is this?
I was the one who asked you
to come here.
Don't worry,
Monty is my co-worker.
So he gave you
the remaining items?
What do you need?
I just want to get
the remaining items.
I'll take care of selling them,
so you won't be bothered
anymore.
Just tell me
where you kept them.
Bro, there they are.
Who's that other girl?
That's not important anymore,
Bro.
Look, he's pointing a gun
at them.
Come on, we need to take action!
We have to wait
for the right time.
Come on, let's go around.
Come on, hurry!
Come on.
What do you want?
I already told them everything.
Romel, I'm Master Sergeant
Bobby Enriquez,
and this is my partner,
Patrolman Jake Noble.
Maybe you remember something
Mando mentioned to you.
Anything that might help us
find him.
Nothing, you're just repeating
yourself.
Our plan is, until we escape,
we'll be on our own after that.
Do you know who helped you
escape?
It's possible that he helped
Mando hide.
He didn't mention anything
either.
Just someone with a lot
of contacts and connections
here in Calabari.
Do you know why he helped him
escape?
No.
Mando said that he was
his old boss.
I don't know. Maybe he's got
a new job for him to do.
Okay, thank you.
Wait, wait.
Maybe you can talk to Warden.
I'm having a hard time
being isolated here.
I'm sorry.
That's the result
of your bad decision.
We really hope that
you're telling the truth,
because if Mando hurts someone,
it's on your hands too.
Let's go.
That's too bad, Conde.
Your girlfriend is already dead.
The problem is...
who can I use to get you
out of the hospital?
Hurry up, hurry up!
There you go.
Hey, Selena, you're crazy.
Does Sir Tonyo know
that you have a duplicate key
to his house?
Oh, come on. Of course,
I didn't tell him.
Oh my, Sis.
You're crazy!
You're really assuming.
Well, it's useful, isn't it?
I'm sure Sir Tonyo needs
a change of clothes
at the hospital.
It's better to have some
rather than none.
- You do have a point.
- Come on.
- Come on, let's hurry.
- Hurry.
Sir Tonyo is waiting.
Hurry, hurry.
My contact said that Rodell
Pacheco's former residence
is in this village.
We need to catch him
as soon as possible.
He might hurt someone else.
Positive.
There he is.
Son of a...
- Let's go!
- Hurry!
Stop!
- Let's go!
- Get out of the way!
- Hey! Come here!
Hey! Let's go this way!
Hey!
Hey! Hey, stop!
Come on, let's go.
I want to talk to Monty first.
What's the point?
Are you guys dating?
You're still young!
I need to talk to Monty.
I need to know if he knows
what you're doing.
You don't seem to understand,
Kid.
Monty works for me,
so you need to listen to me!
You won't know
where the remaining items are.
Unless you tell me that you can
get Monty out of jail.
Hey!
Come here. Kneel!
Don't fight back. Kneel!
Don't fight back.
Rodell Pacheco,
you're caught already.
Rodell?
Rodell...
Dad's there?
Dad!
I'm glad you came
to my birthday.
Are they the ones you said were
your hide-and-seek friends?
Yes, my child.
But they caught me.
Are you happy that I'm here
on your birthday?
Your dress looks nice,
my child.
My child, this is my gift
to you.
Wow!
This is beautiful!
Thank you, Dad!
I know you've wanted this
for a long time.
Happy birthday, my child.
Your dad loves you very much.
Peach...
Sir Tonyo will be happy.
He has a complete set
of clothes.
You know, girl,
you're so obvious.
What do you mean?
That you like Sir Tonyo.
You know, we used to be
like that too.
But we've long accepted
that Tonyo loves someone else.
Who?
The beautiful police officer
he works with, Ma'am Bobby.
During the fiesta,
there was something in the way
they looked at each other.
You know, that's just
your hunch.
As for me, I feel
that Sir Tonyo likes me.
Okay? Let's go.
Come on.
Where can I find Bobby?
It means you did all this
to give your daughter
a present for her birthday?
And to give money to my wife.
I haven't given her money
in a long time.
Love...
what now?
Everything you gave us
was stolen.
We need to return this money
and your daughter's teddy bear
as well.
I'll take care of that, Ma'am,
and the vendor whom he robbed.
Thank you.
Really, Boss?
Thank you very much.
Don't thank me.
I just remembered my father.
He's like that to me, too.
He's always absent
on my birthdays.
But I'm sorry, we need
to take you back to Calabari.
I understand.
I know I won't last long
as a fugitive.
I just want to see my family
on my daughter's birthday.
Let's go.
Rodell...
Dad!
Are you leaving again?
Yes, my child.
When are you coming back?
I don't know yet.
Thank you for the teddy bear,
Dad.
I love you, Dad!
Jhem...
Jhem, tell him where
the pimple patches are.
Tell him, please.
- Please.
- No.
I'm not afraid of him, Anika.
He needs something from me.
I know you can't kill me.
Unless I tell you where the
remaining items are, right?
So if I were you,
stop wasting your time
and tell me that you're going
to get Monty out of jail!
When he gets out, fine,
I'll give you those damn
pimple patches!
You know, you're right.
I can't kill you...
but I can kill her.
Anika!
Shut up!
You animal!
Do you want to be the next one?
Where are the remaining items?
Where?
Don't move!
Hey, stop!
Vince, wait a minute!
I know we're tired,
sleep-deprived, and hungry.
Don't worry.
I'll have the food delivered,
okay?
- Sir, thank you!
- Sure!
Samson, Paloma.
Chief.
What are you doing here?
What's up?
One of the fugitives
were found near our area.
We caught him.
He's in jail already.
Really?
Thank you very much!
You're welcome.
Thank you very much
for your help.
Perfect timing.
Don't leave just yet, okay?
I ordered some food.
Let's eat here.
- Yes, okay.
- Okay.
Come in.
Let's go.
Enriquez!
Sir.
What's the update?
Sir, we came from Mando's
old house.
It's now a factory.
Bobby, we've caught
one of the fugitives.
He's in jail already.
Thank you.
Bobby.
Major.
Major, a tip came in
about Mandong Warak.
Did you check if it's legit?
Yes, Sir.
The caller sent a picture,
but it's a bit blurry.
Let me take a look.
Enriquez...
go there.
Bobby, do you need backup?
Thank you very much,
Lieutenant Samson,
but we can handle it.
- Sir, we'll go ahead.
- Okay, be careful.
I'm really good
at faking things.
Let's see if they will take
this bait.
Go ahead.
Send someone over.
I miss killing a cop too.
Hey, stop!
I'll kill you!
Don't kill me, please.
Miss, don't be afraid.
I'm a police officer.
Are you going to arrest me?
I'm not a bad person.
I just really want Monty
to get out of jail.
Please, don't...
Miss, we already know that
you're Monty's girlfriend.
But I'm sorry,
I have to arrest you
because you're selling
pimple patch drugs on campus.
If I were you, Miss,
I'd confess and surrender.
Tell everything.
Maybe your sentence
will be reduced.
Hey!
What are you doing
to our friend?
Hey!
Hey, come back here!
Who were you talking to earlier?
I don't really know him,
but he's Monty's boss.
Where's the stash?
The pimple patch drugs
you were selling on campus?
It's in my dorm.
Anika!
What's our plan, Ma'am?
Chief said we need a positive
identification of Mando.
Once we see him,
we'll call for backup.
Copy.
Noble...
Remember...
no one's going to engage.
Let's just ID him,
then we'll regroup here.
It's clear, Ma'am.
Okay. Go there, I'll check here.
Bobby...
Sir Tonyo!
- Good thing you're awake!
- Hi, Sir Tonyo.
No need for that.
You're just interrupting
our moment here.
Sir Tonyo, here. We brought you
your clothes.
My clothes?
Sir Tonyo, don't ask where
your clothes came from.
She's right. Or where did
we get your clothes.
We're not involved in that.
That's all Selena's doing.
Okay, fine. I'll take
all the credit.
Come on, girls. Sir Tonyo
hasn't fully recovered yet.
But it's true, Sir Tonyo.
I'm the one who chose
your t-shirt, your shorts,
even your briefs!
You know, do you want anything?
Do you want to eat?
Are you thirsty?
The doctor said that
we can change your clothes.
I'll just change your clothes.
Do you want me to give you
a bath too?
I know how to give
a sponge bath.
We have fruits here as well.
We brought you some fruits.
Solid job.
Conde made the right choice
when he chose the two of you.
And I also heard about
you covering for Mariano.
Thank you very much, Matibag.
It's part of the job, Chief.
Good thing, Sir, my friends
have arrived.
Otherwise, I'd be dead by now.
Yes, Sir. Sir, maybe we can get
something to eat there.
- We're hungry.
- Hey!
You always expect something
in return for everything you do.
- Sir, I'm sorry.
- Why? Is it bad to be hungry?
Abi is downstairs
and brought some food.
Get whatever you want.
That's what I'm talking about!
- There you go!
- Thank you, Sir.
Eat well!
Nice!
Sir...
what now?
We didn't catch the guy Jhem
was talking to last night.
Well, you said you could
describe him to our artist,
right?
And he also left his gun behind,
Yes, Sir.
We'll profile him.
It'll be easier to find him.
Sir, by the way...
as for Jhem, what's going
to happen to her?
She'll definitely go to jail
for selling the pimple patch
drugs.
And we also got a large volume
of drugs in her dorm.
- She's beautiful, what a shame!
- She's too young, what a shame!
What did she do?
You wasted your life.
I think she's the same age
as my child.
You're so beautiful, Miss.
Sit down, Miss.
You're so beautiful,
what a shame.
What did she do?
Sorry, Monty.
You're useless!
I'm paying you, right?
Wait, Boss, relax, easy.
Why am I involved in this?
You asked me to lie low,
remember?
Go ahead and ask yourself.
Why were you asked to lie low?
Because you're a failure!
You're a failure, Roman!
And you, Dante...
two women,
and you can't handle them?
You can't handle them?
Boss, I told you some guys
interfered,
that's why my plan was ruined.
I almost got Monty's girlfriend
to confess where our items were.
Almost?
Where are they now?
Aren't they in the hands
of the police?
Even my products,
they've been thrown away!
They probably even
recognized you!
And aside from that...
Aside from that,
you left your gun behind.
You're so stupid!
Boss, you know that they don't
have a record of me.
So they can't get anything out
of me.
And you've really got the nerve
to talk back?
Really?
It's only a matter of time
before that Monty talks.
You know, you two, I don't care
what you have to do.
Monty and his girlfriend
must be killed.
Do you understand that?
Yes, Boss.
Go ahead and leave!
What now?
This won't take long, Boss.
My project is almost finished.
After this, I'm all yours.
Let's make things clear, Mando.
I gave you the money,
so I wouldn't have
to worry about you.
Boss, this won't take long.
You know that Conde ruined
my life, right?
I'm just going to get even.
I've found a way
to go after Conde.
I have his love team now,
Master Sergeant
Roberta Enriquez.
Bobby?
Yes, Boss.
Do you know her, too?
We won't have any problems,
Boss?
None.
Report to me afterwards.
Great.
Hello, Noble?
Did Ma'am Enriquez contact you?
No, why?
She suddenly disappeared from
the place you asked us to check.
What?
Let me go.
Hey!
I'll send our picture
to your boyfriend, okay?
It's Enriquez,
Mandong Warak got her.
Sir Tonyo is really
something else, Sir.
He really went alone
to save Ma'am Bobby.
If I were in his situation,
I would do the same.
Do you have a special
someone too, Sir?
Special someone?
Leave Bobby alone.
Not yet. I still want to play
with you.