- Dad! Dad!
- Victor!
Are you behind all of this?
Let go of me!
Aren't there a lot of people
angry at you?
Why are you blaming me?
It's over, Joaquin.
Your public image
is completely ruined.
This is bigger
than your rivalry with Victor.
People will lose
their trust in you.
This is Mayor Joaquin Guerrero,
Mira.
Are you ready
for your big break?
Ms. Beautiful!
You really don't want
to leave this place?
I just noticed in the video...
it sounded like a name Batsi.
Sebastian Placido, alias Batsi.
Sir, we might get in trouble...
If you don't want to come,
then don't.
I admit I didn't react well to
my daughter's abduction.
Victor Santiago, I'm asking
for your forgiveness.
El Hepe, 50 million.
I'll text the address and time.
I want that animal
captured alive...
I need to know
who's behind this.
Sir, they said they're already
at the exchange site with Mayor.
- No movement yet.
- Boss Tonyo.
We just want
to ask you something.
Sorry about the mess, Boss,
the house is a little chaotic.
El Hepe!
This belongs to Faye.
I don't know that person, Boss.
Lieutenant Conde!
What is it, Enriquez?
Let's go!
The kidnappers are here.
Mayor!
You all did well.
Oh, there's Faye!
- There's Faye!
- Mom, Mom.
You monsters.
Faye, sweetheart,
daddy's here now.
We can go home.
She can't hear you now, Mayor.
She's in a deep sleep now.
What now? Are we going down?
Mom, wait.
Let them be.
Oh my God, there she is.
The money is there.
Give me back my daughter!
Give me that!
No one moves until
the exchange is complete.
We need to make sure
that the victim is safe.
Copy, Chief.
There. Hey, check it out!
Once the Mayor
secures the package,
we move in.
What's the status
on the roadblocks?
They've got no way out, Chief.
Check it if it's real.
What? Is it real?
Boss, it's real.
Give me back my daughter.
Mayor, are you sure you didn't
bring any cops with you?
No.
I'm sure.
All right, Mayor.
But before you join her,
I want you to turn around
and raise your hands.
Don't want to, Mayor?
Turn around!
Oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Hands up...
Hands up!
Dance, Mayor.
Dance, Mayor, dance.
There, there, dance, Mayor.
Don't you dare turn around,
Mayor!
All units,
move towards to target!
Secure the victim!
Move, move, move!
Let's move, let's move!
Hurry!
Come on, hurry up!
- Let's go, come on.
- Move!
Daddy's here now.
Dear...
Mayor!
- Faye!
- Dear!
- Mom!
- Faye!
- Dear!
What is this? What is this?
- Dad...
- Where's Faye?
- Joaquin!
- Dad, what happened?
We've been played.
Major, bring those
bastards to me
as soon as possible!
Yes, Mayor.
It's Ms. Faye.
You're safe now.
Something feels off.
Get our gear.
Yes, Boss.
Would you look at our luck.
Turns out,
Batsi was the only answer.
Let's go, we can't stay here
any longer.
Come on!
We'll take you back to your
family now, Ms. Faye.
Miss, thank you so much.
Let's go.
Die, all of you!
This way! Go, go!
Hurry, hurry!
Take cover, take cover!
Sir, what do we do?
Surround them!
Let's find
a way around the back!
Let's go!
Come on! Here.
Stay there, don't move!
Noble! Dizon!
Get back in the car.
We'll handle it from here!
Go ahead.
- Enriquez, let's go!
- Okay, okay!
Stay here.
I'll go help Lieutenant Conde.
Bro.
Thank you.
Drink first.
Conde!
You two,
you're really hard-headed.
Good job.
Thank you, Sir.
Next time you disobey my orders,
you both better watch
yourselves...
especially you!
- Copy, Major.
- Faye!
- Where is my daughter?
Daddy?
- My daughter!
- Faye!
- Daddy...
- My dear...
It doesn't matter anymore,
Joaquin.
The damage has been done.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Faye...
Daddy...
Are you okay?
- It's done, it's done.
- You are safe. You are safe.
Secure the hospital.
Keep that one alive.
Whoever's behind this will pay.
Yes, Mayor.
Lieutenant Conde...
we meet again.
My office is always
open for you.
And for you too,
Sergeant Enriquez.
Just tell me what you need.
Thank you, Mayor.
Major, assign Conde
to the investigation team for
the San Isidro bank robbery.
I need a top-notch cop
on that case.
Thank you very much,
Lieutenant Conde.
Thank you, Mayor.
You too...
Mayor.
Thanks to all of you.
Come on, let's go.
Oh, Dad...
Wait.
All right.
Thank you so much,
Sergeant Enriquez.
Can I call you sister?
Of course.
Take care, okay?
Thank you, Sister.
Welcome to the dream team.
There you go.
You know, I'm really excited
to work with you here.
Have a seat, go on.
You should've brought...
Enriquez with you,
so we'd have a muse around.
Oh, by the way...
Just want to make it
clear to you...
that Robles and I are still
the leads on this case.
Just in case,
you know what I mean.
Don't worry, Bok.
The credit's all yours.
I'm just here to do my job.
It's better to make thing clear.
Oh...
by the way...
Do you think the kidnapper
will actually talk?
- Why do you ask?
- Oh...
Well, I just feel like
he's saying that
so he can stay alive.
But, but I also think
his buddies are planning to
break him out of the hospital.
That's what happens in TV
dramas, right?
It's possible, isn't it?
Oh.
Conde.
Has Enriquez arrived yet?
Not yet, Sir.
Tell her to head straight
to the hospital.
The Mayor's expecting us.
Yes, Sir.
Enriquez!
Sir.
I haven't gotten the chance
to thank you yet.
For what, Sir?
Because I got into the team
investigating
the San Isidro bank robbery...
because of you.
Thank you so much.
It's nothing, Lieutenant Conde.
Just call me Tonyo.
Thank you, thank you.
Good morning!
Morning.
Joaquin, look at this.
Doesn't Sergeant Bobby Enriquez
look like someone?
Really? Who?
Your mistress, Amanda.
Don't they look alike?
Wait.
What exactly are you
getting at here?
You do know the family
just went through
a traumatic experience, right?
And now you're telling me this?
What is your problem?
Sorry, okay? Sorry.
It's just, for me...
If anyone related to you is
going to get hurt
because of this politics mess,
maybe it should be the child
you had out of wedlock...
wherever she is.
Sir, did you hear?
They're transferring the
kidnapper to a regular room.
We'll be able to talk
to him soon.
You got a theory on
what he's gonna spill?
Usually you have, right?
But this time, Sir, nothing.
Paging Doctor Gutierrez,
please proceed
to the operating room.
Oh, forensics just messaged me
ballistics results are in.
What did they say?
They found a match
for the bullet.
He was part of
the San Isidro bank robbery.
I guess this is the part
where you going to tell me...
what your favor's going to cost
me.
Dizon, Noble,
man the main entrance.
Get the names of everyone
who's gone in or out
of this hospital
in the last 24 hours.
Garcia, check all CCTV footage
for the last 24 hours.
Conde, Enriquez,
interview the entire
hospital staff.
I want to know who had access
to our kidnapper.
Here is what will do, Nurse Pam.
Let's say someone wanted to
switch the medicine
meant for a patient.
Where and when would they most
likely be able to do that?
Well, sometimes...
we leave the medicine
at the nurse's station
while waiting for the right time
to administer them.
Sir, let's check the CCTV
at the nurse's station.