Have you seen those riders
that were shot?
He looks like
our mysterious oppa.
Those two in the other table,
they're the cops
who will replace
the escorts of our target.
Just last night, there was a
shooting here in our town.
No one was caught,
not even a suspect.
Lieutenant, can we
check your ID?
- Of course.
- Miss Selena.
Don't you know my ex, Sonny?
Let go of me!
Sergeant Ramos,
do you need help?
- Seriously?
- Put your gun down.
Okay.
Sir, what are you doing?
You know, Sir,
when I saw Ma'am Bobby
last night,
I thought she couldn't break
a plate.
What do you want in a pakbet?
Half-cooked or the vegetables
are a bit well done?
Selena is secured, Sir.
The man who pretended
to be a police officer
has also been neutralized.
They're desperate
to silence Selena,
so she needs to speak.
And the next question
will come from the public.
Let's call our Captain,
Captain Isang.
Good morning, Boss.
Good morning.
And good morning, Mayor.
I just have a question.
What can you do
for senior citizens?
You know, I love the senior
citizens of Calabari very much,
and I want them to enjoy
their sunset years.
And one,
I want them to be given
free healthcare
and recreational activities
like bingo, ballroom dancing,
gardening,
and life planning consultation.
El Hepe! El Hepe!
Aside from enjoyment,
maybe we should empower our
senior citizens.
One problem I see with them
is age discrimination
in the workplace.
If I get lucky,
then we'll create a program
or ordinance
for offices and
businesses here
to hire our senior citizens,
even if it's just
for 4-5 hours of work.
Boss! Boss! Boss! Boss!
When we give them jobs,
we can make them feel like
they still belong
in our community
and that they have something
to contribute to our society.
And when, ah, they're about to
become official senior citizens,
we'll give them retirement
planning.
That's free
and financial literacy,
so they can be at peace
and really enjoy
their senior years.
Boss! Boss! Boss! Boss!
Thank you very much, Boss.
I liked your answer.
Thank you very much to you too.
Put your hands up!
Miss Selena, we haven't met yet.
Is the man from earlier dead?
The one who pretended
to be a police officer?
But the suspect is still alive.
He is in surgery now.
Still unidentified.
I think he is Chinese or Korean.
Sir...
we'll move the suspect
to the room.
His condition is stable.
Selena, I'll just go there.
Just rest.
Ma'am Bobby,
maybe you can stay.
Please, just be with me first.
Sure, I'll be right here.
Thank you very much
to those who listened and
attended
today's Tapatan 2025
Calabari Mayoralty Debate.
Let's also thank
our two candidates.
On my right, our El Hepe,
Mayor Joaquin Guerrero.
El Hepe! El Hepe!
And let's also thank Boss,
Victor Santiago.
Boss! Boss! Boss! Boss! Boss!
I love you, Boss!
I love you too!
Boss! Boss! Boss! Boss! Boss!
Just a moment.
Let's also thank
Mayor Joaquin Guerrero
for his participation in
sponsoring food
for our volunteers.
El Hepe! El Hepe! El Hepe!
- El Hepe! El Hepe!
- Hey!
Hey, what's that?
Hey, hey!
Hey!
That's enough, that's enough!
Don't make a fuss!
Don't fight!
That won't do any good!
- Dad.
- Oh?
- What's that? What's that?
- Yes.
They threw an egg at me.
I think it's rotten, it stinks!
Dad, are you okay?
I'm okay, I'm okay.
It's a good thing
a bullet didn't hit me.
That's right, don't get angry
Oh.
Hey! Stop!
I said stop.
Raise your hands!
Come forward.
Come forward!
Remove that from your face.
Daga? You even threw an egg.
What you did earlier
was unjust vexation.
Handcuff him!
You fool,
it's just you,
you've made us tired.
Hey!
Thank you.
You know, Ma'am Bobby,
I idolize you.
You were good at fighting
earlier,
You were fighting head-on,
and yet you're still pretty.
Oh, I'm surprised.
I thought you'd rather be
with Sir Tonyo.
Maybe I'm comfortable
with you and trust you more.
You remind me of my Sister.
Oh...
Why? Do you miss her?
I'm just scared because...
I feel like I have no one
to trust but you both.
Are you thinking about
something?
Here, here!
There!
Hey!
Get down there, Daga.
Hey, Daga!
Bye, Sirs!
You fool!
Let's go, Sir.
Hey! Push me!
Okay, Sir!
You can do it, okay, okay.
I can't.
- One more, Sir.
- Use your brain!
This is the house, see!
Anybody home?
- Sir?
- Miss, can I borrow a ladder?
We don't have a ladder, Sir.
- None? Okay.
- Yes.
Come on, come on!
This hurt.
Wait, one more, just one more.
One, two...
What's with you?
That man...
That guy earlier,
who tried to kill me,
I recognize him.
He's a friend of Sonny's.
His name is Bullet.
Are you sure?
I recognize him.
Do you know anything else?
Ma'am...
I've had this hunch
for a long time.
I think I know
who their boss is,
the one who gives the orders.
I think he's the one
who wants me killed.
Who?
Victor Santiago.
Countrymen, let's not insult
the Mayor.
He's our Mayor,
he's very pitiful.
He's going to be defeated,
you're still throwing eggs
at him!
Boss! Boss! Boss!
Oh, thank you very much
for this opportunity.
Long live!
Boss! Boss! Boss!
Countrymen, let's vote...
Boss, Mayor of Calabari!
Boss! Boss! Boss!
How are you so sure that
Víctor Santiago is the boss of
Sonny and Bullet?
Listen to me,
I remember something.
Sonny used to tell me something
about his job
that he needed to take care of.
I didn't believe him
because I thought he might just
be cheating on me.
So I followed him.
Did you hear what they were
talking about?
No, but...
it makes sense, right?
That's why Sonny can't tell me
who's giving him orders,
because maybe he has
a strong influence
and has lots of connections.
Victor Santiago,
that's him, believe me.
Look, he used to be an actor,
and now, he's running for Mayor.
Hey, Daga!
You fool! So this is the way
you're taking.
Abi, block him!
You fool!
You even went up to the roof,
But it turns out, only spring
rolls can knock you down.
You fool!
My spring rolls!
That is Mayor's order for the
volunteers.
That's enough! That's enough!
Let's talk about it in
your precinct.
- That's enough.
- That's enough!
Mayor, Mayor, are you okay?
It's okay.
Oh, can I interview you about
what happened earlier?
Who do you think is behind this?
I don't want to be interviewed.
Find out who did this to me.
Find a loophole for that Victor.
Boss! Boss!
You're the one who threw
at the Mayor!
Really? You're such a smart
aleck!
What smart aleck?
I saw you, you're going to lie,
huh!
Why are you causing trouble
around here?
I saw, and you're still
denying it?
Why are you causing trouble?
What? Why? What?
You're out of line!
That's enough! That's enough!
You're insulting the Mayor!
Let's stop that.
That's enough.
They started it.
What do you mean we started it
when I saw you?
You threw eggs at the Mayor.
Liar! Oh, why?
It doesn't matter
who threw the eggs at me.
I'm fine, I wasn't hurt.
That's enough, that's enough.
I'll also ask my supporters to
avoid the trouble.
Let's respect who each person
wants to vote for.
What?
Oh, okay, I'll give
a tray of eggs
- to the people here,
- Hey! There!
including Victor's supporter.
- There you go!
- Okay?
- Okay, thank you!
- Okay, Mayor!
Thank you, Mayor, thank you!
- Okay!
- Thank you, Mayor!
El Hepe! El Hepe!
Miss Bobby, believe me.
Listen to me.
You're the only one I'm going to
tell you this.
Who is the only one
who has a motive
to hurt Mayor Joaquin
and his family?
Only Boss.
He's the one who ordered Sonny
to be killed.
He wants to silence me so he
won't be exposed.
He's a bad guy,
you need to catch him.
It's not that easy.
We need to have solid or enough
evidence
to prove that Boss is the one
who ordered to kill Sonny...
to try to kill you
and the kidnapping.
Selena...
Is there anything?
Did Sonny give you anything?
Nothing, Miss Bobby.
I'm sorry.
Even if I wanted to, Sonny
really doesn't want
to tell me about his job.
But believe me.
Boss is a bad guy.
Believe me.
Dr. Cabral,
please proceed
to the emergency room.
Paging Dr. Gutierrez.
Please proceed
to the operating room.
Sir, is Sir Eric there?
Because my goods were spilled.
- Who will pay for this?
- Ms. Abi.
Did you see Boss Tonyo there?
I didn't seem to notice.
Why are you carrying
a tray of eggs?
Oh, this?
Because the Mayor is giving away
free eggs.
Do you want to get some?
That's big savings
I can't because I'm waiting
for Sir Eric.
My goods were spilled.
Someone has to pay for that.
Too bad.
- Sir Eric.
- Oh?
My goods were spilled.
Who will pay for that?
How's my income for today?
Don't worry,
when Daga comes out,
I'll have him pay
for your goods.
After all, he's the one
who bumped into you.
That's good. Right.
Oh, Sir, have you seen
the gunman
who went on a road rage rampage
in Milagros?
The one who shot the riders,
- has he been caught?
- Oh, right, I saw that.
Mar and Abdul said
that the gunman is loitering
around here.
Did they recognize him?
Yes, Sir, they recognized him.
Oh, what, let's go inside.
Get in line, okay,
so you can get a tray of eggs,
okay?
Yes, there is.
Just say Mar's name, okay?
Yes.
Oh, Sir, why?
Oh, someone told me
that you know the one shot the
riders at Milagros.
Oh, no, Sir,
but we recognize him.
Yes, Sir. Besides,
we're not close.
So, did you see him?
Actually, smooth, tall.
Sir, that's the kind of creature
that Mar and I saw.
Yes, and his lips
were slightly rosy
and shining,
shimmering with saliva!
- Isn't that right?
- Yes.
Sir, that's all, yes.
You seem to have memorized
his appearance,
every corner of his face.
You seem to be dreaming
about him.
- He's so handsome.
- Actually, I dreamt about him.
- Oh, ah, Sir, well...
- Oh...
Can we invite you
to the precinct
so we can cartographically
sketch the suspect?
Okay, okay, yes.
- Okay, I'm coming too.
- Yes.
- Just stay here.
- I'm coming with you.
Hi, officer.
- Hello.
Hurry up, come on.
This is them, Sir.
This is the one taken
in our parking lot.
- Hey, I'm nervous.
- Me, too.
- Act like a man.
- Abdul, Mar.
- Chief.
- Hello, Sir.
This is the composite sketch of
the suspect you mentioned.
It's him, Mysterious Oppa.
Yes, it's like
I'm right in front of him.
Oh, hi, Baby...
Actually, I missed him.
- He's so handsome, right?
- Yes.
Yes, we met.
- My baby.
- Hello.
That guy's dangerous.
What?
He killed two police officers
and five riders at close range.
He's also a sniper
and highly skilled in combat.
So you shouldn't
find him handsome
because he's a monster.
You should find me good-looking
because I'm a monster in terms
of handsomeness.
Conde sent me photos
of the shooter
Please identify if that
foreigner is really him.
Chief, is that him?
Is Oppa in the hospital?
Has he been caught?
Unfortunately, he escaped
a few hours ago
after his operation.
What? Did he escape from Conde?
Conde is something else.
Lieutenant Conde did enough.
Let's just be thankful that he
and Enriquez are alive.
But Conde mentioned to me
that the shooter passed by here
before heading to the safehouse,
and I confirmed it.
I checked the CCTV.
Wait a minute, Chief.
Why did the suspect
come to the precinct?
What's his purpose?
That's what I want to know.
Robles...
based on the footage,
you approached him
and spoke to the shooter.
What was his motive?
How did they escape, Sir?
Someone helped him.
What Selena said must be true.
Why?
Selena confided in me earlier,
and she identified Sonny's
coworker
is the deceased assassin.
And the one they're pointing to
as their boss
and mastermind in the case
we're investigating
is none other than
Victor Santiago.
Sir, the suspect entered the
precinct
as if he were
looking for someone.
I approached him and asked him,
but he didn't tell me anything.
Don't you remember his face
when the viral video of his
shooting came out?
Sir, I didn't expect the suspect
to go to the precinct.
I'm sorry, Chief,
but he's so gutsy.
Well,
me too, I can't imagine
why he would come here.
But, Chief, I think...
this is my idea.
Couldn't the suspect have come
to the precinct
because he was looking
for Selena?
And he wanted to kill Selena.
Because if I were the killer,
I would kill everyone
who knows me, right?
Wait, wait.
Isn't that scary?
Well, the gunman got away.
Maybe he's loitering around our
area.
What about us, Mar?
Chief, he might know us.
Maybe he'll come back
and say, Chief,
we were the ones who reported
him, that's why he got caught.
Maybe we can get into the
witness protection program?
Yes, help us.
Based on what I gathered,
I'm sorry, but you aren't
qualified
to be under witness protection
because the suspect didn't give
you direct a threat of death
or bodily harm to you.
I'm sorry.
Chief, we're scared.
Why? Does she have evidence?
She doesn't have evidence yet,
but Selena told me she saw Boss
and Sonny talking
the day before the kidnapping.
Anyone can talk
to Victor Santiago
because he's a public figure.
But you know, Sir,
I've had a hunch for a long time
that Boss is involved in this.
Well, Selena just confirmed it
to me earlier.
There's no basis for
what Selena is saying.
And another thing, hunches
aren't accepted in the Court.
Why, Sir? Do you think
Boss is that clean?
That he doesn't hide any stench,
even a little?
We all hide some stench,
Enriquez.
But that's not important
anymore.
Only evidence is the truth,
not our opinions.
So Boss paid you
to throw eggs at the Mayor?
Whatever Boss gave you,
- I'll triple it.
- What favor you will give me?
Tonyo, Son, I heard
from your Chief
that there was a shootout
at the safehouse.
Are you okay?
Let's talk some other time.
Sir, who are you talking to?
This has nothing to do with you,
Enriquez.
Why can't you entertain the idea
that Boss could have done
all this?
You know, Boss won the debate.
I have a favorite of his,
women's rights.
Women's rights?
When he was famous,
he hurt a woman.
Are you saying that Boss
has a criminal record?
I've been to the house of two
targets,
but there are a lot of pests.
Just don't move
while the policewoman is there,
clear?
Tonyo, can we talk?