Everybody, put your hands up!
Organs...
Organ harvesting...
Reign.
Reign, wake up.
Sir, you take care of Reign.
I'll just look for Sir Tonyo.
Okay.
You're ruining everything
I've worked hard for!
For sure, they will be
in trouble with the chief.
Disobeying direct orders?
There's a sanction for that
when they get home.
I'm sure Conde knows that.
He just can't leave Enriquez
behind.
Believe me, Chief.
It's really just me.
So I hope you'll just
suspend me.
Sir, you don't have to cover
for us with the chief.
I just don't want to burden
the whole Station 12.
You'd better get
your people ready.
Because after the elections,
I want you to finish off
Enriquez and Conde.
Did I hear that right?
You're going to finish off
Sergeant Enriquez
and Lieutenant Conde?
Dad, I didn't know you're there.
No, I was just talking
to Station 12,
and I told them that
I hope they finish whatever
mission Lieutenant Conde
and Sergeant Enriquez
were given abroad,
because I feel more secure
when they're here in Calabari.
The election is coming, and
we need good police officers.
Actually, you're right
about that.
They're the reason why the bad
guys here in Calabari go crazy.
Anyway...
okay, I'll go ahead.
I still have to attend
to something.
Wow!
Idols!
Markus has already been
caught...
and Selena and your godsister
were saved.
You know, no matter how
many times I questioned you
when you were abroad,
you did a good job.
Solid police work.
Congratulations,
Lieutenant Conde...
Thank you, Sir.
- Sergeant Enriquez.
- Thank you, Sir.
But, Sir, let's not forget
about Lieutenant Garcia as well.
Of course...
but he asked if he could extend
his stay in Switzerland,
so I let him go
because we disturbed him
during his vacation.
I really idolize
Sergeant Enriquez
and Lieutenant Conde!
Yeah, that's right!
Lieutenant, maybe you can buy
some stir-fry noodles for us.
Please, Sir?
Okay, we'll treat you all later.
There you go!
Sir, bring some soft drinks
with you!
Sergeant Enriquez...
I'm sure your Godmother Dina
is so proud of you.
Thank you, Sir.
Okay, back to work!
Yes, Sir!
Just wait for the stir-fry
noodles later, okay?
There you go!
I'll go ahead, Sir.
Enriquez...
are you okay?
I'm sorry, Sir.
I don't understand
what I'm feeling right now.
For the first time,
I did something right
for Godmother Dina's family.
Excuse me, Sir.
We still don't know who Amo's
spy is here in Station 12.
So I'll have you finish all
the cases connected to Amo.
That's good, Chief, so we can
control all the information.
But take a break first.
I know you're tired.
Tomorrow, we'll go through
everything we have.
I'm proud of you.
Good job.
Thank you, Sir.
You can go ahead.
In fairness to the police
officers who were with us,
they're so handsome!
True, but they're so...
snobbish.
They're so aloof.
You know, I hope we can be
with them again.
Oh!
I thought of a way to see
them again.
Are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
I hope Captain Isang
gets kidnapped again!
Ouch.
- Ouch.
- What's that?
- Why?
- You're being silly again.
It's just a joke, Captain.
Is that a joke?
You want me
to be kidnapped again
so you can see
some handsome guys?
Yes.
Why?
You really have the audacity
to laugh?
I won't let that happen again,
Grandmother.
They'll have to go through me
before they get to you.
My grandchild!
Oh, my!
- Bobby!
Grandmother!
We missed you.
Yes.
- Grandmother...
- My grandchild...
Thank God you're here already.
Sorry, Grandmother,
that you got involved.
No, no, it's okay.
The important thing is
that you're here
and we're together again.
Mar, Abdul, thank you very much
for saving my grandmother.
Oh my, it's nothing, Bobby.
I hope Captain Isang
gets kidnapped again.
Yes, we're just waiting for her
to be kidnapped again.
- What?
- There you go again.
There you go again.
Stop it.
My grandchild is here.
Oh my...
The...
I just got excited.
- We missed you, Bobby.
- Yes.
Grandmother, the one we caught
abroad, the kidnapper...
he and his lawyer
have already admitted
that Amo is the mastermind
behind everything,
from the museum thefts
to the San Isidro bank robbery.
Does that mean you'll be able
to bring justice
to your Godmother Dina?
She'd be happy.
Grandmother, I'm going to
prioritize my promotion too.
I'm also going to take the exam
to become a Lieutenant.
Wow!
Perfect, right?
Oh my, your mother
and godmother will be so happy.
I missed you, Grandmother...
Before I forget,
how were you and Sir Tonyo
when you were abroad?
You already went to Dubai.
Now, we're here in Milan
to save your godsister.
You did everything, Enriquez.
I'm sure your Godmother
Dina would appreciate it.
Enriquez...
be careful.
I should also thank you.
What for?
Because of you, I remembered
why I became a police officer,
because I want to fight
for what's right
and protect everyone
I care about.
It's okay, Grandmother.
Lieutenant Conde is a great cop.
Oh my God, Bobby! That's it?
You're so stingy
with your answers.
We want the details.
- Details?
- Of course.
Did you sleep next
to each other?
Did you shower together?
What are you talking about?
Wrong!
You showered together?
Grandmother, what's with you?
No!
You slept together?
- Did you sleep together?
- No, Grandmother.
Come on, let's go home.
Just admit it already.
Stop it, you two.
Come on, come on.
I'll cook for you. Let's go.
Us first.
- No, us first.
- Us first.
- You're not included.
- You should be kidnapped.
It should be you.
- Hey, Boss Tonyo!
- Boss Tonyo!
- Hey, Lee, Bal.
- How are you, Boss?
What? How are you?
Boss, we're fine.
Too bad, he's not here.
You haven't seen the heroism
we've shown.
We've done something different,
Boss.
- We were really up against...
- It was a big fight.
Oh my, I heard about that.
So thank you very much.
You don't know how important
what you did was
for us to complete
the mission abroad.
So is that it, Boss?
Yeah, right.
I feel thirsty, Boss.
- It's hot today.
- Yes, it is.
Okay, okay, drinks
are on me later!
Yes!
That's what we're waiting for!
Boss, by the way,
how have you and Ma'am Bobby
been while abroad?
Thank you, Sir. Thank you.
If it weren't for you
and Lieutenant Garcia,
I wouldn't have been able
to save my godsister.
So, thank you, Sir.
We enjoyed it.
Dubai, Switzerland, and Italy
are really beautiful.
Hey, in...
in Italy, Boss?
Do you know where Italy
came from?
When Lapu-Lapu's ship docked,
he said, "Tie it."
- Tie the ship?
- Yes, tie it.
That's true, Boss,
because when Lapu-Lapu
went there,
he said to the kid from there...
- "Tie it."
- Italian.
That's how Italians got their
name, that's how it began.
Okay, tell the turtle about it.
Tell the...
Tell the turtle about it?
Do you have a shell?
I don't.
How can I tell the story to him
if he doesn't have a shell?
Amo's hearing will begin
in 2 days.
I hope we can close the other
cases we have,
like the museum theft
and the San Isidro bank robbery.
Sir...
there are a lot of references
to Amo's movie,
the masks, the strychnine,
and the bullet in Bullet's
head came from Amo's gun.
Conde, what are you thinking?
Sir, we need to talk to Markus.
I think he's the one who
will connect all the cases.
I'll be direct to the point,
Markus.
With the amount of evidence and
witnesses we have against you,
reclusion perpetua
or life imprisonment,
that's what awaits you.
But if you cooperate with us,
your sentence can be reduced.
12 to 20 years.
Is that right, Lieutenant Conde?
Right.
You just need to tell us
who your mastermind is
in Selena's kidnapping.
I'll only talk to the lawyer.
Markus,
tell us who tipped you off about
where Selena's safehouse is.
I'll only talk to the lawyer.
Are you really going
to waste the chance
of getting your sentence reduced
just to protect your mastermind?
I'll only talk to the lawyer.
Have you talked to Markus?
Yes, Sir, but we're really
getting nothing.
If we don't get a solid
connection to Victor
in the San Isidro bank robbery,
we might not be able
to solve this.
Sir, I think one of us
tipped Markus off
about how to find Selena's
safehouse.
We need to catch Roman.
I feel like he's the key
to all of this.
We don't know where Roman is.
Maybe he's gone far away.
Enriquez...
can you please get the files
on my desk?
Sure, Sir.
What's your plan, Conde?
You might not like it.
Wake up.
We're going somewhere.
Get in.
There you go.
Where are you taking me?
Just relax.
Let's just go for a stroll.
Hello, Dizon?
What are you going to do
with me?
I've run out of options for you,
Markus.
It seems like you're not going
to admit it either.
So I'll kill this guy.
What you're planning
isn't right, Conde.
Don't interfere!
You stay there, Dizon.
Keep an eye.
If anything happens here,
I'm out of it, okay?
Keep an eye out there.
Pray now, Markus...
because this is your end.
You're still lucky.
Hello?
What, Dizon?
You'll hear when it's over.
Keep an eye out there!
Where were we?
There...
Say goodbye already.
Bro...
Bro, let's go. Markus is gone.
What?
Was it convincing?
Yes. Your acting was superb.
That hurts.
Good thing he didn't notice you
were wearing a bulletproof vest.
Is that why you let
Enriquez out?
Well, we know Enriquez, Sir.
I'm sure she won't approve
the plan.
So Dizon and I will work alone.
Sir, I'll let Markus out.
I'll pretend that I'm going
to kill him,
but I'll just let him escape.
I'm sure...
he'll go to Roman first.
Okay.
Just be careful.
Go ahead, report to the chief.
Call him.
Hello, Dizon.
Any news?
Sir, Markus is gone,
the plan worked.
We'll track the motorcycle now.
Stay put for now, okay?
Wait for backup.
Copy, Sir.
He hasn't gotten far yet.
Let's go.
Where is Roman?
Call him!
Boss!
Markus, what are you doing here?
How did you escape?
Conde got me out.
That fool was planning to
kill me just to get me to talk.
It's Roman.
Does that mean
he's Amo's henchman?
From Dubai, Italy,
and Switzerland,
they're bringing me trouble.
But they won't be a problem now
because I've killed Conde.
Let's not talk here.
Get some coffee first.
Stay alert.
Drink some coffee first.
I've already talked to the boss.
What?
Can you help me?
That's the...
I really need to leave
the country.
That's the problem, Markus.
If only Selena testifies,
Victor might not be convicted.
What?
What do you mean?
I can't go back inside, Roman!
- Are you crazy?
- Look at this, look at this!
Did you see this?
We're still gathering more
evidence against Victor.
But if only one person testifies
against him and no one else...
he might use that
as his defense,
he might get away with it.
That's why you shouldn't
run away.
You're crazy if you think
I'll agree to your plan.
Markus, let's not make this
any bigger, okay?
Do your part.
Trust the boss' plan.
I'll get you out myself.
Wait a second.
Don't fool me, okay?
Yeah, whatever you say.
You're an animal, Roman!
If you think your plan is right,
you're the one who should do it!
You're the one who should go
to jail!
You're being followed!
Plant this in your brain.
It's better to have the boss
indebted to you...
than the other way around.
So think about it.
Hands up!
I said hands up!
It seems you've got me now, Sir.
You're really cool.
Put your hands up!
Bok...
Sir...
that's the evidence we got
from Markus' hideout.
It looks like the money will be
used for Amo's campaign.
This is the solid evidence
we have.
Even if you didn't catch Roman,
it's still mission accomplished.
And with the help
of Markus' testimony,
I'm sure Victor Santiago will be
held accountable by the law.
Good job, Dizon.
Thank you, Sir.
Good job, Conde.
Sir, why didn't you include me
in your operation?
I'm sorry, Enriquez.
I thought you might not be able
to follow through with the plan.
Really now, Sir?
After everything we've been
through abroad,
am I still not going
to trust you now?
Enriquez...
we just wanted to make sure.
Don't worry...
I'll make it up to you
next time.
How was your operation?
Any news yet?
Have you got any solid evidence
against Amo?
Yes, we have.
So, does that mean
we can put Amo in jail now?
The goal is to identify the
seller of the pimple patches
at school.
So let's blend in for now.
It's better for both of us
to keep a low profile.
What's our next move?
Kill Markus.
Markus was killed last night.
What?
With Markus' death, will
our case against Amo weaken?
Not really, Enriquez,
because we have a lot
of evidence against Amo.
What do you think our next case
will be?
I'm going to start ruling
here in Calabari.
What's the update on Jane Doe?
She has been identified, Sir.
She's Shaira Reyes.
Sir, do you think we can get any
information from this person?
I'm still not sure,
but I hope she cooperates.