Sorry?
The truth is, that was
my first kiss earlier.
But if you were already
pissed off with me earlier,
why did you do that?
Maybe you're just stupid.
What are you talking about?
Because Vince, the truth is,
I talked to Allan
to make you jealous.
Isn't it obvious?
I like you too.
Yes!
Sir, I had a hunch that
the killer might be outside.
Suddenly, a bystander ran away.
- Hey!
- Hey, stop!
Follow him, I'll go around!
Hey, stop!
Where? Did you catch it?
- No, Sir.
- What?
There are two of you,
and yet he got away?
Submit a report tomorrow.
Well, Attorney, make sure that
bastard doesn't get anything.
Do you understand?
Yes, Madam.
I'll do it right away.
Listen, Enriquez.
You'll have a desk job
until further notice.
We have a lot of
unsolved cases, Chief.
I don't think it's right for you
to just assign me to a desk job.
You're right.
That's why I asked for
additional support
from the other station.
She's here.
What do you want to learn
from me now,
- because I have it all?
- Where is Major Flores?
In the office.
Lieutenant Samson?
Lieutenant Samson...
What are you doing here?
Lieutenant Paloma and I
are assigned here for now.
That means Station 12
will finally solve a case.
I like your confidence.
But admit it,
that's why you're here,
you want to do OJT with me.
You know, I like
your confidence, huh?
That's why you're so popular
at our station...
Oh, did you hear that?
That you were rejected
by the Mayor's girlfriend.
Samson.
- Chief.
- Welcome to Station 12.
Thank you.
Where's Paloma?
He's just taking care of
something, but he's on his way.
Let's go to my office.
How's that?
I'm excited to work with you.
How's that, Bobby?
It seems like we'll be seeing
each other often.
Did you hear that?
They say I'm popular
at their station.
Oh, okay, back to work,
back to work!
Vince, oh.
Look, oh.
It's so early,
and he's busy fantasizing.
That's right!
Dude, what I'm doing
is not a fantasy anymore.
What's that?
Does that mean something
happened to you and Faye?
Hey...
Hey, you're really rude,
aren't you?
Don't be like that.
What is it? Tell me!
Dude, Faye has
confessed to me.
What?
That she still likes me, too.
Hey, she's lying.
Hey!
I'd believe a politician
more than you.
Liar!
- I don't care if you don't.
- There!
That's still a fantasy.
I'll invite you to Glen's
oath-taking on Monday?
There. Look.
Wow!
It seems like you've got
all the luck, Vince.
You should share.
Hey, you've been undercover,
and now you'll be part
of the first fam...
- You're so lucky!
- That's right.
Vince, you should treat us!
Oh, that's right, let's go!
Okay, go get what you want
from the store.
That's right!
Miss, he'll pay for it, right?
Faye!
Oh, Glen?
Did you see Mommy?
She went out, but she didn't
tell me where she was going.
Okay, well, I was going to
discuss something with her
regarding the oathtaking.
- Glen.
- What?
Is it okay if I bring
a plus one?
Will I like that?
I'm sure if Daddy
were still alive,
I'm sure he would like
this guy too.
If it makes you happy, okay.
I'm excited to meet him.
Thank you, Glen.
- Wow, delicious, Dude.
- What? Are you okay now?
- Hey!
- Nothing beats free snacks.
Cheers, bro, cheers.
This is delicious.
Delicious, oh.
- Hey, Dude.
- Dude, how are you?
- What's up?
- Bro, Vince is treating us.
He's in a good mood!
You should ask him
to treat you.
Really? Wait, what's up?
Is it your birthday?
Oh, no.
Well, didn't he win
over you with Faye?
But, man, good job.
- Thank you, thank you.
- You're welcome.
Oh, so what's up?
What's your plan with Faye?
She invited me to her
brother's oath-taking.
But this egg is better, oh.
Is that so? Do you have
something to wear?
That's the thing, Bro.
I have nothing to wear.
I can lend you some.
Really?
Of course! We're partners.
You, of all people.
Wow, Dude, thanks!
No problem.
Bro, I have something to wear!
I already have something
to wear, Dude!
Thank you, man.
Thank you, thank you.
Partner.
Thank you, bro.
Welcome to Station 12.
Thank you very much
for the opportunity, Chief.
You can count on
Lieutenant Paloma and I.
- Thank you.
- What is our first assignment?
Since you were the ones
who caught a fugitive,
I will assign Mateo Ramos
to you.
His case is robbery,
and he is the only one
who escaped with Mandong Warak.
I thought, Chief, we need
to review the events
that have happened here
in Calabari since Mateo escaped.
That's right.
Just cross-reference that.
Maybe Mateo is the one
behind of those.
Chief, just in case,
who should we get
the record from?
From Enriquez.
From Sergeant Enriquez?
Yes.
Why? Doesn't she have
any other cases?
None because she's doing
desk duty right now.
Thank you.
Lieutenant Conde.
Enriquez, have you eaten yet?
Come on, let's eat first.
So, how are you?
Here, I got scolded.
I'm on desk duty
until further notice.
Can I talk to you?
Sure. What is that?
I just wanted
to ask you something.
I just wanted to know
if you told Chief thay
I did it because I just wanted
to help with the case,
or did you just said
that the suspect escaped
because of me?
Enriquez...
I talked to the Chief.
I explained it to him.
It's just that...
It's just that you can't
avoid blaming me
that the suspect escaped
because of what I did.
Bobby, I don't want to blame you
that a suspect escaped from us.
But look at Noble.
Or what if you were
the one who got hurt?
For example, you caught up
with him and fought back?
Oh, why?
I can fight for myself.
If you want, we can fight
one-on-one.
Bobby, I'm just protecting you
from yourself.
Listen to what you're saying.
So maybe it's better...
if you get a desk job first.
Cool down first.
Also, can you listen to me?
Because I'm with you in
everything you're going through.
You're with me?
With me?
Okay, tell Chief
that you're also at fault,
so we can both have desk jobs.
What? Can you do it?
Really? You're with me
with what I'm going through?
You know, Sir,
I'm grateful to you
because I know
you're worried about me.
You're thinking
about my well-being.
But you know, Sir,
sometimes, we don't need lessons
and worries.
Sometimes, all we need
is an ally.
Niko, do you still
remember me?
I'm Tootsie's friend.
Thanks for the sympathies.
Take a look at Tootsie.
She's still so beautiful.
Well, I really feel like
this is a hate crime.
Imagine, second in a row
in the sisterhood
that's been killed.
It's scary.
What's their problem with us?
We're not doing anything wrong.
That's true.
In fairness, Madam is beautiful.
Don't worry, Tootsie...
We'll hunt down the one
who killed you..
Even if it means our lives
will be in danger.
Even if it means...
Why am I involved?
We are ready to sacrifice
our lives
just to give you justice,
my friend.
Hey...
Friend...
Do you really need to include me
in your promise?
Girl, as far as I know,
I'm just an extended friend.
Hey, are you just going to let
our brothers and sisters
live in fear?
Well, we're just town guards,
Friend.
So let's not give in to fear.
I don't have a choice, do I?
- Abdul.
- What is it?
Look at the girl in pink.
Who is that?
That's the daughter
of the first victim.
She's Zondra's child.
Remember?
Oh, yes, right?
Wait...
Hey, friend, what Mar said
was just a joke.
You might haunt me
if I don't keep my promise.
Girl, I'm scared.
Please don't do that.
We're friends, right?
Behave.
Jake, I'm going somewhere.
I'll go ahead, okay?
Where are you going now?
Well, I'm investigating
something in Sitio Manggahan.
Manggahan?
That's a bit far.
That's why I had to leave
so I wouldn't be late.
Sorry, I can't come with you.
That's okay.
Just wait.
Ma'am Bobby, I'll go ahead.
Are you leaving now?
- Yes.
- Oh, okay, okay.
Be careful.
Okay.
Noble.
- Ma'am?
- Why are you standing doing?
Walk her out?
- Okay.
- Go ahead.
This guy is something else.
Bobby!
You're really busy.
What's your assignment?
Yeah, you have a desk job.
All homework, that's sad.
Lieutenant Samson,
if you don't need me anymore,
can you give me a break for now?
I'm not having a good day today.
Actually, I need something
from you.
Get me all the files
for robberies and thefts
that have been reported here
at the station
since Mateo Ramos escaped.
Oh, why?
You asked, didn't you,
if I needed anything?
Well, Chief said
to ask from you.
So is that okay?
Can you?
Okay.
Bobby...
Get me some coffee first.
Do that first, okay?
There.
Thank you.
Hurry up, okay?
How are you, girl?
I still can't believe it.
The deaths of Mommy Tootsie
and Zondra were the same.
Do you think so, Marie?
Well, in that case,
it looks like a hate crime,
and that's what mother's friends
are talking about.
Well, if that's the case,
we all need to be careful.
Oh, what's that?
What happened to your arm, girl?
Oh, this?
- Yes.
- Hey, girl!
Don't say that's
from your boyfriend
who's been hurting you.
Oh my, if I were you,
you'd just go with the shibs.
You'll be safe.
What's with you?
This isn't from my boyfriend.
Besides, I don't have
a boyfriend right now.
This is from mother.
Zondra?
- Is she hurting you?
- Oh my.
Well, I'm a bit troublemaker
and I like to run away.
But that's okay.
Mother's hand is really heavy,
but I know that she loves me.
I'm used to it.
Garcia?
Yes, Sir?
I have something special
for you to work on.
Who else would work on
those special assignments?
But special police officers,
right?
You always have an answer,
Oh, what?
No, I don't have an answer.
You're difficult to talk to!
Call Dizon!
No, no, Sir,
I mean, you didn't ask,
but I have the answer.
What do you want me to do?
I spoke to Mayor Joaquin
before he died,
and he said he had
a strong feeling
that Calabari had a new enemy.
Does that mean someone has
replaced Victor Santiago?
It's always like that.
When you cut off one head
of a snake,
a new one will sprout.
Sometimes two, even three.
So I want you to find out
who Calabari's new enemy is.
Yes, Sir.
Don't worry.
We'll find that snake
and crush it.
You should look
for a partner.
You can choose anyone,
as long as trustworthy.
Anyone? Sir...
I've thought of someone.
- Who?
- It's you.
You're really difficult
to talk to.
- I can't! Call Dizon!
- No, Sir.
You're the one who's
difficult to talk to.
You said anyone.
But I've already
thought of someone.
It's just my dream to have you
as a partner,
and I can trust you,
but I've already thought
of something else.
- Okay, Sir.
- Go ahead.
I still can't stop
thinking about it, Bok.
Which one?
Are those Alma's visions
you're talking about?
Yes, Bok.
Because what she told me
came true.
It was a bit vague at first,
but when it happened,
what she wanted to say
became clear.
I don't know, okay?
There's something called
coincidence,
and then there's also
a term called scam.
I didn't want to believe it
at first, either, Bok,
but this coincidence
is too much to be a scam.
So you want to talk to Alma?
This killer has two victims.
So, where can we find a lead
or help?
Let's figure it out.
Let's go.
Here's what you've asked
from me, Lieutenant Samson.
You know, Bobby...
I seem to like this Station.
Where's Lieutenant Conde?
Maybe the news is true, right?
That you two had a fight.
Why? Are you together?
So, what's this?
It's like you're having an LQ?
It's only your first day here,
Lieutenant Samson,
and you're gossiping
right away?
Oh, no. The news just came to me
out of the blue.
You know, Bobby, I just want
to give you some advice.
If you really like Tonyo,
don't be too fuzzy, okay?
Because Tonyo might find someone
better than you,
especially since I'm here.
Thanks, Sergeant.
Ma'am Bobby, looks like
Lieutenant Samson
is taunting you again.
Never mind her.
Oh my, she'll tease you
even more.
You won't be able to solve
any case
if you're here at the precinct.
Okay, Ma'am, I'll just
attend to something.
Anybody home?
Alma!
This is Tonyo.
- Bok...
- Anybody home?
It looks like
there's no one here.
Excuse me,
what are you doing here?
Alma...
Can we talk?
I don't want this anymore, okay?
I don't want it anymore.
I feel like you're just
enjoying my powers.
Why do you call them powers?
Shouldn't it be a curse?
Who are you?
By the way, Alma, my partner.
Lieutenant Fred Dizon.
Sorry, I don't want
to offend you,
but I just don't want
any triggers.
Do you get triggered when
you're touching something?
I don't know!
It's just that sometimes
when I'm holding a random thing,
sometimes it's like
I'm having a daydream.
Alma, what you said about
neon lights and stilettos?
It came true!
Oh no!
I don't want this, okay?
I don't want this!
I want to be in peace!
I want to have a peaceful life!
Do you understand?
Alma, wait a minute! Please!
We're begging you.
You don't understand me!
You don't know how I feel!
How about you? You're dreaming
about that heinous crime,
and then you find out
it came true?
How hard it is!
I feel like I'm guilty!
I didn't mean for this
to happen!
Alma, believe me.
No matter how you look at it,
you're not guilty.
So help us so that there
won't be more victims.
If anyone should be
guilty here, it's me.
Because you did your job.
Your prediction came true
at the Stiletto Comedy Bar.
I was the one who failed,
and a comedian died.
So help us.
We need your help.
Because I have a hunch
this killer has another victim.
Your hunch is right, Tonyo.
What?
What do you mean?
I saw something in my vision
that there's another victim.
Our mission is to find out
who let Mando escape.
One of our jail guards
was involved.
Mando gave him P100,000.
How did Mando get
that much money?
Glen, he's the one I told you
that's my plus one.
We really need to do
something, Abdul.
Even if there's a risk that
we'll be targeted by the killer?
Because if he really
victimizes gays
due of a hate crime,
we are all in danger.
It's either a cheater,
an abusive parent,
or a swindler.
That seems to be
the killer's pattern.
Not just gay!
What did you see
in your visions, Alma?
I saw a rainbow.
I also saw a street sign.
What's written
on the street sign?