That's why that jerk doesn't
answer the phone anymore.
Grandmother...
Sir Tonyo, thank you.
It's Lee and Bal,
they're the ones
who found your grandmother.
What did I do wrong to you?
Stay away from Faye Guerrero.
You know what?
Some men jumped on Vince
on his way home.
I'm just protecting my sister
like I protect you.
We don't need your protection.
I'm a grown woman
and so is your sister.
Can't you just let us
live our lives?
Dante was warned, Sir.
He knew he was being watched.
He even knew the vehicle
we were in,
so he shot at us immediately.
We need to plan this properly.
But I want to assume that
everyone is compromised.
This is your job now.
Make sure that Dante's name
doesn't get attached to boss.
What did you have
for breakfast this morning?
I can't remember.
Bobby, let's go home.
I'm not sick.
Sorry for my questions, Mother.
Just a moment,
I'll talk to your granddaughter.
It's possible
that she has dementia.
Dementia?
Isn't there no cure
for dementia?
There are treatments to manage
the symptoms, but you're right.
There's no known cure
for dementia so far.
Hello, Tonyo?
Hello, Bobby?
How's Grandmother Isang?
Tonyo, grandmother is sick.
Most likely, dementia.
What does Grandmother Isang
need, Bobby?
Right now, nothing.
But she needs to go through
tests to confirm
if she really
has a dimentia.
And you, do you need anything?
Just tell me, okay?
Tonyo...
I've been absent for two days.
I wasn't able to get permission
from the Chief.
I'll take care of that.
Thank you.
Besides, I need to
file for leave.
Bobby...
Don't think about it anymore.
What's important is
Grandmother Isang.
Thank you.
I just have something
to take care of, but...
I'll visit you right away.
Thank you.
Okay.
Good morning, Mayor.
Hello.
Cecilia isn't answering me.
Glen, if he doesn't want
to pay attention to you,
it means he doesn't want
to talk to you.
It's that simple.
Okay.
Oh...
If she doesn't want to talk to
me, why did someone text me?
Dante is gone.
Robles is making sure no one
will get in trouble.
What did Cecilia say?
It's not her.
See? She doesn't want
to talk to you.
Bok, it looks like Enriquez
really didn't come today.
I told you.
You should have talked
to her last night.
Oh, why are you
blaming me again?
Why? Who else?
Well, actually,
this could be my fault again
because I didn't
conduct a workshop
when it comes
to handling love life.
Don't worry, Bok...
when I have extra time,
I'll train you.
I'll give you a seminar.
- Sir.
All right.
Men...
We need to focus.
We have an important
mission today.
Yesterday, Garcia and Conde...
killed the one who let Mando
escape.
Unfortunately, we haven't gotten
any information...
that can point
to who ordered him.
Sir, I already spoke
to Doc Cecilia.
She said she would deliver
Dante's autopsy report later.
Wait, wait, Bok.
Why are you the one
who talked to Doc Cecilia?
It should have been me.
I ordered Dizon...
because you're losing
your focus...
when it comes to Doc Cecilia.
You're putting
your love life first.
Bok, that love life,
that's just trouble.
Look at Dante.
He put his love life first,
that's why he got killed.
Anyway, what do you think,
Conde?
It might be better if we wait
for the autopsy report...
before we act.
Okay.
For now, let's just stand by.
And report to me all the
information you get.
Dismissed.
Garcia, Conde...
you guys stay.
I have something for you to do.
Just woo her.
She's just sulking.
- Vince?
- Where can I get...
- a birth certificate?
- Vince!
Okay, I'll be right back.
What's wrong with him?
Faye...
if he ignores you,
it means he doesn't want
to talk to you.
It's that simple, right?
What's wrong with him?
Maybe he just didn't see you.
You think?
Probably.
Anyway...
Chief...
what are you going
to ask us to do?
Conde, what are you thinking?
Why did you stop me
from saying or discussing...
with our colleagues
what you suspected?
Bok...
did you tell anyone why we were
waiting for Dante yesterday?
Oh, the one that
your informant said...
that Dante's girl lives there?
None, why?
Because I didn't put
that in the report either.
So that means...
only the two of us know
about it.
Sir...
I think I know how to catch that
snake here at Station 12.
I just hope
my suspicions are wrong.
I called you again
because I received intel.
Unfortunately...
Dante had a relative...
whom he told
before he died...
who his true boss was.
Here in these files...
is the address of
Dante's relative.
Conde, tomorrow morning,
go and convince him
to cooperate with us...
so we can find out
who his boss is.
Yes, Sir.
Okay, dismissed.
Okay, Sir.
For that idiot Dante.
You're already dead, you're
still giving me a headache.
Hello?
Hello, Roman, we have a problem.
Do you really miss me?
Two calls in one day, Robles?
I'm serious.
Dante has a relative
who knows boss.
Who did you hear that from?
Here with my colleagues
Just keep it simple.
The mayor shouldn't be involved,
no matter what.
Because if that happens,
we'll all be dead.
I know, that's why I called you,
right?
Since you already know...
well, you should know
what to do now?
Yes, I'll take care of it.
Make sure the body
of Dante Eusebio is clean.
Just follow me.
When my techniques, for speed..
Oh...
Why are you so slow to get up?
Because isn't it
in love stories,
when they collide,
like this,
slowly, in slow-motion...
Anyway, why are you here?
I've finished Dante Eusebio's
autopsy report.
What's up with Dante's autopsy?
Any clues that will lead
to his boss?
No, he's clean.
Nothing unusual.
Is Chief there?
Yes, he's there, upstairs.
Oh, okay, I'll go ahead.
Cecilia...
Are you okay?
Because you seem to be...
deep in thought.
Oh, sorry, I think
I'm just tired.
I haven't slept yet...
to finish this autopsy.
You haven't slept yet
in that state?
You look so fresh.
Okay, I'll go ahead.
Oh, okay.
Slow-mo, Sir?
Sir, how's the slow-mo?
Hey, you two, do you know what
the other slow-mo is?
- What else, Sir?
The one who's dying...
- Sir, you can't take a joke.
You two are too invested in our
love story.
Grandmother,
get some rest, okay?
Okay, Bobby, thank you.
Go to bed early, okay?
- Good night!
- Good night.
Oh, Bobby, you're home now?
How was captain's check-up?
The doctor said...
maybe it's dementia.
Oh, how are your bruises?
You've been going solo,
since you courted Miss Faye.
That's right!
You know, Bro,
if you were with us,
that's unlikely
to happen to you.
Wait, what else did those who
beat you up say to you?
They said, Bro, that I should
stay away from Faye.
That's why I have
a strong feeling...
that Faye's family gave the
order to beat me up.
What? Why?
Because they don't like you?
Oh, that's impossible, Bro.
And the mayor is very kind, Bro.
He was with us who saved
captain, remember?
Madam!
Madam, I have some
hot news for you.
From my friend who works as an
orderly at Calabari Hospital.
Will that make my night better?
I have a feeling, Madam.
He said Bobby and her
grandmother...
came from the hospital earlier.
And guess what.
The old woman is sick...
Dementia.
Karma is starting
to take its toll on them.
Cheers.
You know, Bobby,
when your grandmother
and I first met,
she was looking for someone...
to join the boxing club
in the village.
So I was forced to join...
because...
I didn't want to get caught.
But before that day,
she told me...
not to join...
because I punched like this.
As for me, Bobby,
I was being pressured to join
the league.
They said I would be made the
center of the basketball team.
Well,
I couldn't refuse...
because I was afraid
we would get caught,
especially me.
So...
I joined.
Captain approached me.
She told me, "Abdul...
don't join.
I can feel that you're just
being forced."
How did she know?
Because...
this is how I shoot.
You know,
when mother was robbed
and killed.
I cried so hard.
I just stopped when grandmother
came and hugged me.
Since then,
grandmother has been with me
in all our fights.
That's why it hurts me to see
her like this,
because I feel like...
I can't be with her in this
fight that she's going through.
I feel that...
I can't give her courage,
especially now.
Because even I am getting weak.
Mar, Abdul...
I don't know what I'll do...
if something bad happens
to grandmother.
I'm ready to trade everything
just so she can get better.
Oh! Oh!
My granddaughter is beautiful.
Beautiful.
Do you know what's more
important to me?
You.
You are the most important thing
to me than anything else.
I love you, Grandmother.
I love you.
I just don't want
to leave you alone.
I'll be sad.
Oh, what's with you,
Grandmother?
That's a long way to go.
You're still so strong, see?
We have all the time in the
world.
Just remember.
The grandchild
who is beautiful...
- inherited grandmother's looks.
- Correct!
So, Bok, Ms. Isang is sick?
How's Bobby?
Well, she's so affected.
You know how much
she loves her grandmother.
Don't spread the word, okay?
I only told you.
Of course, it's our secret.
What do you think of me?
But, Bok, why are we
waiting here?
What's your plan, Conde?
Sir...
you're going to tell us
that Dante said...
he told a relative
who his boss is.
Now, the syndicate...
will want to find out
who that relative is.
Then you're going to give us
different addresses.
Once the syndicate goes
to that fake address,
that's where we'll find out
who the traitor is here
at Station 12.
That's the address
Regan was given.
And he's the one
you're suspecting?
Oh, didn't he say earlier...
that Dante was
having a love life?
I didn't tell anyone else.
You said you didn't tell
anyone else, right?
Oh, how would he know that?
You're right.
You know, I admire
your instincts,
but, I hope, I hope
you're wrong this time.
Bok...
there's a car.
Bok, it's loaded.
Bok...
well, it seems
my suspicions weren't wrong.
Robles is the snake
of Station 12.
It's Robles?
Maybe from the very beginning,
the criminals have paid him.
But we'll only know
the answer to that...
when we find out
who Robles' real boss is.
I really don't want to be nosy.
Maybe later on,
they'll doubt me too.
If you can't do it,
we can easily find
a replacement.
You know, if you could talk,
you'd think you'd be
more useful than me.
Let's sweat it out
so we'll find out who's useless.
You want to drop the case?
I'd rather focus on
taking care of grandmother.
What's this nonsense, Glen?
What's this bastard doing here?