A mix of acid and NBOMe.
It's like a level up of LSD,
so it's really potent.
You mean you can die
from just one pimple patch?
Not really.
But in Shaira's case,
it looks like she used three
to four pimple patches,
which is why she overdosed.
The problem is,
it's very accessible and cheap.
That's why the youth
are really going for it.
Sir, based on the stakeout
we had with Lieutenant Conde,
it looks like there's only
one way to pinpoint
who the source is inside.
What is it?
We'll go undercover inside,
Chief.
What's the problem?
- It suits you.
- Your clothes suit you too.
Sir, what if you leave me
alone here for now?
You know, someone might come
to me when I'm alone.
Do you really want to party?
Do you want this?
What's that?
Pimple patch?
This is the secret
to the hardcore party here!
Sir, I sent you a photo
of the possible target.
Sir, there he is.
Garcia, the target
is heading that way.
Enriquez, let's go!
- Stop!
- Hey!
Go inside!
You have a pimple patch
stuck on your arm.
Sir, don't tell my grandmother,
okay?
I don't want her to see me
like this.
Let's party!
Tonyo, you're tickling me.
What's with you?
Wait a minute. Stay still!
Sir Tonyo...
Come on, come on, come on.
You're handsome, aren't you?
Your outfit suits you.
Enriquez, just calm down.
Better yet, sit down first.
- You smell good, Sir.
- Ouch!
Sir...
Let's party!
Hey!
Hey! Everybody!
Everybody!
- Enriquez, calm down.
- Yes! Let's party, Sir.
Calm down, just calm down.
Let's dance.
Come on.
What are you doing?
Can you please sit down?
Come on!
Enriquez!
Sir...
Enriquez, listen up.
You're high, okay?
So just calm down there.
- Wait a minute, wait a minute.
- No. Hey, wait a minute, Sir!
- I have something to tell you!
- Ouch!
- What?
- Sir Tonyo...
do you like me?
Because I like you too.
What? Do you like me?
You don't like me?
Enriquez...
Okay...
Let's party!
- Hey! Sit down! Calm down!
- Yes!
Enriquez, please...
- you're really something else.
- Sir...
You're high.
You're high. Just a moment.
Just a moment,
I'll just make a call.
Sir...
Sir, wait! Don't leave me!
Sir, don't leave me!
Please! I can't breathe!
I can't breathe!
Please calm down!
Just a moment!
- Hello?
Hello, Doc Cecilia?
Lieutenant Conde, you called.
What's up?
Yes, I'm sorry to bother you.
I was just going to ask
for your help.
Why? Is there a problem?
Bobby and I went undercover.
It looks like she accidentally
got a drug-laced pimple patch
stuck on her arm.
She's acting wild.
Where are you?
We're at my place.
The effect of the pimple patch
is really powerful,
especially since Enriquez
is not a user.
Don't worry.
I'll guide you through this.
It's good that you took
her home.
I know she's in safe hands
with you.
First, be patient with her.
No sudden movements.
It's harder when she panics.
Tonyo!
Antonio Conde, come here!
Next, keep her warm,
but keep an eye
on her body temperature.
Third, is keep her hydrated.
That's important.
And just be with her all the way
until the effect wears off.
Hello?
- Okay, Doc.
- Sir!
- Doc! Doc! Hello, Doc.
- Enriquez! Wait!
- Doc! Doc!
- Doc! Come on, let's party.
- Hello, Doc?
- Doc, text me!
Let's party!
Come on, everybody!
- Let's party!
- My God.
- Yeah!
- Enriquez, Enriquez...
Enriquez, calm down!
Calm down, calm down, okay?
Just relax, just relax.
I'm tired.
Sir, get me some water.
Yes, wait a minute,
I'll get you some water.
Just stay there.
Stay there, okay?
Wait a minute.
I can't breathe.
Get me some water, Sir.
My chest hurts.
Drink first, drink first.
You need this. Drink this first.
- Go ahead, drink some more.
- You should drink also.
- Have a drink too.
- Yes.
No, you need this!
Drink first, come on!
- Finish it, come on.
- I don't need it, Sir.
Antonio, stay here by my side.
Let's party!
- Let's party!
- Calm down.
Sir...
Calm down. Just relax there.
Okay?
Stay there. Wait a minute.
Where are you going, Sir?
Captain, has Bobby
reached out to you?
Yes, Captain.
It seems like she didn't
come home last night.
Right?
Yes, she didn't.
Wow.
She's nonchalant.
Well, if you think about it,
Bobby had a police operation
last night.
That's probably why
she didn't come home.
You know, Captain,
your back looks like
there's a little bit sulkiness.
It seems stiff.
And I noticed that she did not
get enough sleep.
I agree.
Right?
If it were me,
I'd be worried about that.
- True.
- Can you please stop?
Did you come here to annoy me?
Oh my, Captain, just relax!
Just calm down.
Call the village guards.
Abdul, you take care of it.
- Call them. Yes, hurry.
- I'll take care of it.
I'll take care
of Captain Isang here.
Village guards!
Your back is so tough.
It seems like there's
some sulkiness.
Captain, here they are.
They've been waiting there
for a while now.
Listen up.
I heard that a new drug
is spreading among the youth.
I don't want that
to enter our village.
Is that clear?
Yes, Captain.
Go ahead, patrol the streets.
Okay.
Just relax, Captain.
Captain, you should patch
things up with Bobby.
He's right.
She's your granddaughter.
You can't ignore her.
- True.
- Just relax there, Captain.
We'll just patrol the streets.
Let's go.
Think about it...
As long as you don't tell me
the real reason
why you're doing this and why
you don't want me to join.
I'm sorry, I can't follow you.
Well...
She's still sound asleep.
I'll take a bath first.
Where's my towel?
Oh no, I left it outside.
Enriquez is still sleeping,
right?
I forgot to text grandmother,
she might be worried by now.
It's your fault, Bobby.
Your heart is so hard.
Oh my, you're so stubborn.
Your heart is so hard, Bobby.
It's hard...
Cover up, Sir!
Why did you use that
to cover yourself?
- You gave it to me!
- Give it back!
- There you go!
- I don't want it anymore, Sir!
Why am I peeking?
Bobby!
Enriquez!
Sir?
Do you want some coffee?
Oh, no, Sir.
I'm fine. Thank you.
Well, you got a pimple patch
on you last night.
You told me not to take you home
because your grandmother
would be angry.
That's why I let you sleep here.
Thank you, Sir.
Did we catch the seller?
Yes, we caught him.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine, Sir. I'm okay.
Sir, did something...
Did something happen to...
No!
I'm not that kind of person!
Wow, Sir.
You react as if you're
the aggrieved party.
Not really.
I was just asking,
because earlier,
you were just...
You were...
You didn't...
Yes, because earlier
you were still sleeping,
I said I'd take a shower first
but I left my towel behind.
I went out to get it,
but you're already awake.
Okay.
Sir, did you tell anyone
that I was here today?
Did anyone know?
No one else knew,
but I called Doc Cecilia because
I asked how to take care of you.
Okay, okay, Sir.
Thank you, Sir.
Don't worry, Enriquez.
No one else will know about
what happened last night.
Okay. Thank you, Sir.
Okay, Sir, I'll go ahead.
By the way, you forgot your...
Okay, never mind.
I'll wash it first.
Okay, Sir.
Good morning, Boss Tonyo!
What are you doing here?
It's still early.
Didn't you say we should
treat you to breakfast?
Here, we brought you some!
Yes, Boss.
Ma'am Bobby,
what are you doing here?
Did you sleep here?
No, we had a police operation
last night.
We finished late, so she slept
in the living room.
In the living room...
But I'm about to go home now.
- I'll go ahead.
- Oh, no. Wait, Ma'am!
The breakfast we brought
might be wasted.
- Right, Bro?
- Yes!
Why don't you join us?
- Come on, feel at home!
- Yes!
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on, let's grant
their request.
The party drugs are getting out
of hand these days, aren't they?
My God, they're even
targeting teenagers.
Well, yeah,
it's not like they're going
to target someone
as old as the captain.
Do you think anyone will buy it?
You know, you're not
even thinking.
Please, Abdul?
My God, just for once,
can I talk to you properly?
Just for once.
No.
I'll knock you off the tricycle.
You're annoying.
It's not going to happen.
Just kidding!
Come on. Don't be mad.
That will lighten your skin.
It comes with a toner,
sunscreen...
Beauty products?
Beauty products...
Even if you're already
light-skinned,
you'll become even lighter.
I smell something fishy.
Let's go.
Hey!
Just a moment.
What are you selling?
Beauty products.
Beauty products?
Yes.
Do you sell pimple patches?
Why?
We're village guards here.
Let me see.
Hey!
Quick!
You're so fast, girl!
Hey!
Stop!
Abdul, I told you that we should
go to the gym!
No! Mar, I'm sending a lot
of people to school.
You want me to add more
to my expenses?
My God.
Let's skip the coffee runs
every weekend.
We can't catch up
with that witch!
Coffee is delicious!
What?
We're really going to talk
about this now, Mar?
Are you serious?
In the middle of a chase?
Here it is. We're sure
you'll like this, Boss.
- Oh my, of course. There.
- What's that?
You'll definitely like it.
Here it is. That's delicious,
so delicious.
Naked spring roll.
What's that?
Why are you covering your eyes?
Because when someone is naked,
you should cover your eyes?
Right, Ma'am Bobby?
Am I right?
- Let's cover our eyes.
- Yes.
Yes, of course.
There.
If you don't want this,
Ma'am Bobby,
we have a jumbo hotdog here.
Bro, there are only
three hotdogs.
There are four of us here.
Boss Tonyo, we'll open
your fridge, okay?
So we can get some
more food ready.
Come on, Bro, let's take a look!
Let's take a look at his fridge.
This, this. What's in here?
- There!
- This one.
Ma'am Bobby, do you want
Boss Tonyo's cheesedog?
- That's delicious, cheesedog.
- That's delicious.
Ma'am Bobby, there's skinless
longganisa here too.
Oh, it's fat and reddish too.
You'll definitely like this,
Ma'am Bobby.
Sir Tonyo's footlong.
Oh, it's long!
- It's so long!
- This is okay!
I'm okay with this!
- Stop it, you two.
Come here.
- I'm okay with this.
- Are you sure?
Boss Tonyo, your eggs are white.
That's delicious.
You really don't like it?
But I saw another one, Boss,
the other egg you have is red.
That's good for fried rice,
right?
Is that salty?
That's okay...
No need for the salted duck egg.
I'm okay with this.
No. Boss' egg looks salty,
right?
This naked spring roll
is delicious.
Naked again?
Okay.
Try the naked spring roll, Bro.
Isn't that your favorite?
Is she a kangaroo?
Hey, witch! Can you please stop?
Why are you chasing me?
I'm not doing anything wrong.
Of course, you ran.
You're crazy.
Yeah.
Wait.
Where do you go to the gym?
And how long do you spend
on the treadmill?
I don't go to the gym.
But the things you were selling
to the teens earlier,
they were drugs, right?
I wasn't selling any drugs.
I had nothing to do with that.
So why did you run?
Because I was scared.
You said you were
the village guards.
I sell fake beauty products,
but they're good quality
and cheap.
Are you sure?
Yes. Check it out. Look.
- Okay, let's see.
- Let's see.
- Buy one, take one.
- Oh my God! I have this!
Perfect!
I bought it before
on the marketplace.
- Do you accept credit?
- Sure.
Perfect!
Girl, you're so greedy when
it comes to things like that.
- Hey, I like this product.
- Yes, that's nice.
But you run so fast.
You sell so fast, too.
Yes, that's right!
Boss Tonyo!
We'll go ahead. Thank you, Boss.
- Thank you, Boss.
- Thank you.
- Ma'am Bobby!
- Take care!
Thank you!
- I hope you eat the hotdog.
- Thank you for the breakfast.
- No worries!
- Take care!
Sir Tonyo...
- Leave it there.
- Where am I going to put this?
Okay.
There's still some more.
This is delicious.
Sir, there's something
on your...
You have a big build, Sir.
We're okay, right?
Us?
Your clothes look good
on you too.
Thank you, Miss.
In fairness to her...
her fake items are legit, right?
Are you crazy?
Legit, and then fake?
You're talking nonsense, Abdul.
What do you mean by nonsense?
You're the one who brought up
the gym
while we were chasing her.
Hey.
Captain...
Hey, Captain, I noticed...
you've been on your cell phone
for a while now.
It looks like you're waiting
for a text or call.
Oh, I know it already.
She's meeting someone.
Captain, have you joined
a dating app yet?
Swipe left, right.
- Right?
- I used to swipe right a lot.
Oh, yeah.
I chatted with lot
of people there.
I know that.
Stop bothering me.
What if I slap your faces
with my shoes?
The sole is thick, see.
That's it.
But, Captain,
why don't you call Bobby?
I know you miss her, too, right?
- She hasn't come home yet.
- Yeah.
Yes, Captain.
Don't you have any load?
- I'll send you a load.
- Or connect to my hotspot.
I have some extra gigs left.
What's happening?
Captain is getting poor.
You connected to my hotspot
earlier, right?
You're so shameless.
Hotspot, just connect
to my phone.
Captain!
You look bad in your picture.
Let's change it.
Abdul...
She doesn't look good...
Captain is still affected
by her fight with Bobby.
But we know they can't ignore
each other.
They'll eventually patch
things up.
I agree, but I hope
Booby goes home.
You're right.
Because Captain Isang
will take it out on us.
Correct!
Didn't you see those heels?
They're thick.
My beauty will be ruined
by that.
What if that's the one we bring
while patrolling the streets?
And for strolling too.
Besides, it's scary to look at,
isn't it?
- Yes.
- That's right.
I like that. We can use it
when we go for stroll.
But you know, it looks ugly.
I think that's Lee and Bal.
Wrong timing.
What do you need?
Selena...
What are you doing here?
Sir Tonyo, I need your help.
Ma'am Bobby,
what are you doing here?
We had a police operation
last night.
We finished late, so Bobby
slept in the living room.
Why are you carrying a suitcase,
and what help do you need?
Well, Sir Tonyo...
I haven't been able to pay
the rent.
Well, you know, I haven't been
able to work
because I'm busy being a witness
in Amo's case.
I've been kicked out.
If it's not too much trouble,
maybe I could stay here...
for a long time?
For a long time?
For a short time.
Just kidding.
You're too serious.
I promise, I'll leave
when I find a new job.
Whatever you need, I'll do it.
If you need a cleaner, a cook...
If you want, Sir Tonyo,
I'll massage you every night.
Selena, I'm sorry...
Selena, it's a good thing
that you came here.
You know that Sir Tonyo
won't refuse you.
Really?
Oh my, thank you very much.
Your house is beautiful,
Sir Tonyo.
Looks cozy.
Sir, I'll go ahead.
Bobby...
Sir Tonyo, where can I put
my things?
Will we stay together
in the room?
- I'm getting hungry.
- I want to eat too.
Right?
- Where should we eat?
- I don't know.
Good day, Captain.
Captain...
Let's go.
You know, Mar,
Bobby's job is hard, right?
Oh, yes, you're right.
Especially when they conduct
a police operation.
One of her feet is in the grave.
Oh my, it's scary.
But you know what's scarier?
What if something bad happens
to Bobby?
She and Captain Isang are not
okay. Isn't that harder?
My God, you're right!
Oh my, they'll both regret it.
Nothing bad will happen
to Bobby!
We know that, Captain.
Well, our point is that
the future is uncertain.
That's why it's better if you
don't prolong the fights,
especially with the ones
you love, right?
Yes.
And Captain, you're Bobby's
only family.
What if you get kidnapped again?
We can't save you.
What about Bobby?
She'll be all alone.
Poor Bobby.
She'll be an orphan while you
have a misunderstanding.
Why?
Because you don't want
to let her join
the mayor's task force
in Calabari.
Why, Captain?
Why?
Oh my God!
You're so petty, Captain!
What a shame, what a shame...
Bobby texted.
What did she say?
"I'm on my way home.
Has grandmother eaten yet?"
"Please tell her
to take her medicine."
Look!
Bobby's still thinking
about you!
What a shame, Captain.
What a shame...
That's how we are.
When we wake up,
we look fresh and beautiful
because that's in our genes.
Yes.
- Are you ashamed?
- My name is Shame.
I am ashamed.
No, you're not.
You're here already.
Grandmother...
I was so worried about you.
I wish you had texted me.
Grandmother, I'm sorry.
We had a police operation
last night,
the one I told you about,
the pimple patch.
Sorry, Grandmother,
I just got home today.
I was really worried.
But I have something
to tell you.
- Grandchild, I'm sorry.
- Grandmother...
you're right.
I can still do all my work
even if I don't join the mayor's
special task force.
Do you know what's more
important to me?
You.
So if we're just going to fight
about this, there's no need.
I'll just decline it.
Because you're the most
important thing to me.
I love you, Grandmother.
I love you.
Grandchild, I have something
to tell you.
What is it?
You already know that your
mother was rejected by the man
who got her pregnant?
Yes, Grandmother. Why?
Because the one who got her
pregnant is Mayor Guerrero!
I'll admit something to you.
I've cheated on your mother.
What?
Study your identities.
Take it to heart.
For people to believe you,
you have to be the first
to believe.
Where are these two?
They're at the gym, Bro.
This is the first time
I saw your faces!
What do you want?
We just want to see
how good you are.
Bobby got promoted?
Yes, Bok.
Not just here at
the police station.
Where else?
In your heart.
We are here at the clubhouse
because today we will witness
a friendly swimming race
between two competent
police women,
Lieutenant Charlie Samson
and, of course,
Sergeant Bobby Enriquez!