Be careful with Enriquez.
He asked me
if you're related to Boss.
You, Enriquez, do you have
anything to say?
Nothing, Sir.
You've been so distracted
lately.
Sir, I know I've wronged you,
but please, don't disrespect me
here at work.
Bacause I love being a cop.
I just really took out all
my frustration on her
because of that case.
Are you mad at the case,
or mad because
I reported her to you?
I need to solve this case, Bok.
For Lara.
What happened to Grumpy here?
- Hey!
- I said that's enough!
What I hate the most
is a man who hurts women!
Excuse me.
Because of you,
I lost my mistress!
Hey! Stop that!
I'm a cop!
Cop! Cop!
Where are you now, Dear?
I'm at Lt. Conde's place,
Grandma.
Remember...
I'll be careful.
Don't be careful,
I want a grandchild!
I'll come home.
I'm just waiting
for the rain to stop.
Hey! I'm not gonna fight you,
okay?
What did you say?
My wife will get mad.
Lara will get mad.
There is so much of this.
You're actually a drunkard, Sir.
I won't meddle anymore.
You might get mad at me again.
Lara...
Sir, I'm sorry.
I'll just watch it.
So what now?
Would you find someone new
if I'm gone?
That's such a hard question.
It feels like a trap.
No matter what I say,
you'll still get mad.
No, really, it's not a trap.
Promise I won't get mad.
Why are you even asking that?
Nothing...
I was just thinking...
like, what if I die,
and you never find someone else?
I wouldn't want that.
Even if I'm not in your life
anymore,
I want you to be happy, Tonyo.
That's how much I love you.
And if you find someone who
takes care of you,
then go for it.
Lara, I don't even think about
that stuff,
because you're
the only one I love.
And I love you so much.
Good answer.
You really know how to say
the right things.
Don't worry, Lara.
I won't leave Sir.
Sir, don't worry.
I'll stay with you here.
I won't fall asleep, I promise.
- This guy?
- Yes, hit him, Bro. Go hit him.
Hey.
You've got rabies or something.
Here I am putting up with you,
and you act all tough.
Remember, you've never
had real friends
because you bite everyone
in the leg.
- Oh! Bro!
- You're filthy!
You're so dark!
I'd like to hit you.
You're so dark,
every time you change your
profile picture,
the comments are condolences.
Oh, Bro, fight back.
- Me?
- Fight back.
- You're nothing.
- Did you hear his remark?
It's like a malfunctioning
machine.
Listen to the hum,
it's like an out-of-tune fart.
I'm the one Dennis Trillo
was fighting against
young Max Alvarado.
- Oh...
- Look at the skin.
Maybe you used to be a soldier.
Oh!
But, Bro, no matter
what you say,
even if I don't know how to rap,
I'm still more
handsome than you!
- That's it, Bro.
- That's it.
That's it, that's it.
We're done.
You know, your lumpia is really
delicious, Sis.
Of course.
Wait, why don't you vlog it?
You know what?
That's not a bad idea.
But wait, why are you alone?
Where's your twin?
Oh, Apple?
She is moping
because we saw Sir Tonyo
earlier,
with a woman.
Sir Tonyo, with a woman?
Yes.
You know, it's unfair
The line was long,
but someone got ahead.
- Hey, barbecue.
- Oh.
That looks delicious.
How much is this?
Twenty peos only.
How much is it for a rebond?
- Me, another one Miss.
- Hi, Miss.
Do you want to drink?
Let's go.
It's nice to drink with someone.
Mister, you guys go ahead.
You guys are a maniac.
Miss, sige na.
It's nice to drink
with someone sexy to hold.
You idiots.
She said she didn't
want to come, right?
Can you please stop being rude?
Miss, you're just jealous.
Don't worry.
I'll be hugging you.
Hey!
Hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey,
What's that?
You're being rude
when you're so ugly.
Why? Do you have a problem?
You're rude to my friends.
Boss...
That's enough.
Why? Are you going to fight
back?
Boss, no.
We're trying to break the fight.
- Where is mine?
- But if you want...
What? What?
There! There!
He still wants to get up!
What? What?
Let it go, let it go.
- It's up to you.
- What?
- Get up!
- Let's fo there, Bro.
I got tired there.
This is mine.
Here, that one
from earlier again.
Oh, what?
Well, it's morning already.
Are you okay?
Enriquez?
- Oh...
- What are you doing?
Sir...
I'm sorry.
What are you doing here?
Well Sir, didn't you text me
last night?
You said two bottles,
so I went to the store.
Well, I saw you all beaten up.
That's why I brought you home.
Sorry, I didn't make it home
last night
because of the heavy rain.
I texted you.
Did you treat me?
Thank you.
Welcome.
Okay, Sir.
I'll go ahead.
Hey...
Your wounds
and bruises just put
ice on them.
You can handle that.
Your body is big now.
It's big...
You're already big.
Okay.
Bye.
- Come on, Bobby, tell us!
- Yes.
- We're excited.
- What am I going to tell you?
Nothing, nothing happened.
What's that?
You're so slow, Bobby.
- You know, if it were me.
- Oh, that's sure!
- Oh, right?
- You know that, Girl.
Stop it!
Yes Grandma, okay, scold them.
Stop it. stop bothering
my granddaughter.
She's not like that.
But I believe something happened
to them.
Oh my!
She just doesn't want to say it.
Grandma, nothing really
happened.
I slept there.
It's embarrassing.
What did Lieutenant Conde say?
I don't know.
I just told him
that he could treat his wounds
and then I left.
I don't want to report for work.
Why?
Because of Sir Tonyo?
Maybe he's thinking
something else.
Come on, Bobby, you're the only
one thinking about that.
Yes, Bobby.
But maybe with Sir Tonyo,
that's nothing for him.
Right?
Oh, they're right.
Report for work.
It's work, nothing personal.
That's true.
Okay.
Okay, Grandma,
I'll report for work.
- Grandma...
- There's something.
What is it? Spill the tea.
Tonyo, the room is messy again!
You're so annoying!
Does this look like laundry?
Why are you filming me?
You're so beautiful
when you're angry.
Beautiful? Stop it.
- Your style is rotten.
- There!
- There
- What's that?
So beautiful!
You're pissing me off again!
- Fix this!
- Come on...
Does this look like laundry,
Tonyo?
Are you kidding?
Come on and give me a smile.
Let's do this.
Don't cook food later, okay?
Why? Are we going to eat out?
No. We're going to eat here.
What's wrong, Tonyo?
I told you not to touch me!
I'm going to find out
who killed you, Lara.
This isn't mine, ah.
Enriquez...
Just let it be.
This guy has a beard.
- Anybody home?
- Fix it.
- Hey!
- Oh...
Hey, someone's at the door.
Can't you hear?
Oh my God, Kapitana, we're
wearing face masks.
- Why don't you check it out?
- That's right.
- Can you dot it?
- Oh, anyway...
- So, here...
- You're disturbing us.
Please fix it
Freshen up a little.
What kind of beard is this?
Is it true?
- Oh, where's Grandma?
- Oh, hi, Bobby.'
She stepped out.
There's someone outside.
I don't know who it is.
Come in, come in
Bobby! Bobby!
Someone's looking for you.
Who is it, Grandma?
Come in.
- Oh.
- Enriquez...
Hurry up, Sis!
Sir Tonyo!
Have some coffee first.
Oh my Grandma, you even went out
of your way.
- Thank you very much.
- Of course.
- Thank you.
- That's for you.
Good morning, Captain.
- Mr. Tonyo is here.
- Hey, man.
How are you?
- How are you, man?
- Oh...
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Sir.
Enriquez.
Thanks for bringing
the medicine here.
You should've brought
that to the precinct.
That's nothing,
after what you did
to me last night.
- Did something?
- Last night?
- I wish everyone had that.
Sir, what did my granddaughter
do to you?
Grandma, I didn't do anything.
Ah, no, Grandma,
it's because Bobby
took me home last night
because I got beaten up.
And...
she forgot this at home.
Maybe you need it,
so I brought it here on purpose.
Oh, the medicines.
I need these medicines.
Grandma...
Sorry, Sir.
So, Enriquez, I'll go ahead.
Mar, Abdul, nice to meet you.
Dude, come back anytime.
Yes, Sir, even at night,
even if Bobby isn't here,
just come visit.
- Yes, anytime, at night.
- Yes.
Grandma, thank you very much
again for the coffee.
Oh, yes, of course.
You can have coffee here
anytime.
Okay, I'll go ahead.
- Enriquez.
- Okay, Sir.
Bye.
Hey! You're noisy!
Grandma...
Grandma, that's enough.
Come on, I'll bring you to work.
You too, Captain?
Restrain yourself.
Sir Tonyo is fine, right?
He looks like he smells good.
Wow! Wow!
You know, that's true.
I noticed that too.
He looks like husband material.
- Hey!
- Right?
That's right!
I'm thrilled.
Of course.
Of course, Grandma.
You know, my opinion
of Sir Tonyo has changed.
I just can't imagine his life
now that he's home alone.
Oh, my, it's really hard to lose
someone,
right?
Let's go.
Are you okay, Dear?
If only I had done something
different that day,
I wish Godmother Dina
was still alive.
I wish Sir Tonyo's girlfriend
Oh, that's okay, Dear.
Just hide that
because you can use it to help
them.
Okay, Grandma
I'll go ahead, okay?
Take care.
- Okay, Bobby.
- Bobby, be careful, okay?
Hey, Abdul, Mars, take care of
Grandma, okay?
- Take care, Bobby.
- We'll take care of Captain.
- You take care of Tonyo, okay?
- Take care, Dear. Take care..
Say hi to Tonyo for us!
Work, work.
Hey, Enriquez.
Have you seen Lieutenant Conde?
Huh? No!
What are you saying?
You know, I just got here.
It's impossible for the
two of us to meet.
I just got here, you,
what are you saying?
What happened there?
I was just asking.
Enriquez.
Are you looking for something?
Looking for something?
Oh, nothing, nothing.
Chief, that's just an excuse.
She's just looking for me.
Enriquez, not now.
Let's work first, okay?
Why not?
I can shoot that
for three points.
Oh, oh...
Sir...
Sir, sorry, Sir.
Sorry.
It's because I am doing...
I'm going to throw it away.
I'm looking for a trash can.
When I tried to shoot you,
you were there.
So it's my fault?
Oh, no! No, no, Sir.
Sorry, sorry.
Your body is big, Sir.
Sorry again, Sir.
Enriquez...
Do you want to talk about what
happened last night?
What's that, Sir?
Nothing happened, Sir.
Are you sure?
Yes, Sir, nothing!
I'm sure.
No, are you sure you don't want
to talk about it?
Oh, yes, Sir.
I don't want to talk about it.
Oh, no, we have nothing
to talk about.
Okay.
Three points, there you go
with three points.
You know, it's really my fault
because I left you.
When you're left behind,
you're out of control.
It's a good thing you got home.
Wait a minute.
How did you get home last night?
Enriquez, can you help me?
Chief asked me to do something.
Come on. What do you need?
Bok...
how are you and Enriquez?
We're fine.
Oh, Chief doesn't like fights
like that.
But you know, I think
she's just fighting you
to get closer to me.
That's her style.
Guys, the Chief's calling us.
The case is not moving forward
and we have no new leads.
So let's take a different turn.
Sorry, Sir, I'm late.
I just read the message.
We're focusing too much on Sonny
and who knocked him down.
Better yet, let's go after
those who might have a motive
for kidnapping
the Mayor's daughter.
Keep in mind.
If we solve this case,
maybe we can solve
the other cases too.
Is that clear?
Sir, yes, Sir.
You're all dismissed.
Enriquez, stay behind.
I saw your altercation with
Conde yesterday.
Oh, that's nothing, Sir.
Make sure you two don't do
anything stupid today
because the mayor
will award you.
You, Conde, Noble, and Dizon.
Ah, award Sir?
What for?
Because you saved
the Mayor's daughter.
But Noble and Dizon will follow.
Conde and you can go ahead to
Barangay Sta. Fe.
What?
You can go, Enriquez.
Just when you're avoiding him.
Why do we have to go together?
Noble!
Ma'am?
Where are you going?
Aren't you going with Tonyo?
Mmm, no, no, Ma'am.
We have something else
to take care of.
Maybe we'll just follow.
Okay.
Okay, Ma'am.
Hurry up, huh?
Enriquez, let's go.
Sir, ah, where are we going?
We're going to the awarding,
right?
Ah, yes.
Conde, can I go with you?
Do you want to go with us,
Sir? Okay, Sir.
Enriquez, calm down.
You're too obvious.
I thought you and Robles had an
assignment too.
Robles can handle that.
What? I'll go with you.
Yes, Sir, that's okay.
The more, the merrier.
Enriquez, Enriquez,
don't be so aggressive.
I'm getting turned off.
Garcia, you can't join.
If you want to catch up with the
fiesta, finish your work here.
Conde, go ahead, leave.
Yes, Sir.
Well, Enriquez, I'm sorry,
but I can't fulfill your dream
of being with me.
Sorry.
Enriquez, come on.
Let's go.
Oh, Roman?
are you going to tell me
something about the police?
There's a newbie at Station 12.
You're the one suspected
of being behind all the chaos
that's been going on.
Who is that?
Sergeant Enriquez.
Sergeant Enriquez...
I think I know who you're
talking about.
- Sergeant Enriquez...
- Boss?
what was the result of your
investigation?
Your masks were
used in the robbery.
That means the same group robbed
the museum
and the same group robbed
the San Isidro Rural Bank.
Good morning, Boss.
Oh, good morning too.
I thought you were here
because you wanted to
investigate me.
Investigate?
Roman, make sure
they don't find any holes in me.
I want the police to take their
eyes off me,
especially Sergeant Enriquez.
Consider it done, Boss.
Here it is.
Please check if it went through.
Okay, we got it.
Next time, tell your boyfriend
not to get drunk here.
Enriquez, are you okay?
You seem to be deep in thought,
ha.
Oh...
I was just thinking about last
night, Sir...
Last night?
No, because, Sir you owe me,
five thousand.
Five thousand?
Yes, Sir, the ones that were
broken at the convenience store.
Oh my,
you didn't even negotiate?
Five thousand, really?
Yes, five thousand.
I was wondering
what you did to me.
Hey, Sir, I'm not like that.
Hey, why do you think like that?
Calm down.
Just kidding! What's with you?
Can't you take a joke?
Let's go.
Enriquez.
What's that? What's that?
Sir, hey, you're too much.
- What's that?
- Your seatbelt.
Well, you have to make it clear
what you're saying.
You were doing this...
I thought it was something.
You're so grumpy.
Let's go.
Are you Bullet?
Yes.
Here's the target.
Hey.
You listen to me.
This job is very important,
okay?
So you...
Hey.
You listen.
I never miss.
- Hello?
- Hello, Chief?
I need backup.
I followed some kidnappers.
They kidnapped someone in
Calabari Townsquare
and it looks like I'm already in
their hideout.
We were kidnapped.
Have you seen that biker video,
the one where the riders were
being shot?
We should have been in there.
We failed to go there
because the Mayor ordered us to
roast a pig.
Oh my.
Come on, Mar!
What's with his face...
Oh, he looks like
our mysterious guy, Bro.
Is that him?