What happened to you?
Why are you looking suspiciously
at the Taho vendor?
Remember, we recognized
Oppa sniper?
What's in your bag?
This?
Go around, I'll follow him!
Mister, wait a minute!
I was just going to ask you
something.
Stop!
Where did he go?
You, go, go, go!
Don't try to do something bad.
I'm tired!
Move aside! Move!
They're just sending me
the money.
They're just giving me
instructions.
That's all.
Let's talk at the police
station!
Dizon!
Die!
You made a mistake
in challenging me
because I don't give up.
Ernesto Makvar alias Gatilyo.
The one you fought was a known
hitman, Enriquez.
So, Chief, that means he has no
boss,
that he will only act when
someone is willing to pay him.
But he was knocked down.
That means he knows something.
Enriquez is right.
That's why I really want
to catch him.
I'm sure we can squeeze
a lot out of him.
But I really had no choice
earlier.
If I didn't beat him to it,
I'd be the one to die.
That's fine, Conde.
Good job anyway.
If you get any information,
tell me right away.
Go ahead, you're dismissed.
Sir.
I'll go ahead, Enriquez.
It's a shame, Sir, if we had
brought the Korean here alive,
he probably knows a lot of
things, but you killed him.
Is there something you want
to tell me, Enriquez?
I'm just wondering, Sir.
You said earlier that you wanted
to catch the Korean.
Why did you kill him?
Enriquez, I had to choose
between him and me.
Now, if you have a problem
with me, report it to the Chief.
Hello, boss?
Have you heard the news?
That Korean is crazy.
All he does is rant,
but he's good for nothing.
Did you know that Selena
is still alive?
And until now, Sonny's SD card
has not been found.
Boss, just tell me.
Maybe it's time for me to shine.
You saw what I did, right?
Thank you.
- Ma'am?
- Ma'am, Sir...
Do you need something?
I'm sorry, I know we discussed
this at orientation,
but maybe I can ask you a favor.
What is it, Miss Selena?
Is there a problem?
No, I don't have a problem,
but I really need
to make a call.
Maybe you can grant my request.
It's really important.
Oh my, Ma'am, I'm sorry,
but that's really against
our protocol.
Why don't we do this, Ma'am?
We'll be the ones to call
whoever you want to talk to.
Who do you want to talk to,
Ma'am?
No. Okay, thank you.
Hey Bok, thank you.
Bok.
Thank you, Bok.
Cheers.
You know, I told you,
be careful with that Enriquez.
She's hardworking,
but her meddlesome ways
are on a different level.
I don't know what I will do with
that girl.
She's a troublemaker.
No matter what I do,
she doubts it.
Bok, just understand her.
That's how it is,
with the newbies, right?
They want to show off and want
to prove something.
It would be good if she's really
focused on the case.
The problem is, she's looking
at it from a different angle.
It's annoying.
Bok, I have a suggestion,
just so you don't get annoyed.
What?
What if instead of being mean to
her, you try to be nice to her?
Who knows when you two become
okay,
she will no longer bother you?
It's like a good cop,
just a bad cop.
But with you,
the other way around.
From bad cop to good cop, right?
Good morning, Bobby!
Bobby, morning!
What happened there?
Deep in thought.
I thought of something.
What's that?
Hey, it's Sir Tonyo, oh!
Sir Tonyo!
Sir Tonyo?
Look at how she reacts.
She has a long neck.
Is that a giraffe?
You've got nothing to do
with your life, right?
Sis, please, you know,
we get you.
We're like that too,
when we have a crush.
And Bobby, admit it.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Doesn't it?
Especially when your crush
is an action star!
Yes.
That's right.
Doesn't it?
Stop it, you two!
He will not come here.
- You're not sure.
- Okay.
Hey, you two,
you're making so much noise.
Grandmother,
scold them go there.
- Stay there. Over there.
- Kapitana.
Grandchild, how are you?
Are those people bothering you?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm just thinking a lot of
things, Grandmother.
Oh, really?
Bobby!
It's Sir Tonyo!
You're so annoying!
Didn't I tell you he won't come
here?
Okay.
What if he's here?
What are you going to do?
Yes.
Yes, okay.
When he's really there
and comes here, I'll treat you!
Okay, okay, deal.
Okay!
Deal.
Kapitana, you're our witness,
right?
You guys are just fooling us.
You guys, you're making
a lot of noise, the neighbors.
Okay.
Surprise...
Check it.
Just check it.
You don't want to believe.
Enriquez.
Sir Tonyo?
The power of the sun!
It contains light.
Twins, be strong.
We are the Super twins!
Told you!
Tonyo!
Come in!
I cooked, stay and eat here.
I'll prepare the table for you.
No need, thanks.
I am here to fetch
your granddaughter.
Why, Sir?
Where are we going?
I'll just take you with me
and we'll talk to Daga
about Victor Santiago.
In the formal complaint
filed by incumbent
Mayor Joaquin "El Hepe" Guerrero
against the alleged hostage
situation of mayoral candidate
Victor "Amo" Santiago,
whistleblower Brando Salazar,
alias Daga,
will play a big role,
especially if the Court
subpoenas him.
Amo, Amo, it's VM.
VM, hello.
Vice, you're here.
Amo.
I'm sure you want to talk
about the latest character
assassination against me.
Look, Amo, I understand
that politics is really dirty.
That's why I stayed this long in
politics,
because I do my best to steer
clear of dirty things
but I'm sorry, Amo.
I need to disassociate my name
from your candidacy.
No, no, you can't do this.
Now really?
We have an agreement.
Amo, we didn't talk about this
kind of exposés
against your name.
I'm sorry, Victor.
I value CNL's backing.
It's my responsibility
to take care of their vote.
I'm sorry, Amo.
Don't tell me you're going
to endorse Joaquin.
I'm not sure.
We'll see.
Are you wondering, Enriquez,
why I fetch you?
Not at all, Sir.
I just thought Lieutenant Garcia
was the one you were with
in the investigation of Daga.
I just thought it would be
better if you could hear
what Daga had to say
for transparency, right?
I don't know what we'll get out
of it,
but I hope it helps in the case
we're investigating.
Enriquez.
Good morning, Grandmother.
Good morning.
What's that, hija?
Can I ask, Grandmother?
Do you know where Brando
Salazar, alias Daga, lives?
Are you police officers?
We just wanted to talk to him
about what he said
about Victor Santiago.
I'm sorry.
Well, I don't know him.
No, I don't know anything like
that.
Just ask around there...
Over there.
I'm sorry.
Okay, thank you.
It looks like we're not going
to get anywhere here.
Let's go in, Sir.
What's your problem with me?
What's your problem?
Hey...
Good morning, guys.
Good morning.
I'm Lieutenant Conde.
Sergeant Enriquez is with me.
Good morning.
Boys, please be respectful
of our guests.
We were just wondering
if you know anyone named Brando,
Brando Salazar.
That's an old name!
Hey, maybe that's your father!
No, his father's name
is Wilfredo.
He's better known as Daga.
You're on another level,
Miss Mira.
You're unreachable.
What's with you?
You just have to be at the right
place and the right time.
Your source is also good,
really reliable.
That's why I'll take care
of you.
We'll both succeed as long
as you work with me, okay?
Sure.
Mayor, good morning.
Hey, morning, morning.
You're something else,
Miss Mira.
Morning, morning.
We need to talk to him about
that exposé she gave
to Victor Santiago.
Hey, I recognize them.
Those are the ones who helped in
the riot in the court.
That's them?
Yes, that's them.
Is that true?
Are you the police who helped
with the riot in the court?
That's us.
Do you want to talk to Daga?
We hope so.
That's fine, but we have a law
to enforce here.
Now, if you really want to talk
to Daga,
surrender those...
You know.
Sorry.
You don't know, but in our area,
there's a bit of a gun ban
right now.
That's why it's not allowed,
right?
Aren't they forbidden?
It's forbidden.
That's forbidden because you'll
never know, right?
But if you don't want to,
we are understanding, right?
Let's go.
Okay, you can leave now.
Wait, wait a minute.
Sir, that's dangerous.
Chief.
Don't point it at me.
That's it.
Now, of course,
before the meet and greet,
before you meet the star
of the day...
Okay.
Wait, what's this?
Easy, easy, Ma'am.
Ma'am, Sir, easy.
Remember?
We have laws here.
Of course, you need
to be blindfolded.
Just relax!
Remember?
Gun ban.
Safe.
Is that secured?
Maybe, it's still visible to
them.
Assist them.
Hey, Mayor!
Major.
Good morning.
Major Morning, morning.
- Good morning.
- You're my idol.
Is it okay to take a picture?
Yes, yes.
Let's take a picture, Sir.
Just a selfie for...
Okay.
Sir, come on. Selfie.
Let's go.
Excuse me.
You. Us.
One, two...
Thank you.
Mayor, what can I do for you?
By the way, Major,
are you aware that I filed
a formal complaint
against Victor Santiago?
Yes, Mayor.
I want us to talk about...
what I can do to stop this
Victor Santiago nonsense.
Okay, Mayor.
Let's go to the office.
Okay.
Daga!
You're preparing something.
By the way, you have a visitor.
Hey!
It's you.
Sit down. Sit down.
Which one are we?
The one I called pig during
the hostage taking.
I'm sorry.
That was just acting.
Sit down.
It's okay.
You said you wanted to talk
to me.
Why are you hiding, Daga?
Are you afraid of someone?
You know that Amo can be
influential.
Just playing it safe.
It's hard.
Well, if someone tries to take
your life, we can protect you.
Oh my.
Here in my territory,
no one can touch me.
But of course,
don't tell them I'm here.
Of course.
Victor Santiago's payment
to your group,
what proof do you have for that?
Well, this!
This is the first time
I was able to have this.
This too.
That gun is new, we bought it.
And him, I paid off his debt.
He is a beast.
Yes.
All that, from Amo?
We have no receipts to show,
except for the ones we bought
with Amo's payment,
but all I can tell you is,
I'm not a liar.
Why would I mess up my life?
Is Amo the only one you've met?
Didn't you talk to anyone else
from Amo's camp?
None, but I saw someone
with Amo.
Okay, Amo, we'll go ahead.
Okay, okay.
Amo, can we use your restroom?
Sure, okay.
I'll go first. Okay.
But it had nothing to do
with the riot.
Do you know him?
No.
I haven't met him.
I just saw him with Amo.
He must be his driver.
But I seem to remember his face.
Better yet, Daga, let's go to
the police station.
Describe the person you're
talking about there
so we can make a sketch.
Boss, take it easy.
Just stay there.
Sit down for now.
We're still talking.
Just sit down.
And what did I tell you?
I'll just stay here
in my territory.
Why would I go out?
I'm just letting you talk to me.
I don't trust the police.
Who knows if Amo has an ally
in your force?
What if I send someone here
to sketch?
Is that okay?
It's up to you.
Okay, send him here.
Hello, Dylan?
Daga, you have a visitor.
Boss, where are you taking me?
Is this your contact?
Okay, take off the blindfold.
Dylan.
Daga, Dylan, sketch artist.
How do we do this?
Just describe it to me
and I'll take care of it.
Come on, let's go there.
Let's start with the shape
of his head.
His face looks a little round.
A little rounder.
Good morning, Mayor.
Hey. Good morning.
What are you doing here
at the police station?
No, I just want to show the
people here
that someone still cares
about them.
I just want to clarify,
are you saying that you're going
to focus more on curbing crime
in Calabari now than
campaigning?
That's right.
I'm willing to sacrifice my
campaign
just to curb crime here
in Calabari.
You know, people from Calabari
are smart.
They want to see some work done,
it's hard if I go around here
in the campaign,
and Calabari is not doing okay.
Oh, okay.
- I'll go ahead.
- Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Good morning, Mayor.
Did you get it?
A little thicker, boss,
his eyebrows.
Okay.
Borrow?
Like that?
This is it.
That's him.
This is Amo's driver.
You're good.
Maybe we can use to do a selfie.
There are four of us.
But a portrait, okay?
Do you know this, Sir?
Sure.
Okay.
You're good.
We'd better take that
to the station
so we can compare it
with the record.
I'll take care of this,
Enriquez.
Enriquez,
let's meet at the station, okay?
Why, Sir? Where are you going?
I have something important
to take care of.
What about the sketch?
I'll take care of it.
Here, you can take the car.
Okay, Sir.
Can I talk to you?
Tonyo, is there a problem?
Just make sure
that all your answers
to my questions are true.
If not, we'll end up fighting.
Is this about Daga?
You know, son, they're just
trying to ruin my name.
It's not about him.
It's About the museum robbery
and the San Isidro bank robbery.
Did you have anything
to do with that?
I'll have my fingers cut off
if you discover that I had
anything to do with it.
The gun is registered to
Victor Santiago,
but is that enough evidence
to prove
that he really shot Bullet?
Well, that was 10 years ago.
Well, if it wasn't him,
then this is a terrible
coincidence.
Let's start with the mask used
in the bank,
then the poison used on Sonny,
and the bullet in Bullet's head.
Come on, come with me.
Where, Sir?
Daga was killed.
Do you have any idea who did it?
No name was mentioned,
but I heard it from Daga's own
mouth that he was talking
to a policeman,
a policeman he trusted.
Tonyo?