ALL CHARACTERS AND EVENTS
ARE FICTITIOUS
FILMING FOR CHILD ACTORS DONE
UNDER BROADCASTING GUIDELINES
- Let us go!
- Oh, no!
Let us keep going!
Okay, here we go.
Number two!
You guys!
Enjoy.
That man is Kim Man-dol.
- It is over! Man-dol won!
- Oh, my!
That is just unbelievable.
Man-dol, you are so lucky today.
I am Hong Deok-su
and I would like to join.
- What do you say?
- Hong Deok-su?
- Who is that?
- Who is he?
- Hong Deok-su?
- I have never seen him before.
So? Did you bring
some money to wager then?
You can start us off.
ROYAL PALACE
Let us go.
Stop right there.
Who goes there?
Prince Muyeong.
Bow down and show proper respect.
It is Prince Muyeong.
Let them go.
- A pair of twos!
- A pair of twos.
He is simply unstoppable.
So why did you keep going?
You lost everything.
Gosh. Did you run out of funds?
If you did, a deed for a house
or land could work.
- I should get going then.
- Stop!
The Yongcheonru Red Certificate!
- The Red Certificate!
- It is!
The precious Red Certificate?
Have you lost your mind?
The new-recruit exam pass for Yongcheonru!
Will you accept it?
My word.
And how do I know
that it is the real deal?
Unbelievable.
Are you blind or something?
Go ahead and take a closer look.
It is the same emblem
as the one on Yongcheonru's main gate.
Even the highest-ranking minister
in the land
cannot get into the new-recruit exam
without this.
The Red Certificate.
Open the gates!
YONGCHEONRU
Yongcheonru.
I shall wager this. Hong Deok-su!
You should wager all this.
Come on, now.
Let me see that.
Even so, I still need to check for myself.
Yes, this is the real deal indeed.
Fine.
Do not cry and beg for a refund later.
Unbelievable. You better not cry either.
Goodness me.
Single round.
Deal.
Let us go to the west gate.
POLICE BUREAU
Who are you?
Sir, please lend me your ear.
There is a huge…
- A pair of fives!
- You won!
You are set. It is already over!
It is over.
A pair of sixes!
A pair of sixes? How is that possible?
I won. All right.
Right, I should at least give you
a consolation prize.
Thank you for the fun game.
Brother Deok-su!
Please help me out.
It belongs to my guild.
My boss will kill me if he finds out.
We agreed to no refunds.
Please!
Brother Deok-su! Please have mercy on me!
- What the…
- I beg of you. Just this once.
- Please!
- Help yourselves!
- Come on. Move.
- Move!
Stop this instant!
Arrest every single one of them!
Finally.
Gu-sil.
Stop right there!
- Did you win the Red Certificate?
- Of course.
You really did it!
Stop right there!
Let us go.
Come on.
Hurry up!
YONGCHEONRU
ROYAL PALACE, YONGCHEONRU
The palace built across
from the royal palace.
Yongcheonru.
Joseon's premier inn,
built on a site blessed by a dragon.
Its prestige is celebrated
throughout this land
and even in the West.
GEUMUI CHAMBER
Each guest is welcomed
in the most elegantly dignified fashion
as soon as they walk in.
GEUMOK HALL
They have every delicacy known to mankind.
- Bring over the cabbage and green onions.
- Yes, I will get them.
Let us hurry up.
And one could even be served
the king's royal meal if they desired it.
At Yongcheonru,
the guest is the king.
Joseon's unparalleled slice of heaven.
If you have the money,
nothing is out of reach.
And you can even be reborn
as someone else from head to toe.
If you have the money,
anything is possible at Yongcheonru.
And that is all thanks to its employees.
These are dream jobs
for the youth of Hanyang,
where social classes do not matter
and talent is all you need to succeed.
Yongcheonru becomes
fully realized in their hands.
And they are all led by…
the innkeeper.
My target is
Let go of me! Is the queen still not back?
Tell her to come and pour me a drink!
Is that man…
If she is not around,
bring me a royal concubine!
Is he wearing the Dragon Robe?
My goodness!
You cannot do this out here, Your Majesty!
How dare that abominable man…
You cannot, Your Highness.
This is not the time.
Let go of me!
DOHWA HALL
It seems we have
uninvited guests in our midst.
Shall I dispatch the guards?
Let them be.
You cannot chase after every stray cat
that climbs over the fence.
Hand over my Red Certificate!
Hold on. Wait.
Just hand it over, and no one gets hurt.
Deok-su!
All right.
I will leave all my money here.
You can take it.
No, I do not want your money.
Just hand over the Red Certificate!
Do you really mean that?
I just return this to you,
and we are all good?
Yes, that is it.
Fine.
Here.
Take it.
Why, you little…
Gu-sil, you need to run. Get up.
Go on!
- Deok-su!
- Go, Gu-sil!
Go on!
Hand over my Red Certificate! It is mine!
Give me back my Red Certificate!
Stop!
Stop right there!
Hand it over!
My Red Certificate!
Damn it!
Let go! Why, you little…
Let go!
Where do you think you are going?
Come here!
It is my Red Certificate! It is mine.
- Give it back.
- What the…
What are you doing?
Let go! Let go of me!
Give it back.
- Wait.
- Let go of me.
Let go of me already!
- Let go!
- Come on.
Are you all right?
Are you two from Yongcheonru?
Give it back. It is mine.
Wait, no. It is mine.
That is nonsense.
I mean… It belongs to my boss,
but he conned me
into going double or nothing--
Double or nothing?
No.
What I meant was…
You better tell the truth.
Hold on.
We are future apprentices of Yongcheonru.
That is the certificate that verifies it,
so please return it
and be on your way, my lords.
Future apprentices of Yongcheonru…
Do you even know
what you are getting yourself into?
Are you aware
of the abominable acts committed there
by the lawless and depraved?
I do not care about their abominable acts.
I just need to get in there.
- Mind your own affairs and be on your way.
- What did you say?
Yongcheonru is probably
more honest and just
than you two threatening me with swords.
These two going for double or nothing,
gambling and fighting
in the dead of night,
dare to speak of "honest and just"?
Did you say this belonged to you?
- Yes, it belongs to me, my lord.
- Seriously, going back on your word?
And you also claim
that it belongs to you.
What?
One certificate but two owners…
I have the ideal resolution.
I ripped it in half
because you appreciate "honest and just."
What do you think?
Share it. No need to fight.
I hope you both make it into Yongcheonru.
I am done for. I am ruined.
What have you done?
It becomes void if it is ripped!
You…
Attacking from behind like a coward,
and you talk about "honest and just"?
Do not make me laugh.
Then again, you are
aspiring Yongcheonru apprentices.
Shame must feel foreign to you.
You ripped someone else's certificate.
You are also--
You are just as cowardly.
I will use the blade
and not the sheath next time.
You will pay for this one day.
I will be sure to include assault
on your list of charges!
Let him be.
After all, I owe a debt
to the esteemed gentleman.
Damn it.
TAVERN
Hey, are you okay?
And the Red Certificate?
You have it, right?
What is wrong with this?
It is ripped in half!
How could you let this happen?
Darn it. How could he rip
my Red Certificate?
I ripped it in half
because you appreciate "honest and just."
Share it. No need to fight.
I hope you both make it into Yongcheonru.
That vile punk.
Who did this?
Was it that jerk Kim Man-dol?
No, it was some other jerk.
After all that work you put
into acquiring that darn certificate…
What are we going to do now?
We have no other choice.
Since we cannot undo it…
we just move on to the next step.
THIRTY
Here are the ten chests
of gold bars for this month.
You could have just sent them
in a palanquin.
Why come in person?
I am a shrewd businessman
down to the bone.
How could I possibly trust
my subordinates with gold?
It was my pleasure.
I enjoyed the tour of the royal palace.
Even the walls have eyes
in the royal palace.
The Minister of War will find out
soon enough.
No good can come from your presence.
For both you and me.
Then, perhaps Your Majesty could pay
a visit to Yongcheonru?
You could consider it a visit of goodwill
to your close friend.
"Close friend"?
You dare to consider yourself
my close friend?
You do utilize my coffers
as if they were your own, after all.
If I am not your close friend,
then what could I be?
You dare to insult me and the royal family
over some measly gold?
My deepest apologies.
My lack of knowledge
regarding moral principles and laws
has led my lowly self
to commit an unforgivable sin.
Therefore, starting this month,
as a show of repentance,
may I add 10 more chests
to make my monthly offerings 20?
This lowly creature has committed
an unforgivable sin to His Majesty.
You must command what you desire
for me to have any hope
for your forgiveness.
I await your command.
What do you desire, Your Majesty?
And if he desires Yongcheonru?
I shall hand it over.
Your reputation certainly precedes you.
Your tongue is sharper than a sword.
Do you not agree, Father?
And why have you shown up unannounced
in the dead of night?
Forgive me, Father.
I ignored the rules of etiquette
because I had an urgent request.
A request?
Did you say you were willing
to offer anything?
Yes, Your Highness. I await your command.
I hear Yongcheonru is accepting
new apprentices this season.
I would like to join
to acquire some expert business acumen.
What do you say?
Prince Muyeong.
What in the world are you saying?
"The power of gold is
what feeds the people."
That is what you have taught me
time and time again, Father.
Therefore, I would like
to master the craft of business myself.
I beseech you for your royal permission.
However,
even with His Majesty's royal permission,
if you enter Yongcheonru,
you will also have to learn
as one of the lowly apprentices.
What did you say?
That is the way of Yongcheonru.
Regardless of class or background,
one must start at the bottom
and survive the hardships
to claw their way to the top.
That is the very teaching
we bestow upon our apprentices.
Would you mind that, Your Highness?
Not at all.
The future crown prince possesses
such modesty and audacity.
Having such a dependable son
must be quite reassuring.
You are in no place
to commend me for such matters.
I shall review
Prince Muyeong's request later.
Leave me now.
You wish to join Yongcheonru?
Why would you dare
to take such initiative?
I am aware what you seek is
inside Yongcheonru.
What is it? Please tell me, Father.
There is a shadow ledger.
It is the one weakness
of those wrapping me around their fingers.
We must find it if we wish to eradicate
the parties who scorn the throne.
Then I shall find it as soon as possible.
The brass key.
That is the only key
to the safe which holds the shadow ledger.
Those two pieces must come together
to open the safe.
It cannot be opened by one alone.
That despicable Cheon has hidden
one of them somewhere in Yongcheonru
and is looking for the other.
Prince Muyeong, you must find it first.
They seated me on this royal throne
to be their puppet
for the sake of their personal gains.
Finding that shadow ledger is the only way
to safeguard this feeble throne
and the royal line.
For the sake of the sovereignty and state,
and to relieve you of your distress…
I shall go in there myself
and find that key.
Get them!
12 YEARS AGO
Hand over the safe!
Jae-on.
Father.
Let us go. Hurry!
I am very scared.
I know, my dear child.
All right.
You must keep this safe.
You can never lose it.
Do you understand?
From now on, you shall live as a boy.
Run far away. As far as you can.
You must never go near Yongcheonru.
Do you understand?
Find Hong Min-sik's daughter!
Search thoroughly!
She must be nearby!
After staying out all night
like some stray cat,
you dare touch my meat?
Why would you even bother crawling back?
Come on, now.
I am going to have you living
in the lap of luxury real soon.
You are going to regret it
if you continue treating me like this.
You will be filled with remorse.
Lap of luxury, my foot!
- Welcome.
- Come on in!
- Have a seat.
- Welcome.
- What can I get you?
- Two soups with rice.
Sure.
WANTED
REPORT TO KIM DU-PAL
It has been a while,
but I guess the search is back on.
Her dad must be some big shot.
They are offering 100 nyang for any tip.
They just started the search back up.
She must be dead after ten years.
Come on, now.
Right, surely she must be dead by now.
Excuse me.
- Make it quick.
- Sure thing.
A generous portion.
- Come back next time.
- Sure.
Take care now.
Hello there. Are you looking for some dye?
- Is this it?
- It is of the highest quality.
- I will take that.
- Thank you, kind sir.
Hey, Deok-su!
Do you need something else?
Let me see here…
Hold on. Let me see that one.
- This one?
- Yes.
Here you go.
This will do.
Let me get a bundle of this.
Sure. You have got quite a discerning eye.
I will wrap it right up for you.
This is nice.
- Hey, take a look at this.
- Yes?
It was imported from the Qing.
Oh, my.
My goodness.
You look like a clown bride.
As if you know anything, Hong Deok-su.
- Do you? What do you know?
- Goodness.
Stop it.
I need to concentrate.
That looks just like the real one.
You will forge the royal seal
in no time at that rate.
Of course.
I am the Hong Deok-su.
You are willing to do all this
just to get into Yongcheonru?
Yes.
There is someone I need to meet.
What? Who?
The lady tends to suffer
from a persistent minor cough.
Avoid using flowers with excessive pollen.
Yes, my lady.
I set aside some agarwood from the West
for deserving subjects.
Shall I send some to the palace?
The palace?
No need.
What will you do about Prince Muyeong?
The king must be having him search
for the brass key.
They are just scurrying around
in the palm of my hand.
GRAND PROPRIETOR
Let them have at it.
Uncle!
Eun, do not run!
- Uncle!
- Eun!
My goodness! Why, it is Prince Muyeong.
Dear brother.
I see you are
with the crown prince, Your Majesty.
You must behave in His Majesty's presence.
Let him be.
Let my adorable nephew be.
Brother, do you have a cold?
Are you worried about his health?
I shall protect you if you are sick.
What comforting words.
All right. Prince Muyeong,
be sure to keep him safe in the future.
Can you promise me that?
Yes, Your Majesty.
- Your Majesty!
Brother!
Father!
Father…
It is late. What are you doing there?
Has the physician come by?
Yes.
But with tonics day and night,
the physician
only provides more suffering.
You must take care of yourself
and hang in there, Brother.
The royal line must be steadfast.
Is Uncle…
I mean, is His Majesty doing well?
You must prioritize
his and your well-being over mine.
Promise me that.
Twenty-eight.
Are you sure you will be all right alone?
I must be.
We only have one Red Certificate.
What choice do we have?
I will be sure to remain in your vicinity.
Beom-ho?
What are you doing?
TWENTY-EIGHT
Yongcheonru.
What is that?
My goodness. Look at all this.
What is going on here?
That is a meaty chicken.
So you are really going?
I told Gu-sil to help you out
with the cooking.
Do not get up at the crack of dawn
to prepare it all by yourself. Okay?
You never listen to your mother.
Do not even think about coming back.
Eat. Fill your belly.
Food must be eaten when it is warm.
It is no good when cold.
You must never skip meals,
wherever you are.
- Okay.
- Got that?
Why must you insist on going there?
You do not need to worry about me.
I will be safe.
When are you coming back?
After about a month?
Who knows? Maybe sooner if I get fired.
Even if you do not get fired,
just make sure you do not get exposed.
I will.
- You should have some too.
- I am good.
- Come on. Open up.
- No.
- Go on.
- My goodness.
Open up. Go on.
Is it not good? So good, right?
- Have some more.
- No, I am fine.
Let us eat it together. Come on.
- You eat it all.
- No, eat it with me.
- You have a long journey…
- Then I will not eat it either.
Okay, fine. We will eat it together.
- Eat up.
- This one is mine. Where is yours?
ESCAPE FROM THE HEAT
GOLDEN ICE
When are they going to let us in?
I am going to die waiting
for this golden ice or whatever.
How precious is this golden dish for them
to only make five servings per day?
Unbelievable. This is all just
a sales tactic at the end of the day.
Do not worry, my lady.
Our palanquin is the fifth in line.
You will taste it today.
Make way. Move aside.
And who is that?
Why are they getting in before us?
Stop right there.
- Who are you to cut the line?
- Who is that?
What is all this commotion about?
There is no more golden ice for the day.
I am the fifth and last serving.
Do you know who I am? Let us go in.
- Who are you to cut the line?
- Move it!
- My goodness!
- What in the world?
Madam!
Welcome. We have been waiting for you.
See?
One should respect order.
Order? What order?
It is only right to follow the order
if there is a line.
He is right!
You can go to the police bureau
way over there to argue right and wrong.
This is Yongcheonru.
It has its own code of law and order.
This way, madam.
Thank you for stepping in
and taking my side.
Compensation will not be necessary.
Take care.
Excuse me.
I have a novel idea.
Would you like to hear it?
Look here.
A shortsighted scheme
may seem useful at first,
but it will leave a dishonorable stain.
Right. Such awe-inspiring words. Thanks.
So, what exactly is
this useful, shortsighted scheme?
My scheme will indeed leave
a bit of a dirty stain.
What should we do?
Let us just wait
and see what happens for a moment.
Yes, my lady.
YEONHWA HALL
RESTAURANTS IN YONGCHEONRU
It has been a while, Lord Yu.
Yeonhwa Hall is already
so bustling this early in the morning.
Word has spread throughout the capital
about how tasty the golden ice is.
I am also here to taste
that famous golden ice.
That must be the golden ice.
My goodness.
I have only ever heard about it.
It is my first time seeing it.
What a precious dish.
You always go above and beyond for me.
Thank you, madam.
This is one of the five daily servings
of the golden ice that we serve.
Unfortunately, that is why
I missed my chance to taste it.
I shall now take my leave. Enjoy.
Hold on.
What have you done?
Pardon?
This is no golden ice.
- What?
- Pardon?
It certainly is. It was
just freshly prepared in Yeonhwa Hall.
Did you think you could trick
her ladyship like this
because it is her first time?
Golden ice should be served
with a heavy dollop of condensed milk.
I do not even see
a single drop of it here.
Well… That is a misunderstanding…
Tell me the truth!
It is because
first-time tasters could experience
an upset stomach after having it--
Are you sure it was not left out
because it is a pricey condiment?
If you lack the funds, I will gladly pay.
So serve her a proper bowl
of golden ice immediately.
Stop underestimating
and fooling your guest.
That will not be necessary!
Fetch me a dollop of condensed milk now.
I do not care how much it costs.
Bring me every last drop
in this establishment!
Yes, madam.
Golden ice is a summer confection
of finely shaved ice
with simmered red beans, fruit,
and condensed milk on top.
So?
The noblewoman who just walked in had
an undoubtedly pale and frail face.
Her constitution must be weak.
And what does her face have to do
with golden ice?
A weak constitution and condensed milk are
an ill-fated match.
You cannot eat so much of it, madam.
Please stop there. My goodness.
What is wrong?
What is it?
Goodness me! It happened.
You have an upset stomach now.
That is what happens when you are greedy.
Goodness me!
She suffered in the restroom
and went home just now.
Lord Yu tried to stop her,
but she consumed
all of the condensed milk.
Another guest at Yeonhwa Hall
suggested condensed milk to her?
Yes, my lady.
It must have been that boy
who had the face of a sly fox.
What an adorable rascal he is.
I hope there will be such clever ones
in the upcoming recruitment intake.
No.
Maybe they would only give me a headache.
You are all set.
Go on up.
Listen. The apprentices can collect
their supplies after registering.
- Excuse me.
- Jeez!
Why are you so startled?
Maybe your petite physique comes
with equally frail nerves?
My name is Cheon Jun-hwa.
Okay. I am Hong Deok-su.
No, I was not asking for a handshake.
Help me carry this instead.
Two grown men should not hold
each other's hands.
Seriously?
I did not know we could only bring
two bundles per person when we enrolled.
I only found out
after I came with all this.
Too bad. My heart goes out to you, really.
It is indeed terrible.
But what can I do?
I cannot just toss out my belongings.
Since you only have one bundle,
holding my third one would
only complete you.
No thanks.
Right.
A merchant must know how to deal.
These bundles are filled
with jerky and other snacks.
I heard this program is arduous
and you find yourself constantly famished.
Proceed that way.
I will give you a tenth of mine.
- Make that five-tenths.
- Five-tenths?
What sort of merchant asks for half
for such a short delivery?
You can just toss it
if you do not like it.
Two-tenths.
Two-tenths. Final offer.
This jerky is from Damyang. Heard of it?
Top-grade and enjoyed by the king.
Five-tenths.
I am being robbed in broad daylight
as soon as I arrive.
Fine. Five-tenths.
Now, half of this bundle is mine, right?
A deal has been struck, so yes.
Goodness. Thank you for your service.
Excuse me.
RECEPTION DESK
Attention.
My name is Bang Sa-seon.
I will be your mentor here.
Since you have enrolled in Gyohwa Hall,
you are now mere pupae.
What exactly is a pupa?
Just another bug.
You are past the caterpillar stage
but still nowhere near being a butterfly.
A pupa.
A pest! Got that?
- Yes, sir.
In Yongcheonru, you will be assessed
only on your achievements.
You could climb up with merit points,
or come crashing down with demerit points.
What happens when you hit rock bottom?
You will be kicked out immediately.
Now, all you pupae will swiftly
get changed and gather in the front yard.
The order of your arrival is crucial.
What happens if you are late?
Death.
What are you standing around for? Move it!
Where do we…
Wait. Here?
Pardon me.
Did you see the uniform
that was just here?
Let go of me! Jeez.
You! It is you! The ripper!
You are a Yongcheonru apprentice too?
So that is why you ripped my certificate.
You rotten jerk!
Have you lost your mind?
I just need a moment.
Just a moment, my foot!
Get off me!
Come on, now. Use your words.
Darn it. Insane bastard.
You just ripped my shirt.
Should I rip yours too?
You just need to show me once.
It will be quick.
Come on, now. Hold on.
Such vigorous quarreling on the first day.
That is youth for you.
A strong first impression.
Just show me what is
under your undergarment.
Look here.
Why are you trying to see
another man's bare chest?
That is some bullshit. What is with you?
"Bare chest"? Such abominable phrasing.
Watch it, now.
Dirty bastard.
Such insolence!
How dare you call me dirty!
You scoundrel!
- Stop it.
- Look here.
Let go of him.
I just need to check once. Just once.
We are both men.
What do you need to check? Let go!
A scuffle on the first day
will get you kicked out.
Just let go of him.
Hold on.
I think our uniforms were switched.
Who are you?
- Let go and talk it out.
- They were switched!
It would not take long.
Move those feet swiftly.
Do you not grasp the concept of ranking?
Lady Seol, what brings you here?
Yongcheonru just welcomed new trainees.
Of course I should be here.
Yes, my lady.
Move it!
Faster! Your arrivals will be ranked!
Do not do this here!
That is my uniform.
You have eyes. Use them and look.
Mine is clearly bigger.
Bigger?
Who is bigger? Well?
I am telling you, that is my uniform.
- Let go of me!
- What are you scoundrels doing?
Demerit points for all you scoundrels!
12 YEARS AGO
Find Hong Min-sik!
Where is the safe?
Hand over the safe!
Where is Hong Min-sik?
You must keep this safe.
You can never lose it.
Do you understand?
From now on, you shall live as a boy.
Once you climb over this wall,
you will no longer be Hong Jae-on.
But I am Hong Jae-on.
I am Hong Jae-on, your daughter.
No! You are no longer my daughter!
No one can know you are Hong Jae-on
or that you are a girl. Do you understand?
Yes.
All right.
Let us go.
- Go on.
- Find Hong Min-sik!
Go on. Now!
Go.
I saw the brass key.
It was not Lord Cheon.
Someone else had it.
What is his true identity?
Could there be something you are hiding?
He sure is a weird one.
I am staying clear of him.
Such fine, delicate hands.
This is how a true man studies.
Something is not right.
Darn it. Lee Eun-ho?
I have to share a room with him?
You are hiding something under there.
Damn it. Seriously?
Watch yourself, Deok-su.
Hey, Lee Eun-ho. Why, you little…
What are you looking at?
Hong Deok-su.
You cannot be expelled just yet.
I am telling you to behave.
Where does the innkeeper stay?
A man was killed for his Red Certificate.
One desired Yongcheonru so much
that he killed for a spot?
And where is the other half?
Who goes there?
Someone must have forged
the stolen Red Certificate
to join Gyohwa Hall.
Lady Seol,
I have been wanting to meet you.
Subtitle translation by: Justin S. Kim