ALL CHARACTERS AND EVENTS
ARE FICTITIOUS
FILMING OF CHILD ACTORS DONE
UNDER BROADCASTING GUIDELINES
12 YEARS AGO
Did you keep the royal physician quiet?
If word gets out,
we will go down together.
There is no mouth
that cannot be silenced with gold.
Could it be…
that you recorded the bribe
you offered the physician?
Of course not.
Your obsession with recording everything
in writing is pathological.
In the end, that will come to bite you.
Your concern is unnecessary.
This is no childish prank we are planning!
It is to replace
the sovereign of this nation.
It has already been disposed of.
You need not worry.
Goodness. Greetings, Your Majesty.
That is how you will be referred to
as of tomorrow, after all.
Have you received the abdication edict?
ABDICATION EDICT: DOCUMENT
WHERE THE KING ANNOUNCES
HIS ABDICATION FROM THE THRONE
Everything is going as planned,
so do not fret.
You offered to secure
a residence for my brother to stay in
after leaving the palace,
Proprietor Cheon.
Yes.
I have secured a place
where he can reside in peace.
This is the will of the heavens.
We are past the point of return.
It is time for you to make a decision
for the sake of this nation
and Prince Eunseong.
No one will benefit
from you dragging this out.
And Prince Eunseong?
I will serve him well.
Heed me!
His Majesty has collapsed!
Is anyone out there?
Your Majesty!
GANGNYEONGJEON
You said you would have him
abdicate the throne.
But you poisoned him?
The outcome is the same, is it not?
Your Majesty.
You must only think of the nation now.
Is there still no word
from the Royal Swordsman?
I am afraid not.
Bow down and show respect.
Lift your head.
Jun-hwa.
Leave with Deok-su.
Eun-ho.
You are…
Prince Muyeong?
We will return to the palace.
Escort His Highness.
Do you not realize that Deok-su could be
put in danger if you stay by her side?
Just…
leave now.
You were ordered to kill everyone here?
"Never attack anyone
untrained in swordsmanship."
As my tutor…
that is what you taught me.
I am only following His Majesty's order.
We should head back, Deok-su.
Deok-su.
Yes?
It is nothing.
Let us head inside.
We should get you treated.
Does it hurt a lot?
I am fine as long as you are safe.
As if.
How did you know to be there?
What about you?
What were you
and Prince Muyeong doing there?
Were you aware…
that Eun-ho was in fact
Prince Muyeong?
Yes.
How?
How is that even possible?
He lives in a different world
than the rest of us.
You are bound to be hurt
if you stay by his side.
End things with him.
That is the right thing to do.
He is the sworn enemy of Eun-ho's family.
Just like how my father
died a wrongful death,
Eun-ho said his family…
was also victimized
by Grand Proprietor Cheon.
Eun-ho said he must get his revenge.
What about Grand Proprietor Cheon?
That is why he and I…
No, forget it.
It has nothing to do with you.
A military official sent from the palace?
Yes.
He may not have been dressed
in formal attire,
but his swordsmanship spoke for itself.
It must have been the Royal Swordsman.
The fact that he had the Royal Swordsman
leave the shadows
shows how the king is
backed into a corner.
Of course.
A fight is only entertaining
when one punches back.
And the ledger?
They were already fighting
when we arrived,
so we could not secure it.
Where is Hong Deok-su at the moment?
I heard you are injured.
It is nothing serious.
Hong Deok-su…
I mean, Hong Jae-on's late father
was your old friend, right?
He was my one and only friend.
How did he pass away?
Why would you be asking that?
You said Hong Jae-on and I
were meant to be.
It is only natural for me
to be curious about her parent.
Hong Jae-on's father, Hong Min-sik was…
Was it…
Was it really you?
He died at the hands of Seol Mae-hwa.
What?
Lady Seol Mae-hwa?
Twelve years ago,
after the incident,
many complications followed.
Hong Jae-on is well aware of the details.
She witnessed Seol Mae-hwa
stabbing her father.
By the time I arrived
at his house to save him,
he was already long gone.
I was too late.
Then why did you keep Seol Mae-hwa
at Yongcheonru
when you knew she was the murderer?
I had no idea until Jae-on told me.
However,
after learning the truth,
I could not let it slide.
That is why…
you got rid of Lady Seol Mae-hwa.
Grant me your support.
I will protect Hong Jae-on
from here on out.
Sure.
What do you need?
Your Majesty.
You are late.
And the ledger? Did you find it?
Do tell.
What have you been…
hiding from me?
Why…
is your name in the ledger?
Present the ledger.
There is something I must confirm.
What is there to confirm?
The fact that the former king
did not die of a chronic illness
twelve years ago
but was poisoned to death?
In the ledger were the names of
the former king's physician and court lady
and the receipt
for the purchase of poison!
I will explain everything in detail…
so hand me the ledger.
You are well aware
of how cunning Lord Cheon
and the Minister of War can be.
Could it be…
that you were involved…
in the death of the former king
along with the Minister of War?
Tell me it is not true.
Father, please.
That is not true.
That was never my intention.
The plan was to persuade my brother
into abdicating the throne.
I had no idea those rats
would poison him.
Back then!
You should have stopped them.
I was going to stop them
from mocking the royal family ever again
once my brother
abdicated the throne to me.
So…
you joined forces
with those vile men?
You have no idea how it is to be
a powerless sovereign.
There is nothing you can do yourself.
Father.
But that will all change now.
Now that we have the ledger,
we can finally have
the Minister of War removed.
A family was ruined
because of that ledger.
What do you mean?
Do you mean Hong Min-sik's?
Do you know what kind of life
his daughter has had to live?
To avenge the unfair death of her father,
she spent her whole life in agony!
All you see
is her agony
and not mine?
Father.
Give me the ledger now.
I will take care of the rest.
The ledger…
I do not have it.
What?
Many innocent lives were lost
because of that ledger.
How could I bring it to you knowing that?
- Prince Muyeong!
- Father!
Father.
You cannot cover up your mistake
with another wrongdoing.
I have been receiving reports
of your indiscretions…
but never did I think
you would ruin our grand plan
for a mere girl.
How…
How could you not bring the ledger?
Our grand plan, you say?
Maybe you have been fooling yourself
with such pretext.
As if you know anything!
Do you think this was to only save myself?
You ungrateful thing.
You, Prince Eunseong,
and the entire royal family!
I will restore all of us
to our rightful places.
By choosing a path
that is different from yours,
I will prove myself.
Royal Swordsman!
Lock him up in his chamber.
Do not let him set a foot
outside his chamber!
Father.
Lock him up
and head to Yongcheonru.
Bring me the ledger.
Whoever holds it,
whoever stands in your way!
Kill them.
Your word is my command.
No, Father.
- Your Highness.
- You cannot.
- Father.
- Heed me!
You must stop this, Father.
Father!
You must stop this, Father!
I promise you.
I will protect you
no matter what.
Whether you are Hong Deok-su
or Hong Jae-on…
Whoever you are,
you are…
the only one I will hold in my heart.
You were right.
It feels much better
to lean on each other.
I have never lived as a woman before,
so it will be hard
and I will fall short sometimes,
but I will still try my best, Eun-ho.
UIJU GUILD
Open the gate!
Relay word that Seol Mae-hwa,
the innkeeper of Yongcheonru, is here.
I am…
Seol Mae-hwa
from Yongcheonru in Hanyang.
I know.
And this is…
where you will die.
Grant me an audience
with your guildmaster.
What is this? Are you hurt?
I am all right.
What happened?
You went to get Deok-su. Why are you hurt?
Su-ra.
I must know what Deok-su does,
whom she meets,
and what is going through her head.
That seems to be
the only way to protect Deok-su.
- What?
- You.
You said you would assist me.
Report to me daily
regarding Deok-su's activities.
Jun-hwa.
You are just like your father.
What?
What on earth happened today?
Also, where is Eun-ho?
That man returned to his rightful place.
That is all.
That man?
- Are you abandoning your friendship?
- Lee Eun-ho is…
Prince Muyeong.
He was never our friend to begin with.
He is a royal.
Now that he has returned to his place,
all will be sorted.
- But Jun-hwa--
- Please do as I ask.
Please.
To the northern back gate,
Your Highness.
Brother.
Leave this way.
How--
I removed the guards but only briefly.
Follow the path you have decided to take.
Brother…
There is not much time.
We will talk later. Go now.
Bring me the ledger.
Whoever holds it,
whoever stands in your way!
Kill them.
That was it?
This was all…
for that ledger?
No.
This--
You should have
just asked me to hand it over.
How…
My father has deployed an assassin.
Having this ledger will endanger you.
Do not be concerned,
for this is my business.
I do not ever want to see you again,
Your Highness Prince Muyeong.
You should leave.
Then, let me join you.
It is too dangerous for you alone.
Whatever you intend to do,
let me assist you.
- Lee Eun-ho--
- Never…
Never will I leave you behind again.
I will not give up
nor stop.
Do you know what I am implying?
My sword might aim at your father.
But you will still aid me?
Only then will I be able to stop him.
Assisting you
is the only way to stop my father
from committing more sins.
Is that so?
Are you willing to be the bait
for the trap I set?
A newly appointed innkeeper, my gosh.
What are you so happy about?
The innkeeper position is vacant,
and it is finally time.
Lord Yu, could you be…
Would I not be appointed
given the talent I possess?
What should my first order of business be?
Maybe I should gather my people from Uiju.
Lord Cho, what say you?
- Lord Cho.
- What?
What are you thinking about
that you are in such a daze?
You have been busy lately,
going out at night.
What are you talking about? Goodness.
Well, duty calls.
Excuse me.
Goodness me.
He has been suspicious lately.
Could he also be seeking
the innkeeper position?
Goodness.
There has been no word from Seol Mae-hwa.
Could something have happened to her?
My goodness.
So, how was your visit
to your father's old house?
Did you find the safe?
What…
Why are you so surprised?
Forgive me.
Last night, I found the ledger
and was going to bring it to you,
but I had to leave it behind.
Lead the way.
We should go and get it now.
This is where it was.
I cannot believe I missed this spot. Move.
What…
It was definitely here.
Did you open this
with Prince Muyeong last night?
Yes.
Cho Seung-ryang, locate Prince Muyeong.
He took the ledger.
Yes, my lord.
Go.
The three men who were responsible
for my father's death 12 years ago
are all after this ledger.
I will make them destroy themselves
while fighting one another.
Eun-ho, you will serve as bait
and spread word
that this is in the minister's hands.
I will make either His Majesty's assassin
or Grand Proprietor Cheon
suspect the Minister of War.
Our relationship is not amicable enough
for us to sit here together face-to-face.
It will be different today
as I have brought you a gift.
A gift?
For me?
What could this be?
BRIBE PAID TO OH YEONG-RAK,
LEE HYEON-WI
Wait. This ledger…
SLUSH FUND TO COURT LADY JEONG,
ROYAL PHYSICIAN LEE
Where did you get this?
Why…
Why did you
bring this to me?
I need to get rid of…
the Grand Proprietor.
Pardon?
I must protect my father
and the royal family.
Your grandson,
Prince Seonyang, is also a royal.
So…
you want to wield me as the sword
to kill Grand Proprietor Cheon?
At a time like this,
noble relatives must join forces.
You should never have
pursued any scheme
with someone of lowly blood such as him.
He repaid you by keeping such a ledger.
You have a point.
If you promise
to get rid of Grand Proprietor Cheon…
I will hand this ledger over to you.
You have a deal.
Now that we have hard evidence,
it is only right
to arrest the traitor
and restore the nation's order.
Since many are after the ledger,
you must keep it safe.
Your father and I
were friends
from even before you were born.
At one point,
we believed we could
have the whole world in our hands.
Jae-on.
Hong Jae-on.
You had better not think
about doing anything stupid with it.
After all, you are the only family
my friend Min-sik left behind.
The ledger is dangerous.
Wanting it for yourself
will result in death.
That is why I sent Jun-hwa
to you last night.
To protect you, Jae-on.
Cheon Jun-hwa?
Yes.
Cheon Jun-hwa…
is my son.
Jun-hwa is…
your son?
Your father shared one of the letters
meant for your name with him.
Jun-hwa and Jae-on.
I believe you two are meant to be one.
Your father and I failed
to live out our dream together,
but I believe it will be different
for you two.
Jae-on.
Will you make that dream come true?
Deok-su.
We are to gather at Chinyeongrae.
Let us go.
Sure.
Where did you go this time?
From here on out,
do not roam around recklessly.
You will have a lot to do from now on.
Is that an order?
Can you not see I am looking out for you?
Do as I say.
That is best for your sake.
It is too early in the morning for this.
Come on. Hurry along.
Hey! The notice is here!
Innkeeper Yu,
it will finally be announced!
Welcome.
Congratulations.
Why are you all here?
Seong-jin.
The Uiju people
should organize a gathering
to celebrate Lord Yu's appointment
as the new innkeeper!
It will be the feast of the century.
Oh, please.
- Shall we?
- Yes!
I cannot watch this.
Lord Yu, let me be excused.
Enjoy yourself.
Where are you going?
Once Lord Yu is appointed as innkeeper,
I will first have those Elementary jerks
all thrown out.
They should all be thrown out
of here, Myeong-ho!
Says who?
Darn.
You will be kicked out first
if you babble on like that, Kim Myeong-ho.
Goodness, you Elementary fools.
You are still yapping on
like a bunch of clueless monkeys.
Just wait and see, you morons.
Finally! The newly appointed innkeeper
is Lord Yu… Wait.
ANNOUNCEMENT
INNKEEPER CHEON JUN-HWA
Cheon Jun-hwa?
Innkeeper's assistants
Hong Deok-su and Ko Su-ra?
What?
Everyone, show respect to him.
He is the only son of the grand proprietor
and our new innkeeper.
After studying in Qing,
he took the clerks' exam
to learn the ropes at Yongcheonru.
But as of this moment, you will serve
and respect him as the innkeeper.
My word. Unbelievable!
Darn it.
I was hoping to tell you in advance.
Are you shocked?
As the newly appointed innkeeper,
I will make choices that are best for you.
You, Cheon Jun-hwa?
Cheon Jun-hwa, the Grand Proprietor's son?
You…
You are mistaken about my father, Deok-su.
Ko Su-ra.
You knew all along, didn't you?
You fawned over him
knowing who he was all along.
You cunning bastard.
Get out of my way.
What?
Was it easier to crawl
between his legs than mine?
Kim Myeong-ho!
- Myeong-ho!
- Are you all right?
- Goodness.
- My gosh.
Ko Su-ra, how dare you!
- Myeong-ho…
- Move!
A clerk dared to punch the innkeeper?
Have you lost your mind?
Well, it was Ko Su-ra
who threw the first punch.
Exactly!
I mean, that is what happened, Lord Cheon.
Crawl.
Crawl between Ko Su-ra's legs,
and I will let you three keep your jobs.
What… What did you say?
Goodness, Lord Cheon.
Lord Cheon.
Do you not want to?
Du-sik, do it on my behalf.
Pardon?
Should I crawl, then?
That is enough, Jun-hwa.
You imbecile!
How dare you call the innkeeper
by his name!
Exactly.
How dare you call our new innkeeper
by his first name?
Just go, will you?
I will not be lenient to those
who mistreat my assistants.
Dismiss yourselves.
- Myeong-ho, let us go.
- Come on.
Let go of me.
We should have seen them
crawl between your legs.
I will have them pay
for what they did to us
in the exact same way.
In the same way?
You think what you did was fair?
Why are you getting worked up?
I was looking out for you--
That was for me, you say?
How are you any different from Myeong-ho?
You two are the same.
You think I am like Kim Myeong-ho?
Is bringing the powerless to their knees
your idea of justice?
You asked for daily reports on Deok-su.
Sure. I will do that.
Just know that it will cost you.
I need money, you see.
Justifications and agonizing
over friendship and love.
That is only reserved
for the privileged.
I do not have that luxury.
That is your position as an innkeeper,
while this is mine as your assistant.
Su-ra!
Those filthy rats.
I would not be Kim Myeong-ho of Uiju
if I let them get away with this.
I will kill them all.
Myeong-ho!
Prince Muyeong gave the ledger
to the Minister of War?
We had the three swordsmen
from his residence followed,
but their ledgers were blank.
Forgive me.
What exactly are they up to?
Your Majesty, it is the Minister of War.
I did not allow you to enter.
How dare you barge in here?
It is an urgent matter,
so I could not wait, Your Majesty.
Minister…
You have such a loyal son, Your Majesty.
Prince Muyeong came to me in person
to drop off
Grand Proprietor Cheon's ledger.
The ledger that proves
how the former king was poisoned.
Grand Proprietor Cheon kept
a detailed record of all transactions.
And?
What exactly are you getting at?
Now that we can prove
Grand Proprietor Cheon's act of treason,
I will have him beheaded.
But first…
you must announce
that you are abdicating the throne
to Prince Seonyang.
Such insolence!
Announce my abdication?
Royal Swordsman!
Your Majesty.
If you kill me now…
the ledger I have safely tucked away
will be distributed
on the streets of Hanyang.
If you do not announce
your abdication tomorrow,
you, not Grand Proprietor Cheon,
will be forced out of your position
for poisoning the former king.
Minister, what brought you
to His Majesty's chamber at this hour?
It must have been because I had
a pressing matter to discuss with him.
Oh, right.
Tomorrow, a shocking revelation
will come to light.
Do not be too shocked by it.
I am telling you in advance
since it could burden your mind and body
which are already feeble.
You must stay healthy.
If you live long enough,
you might be granted
some good days yourself.
MEET ME IMMEDIATELY
IN THE VIP ROOM
TO DISCUSS OUR NEXT MOVE,
LEE EUN-HO
Eun-ho.
You actually came.
Oh, dear.
What is this?
Where is Eun-ho?
Look at you running over here
at the mention of his name.
Who are you to each other?
You have been joined at the hip
like lovers.
You both…
- must be into men.
- Damn it. Kim Myeong-ho.
Do not do anything you will regret.
Or maybe, Hong Deok-su, you…
Maybe you are a girl.
Stop it.
Tell me, then.
Hold on.
I can actually see for myself.
Why bother waiting for an answer?
How did you fool me back then
at Jakyakjae?
I will reveal who you really are,
Hong Deok-su!
Get off me!
You have been chummy with Lee Eun-ho,
but you jumped ship
now that Cheon Jun-hwa is the innkeeper!
Kim Myeong-ho!
Cheon Jun-hwa…
Let go.
I will kill you.
Cheon Jun-hwa, enough.
How dare you!
Hong Deok-su has been fooling you!
Cheon Jun-hwa, you are being fooled.
Do you know who he has been with?
Shut it, Kim Myeong-ho!
Lee Eun-ho!
That broad has already
given herself to Lee Eun-ho.
I saw it!
Shut it!
Die!
Unbelievable.
So much for not associating
with lowly blood.
I guess the invite from Yongcheonru
was too sweet to decline.
Speak for yourself.
You said we should discard Cheon Mak-dong.
Did you change your mind overnight?
By the way,
is the Minister of War not here?
I am not sure.
And who might you be?
I am the new innkeeper,
Cheon Jun-hwa.
Cheon Jun-hwa?
My lord. If he is of the Cheon family…
We have secured meat of fine quality,
so I invited you here
to officially greet you.
Have your fill
and take home the gifts I have prepared.
What on earth is this?
What is the matter?
Do you not enjoy cow tongue?
Cow tongue?
Do you expect us to eat cow tongue?
Why not?
Procuring these was not an easy feat.
How dare you?
You must be too young
to understand how rude this is.
Cheon…
Mak…
dong.
The sly tongues from your mouths
that speak out of order.
Maybe they
should be served on plates instead.
This is such an expensive delicacy.
Will you still not have it?
Oh, right.
I have yet to reveal your gifts.
Take a look.
It is divine.
How could it not be?
What a delight.
I advise you
to watch your tongues, my lords.
I sincerely
ask that of you.
JULY 17TH - PAID TO OH YEONG-RAK
LEE HYEON-WI
I am almost there.
Finally, tomorrow,
my flesh and blood
will ascend the throne!
Where is the ledger?
Oh Yeong-rak!
I welcome you to Yongcheonru,
Guildmaster of Uiju Guild.
Is this the famous Yongcheonru?
It is shiny
but with nothing else to show for it.
Where is my boy Myeong-ho?
It has been a while,
and I would love to see his handsome face.
Let us go in.
Ultimately, everything ended up
in Grand Proprietor Cheon's hands.
First, the minister.
Next, Grand Proprietor Cheon.
Deok-su, do not dirty your hands
with any more blood.
I already made up my mind.
Marry my son.
Use me, Deok-su. Marry me.
Stop playing with her heart.
I am prepared to give up
everything I have.
Do you love Jae-on?
Yes. I love Hong Deok-su.
The unimaginable will soon take place.
"The unimaginable"?
The king will be replaced.
Let us wipe this slate clean
and create a new world.
War must be prevented.
Bring me the girl.
All preparations have been made.
Now,
all I need to do…
is witness his demise.
Subtitle translation by:
Hyelim Park