On my first day at work, I run into something like this
Exciting?
Too exciting
Is this even human?
What kind of thing is that to say?
*Creak*
This one's already laughing
This one's started laughing
Look, she moved
There's nothing
In the pocket
What is this?
Can't be his
Oil-blotting sheets
What do we do? So awkward
Stuff it back in
You'll have to pay for this
Aren't you going to compensate?
You're over 1.8 meters tall
While it's probably just 50 centimeters
And you just sat on it like this
Lift
Back
Welcome everyone to our
Apartment 11
While resting here
let's play together
3a
The result of 6258 is
Wait a moment, slow down
Match point
My heart rate is 280 now
Starting to check my own pulse
I encountered something like this on my first day at work.
Exciting, isn't it?
Way too exciting.
There's another door here.
Let's check it out.
Let's go.
Wait a moment
This place is a track
You can also push it
This is a track
This should be pushed back
Is this a person?
This should be a person
Why does it look a bit like Teng Zhongjie?
It does resemble him
There’s another person here
There’s one more here
Should we call 120 first?
It's my first day at work
and I run into this situation
Exciting?
Too exciting
There's another one here
Hello
This one is already smiling
This one has started smiling
Look, she moved
She seems to be waking up
She's already...
Is this a person?
What kind of question is that?
No
This is a real person
Is this a person?
What else could it be?
She's kind of pretty
Guo Baoyou
Isn't this your sister?
Your sister
Guo Baoyou
Who?
Your sister
Ju Xingyun
Isn't this Ju Xingyun?
Sister
What kind of brother are you?
I...
Sister
Giggle
Wait, don't...
That's not...
They probably won't wake up now
Really?
None of them woke up?
I don't believe it
Go get a basin of water, Xiao Wen
Ready, go
Three two one
How was this action designed?
Lying here like this.
There's a spider near her, did you see it?
Crawling towards her.
There is indeed a small bug.
It started flying.
It bit her.
Quick, let's search them.
Search them one by one.
Let's go check first.
See what they've found.
This is that...
Friend, let me see.
My apologies.
Sorry.
He has nothing in his hands.
In the pocket.
Seems like in the pocket...
It appears to be...
There's something.
What is this?
This can't be his
Oil-absorbing sheets
Really?
Sorry
Excuse me
My apologies
What should we do?
This is so awkward
Just stuff it back in
I'm sorry
Nothing happened here
Whose clues haven't we found yet?
Actually we didn't find anything on him either
We searched
Nothing left on him
Check the pockets
That's not it
What's this now?
Still this one
These are oil-absorbing sheets
This isn't it
So sorry about this
Let me put this back for you
What's this? Wait a minute
These are someone else's oil-absorbing sheets
We're done for
Now the whole world will know
I'm so sorry
I wish I hadn't come to play
Don't cry
What?
Got electrocuted
I'm Pikachu
How do we handle this?
What should we do about this?
Can't we just take this off?
This can't be removed
We have to leave it like this
No violence allowed
What are you guys doing now?
We're not being violent
No violence here
Nope
Just a little irritable, right?
Not at all
After recording this long
Everyone's getting a bit irritable
Everyone's a little on edge
Scared to "death"
What's that sound?
What's wrong?
You go talk to your sister
I'll talk to my sister
Why did you come here?
Surprise!
What's with your eyes?
What is it?
Melancholy blue, can't you tell?
Melancholy blue
What's the matter?
What's she...
Hello
What event are you attending?
Help your sister up first
Get up
Should we sit for a while?
Should we get up?
No problem
Can get up
She's awake
Pet pet
After petting for a while, it came back
If you're not feeling well
Let me take you to the infirmary first
Come on
You take them first
Okay
Are you okay?
I'm feeling a bit dizzy too
My foot's numb
Are your legs numb too?
My leg is numb too
I've had my leg bent this whole time
Foot's numb
Really numb
My back is all cramped up
Come on, let's rest over here first
Alright
I heard you brought oil blotting sheets
Yes, I did
My older sister gave them to me
Then they found out
I couldn't help it
I kept...
Took my oil-absorbing sheets
Took them several times, you know
Thought it was some kind of clue, right?
Let's go look at his paintings
Let's go
Nephew, are you this sad?
Yes
Why are you so sad?
This sad
Because the painter "died"
I'm extremely sad
This pun of yours makes me want to swear
Who pulled out her hair?
It was pulled out from the beginning
Who did it?
I forgot
Probably Old Liu
No
Why is this thing placed here?
I don't understand
Why are you pulling someone's hair?
Don't cry
AK
M
He's so handsome
Really handsome
Let me tell you
You'll have to pay for this
It's fine, go ahead and sit
For real?
Sit down, it's fine
Scared now?
Just sit
It won't break
Go on, rock it
See? What did I tell you?
You'll have to pay for this.
Aren't you going to compensate?
You broke its tail off.
You're over six feet tall,
while it's probably just fifty centimeters.
And you just sat like that?
What's wrong with this?
Bai Sanwan broke it.
It's not my fault.
You're the one who broke it, right?
No.
Yes.
Guo Baoyou.
You really...
Don't you need to pay for this?
You have to pay for it.
There's a projector.
This goes in, right? Just plug it in?
Here.
Right.
This won't move.
Let's try projecting it.
Bring the machine over.
Alright
Yes
Got a face now
Aligned properly
Yellow roses symbolize forgiveness
Where it falls
It's drifting this way
Here?
Is this it?
Wait a moment
There should be something behind this
Yes, feels like it might work
Hold on
Let's just lay it down, maybe
Lay it down
Just lay it down directly
Slowly
Don't let our Keke do it
Keke might be...
What do you mean?
No
You're the brains of the operation
Let me hold this for you
Come
Lift
Lift, good
Coco
Later you shout "retreat"
Retreat
Let's get it half-standing
Right
We need to find a way to power it
I'll go back and get it
Little brother has already climbed
Little brother has taken the lead
Great
Already charging
Thanks for your effort
Okay
Can we block this opening for him?
Let's scare him
Let's turn off the lights
Is it a person?
Not a person
That's too mean
We should do it like this
Everyone's head waits at that exit
You're awake
Once he comes in
You're back
You're here to "poop", right?
Let me try
Who exactly are you trying to scare?
Try it
Old Liu
Give it a try
We're all easily frightened
Let's create some scary atmosphere ourselves
Was this just taken out from inside?
Take a look at this without getting upset.
Shouldn't we check that serial number?
Let's go.
Let's go back again.
After you.
After you, Lao Liu.
You first.
I'm in no hurry.
There must be someone waiting for you inside.
There's someone waiting for you inside.
Come on, Zhou Keke.
Let's be brave.
Are you human?
Truly brave.
Watch your head.
Why is it that we've been here so many times,
yet we still feel afraid?
It's just that towards the production team, we still feel...
Yes, a sense of awe.
Look at Old Liu.
It's quite a hassle
Let me see
Long limbs
Sometimes it's annoying
Right
Come on, let's go
Every time passing through places like this
I feel particularly at ease
What's wrong?
Let's use that light to take a look
Check the serial number
Because when purchasing this
each one has its own serial number
Bai Sanwan
Thought it was oxygen
But actually inhaled that
Bai Sanwan
Sanwan
How boring can you be, seriously?
I knew he would try to scare us.
That's why I didn't dare to approach him.
I feel like giving Old Bai a beating.
How about we team up to get back at him?
Would that work?
Just give him a good thrashing.
Since he's your brother,
you just stay out of it.
You're perfect as you are.
Alright, welcome everyone to our
Apartment No. 11.
I've tried some new games
and I plan to
while we're resting here,
play them together with you all.
How about it?
Okay.
Is it fun?
Super fun.
Really simple too.
First, let's divide into teams.
Physical or mental -
it's a mental game.
Your brain...
What do you mean?
Is it working properly?
Space...
Listen... listen to the sound... space.
Rock-paper-scissors
Let's do rock-paper-scissors
To be fair
Rock-paper-scissors
Now our teams are decided
Let me introduce the first game
The first game is called "Guess the Beans"
How does it work?
Guess the Beans
Each team gets a bag of beans
In three rounds of competition
Put a certain number of beans into the box
The team with more beans wins
Keep your bean count hidden
The losing team reveals their bean count
Best two out of three
After you've decided
Secretly place them in here
I'll check inside here
Is this okay for the first round?
Just show it to him
Okay
I'm sorry
Thank you, thank you
I really should have chosen her
That was my mistake
You can find another place
to discuss
Go to the bar
I think we should play it safe in the first round
Put out about three to four
Okay
Tian Ji's horse racing strategy
Put ten in the first round
Why?
I think
They'll probably put less than ten
Putting a round number like that is...
If they put
eleven in the first round
Keep your voice down
They might hear us
We were indeed quite loud
Did you hear that?
No
We really didn't hear
I really won't tell you
what we heard
We're just lip-reading
So your strategy is
to watch them discuss?
We're practicing lip-reading
Really want to
know what they're saying
Keep your voice down
We need to turn around
Turn around to talk with them
Okay, we're done
Slow down a bit
Can't let them figure it out
How many are inside?
Yes
Be more careful
Right, be more careful
Or else it'll make clinking sounds inside
It would give us away
Exciting, right?
Put one more in
Want to know?
Want to know how many I'm putting in?
Please hand me both boxes
Be careful
Let me check them
I feel like you guys put in a lot
all-in
I already know the results of the first round.
The winner of the first round is...
this side.
Congratulations to you.
In this round, they placed...
a total number of beans equal to...
zero.
This time we can choose not to place...
and trick them out of their beans.
That's what I thought at first too
No wonder we're family
No problem, we carried it out
You can discuss it now
How many to put in the second round
Let's go then, we're satisfied
Otherwise, just release them all.
Fall
Only two rounds left
How many in total
Twenty
Twenty pieces
No matter what, we'll win
Go for it
We've already discussed it
That fast?
Victory is assured
Not bad
Not really
Are you guys done?
We're done
Let's do one final check
Confirmed
Any more changes needed?
No more changes
No changes
Okay, no changes - I'll review it now
Okay
So the winner of this round is
the winning team
Then for the side without victory
how many beans are there?
Take a guess
Zero
It's zero
Would it be more than ours?
Yes
So the outcome is actually already clear
They guessed it right, we are...
I think in the second round
they must have bet heavily
to win
Otherwise not
Right
Alright
They want to go all-in one last time
All-in
Then one more time
Okay, one more time
Okay
Do we really have to "bully" them
Thanks
Do we really have to "bully" them?
The last round is crucial, right?
Right
Extremely crucial
Then let's do it, go straight for it
Start your show
All in
How many should we put in, exactly?
You tell me
This is so frustrating
Alright, I'll follow your lead
Still pretending, huh?
He's over there cutting
Why don't you try biting it?
Can you bite it open?
Biting might cost you two more teeth, right?
Or maybe three
Both upper and lower teeth falling out together
If you can really break it open
I'll count it as two for you
Then you can win, right?
Watch your teeth
Fine
Don't
Just a game
Extremely close
Just one move away
Congratulations to this side
It was truly full of suspense
Next, we will
proceed with our second game
Number Guessing
Number Guessing Game
The host randomly writes down a 4-digit number
with no repeating digits
Two teams take turns guessing the number
Host
responds to each guess by indicating
xAyB
where A means correct digit
in correct position
and B means correct digit
but wrong position
The team that guesses correctly wins
Because normally
I would tell you
x A's and y B's
that's what it means
The basic structure
always works this way
If all four digits are correct
x plus y must equal four
If it's less than four
that means
you haven't guessed all digits yet
My CPU can't handle this
I'm overheating already
Understand?
What should I do? I'm so confused
Yes? Any questions?
Then you can ask again
I've already...
Do you smell that?
Something's burning
It's already fried
Let's do a practice round first
Let's practice first
Maybe burning it out will help
Two negatives make a positive, right?
Right
Let's do a trial run first
Okay
This number is...
Looks like many strokes
Go ahead, guess anything
Is there a pattern
or completely random?
We're in Q&A mode now
I'll only tell you x A's and y B's
Write any number
It doesn't really matter
Okay
Okay, so the feedback I'm giving you is
0a1b
1b
I think it's correct
Because
Because people really like writing this number
I think 4
Right
Then let's go with 2 and 4
Cross out 3 and 5
Then I think you're right
Okay, you've just finished discussing
Now it's your turn
If we show it to him
After he tells us the result
We'll know
Whether these two are correct
7142, right?
0a0b
How could it be 0b?
Remove both 4 and 2
Right
Only 3 and 5 remain
The feedback for 3658 is
3a
Both the positions and numbers are correct
9 or 1
1 isn't there
Then it must be 9
We've figured it out
We guessed correctly
Come on, quick answer
The result for 3659 is 2a1b
Three positions here are correct
Right, so what I'm saying is
This one
And this one
So now it's
Correct
That's right
What?
What did you say?
How did you know?
I don't know, I guessed
You saw the number in my mind
The essence of the game
Extremely lucky
Lucky
Let's go
Okay, we're officially starting now
Xiao He, why don't you move your arm when writing?
How do you...
He doesn't move here, he just does it like this.
It's hard to see his pen strokes.
I only move my wrist.
I'm not writing calligraphy.
He's being sneaky.
Okay, I've now written down
these four numbers in my mind.
Now, first I'll ask you
to give me four numbers.
What feedback will I give you?
Right.
4a
That would be too easy to guess.
Then you're really going easy on us.
1a2b
2b
2b means
correct position.
2b means these two numbers are correct
but in the wrong positions.
Which two numbers are they?
Can I tell you that?
Might as well have him recite his ID number.
Why don't you come take a look?
Want to give it a try?
Okay
Garbled code
Let's pick 8463
Alright, let me check
2b
Two correct
Are you sure?
Confirmed
You sure?
Positive
So we shouldn't change the numbers
Let's get the sequence right first
Just the sequence
The result for 6428 is
2a1b
2a
Let's change it
Then randomly change one
Change one
Never tried this before
Okay
2a1b
Congratulations, you're one step closer to success
No
Wrong
It's missing a 2
This 2 is correct
Isn't this it?
This is exactly what I was saying earlier
Let's go with this one
3b
Correct
These two are absolutely correct
Changed
The puzzle is revealed
The result of 1268 is
2a
So
These three digits are correct
We're on the right track now
Then let's make a blind guess
Okay
Come on
That one
Getting close
The result for 4268 is
2a
2a1b
Right
Between these two
one is in the wrong position
2a1b
Let's try it
Then let's replace this one
Which one haven't we tried?
This one
Alright, let's try
The result for 6238 is
3a
It's 3a
This
3a
The result for 6258 is
Wait, slow down
I already forgot which one was 3a
3a
No
Bad luck
Like this
Let's erase everything now
Erase it all
If we erase everything, what about the previous attempts?
6258 wasn't used before
Let's say
Right?
3a
Then
My heart started racing
Hurry up
The CPU is overheating
Almost there
It's over
You wiped it all
No
When there's no space left
It'll make my mind even messier
My heart rate's at 280 now
Are you all extremely eager
to call out numbers now?
One number is wrong
Right
If the numbers are correct, the position will be right
Match point
Now checking my own pulse
Did we say 6238 before?
No
How could you ask that?
Have you decided?
We've decided
3a
Because we did say it
Why didn't you say it earlier?
Congratulations
Finally got it right
That was so difficult
Thank you so much
Really
My brain hurts
She just said
"Did we say 6238?"
I said you hadn't said it
But we did say it
We did say it
3a
But
I didn't finish my sentence
I was just quietly laughing to myself
Then I wanted you all
to make your own choice
After playing these two games
I imagine everyone's brains
are already firing on all cylinders
Wide awake now, right?
Want to sleep
Now even more confused
Not dizzy anymore?
Now extremely confused
Now super confused again
How about a few more games?
Now awake
Okay, fine
That's good then
Alright
We'll set off at dawn
Those two have gone "mad"
The dream has awakened
The heart won't fear
"Gone mad"
There is a place
The heart won't fear
Everything I have is just to find it
Even at the cost of sorrow
The cost of sorrow
You bunch of "lunatics"
Exclusively on Tencent Video
New episodes every Thursday, Friday, and Saturday at 6 PM
Members get early access 1 week in advance
Every Saturday at 6 PM
Case Files of "Let's Solve It"
Every Sunday at 6 PM
Watch bonus content: "Diary of Apartment No. 11"
Midweek teasers, behind-the-scenes, and short clips
Binge-watch daily
A 360° deep dive into Apartment No. 11
Hurry and open Tencent Video
Search for "Let's Solve It"
Join the detectives for an immersive case-solving experience