There's a "dead" person
Look, there are two holes there
It's a locked-room "murder" case
Someone is trying to frame Old Man Li
Old Man Cang and Old Man Ku discovered
Uncle Wang's secret
That Wang also had a motive to "kill" him
What are you doing now?
Power outage
This isn't 1988 at all
The door opened
Sister Cai
Sweet Little Zhou Zhou
Sister Cai is Old Man Li's wife
Sister Cai, what are you doing here?
No
You
Hurry up and let me out
Quick, get me out of here
What were you all doing?
Took you so long to come rescue me
I've been listening here the whole time
You're so clumsy
What were you doing over there?
For so long
Sorry
What's with the ball?
Fumbling around
I'm sorry
What's this ball for?
And what's with the rope?
Mess around with it
Sister Cai
They're the ones who delayed your rescue
Yes
Really?
Let's go out, Sister Cai
Hurry, let's go out
Who locked you in here?
Open this door
You didn't find the key, did you?
I didn't
Those two keys we had earlier
We took them all out
I have a key
I don't know if it's for this
Let's try it
Come on
Earlier there was a big guy
When he brought me in
I took it from his pocket
Let's go
You go first
Why should I go first?
I won't go first
I'm not going first
What, Sister Cai is afraid of the dark too?
I'm scared
Okay, this should work now
Crawl in
What kind of place is this?
Six unregistered individuals detected
Intruding into Chuyang Alley
This is a surveillance room
Here's a plan to return to Chuyang Lane
Using apartment rumors and elderly pain points
Step two
Renovate my basement-level storefront
to make modifications
Recreate a replica of Chuyang Lane
Then hire actors to perform
To deceive those helpless elderly people
This is awesome
So impressive
6:10
Power outage
The power outage I told you about from 6:00 to 6:10
So there'll be a 10-minute blackout now
But you said the blackout was in 2022
We haven't "time traveled"
This is 2022
That was fake "time travel"
A fake 1988
Wait a minute
So those two who "died"
Aren't Lao Cang and Lao Ku
Lao Cang and Lao Ku
"Died" back in 1988
Isn't this 2022?
Hold on
Who else "died"?
We found two "corpses"
In 1988
The Chuyang Lane "murder and corpse burning case"
Will happen again
Two people will "die" today
Step Three
Trick them into thinking Youth Photo Studio is a "time machine"
To "time travel" to 1988
You need to pay
Round-trip "time travel" requires payment
Exchanging for 1988 currency
Requires payment
Buying "time travel" supplies costs money
Right, Sister Cai
Didn't you come to
Youth Photo Studio and then
disappeared?
If the old folks discover the secret
Or become not even worth deceiving
Then we'll eliminate them by special means
Have you discovered the secret?
I wasn't eliminated, I'm still alive
Look
This door leads to that store
There are people outside
Don’t get caught
Originally, I came to Xiao Wang’s store
Disguised as the owner of Xiao Wang’s store
I hid in Chuyang Alley
to oversee operations
The keys to the warehouse yard and storage rooms
could only be kept by me alone
Just one final step
All areas
Deploy signal jammers
Except for authorized staff devices
These people outside
are still watching us
They're all company employees
Right
When did you get in?
Get them!
Run!
First, we need to clarify the "deceased's" identity.
It should be...
You're dressed like white fungus.
What's the point?
White fungus, silver ear mushroom.
I think the "deceased" should be Old Wang.
What?
Because only he has...
the keys to the compound and warehouse.
Old Wang is "dead."
It's possible...
He's missing a finger.
You can tell by looking at his fingers.
Two "corpses."
One of them is missing a finger.
Then who's the other one?
Come
It's a long story—let's sit down and listen carefully.
Why is Sister Cai here?
Locked up over there.
After I gave you that Youth Photo Studio,
where did you go?
You little scammer, give me back my money!
You're still scamming people out of their money.
He gave me this Youth Photo Studio's
a sort of...
a brochure
and said you could make friends there.
For empty nesters like us,
it looked quite appealing after reading it.
So I went to take photos at that studio.
That person said
I could return to 1988.
I really wanted to go back to 1988.
My spouse was still there,
my daughter was still there.
Yes,
back then,
our family was still whole.
Now it's just me left alone.
They said I needed to pay 100,000 yuan to go,
but I paid it anyway.
Just to see my family again.
Then whoosh -
I went to 1988.
Did you see Old Li?
No.
I lived there for a month,
but never saw them.
After living there a month,
I asked later,
"Why can't I see my family?"
They said to see my relatives,
I needed to pay another 100,000 yuan.
I'd already paid,
then another 100,000,
and another 100,000,
and another 100,000.
How did you end up locked up there?
Because I later discovered
their scheme:
if you tried to escape,
they'd capture you
and take you away.
What are you doing?
Go!
How much money did you get?
I didn't get any.
This is Old Li's son.
Old Li is my father.
But isn't your surname Zhou?
I took my mother's surname.
After Old Li ran away with her,
nine years later they had another child.
That emotional traitor.
Because later my mother "died" first,
then my father abandoned me.
He stopped supporting me.
After that, my aunt raised me.
She treated me like a mother.
My aunt named me Zhou Keke.
Zhou Keke, you've got issues.
Let me tell you,
I think we came here
because he brought us here.
I think one possibility is that
you wanted to find your father
and used us
to investigate this old case
set up a trap
July 2, 1988
Do you remember that homicide case?
Of course I remember
Back in 1988
our family lived right here
near the warehouse area
Chuyang Alley
Their pun isn't very good
Indeed, quite mediocre
Official roast
Then there was a fire
After the fire
Xiaocang and Xiaoku had accidents
But they suspected
that my husband Lao Li started the fire
Then Lao Li disappeared ever since
But I believe
it definitely wasn't my Lao Li's doing
Yes
He was a good man
a kind-hearted person
There was indeed this case back then
It did happen
The Chuyang Alley "homicide" arson case
Thirty-four years have passed
That incident back then
did truly happen
And now these two
are imitating that old case
recreating all the original criminal methods
Now one of them
this "victim" is Lao Wang
Then who's the other one?
What else can we find?
Headphones, computer, things like that
Lao Wang
July 7
There's also a Xiao Wang
They're the same person
See, the ID numbers match
They're absolutely the same person
Haven't seen him in over thirty years
Next one
Gathering evidence to report, be careful
Okay, little bro
I've already decided to withdraw
And made arrangements with Xiao Hezi
To sell all these ground-floor storefronts to her
She's very happy
She can have her complete
Apartment No. 11
I said next week
You'll just be starting your business
Right now there's still the landlord
Yes
Xiao Hezi is the sub-landlord, right?
She's an agent
Is he preparing to flee?
Yes, of course he's going to run
Because someone's going to report him
Right
Lao Wang's (Xiao Wang's) cabinet
What's Lao Wang's (Xiao Wang's) birthday?
Lao Wang (Xiao Wang)
Is it four digits?
Yes, four digits
Try it
Where did you find this, kid?
Right here.
Here.
It says "Little Lin".
We arrested Sister Cai today.
These are all her belongings.
Keep an eye on her.
This was written by Little Lin.
Who is Little Lin?
Little Lin is the person we just saw.
After my thorough investigation,
this is a fake from 1988.
Little Wang revealed
his true colors.
Who is Little Wang?
Little Wang
is the person from
Old Wang's (Little Wang's) shop.
It was from Little Wang that I learned
about the Chuyang Lane plan.
I saw that brat's diary.
It must be that Little Wang (Old Wang)
who framed Old Li.
I wrote this too.
I saw that brat's diary.
It must be that Little Wang (Old Wang)
who framed Old Li.
Yes, Little Wang (Old Wang) is no good.
I must find out
how Little Wang (Old Wang)
framed Old Li back then.
I have all of Bratty Girl and Old Li's belongings with me
I'm going back to 1988
Will I get to see them?
I arranged Old Li's duty room
exactly as it was before
But I didn't see Bratty Girl or Old Li
Why is that?
Even if Little Wang (Old Wang) is old now
I'd still recognize him
He and that Little Little Wang
were actually working together
That Little Wang (Old Wang) from back then
Here
Come
Old Wang (Little Wang)
I have something important to tell you
Meet me at 3:30 this afternoon
at the Chuyang Alley warehouse entrance
Little Little Wang
Sister Cai, is this note yours?
No
It's not
Old Wang (Little Wang)
I have something important to tell you
Meet at the warehouse entrance - Little Little Wang
Then the other "dead" one should be
Little Little Wang
Is that possible?
It's possible
It's possible he was the one who arranged to meet him
Check who's missing from the surveillance footage
This one's here, these two are here
Who's missing?
Little Little Wang isn't here
So
Sister Cai
you're also a murder suspect
Me?
I'd recognize Little Wang (Old Wang) even when he's old
He and that Little Little Wang
were actually in cahoots
You need to investigate
how he framed your husband back then
Right, but
Is the "dead" person him?
It's Old Wang (Little Wang)
Little Wang (Old Wang) and Little Little Wang
Let's take a look
if there are any clues inside here
Get down
Let's see what clues are in this cabinet
Xiaoxiao Wang's personal cabinet
Let's see
There's one here
There's a phone here
There's a mobile phone
This box has a key.
Okay, thanks.
Let me tell you something.
After drinking it all,
there's a key inside.
Here, move this.
Too much.
Let's see what's on the phone.
Xiao Xiaowang told a friend:
"I've been feeling down lately.
Fortunately, with this,
I can temporarily forget
the unpleasant things.
My sleep quality has improved too."
It's this cup with a link.
This link again.
"You'll all 'die'."
Then the friend asked for details.
He said:
"I can't stand it anymore,
working with Lao Wang (Xiao Wang).
Now whenever I close my eyes,
those elderly victims we scammed
appear before me one by one,
as if demanding repayment.
Lao Wang (Xiao Wang)
doesn't value others' lives
at all.
Once when drunk, he even boasted to me
that thirty-some years ago
he 'killed' someone,
and pinned the blame on someone else.
In the past,
the person who 'murdered' Lao Cang and Lao Ku
You see,
now your 'murder' motive is clear.
This person framed your father.
I didn't know about any of this.
I absolutely can't continue
collaborating with such people.
I already have a plan.
I will definitely leave this place.
Wait and see in ten days.
June 22nd.
There's a door lock here
It says "Uncle Li's birthday"
Meaning the door lock's password
is Uncle Li's birthday
Where is this door lock?
Uncle Li's birthday
There's also a video
Let's take a look
10 days left until departure
9 days left until departure
8 days left until departure
Everything must be inside that store
That's the place
Right?
Is this some kind of clue?
7 days left until departure
He "died"
No
He put it in his pocket
He seemed to twist something
Two
Three
Four
Five
With a bang
There was a door sound
He walked out
Tea aroma meets fruit bits
Milk makes it more delicious
Our shop offers various flavors of
Special Grapefruit Four Seasons Spring with real fruit bits
Using Grapefruit Four Seasons Spring with real fruit bits
as the base
Not only has a light tea fragrance
But also chewable real fruit bits
Paired with premium fresh milk
Super delicious
New summer drink choice
Boss, I'll have this one
Deliver to this address
Okay
You always order this flavor
How many do you want?
I'll deliver them to your door
Ten cups
Alright
Little Wang
I finally caught you
What are you doing here?
I've been here all along - didn't expect that, did you?
Isn't this your father's voice?
I haven't seen my father in a long time
He left me when I was five
Actually, I should thank you
For helping me find my grandson and son
Grandson?
So I'm the grandson?
And you're the son
Uncle
You've ruined my life
Let's settle everything today
Let's go inside and talk
Let's sort this out
We should follow along with his
current position to search
There should be something underneath
No
Look at this thing
If we consider it as
representing time
Isn't this the 2 o'clock direction?
Yes
What time direction is this?
Seven o'clock
Three
Three o'clock direction
Nine o'clock
We currently don't need places with numbers
Are we waiting for the clock to strike five?
Not exactly
But that countdown earlier
I think it's definitely important
Why are we pretending to be Sherlock Holmes?
Let's call the police
We're well-informed
I don't want to guess blindly anymore
I'm calling the police
Hello, is this 110? (Police emergency number)
When listening to this part earlier
After the clock chimed
there was a door sound
Did you hear it?
Someone came in
Right
Coming to buy milk
There's no milk sold inside here
Only outside sells milk
It's an outside store, right?
And he opened a door somewhere
Cheese (photography term)
Time travel
Possibly
So cool
Opened a door somewhere
If we're searching, we should look outside
There's nothing left in here anyway
Right
Let's go take a look
Come back quick
The big guy at the entrance might see us
There's actually someone
Yeah
What can they do if I go out?
They'll just drag you back
It's definitely this room
We're just missing a key
There's a door inside here.
I'm going to take a look.
What do you mean?
There's a door inside the cabinet that leads somewhere.
We need to find a mechanism.
To open that inner door.
Could it be related to that bell sound?
Possibly.
Where else is there a clock?
He just carried in a clock.
That clock was just at the very top.
Where was it placed just now?
Right in the middle.
It seems like he wound up a watch
Is it possible
For example, adjusting the watch
The watch chimes
Five chimes
They just left
And then
Check if the inner door is open
It's open
Open now
Got it open
Let's go, guys
Moving out
What's open?
That cabinet?
How did you open it?
Some clever tricks
Go
So he went through here
Hurry up
What are you doing?
Who are you?
What do you want?
Chase them!
Hurry, go!
Hurry up
Close the door
Where is this?
This is Dakaiyan Street
We're home
So this is where he bought the Zhenguoli special drinks
Where are we going now?
Zhenguoli Special Drink Shop
Zhenguoli Ruby Grapefruit Four Seasons Spring
Hello
Welcome
Welcome to
Zhenguoli Special Drink Shop
Was there anyone today
who bought ten special drinks from you?
Many people came today
Called Xiao Xiao Wang
He's a regular customer
He buys every time he comes
He always buys the same flavor
Let me play you the recording
I'll let you hear it
New summer drink choice
Boss wants this
Deliver to this address
Ten cups
Okay
Yes
That's my voice
But I really can't remember
Because I'm not sensitive
to voices or appearances
Right, I only remember flavors
with great accuracy
I happen to have prepared four cups today
Zhenguoli Ruby Grapefruit Four Seasons Spring special
Try all four of these
Then if you can confirm
which flavor he drank
maybe I can identify which person it was
Is it this one?
No
Not this one
Made with Zhenguoli Ruby Grapefruit Four Seasons Spring
special drink
It's so delicious
This one
Right
It has a subtle tea fragrance
With real fruit pieces you can chew
Most importantly, it contains premium fresh milk
Never gets boring no matter how much you drink
Exactly this one
This Ruby Grapefruit Four Seasons Spring Tea special blend
The tea-infused ruby grapefruit one
That would be the one living in B101
That customer
B101
Yes, he often asks for home delivery
Right?
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you, goodbye.
Please come again.
Okay.
That must be someone's password
Isn't it someone's birthday?
Old Li's birthday
It's written in his phone
Uncle Li's birthday
Right, Uncle Li's birthday
So it's 1950, right?
Unlocked
Let's go
Sweet little Zhou Zhou
Why is your photo here?
Look
He said
I can only watch you from afar
But having hugged you
I'm already very happy
Never thought you'd have such a special connection
With
a bunch of peculiar people
Together formed this peculiar
Bai Song
1 Guo Zhou Liu 1 Cool Detective Team
Though I don't understand what you're doing
But seeing you so happy
makes me happy too
It's her birthday today
He's that kitty
He is
He's dressed up as that meow-meow
Come
You only hugged three bowls
That means you two are suspects
Because he only hugged those two
Only hugged us two
And he mentioned above that he hugged you
That kitty
Lives in basement level 1
He's meow-meow
Wait a moment
This...
These are letters
What does it say here?
Current identity
Meow meow?
Yes, meow
Meow meow
Isn't he a meow cat?
That cat
Be careful not to "blow up"
To avoid dragging you down,
I've decided to disappear from your world.
This is my mother
Li's daughter
My mother
"died" in 2007
So that means
You're my grandson
That's right
Quick, give me a hug
Come here quickly
Nephew
Go away
Get away
Nephew
Ah Zhou
You saved me when I was in trouble
You thought
I was your father's "killer"
But after getting to know me
You said this "killer" wasn't so cold
Wouldn't have "killed" your father
We struggled between love and pain
After much turmoil
We decided to be together
This must be Keke's mother
My mom
Yes
To clear my name
We worked together to solve the case
But in the end, you were "killed"
by the murderer and his lackey Xiao Xiao Wang
I could only drown in sorrow
I will definitely avenge you
I hope one day you'll forgive me
Looking forward to taking a photo together with you
"Home With Kids"
Phone
Whose phone?
Old Li
Isn't it Old Li?
Check the photo
Come on
Don't jump
What does this say?
Sleep-talking
Don't jump
What are you jumping for?
Xiaoxiao Wang's Chat History
Xiaoxiao Wang said:
After all we've just discussed,
there's one thing I still can't figure out.
How did you know
about our scam using Retro Street
and all the plans?
Then Old Li said:
Don't worry about it.
I know everything anyway.
He said: "Alright,"
"I know both Old Wang (Xiao Wang) and I
have wronged you."
Then Xiaoxiao Wang continued:
I'm on duty tonight.
After 10 pm, I'll take you to Chuyang Alley
to check something.
We'll discuss
the plan to "eliminate"
Old Wang (Xiao Wang).
By the way,
for easier operation,
you should stay at my place recently.
I've changed the passcode to your birthday -
July 2nd.
I'll first use "Charming Mist" knockout gas
to knock out the staff at Chuyang Alley.
So in that room,
they were knocked out, right?
They were unconscious at the time.
Then invite Old Wang (Xiao Wang) to the warehouse
"Kill" him
and leave behind
traces pointing to those old methods
I hope your children
can help clear your name
Then I can leave in peace
Remember to show them the video
to lead them to Chuyang Alley to find the truth
So this place
actually belongs to Xiao Xiao Wang
Yes, Xiao Xiao Wang's family
Xiao Xiao Wang's place
Old Li came to live here
There's more later
video
The one they showed us
You're the ones from the apartment
The one we just saw on TV
that we watched
He wanted us to handle it
Yes, they wanted to lure us
to that (photo studio)
Right, because they said the "murder and corpse burning" case
would happen again
How did Xiao Xiao Wang "die"
That's right
You see
Xiao Xiao Wang wanted to "take out" Old Wang (Little Wang)
So he arranged to meet Old Wang (Little Wang) there
He wanted Old Li to join him
But unexpectedly
This same Xiao Xiao Wang had previously "caused the death of"
Mother Zhou
So Old Li used this as an opportunity
First to "eliminate" Old Wang (Little Wang)
Then later "eliminated" Xiao Xiao Wang
That's roughly what happened
Your father
Dad
What should I call him?
Grandpa (maternal)
Yes
Who is this fat guy?
This is your husband
Isn't this my Cai?
Come watch the show!
The show's starting!
Long time no see
How come you...
...have aged so much?
It's been over thirty years since we last met.
After thirty years apart, of course we'd age like this.
You're still alive.
If it weren't for you,
I would have "died" long ago.
Have you been waiting for me all this time?
Yes.
Who is he?
He's my son.
You've never met him.
I'm your wife.
He's your son, but I've never seen him.
Because you're my ex-wife.
Did we get divorced?
Yes, we did.
That's nonsense.
In 1988,
you just ran away.
That's right.
I've been looking for you.
I've searched for you all these years.
Now we meet,
what have you brought me?
You've brought me a son.
Sit down
Listen to me carefully
Come here
Cai
Why is he my son?
Because after we separated
I kept thinking
About this
Finding someone else
But I didn't pursue it
This chubby kid
Chubby kid
Is he related to us?
No relation
Good that there's no relation
Otherwise my mind would be even more confused
He's not related to me
They can't all be related
None of these are related
Finally one without any relation
I went back to 1988 to find you
I was tricked
You got tricked again
Why say "again"?
You were tricked by him once
Always saying "again"
Cai Cai, this trait of yours never changes
When I left you back then
I left you a letter
I wanted you to remarry
It was for you and our daughter
To have a complete family
Remember the ones who were "burned to death"
Zhou Cangcang and Zhou Kuku
His mother was Zhou Cangcang's daughter
Right
His mother too
Later, believe me
I didn't "kill" her father and uncle
So she investigated with me
But in 2002
She was "murdered"
Of course
You didn't protect
You didn't protect his mother either
Yes
Then how dare you come here
First, we have a question.
We just want to know about "the deceased."
Are you aware of "the dead people"?
Two people "died."
Of course I know.
Two people "died" today, did you know?
Not the two who "died" in 1988.
I know.
You know again?
Of course.
We're already aware of this matter.
We just hope you could...
Let's compare notes.
See if we have the same information.
Do you suspect him?
No suspicion, just want to know.
How did you...
This is it.
How was the crime committed?
No.
I mean how this case was handled.
Those who "died" today were...
Xiaoxiao Wang and Old Wang (or Xiao Wang).
Right.
This Old Wang (Xiao Wang) was killed by Xiaoxiao Wang.
"Killed."
We're aware of this.
Since Xiaoxiao Wang was the "murderer,"
how did he end up being "killed" instead?
Xiaoxiao Wang "committed suicide."
I don't want to live.
Impossible.
"Suicide" is impossible.
He had an agreement with you.
That after everything was done,
you would spare his life.
Let him go.
It must be "homicide," right?
Yes, definitely ("homicide").
That's what you think.
To leave, he wanted to leave.
You're leaving again.
You want to leave.
I'm not leaving.
This contains Xiaoxiao Wang's...
photo.
Tip-off letter.
And Old Wang's (Little Wang's)
USB drive containing all criminal records
The two people closest to you here
won't give it to either of us
I am Little Xiao Wang
By the time you read this letter
I have already "killed" my boss
and "committed suicide"
We deceived many elderly people
swindling their life savings
Even
drove those lonely elders
to pay with their lives
Our deeds were deeply sinful
unforgivable
only "death" can atone
Moreover
I've left at the scene
clues pointing to the 1988
"murder" and arson case
Little Xiao Wang
So your father is finally cleared of suspicion
Grandpa
Congratulations
Not necessarily
I'm not entirely convinced
So how did Aunt Zhou "die"?
Back then, he was still young.
I have to take care of him
So his mother is investigating
who was responsible for her father's "death"
In the end,
by Xiao Wang (Old Wang)
now Old Wang (Xiao Wang)
discovered
he and Xiao Xiao Wang together
Pushed his mother down
This is the rapper
It was because of your aunt
Aunt Zhou
And your uncle Zhou Zengzeng
He didn’t believe
That I was innocent
Thought I pushed your mom off the cliff
Moreover
Firmly believed that back in 1988
It was me who "killed" your grandfather
I had no choice
So I came out to investigate again
Later I discovered
He "killed" Zhou Cangcang and Zhou Kuku
because he taught them longevity exercises
and got exposed by them
Then I found out
Old Wang (Little Wang) and Little Little Wang were here
They restored
this old Chuyang Alley
and opened this Youth Photo Studio
doing exactly the same things as before
cheating elderly people out of their money again
To hide my identity
I've been staying inside this Meow Meow
I couldn't reveal myself to you
because I couldn't prove myself yet
Until that day on June 25th
when I caught Little Little Wang here
Little Wang
I've finally caught you
What are you doing here?
I've been here all along. Didn't expect that, did you?
I should thank you all
for helping me find my two children
But you've ruined my life
Today
let's settle everything once and for all
I just wanted to
have a final reckoning with him
and make things clear
But then Little Wang told me
that he's actually been dissatisfied
with Old Wang (Young Wang) all these years
Little Wang
also discovered he has a terminal illness
and doesn't have long to live
He told me
he could help me
clear my name
Clear my name
and restore
the truth about
the 1988
warehouse "murder" case
That's why
I deliberately left that
video footage
outside your restaurant today
along with a newspaper
I wanted you all
to solve this case
Solve this case
He recreated
the crime scene from back then
just to show you
that even without the warehouse key
it's still possible
to make two people appear "dead"
There's one more here
This is
This is for you
This was given to me by Xiao Xiao Wang
At that time, he planned to do it in this warehouse
how to "kill" Lao Wang (Xiao Wang)
and then "commit suicide" himself
A diagram of the human body
July 2nd
Using a gasoline can
Strike Lao Wang (Xiao Wang)'s temple
Gasoline can
He hit the back of the head
Both were struck on the back of the head
Look at his head
"Died" from severe head trauma
Suddenly I also felt something was wrong
This reminded me of Xiao Xiao Wang
On June 26th
He went to scout Chu Yang Alley
To put it bluntly, he wanted to recreate
the exact methods from 1988
of the "murder" scene
all the techniques
Then
he asked me to move in with him
and even changed the passcode
to my birthday
Xiao Xiao Wang discovered
a tracking device on himself
A tracker
We discussed at the time
whether to discard the tracker
but were afraid of alerting someone
Since we didn't know
who had placed the tracker on him
so he gave the tracker to me
Moreover, he gave me a key.
It's said that inside here
there are many important clues
Right, there's one box we haven't opened
While everyone's here together,
let me ask you one more question.
About this "Meet You" organization,
what kind of organization is it?
Would you mind telling us about it?
Meow meow
Tea and fruits meet
"Meet You" (organization name)
Thank you to the "Meet You" organization
for giving me this opportunity
Would you mind telling us about it?
No, I wouldn't
Why, grandpa?
Alright
Okay, grandpa
Let me ask one question
Earlier on the phone you were talking in your sleep
What was that about?
Right
That's right
You said "don't jump"
Jump from what?
Don't jump
This "don't jump"
Actually it's because
The most important person to me
When they jumped from the building
I didn't see it
I deeply regret it
I've always wished I had been there
I could have stopped him
Then I think our top priority
is to check the tracker
Where is the tracker?
It's on me
There's also a key
Yes, you gave it to us
This is the tracker
This is the key
Okay
Let's split up
and go to Old Wang's shop
to check the key he left
and see if there are any other clues
Because he said there were important clues
in that box
Where's the tracker?
He gave it to me
Let me get you your favorite snack
Xiao Bai, you like Oreos too?
Did your mom name you Xiao Bai
because you like the white cream in Oreos?
(continuation of previous line)
That's right
No wonder our Lao Li likes
the black Oreos
Just like the black cookies
protecting the white cream
He probably hopes
to always protect you all
These Oreos are our family's
lucky little cookies
Come on, let's all eat together
Oreos are like a family
The white cream can't exist alone
The black and white embracing, playing together
will keep our family together forever
Okay
Alright
Good
You guys investigate thoroughly here
Fine
You just
I'll go find that
Xiao He
I'll go to the boss
To report that everything's fine
All right then
I'll go ahead first
I won't bother with you guys then
Go ahead
Goodbye
From what I remember,
there was a secret passage.
It's over here.
Yes.
Get down
Someone's here
Keep all the elderly safely at home
If you see any young people on the street
Arrest them all
Song Piaoliang, go inside by yourself
Then close the door
You guys
Get out of the photo studio
Go find those young people from earlier
I'm already inside.
Come out
Alright, let's go
Go
I'll cover the rear
Move
Little Wang
Counter keys
There are scratches on the lock
It's been opened by someone
Then this doll appeared again
It's foretelling "death"
It only foretells "the deceased"
This looks like a
tear open
Let's search the Twitter location tracker
Right
Got it
Two hundred thirty
Zhou
What?
b
Isn't this Zhou Keke's "Biao Biao"?
This profile picture
Yes
This username might be Zhou Biao Biao
Yes, Zhou BB
That must be his online alias
Zhou Keke himself
But he uses "Biao Biao" as his username
Right?
Suspicious, right?
Go
Which room does Zhou Keke live in?
7th (floor)
Cocoa is actually a scientist
A chemist
He might not just be making chocolate
Right
Making chocolate doesn't involve such complicated things
There's a notebook here
Friends
Niao Niao's Diary Protecting Keke
Is this Niao Niao a living creature?
Or does this person have dual...
split personalities?
Yes, like having multiple personalities
Is there something?
Youth Photo Studio
Is this that piece of paper?
Yes
Give it to Sister Cai
He's highly suspicious
Find him
Okay
Zhou Biaobiao
said
Stop pinching me
I told you earlier
to confess honestly
Now look
That tracker is mine
Also found at his place was
a dedicated drug-making area
It's a chemistry lab
A place for making drugs - date rape drugs
That was for developing
chocolate-flavored products
There was also a notebook
"Biaobiao's Diary Protecting Keke"
"Keke don't cry"
"Mom is gone"
"Biaobiao is still here"
It's like... what is he
When his mother "passed away"
he became extremely depressed
Maybe he imagined that thing as
protection
emotional support
Yes, emotional support
You see
He was bullied as a child
They said nobody wanted this kid
He would say "Biaobiao"
"Keke don't listen"
It was that kind of protection
comforting him
watching over him
And when someone bullied Keke
he would take revenge
Split personality
There's a phone here
It's yours
This is Keke
Don't don't (a nickname)
I've found the "murderer"
Those who hurt you
should all "die"
He said to Don't don't
I've found the "murderer"
Those who hurt you
should all "die"
Zhou Keke also has a "motive for murder"
Zhou Keke came in last
Zhou Keke didn't come in
The place where drugs are made
Date rape drug
We came here
He must have brought us here
Zhou Keke is acting very strange today
should all "die"
Speak for yourself
It wasn't me
Now that it's come to this
You still won't confess
It wasn't me
How could it not be you? It was Biubiu, right?
Shifting the blame onto
When the next time comes
We won't bring Biubiu
Biubiu's been taken in
Come on, even though there's no property surveillance room today
But you go over there
Zhou Biaobiao
Let me confess honestly
I'm actually Old Li's son
My full name
My real name is Li Erzi (Li Son)
Li Erzi
Truly a great name
Yes, I put in a lot of effort
to come up with this name
Li Erzi
You checked the dictionary
Right, I looked it up
When I was five years old
When my mother went to find cocoa beans
she "accidentally fell to her death"
Then my father
which is you
said nothing at all
He just left a note
"I can't raise you anymore"
and then left me
How heartless
Fortunately I had my aunt
Aunt Zhou
She raised me until I was ten
She treated me like a mother
So Aunt Zhou followed
our Zhou family tradition
of ABB-style names
and gave me this name
called Zhou Keke
Then later
when I turned ten
Aunt Zhou also "passed away"
So I went to the orphanage
Then only Zhou Biaobiao
could stay with me
Mom always kept "Bie Bie" for me
Because when I was little
everyone kept saying I didn't have a father
and "Bie Bie" was
I was the pot that made the first chocolate with Zhou Mama
(continuation of previous line)
But
because Mama
left Zhou Keke
she told me
I must protect Zhou Keke
When he gets bullied
I must come out and fight those bad people for him
Why is he called Zhou Keke?
Because Zhou Keke is afraid of offending others
or making people unhappy
Whatever people ask him to do
he does it
He never says no
Only when I appear
can I say for him
"Don't bully Zhou Keke"
So
"Biao Biao" is the one who can shout for me
"I don't want to do that thing"
"No"
Zhou Keke will do anything
What is this thing?
But we became friends so quickly
Indeed
Right
Let's make another chocolate today
Okay, great
Bai Sanwan, you kicked someone's door down again
Why do you always kick doors?
Yeah
Too violent
Bai Song 1 Guo Zhou
Liu 1 Cool
Then, but
Auntie Zhou kept telling me
that my father "killed"
my mother
But after investigating
I discovered
that actually my mother
was "murdered" by two people that day
One of them
had a mole on his neck
Then I found someone with a mole
That person was called Xiao Xiao Wang
What did you do to him?
On the 25th, I found Xiao Xiao Wang
He lived in our apartment building
Then on the 26th
I secretly followed him to his home
I figured out his password
and sneaked in
I placed a tracker on his clothes
I wanted to track his daily movements
where he went
I wanted to avenge my mother
But on the 27th I discovered
my tracking device's location
stopped updating
When I tried to check the tracker again
to see if there were any changes
I found I couldn't access it anymore
Verification failed
System locked
The password had been changed
I never saw Xiao Xiao Wang again
So I never got the chance
to do this thing
But look at the back of the "victim's" head
Was that hit by your "Biao Biao"?
But haven't you noticed
my dad raised a question?
What he said was
"The victim"
recreated all the original criminal methods
I simply don't know
what those criminal methods were
When that incident happened
I wasn't even born yet
But Xiao Xiao Wang
actually wasn't there at the time either
It's not necessarily that
you had to be present at the time
to know how to "kill" this person
right?
As long as you know Old Wang's (Xiao Wang's)
this secret, that's enough
Koko really doesn't know anything
Koko just wants to help mom
No
There's one question
Why did you want Sister Cai to go in?
For Sister Cai
It's about getting Sister Cai
involved in this scam
That Sister Cai...
I just noticed she's been very unhappy lately
But Youth Photo Studio claimed
they could make every elderly person happy
So you sent her there
to have others lock her up?
No, I didn't know what was inside
I only knew
it was a happy place
I wanted her to be happy
So you'd
been to this place before?
Never been there
I just saw the flyer
Do you know who Sister Cai is?
I don't know Sister Cai
Our relationship...
Sister Cai really liked
eating the chocolates I made
And Sister Cai
she's also someone like me
abandoned and all alone
Who knew we were abandoned by the same person
This is what the three of us rummaged through
You guys are here at their place
rummaging through things again
This is it
So many clues
Because there's another doll
What does this doll say?
Don't go to Chuyang Alley
Disobey and you'll "die"
Don't what?
Don't go to Chuyang Alley
Don't go to Chuyang Alley—you'll "die"
This was their original modus operandi
Just as we suspected
Let me see
Even with both doors locked
The "murder" could still be committed from outside
Replace the mattress with a special air cushion
Hide the extended inflation valve
on the air cushion
Attach a thin wire
Secure the other end of the wire
outside the vent window
Possibly before the fire started
He used something like balloons
to stack this "corpse" unusually high
Step two: after someone enters the warehouse
Use "knockout smoke" to render them unconscious
This is the "knockout smoke"
That is
the anesthetic drug
He likely knocked them out first
Step three
Outside the warehouse, use wooden crates
to build a ladder
Climb near the vent window
Then pull the thin wire
to extend the inflation valve outside the vent
Connect the air pump to inflate
Wait until the bed rises to the vent
"Kill" them with a brick
Up to this point
Then inflate
After full inflation
Reach a hand inside
Take the brick
"Dead"
Great, we've successfully deduced it again
Impressive
Excellent
Then they said
Our "murder" plan
doesn't require executing the full method
Day 1
Complete step one during the warehouse open day
Which is to replace the bed
Then place the inflation valve on the air mattress
Run an air hose from the valve to the outside
Hide gasoline in the warehouse
Day 2
At 3 PM I'll first take down the staff
Hide them behind the counter
Then we'll all enter the warehouse together
After "killing," prepare everything
Then leave peacefully
Xiaoxiao Wang "committed suicide"
No
Xiaoxiao Wang didn't intend to "commit suicide"
Because he originally planned to finish it
and then leave
He crossed out three and four.
He plans to skip steps three and four
Right
He thinks steps three and four are unnecessary
Steps three and four involve inflating from outside
Inflating
Either method could "eliminate" him
So if he chooses arson
He wouldn't need
to "bludgeon" him with bricks
No need for the air cushion
That's the idea
Just knock him out directly
then finish by "burning" him
But both methods
still appeared at the crime scene
meaning both were carried out
No
It means there's another person
Little Wang originally
wanted to follow the plan below
But he didn't do it
and just burned it directly
But there must be someone else
who wanted to "eliminate" Little Wang along with it
holding a brick
to "smash" both of them
That person must have seen this paper too.
Who else might have seen this thing?
This was likely written by two people
One in red, one in blue
Was this done with you?
The initial plan was written by me.
Because he wanted to recreate the original crime method.
Yes.
The earlier plan was drafted by me.
But it was later modified with blue pen.
Disclosed by Xiao Xiao Wang.
I told him.
Old Wang (Xiao Wang) that I discovered.
The crime steps at that time.
Then I told him.
Is there anything inside the bag?
A woman's wig
There's "blood" on this
Little Wang, I won't let you succeed
If you insist on this
then your fate
will be like these stinky dance shoes
and this rotten wig
rotten and stinking
A Pair of Embroidered Shoes
Look, it's marked here with "Ladybug"
This storage room
And there's a circle drawn around Ladybug
Where is Ladybug?
According to this map
The dance hall
Ladybug's office
We still need to go to the dance hall first, right?
Only then can we find out
Right
But we need to find a way to distract them
Before we can go to the dance hall
You guys go out through the photo studio
And look for those young people from earlier
Can we get out from this way?
The problem is
It seems we can't exit from here
Let me check again
Can't get out
Can't go this way, that door's locked
You've found all these keys, right?
Xiao Xiao Wang gave me a key
So this key
is for opening the storage room door
This secret passage leads to the warehouse
Right
Blindfold them
This is the storage room
This storage room should connect to
today's warehouse
So if we exit from here
we can actually reach the courtyard
You can't go to the courtyard, they're still there
If you go out
they'll catch you and take you to the storage room
right?
The storage room is accessible now
so it doesn't matter
We just need someone to make a trip there
Then while they're being captured
you all go to the dance hall
The problem is the remaining person
can't go to the dance hall
We need to find a way to distract them
so we can go to the dance hall
and bring them inside
It's locked
Ours is locked too, we can't get out
The storage room is accessible now
Could this chain be useful?
I've got it
One person exits through the main gate.
Then they're going to
escort him back and lock him in the storage room, right?
Then you turn around
we'll follow his steps
closely behind them
Once they enter the main courtyard
there's that iron gate, right?
Just lock this at that iron gate
lock it
Then he comes out from here
There's also this chain here
We've got so many locks
If he runs out
just lock the windows and it's done
Right
Okay
I'll go lure them
Are you sure?
Don't go alone
Come on, let's go together holding hands
Let's go, no need to hold hands
Alright, let's go, ready
Wait, don't go yet
Wait
Hold on
Bro
Don't do this
Here
have something to eat
Two kids
Let's play marbles
Yes, we're going to play shuttlecock
Have you played this before?
Grab them
Don't
Stop grabbing people
We didn't do anything
Why are we all being grabbed?
Why are you dragging us away again?
Caught
Don't want to
Entering the door again
Back in the warehouse again
Why are we in the warehouse again?
Warehouse again
I'm exhausted
We're in, back in this courtyard again
Come on, hurry
Quick
What are you doing?
Then where should we go?
What should we do?
No key.
Key.
We forgot the key.
"You killed someone"
Shut up
You coward
You irresponsible bastard
How can you face my elder sister?
You little brats causing trouble here
None of you are getting out
Sister Hua locked the door
That threatening letter you wrote
We saw it
You two betrayed the boss
Besides Old Wang (or Xiao Wang)
There's an even bigger boss
Traitors
At this critical moment, you still won't confess
Dad, believe me
I believe
This person's using the "self-injury" tactic
Keke really doesn't know anything
Keke just wants...
Don't bully Zhou Keke
To help mom
Watch on Tencent Video
New episodes every Thursday, Friday, and Saturday at 6 PM
Members get early access one week in advance
Every Saturday at 6 PM
"Let's Solve It" Case Files
Every Sunday at 6 PM
Watch bonus content: "Apartment No. 11 Diary"
Midweek teasers, behind-the-scenes, and short videos
Daily updates to binge-watch
Take a 360° deep dive into Apartment No. 11
Hurry and open Tencent Video
Search for "Let's Solve It"
Join the detectives for an immersive case-solving experience