Someone "died"
This should be Song, the delivery guy
He installed surveillance in Fang Xiaomei's home
To spy on Fang Xiaomei's family, right?
Anyway, the two of them were very sweet together
Good
Liu Xialai
Had an argument
Why is this in my house?
(Hao) The cleaner
So Xiaomei and Yueguang were in an online relationship
Cao Yueguang
Song Huo
Fang Xiaomei
This "scumbag couple" plotted murder for money
"Killed" Cao Yueguang
There's a traitor among us.
How despicable.
Just wait and see how he's going to "interrogate" you.
Seriously.
Good work today, everyone.
Or,
Who wants to briefly summarize
the suspect's identity?
I'll do it.
Let me summarize.
Go ahead, you do it.
Just confess already.
Justice before family.
You go first.
We'd like to hear
You first.
I'd like to hear everyone's suggestions.
Suggestions, everyone's suggestions.
The key people in today's case are:
"The deceased"
Song Huo
Directly related
First
Liu Xialai
and Liu Xialai
One person directly related
is named Cao Yueguang
Then with Cao Yueguang
there's another directly connected person
named Hao Baojie
With these three people
there's someone connected to all
named Fang Xiaomei
Why is there a hole here?
There's suddenly a hole
I think it's very strange
How did you get in?
Do you know him?
I don't know him
The three of us went to Liu Xialai's room
Cao Yueguang's phone
Why is it with Liu Xialai?
Meimei, it's still me
Changed number to add you
Because I need to tell you something important
I recently had surgery
I look different from before
Also due to some personal matters
I changed my name to Liu Xialai
Liu Xialai is Cao Yueguang
There's a combination lock here
(Password) how many digits?
What is it?
Three letters
Cao Yueguang
It actually worked
There is
and an ID card
Whose?
Cao Yueguang's ID card
What does he look like?
That's him
Adoption certificate
This certifies that Mr. and Mrs. Cao from Tuishi City
have adopted a boy
born on January 8, 1997
renamed as Cao Yueguang
His room has an ID card
showing it's Cao Yueguang
There's also an adoption certificate
And then?
Liu Xialai's phone
shows through WeChat that
he is actually "Moonlight Treasure Box"
Which means
Liu Xialai
is "Moonlight Treasure Box"
The top donor
Top donor
"Top donor" is acceptable
Therefore
Liu Xialai is Cao Yueguang
In Hao the cleaner's room
we found something
He summarized a relationship chart
showing Song Huo and Xiaomei conspired
to commit murder for money
against Cao Yueguang
Why would a cleaner
monitor Xiaomei's room
and talk about "scumbags"
and "gold-diggers"?
On that relationship chart
Cao Yueguang's murder case
has a photo attached
labeled "blood brothers"
So
Hao the cleaner is Cao Yueguang's brother
meaning Liu Xialai's brother
Today,
the suspect
First,
Liu Xialai (also known as Cao Yueguang)
why did he "kill" Song Huo?
His motive was self-preservation.
In Liu Xialai's room,
we found a small surveillance camera
that captured
Song Huo
contacting a mysterious "killer"
sending messages
requesting them to "kill" Liu Xialai
on May 13th.
The young man's heart is racing.
Why is it beating faster and faster?
Second,
why did Hao Baojie "kill" Song Huo?
His motive was to avenge his brother.
Revenge.
Why did Xiaomei "kill" Song Huo?
This place,
currently our three-person investigation
cannot directly confirm a motive,
but why can we confirm
she is a suspect?
Because
today we discovered that from Xiaomei's room
to the crime scene
it was like this:
This place,
which is Hao Baojie's room,
this place
is where the "victim" was.
The only ones with direct access
were Hao Baojie
and Xiaomei.
Therefore, based on this,
we can deduce
that Xiaomei had the means to commit the crime.
Thus, Xiaomei is also our prime suspect.
What have you been through
That's amazing
Very good
Everything we have matches your story
Look
This is what we found in Xiaomei's room
Her personal diary
The first entry says
I accidentally came across
Xiaomei's video online
Since you're a fashion blogger
Do you think my fabric
is boyfriend material?
And confessed
Confessed
This was Valentine's Day
February 14, 2021
Last year
Then Xiaomei said
Starting today
I'm no longer alone
You're the light in my darkness
They became official
Then in 2022
Didn't you always want to hear me sing
your favorite song?
"A Light in the Darkness"
The song "A Light in the Darkness"
Here
He can
Let him sing
The muscle one
Quick
Muscles can't hold on, quick
Right
Look, his lips match
Muscle memory
You know this song
Stop pretending
Let me tell you
Your lips moved
Maybe you should sit over there first
Ask (Liu) to come down first, maybe
Ask (Liu) to come down first
He's a bit nervous
Look at his Adam's apple
bobbing up and down
Come on, let's ask.
So you're (Cao) Yueguang?
Yes.
Do you know Song Huo?
Yes, I do.
Did Song Huo cause
that car accident of yours?
Did he steal your five million?
No.
He was
trying to steal my five million.
Can you explain in detail about your dispute
with Song Huo outside the bank that day?
Also, another question.
We noticed this money
was actually withdrawn from
your adoptive mother's account.
Right?
Yes.
This money was given to me by Mother Cao.
I was adopted by their family as a child.
Mother Cao passed away a year ago.
At that time,
Mother Cao was worried that
Father Cao and their biological child
didn't treat me well.
They were unkind to me.
So she gave me five million
to find someone to love
and live well.
This money rightfully belongs to me.
Yes.
So who is Mrs. Cao's biological son?
Mr. and Mrs. Cao's biological son
is named Cao Yangguang.
You're very familiar with him.
The little boy from last week.
Actually, back then,
why did I withdraw that 5 million?
It was because
Mr. Cao and Cao Yangguang
found out about my 5 million
and kept coming to demand the money from me.
So I thought,
"Fine, I'll give it to you.
I don't want it anymore.
I don't want anything.
I want my dignity."
After I withdrew the money,
when I was about to deliver it to the Cao family,
a car came dangerously close to me.
It kept forcing me
to the edge of a cliff.
It wrecked my car.
Then someone got out
and tried to rob me.
He actually took my watch
and wallet from me.
At that moment,
I fought back against him.
During the struggle,
I saw his face clearly.
It was today's "deceased," Song Huo.
Then he ran away.
Actually, that five million
is still in my trunk
and wasn't stolen by him
So through this opportunity
I started thinking
why should I keep suffering like this
why should I return this money
I might as well take this money
and start a new life
So I created
a "fake death" scenario
left my pants and shoes on the shore
pushed the car into the sea
to make them think I "died"
went to get plastic surgery
changed back
My name was Liu Xialai from the very beginning
Do you know
why Song Huo wanted to "kill" you?
I don't know
He must have wanted to steal my money
I know
Song Huo kept lurking around my house
I suspected he would enter my home
So in my room
I installed surveillance cameras
Through this surveillance
I discovered something
He entered my room
and took the bank card
containing five million yuan
Perhaps because Song Huo found out
that he was actually
Right
So the people who know Liu Xialai is Cao Yueguang
how many are there?
After I had plastic surgery
I went to see Xiaomei again
I added her on WeChat
I told Xiaomei
Inside the power distribution room,
we discovered
Didn't we find a phone?
It was Song Huo's phone.
Then,
the boss also found out
that his phone account
could be switched.
Song Huo's phone
had both Song Huo's WeChat
and Meimei Planet's WeChat.
Right, his phone could switch accounts.
There was a Meimei Planet
and a
account.
"I'll switch accounts to add you"
"to tell you"
"something very important."
Xiaomei said,
"Alright, I understand."
"Let's keep in touch via text."
After his plastic surgery,
the person he contacted was always Song Huo.
Right.
So only Song Huo knew
he wanted to "kill" Song Huo
because Song Huo wanted to "kill" him.
Right.
Song Huo wanted to ("kill" him)
because he knew he was Cao Yueguang.
So you know,
when I cut you off with my car
and tried to "kill" you,
I wanted to rob you.
You knew I was a "killer."
Anyway, Song Huo "killing" him
had strong motives.
Therefore,
knowing this, he wanted to counter-"kill."
This makes sense.
Do you have any other questions?
There's one more question.
You were adopted.
Which means your biological brother
might be that Hao Baojie.
I didn't know about this.
But
when I was little,
I had a biological brother
named Liu Xiah Hao.
We were very young
when we got separated at age seven.
Liu Xiah Hao, Baojie...
They are brothers.
In Hao Baojie's room
we found a computer
That computer
was actually the surveillance system for Fang Xiaomei's home
In the surveillance footage
Liu Xialai appeared
with Song Huo
having an argument at home
Song Huo
seemed to be writing
some kind of guarantee letter
He wrote it
today
May 13th at 11:00 AM
Why did you go see Song Huo?
And why were you arguing?
In the end he wrote you
"May 13th at 11:00"
That was written
to tell you
what would happen at that time?
That might be Song Huo's "time of death"
I'd like to see that video
Don't you remember?
What were you two talking about
in Xiaomei's room?
I
I didn't know about this
It's over
He's a twin
So the one with dual personalities is him
I really didn't know
No
Then let me ask you
How do you explain
You saw Song Huo hiring a "hitman"
to eliminate you on the 13th
Actually, I knew
he was coming to "kill" me today
Right
By inviting everyone to my place
he wouldn't dare act recklessly
You're using us
Which of us can actually protect you?
You're the strongest among us
If even you can't handle it
Just give him a bowl of congee
Give him a whole pot of congee (wordplay: "Guo Zhou")
Make him wet his pants (wordplay: "Liu Yi Ku")
Soak his pants
But
Perhaps it's precisely because he knew
Song Huo
wanted to "kill" him
Yes
Exactly
That room behind yours
The one that looks like a specimen room
What's it for?
Secret passage
There are knives and a cat on his desk
That's part of my job
Many people who really love their pets
When their own pets
pass away
I have a skill
I can preserve them as specimens
or cremate them
and make a memorial
I'm in pet funeral services
Yes, exactly
Pet mortician
Suddenly so heartwarming
Just instantly
Very heartwarming, right?
Alright, hurry up
Don't sit there, it's cold
I feel a bit sorry
Good friend, come back quickly
Come back
You see
Everyone wants to ask now
Which suspect
Definitely (Hao) the cleaner
(Hao) the cleaner
Hao the cleaner, right?
Then I'll go call him over
He's coming
Snapped at me
Angry guy
I feel a bit sorry
Have a seat, Liu Xiahao
While it was wrong of me to enter your room,
I discovered that
you've also done some very improper things.
Why did you
install surveillance in Fang Xiaomei's room?
Why spy on her private life?
Here's the thing:
I believe Fang Xiaomei and Song Huo
are connected to my brother's "death."
So to investigate thoroughly
without being detected,
I installed surveillance.
Later you found out
that through
monitoring their household situation,
you discovered Xiaomei and Song Huo
seem to have an unusual relationship.
Not just unusual -
they're actually a couple.
Because Song Huo could come and go freely
in Fang Xiaomei's home
and their behavior was very intimate
But aside from the intimacy shown in your video
did you witness any other intimate moments?
No
Because I didn't pay attention to those things
We care deeply about this, you know
You must have seen something
Can I just pay for a membership?
Even with membership you can't see it
because I deleted it that same day
No, I mean how intimate were they?
What kind of intimacy did you see?
The intimacy we witnessed
was normal intimacy
He's asking about the not-so-normal kind
Well, no...
That kind of closeness he mentioned...
It's just...
Look, you're Xiaomei...
I'm Song Huo...
We entered the room...
See...
Pretty...
Closeness...
This is what closeness means...
No...
What exactly do you want from me?
If there's nothing important...
I still have work to do...
Wait, hold on a second...
Because Song Huo "died"...
Right...
You know?
"Died"...
Song Huo...
The doorknob of an abandoned electrical room...
Was electrified and "killed" him...
We discovered...
Someone wrapped wires around the doorknob...
Then he deserved it...
He should have "died"...
No.
Bad people should be punished by the law,
not by other people.
Right?
Then why are you looking for me?
We suspect you're involved.
In your room,
we found a pair of couple's watches.
The men's watch
was worn by Song Huo.
Why was the women's watch with you?
Yes, why was this watch with you?
Here's the thing.
That watch
was my brother's keepsake.
My younger brother
had been out of contact with me for a long time.
I came to Tuishi City specifically to find my brother.
On April 1st,
someone sent me a WeChat message
saying my brother had been adopted by the Cao family.
The next day I went to the Cao family to find him,
but the adoptive father said
my brother had "died."
But no matter how much I asked,
the adoptive father wouldn't tell me anything.
He only gave me his belongings -
that couple's watch gift set.
Inside was a letter from my brother to Fang Xiaomei.
That's how I learned
Fang Xiaomei was my brother's girlfriend.
So I wanted to find Fang Xiaomei
to ask about my brother's situation.
A perfectly healthy person
just suddenly "dies" like that?
After searching everywhere,
I found Fang Xiaomei online.
She's a fashion blogger,
and this girl
has no concern for her privacy at all.
That's how
I learned she also lives in Apartment 11.
This apartment is really a strange place.
Do you know the secret passage in your apartment
leads to an abandoned electrical room?
The secret passage leads to the abandoned electrical room.
How did we get into your room?
We sneaked in through there, didn't we?
I don't know.
Even if he knows, he wouldn't tell you.
Inside your own room
there's a one-way lock.
Once opened, you can enter a...
But all I know is
that room only leads to Fang Xiaomei's place.
You didn't go further inside?
No.
Even if he really would tell you,
he still wouldn't tell you.
That's right.
I knew Fang Xiaomei lived in
Room 610.
Originally, I wanted to confront Fang Xiaomei directly
and get some answers.
But that day,
a man came out of her room.
That man was wearing
the unique watch
my brother gave to Fang Xiaomei.
I realized this wasn't simple.
I had to investigate.
I had to avenge my brother.
To avoid alerting them,
I thought
maybe I could go through the ventilation shaft
from my room in that direction.
Sure enough, the two rooms were adjacent,
but there was a wall.
I could only dig through
when Fang Xiaomei wasn't home.
Then you sneaked into their house
Installed surveillance in their home
Yes
No
I also found
My brother's "death" report
"Death" report
Found in Fang Xiaomei's house
What did it say?
It stated
My brother was killed for money during a withdrawal
An investigative report, right?
Is it an investigative report?
Which means
Fang Xiaomei knew about this too
Investigative report
Yes
This is what I found in her home
Moreover
I also noticed something suspicious
Fang Xiaomei had a phone
Which I also discovered
There was a
Private WeChat Moments post
Saying "I'm sorry"
It said "I'm sorry"
Yes
Just "I'm sorry"
Then there was your brother's
Screenshot of my brother's WeChat Moments
Mentioning five million
Yes
That's when I learned
My brother was wealthy
So I believe
Fang Xiaomei must have targeted my brother for his money
And conspired with Song Huo
To "murder" my brother
Yes
At 11 o'clock this morning
where were you?
At 11 I was in the common area
You were in the common area?
Yes
From 10:30 to 11
I was sweeping the floor
From 11:30 to 12
I emptied the trash bins in two elevators
Then I went back home
only to find you rummaging through my place
After kicking you out
I stayed inside
That power distribution room on the first floor
does it count as a common area?
The power distribution room
Yes, it does
Was there anyone else besides you at that time?
You were working alone?
I'm the only cleaner in this entire building
I'm sorry
My apologies to everyone
I'll hire a few more
Don't bother
One is enough
There's another folder on your computer
marked with a question mark
Did you find the answer to that question mark?
That question mark
No
Haven't found the answer
I was startled too at that time
Don't know who it was
Also there's this:
He (Liu) came down
and was arguing with Song Huo
Do you know what they were arguing about?
Liu Xialai
This person here
Hurry up and acknowledge each other
Talk quickly
No
Please
Don't joke about this matter
Alright?
My brother has already "died"
Please show some respect for my brother
No
That's not
Are you called Liu Xiahai?
Yes
Stop
This isn't fun anymore
No, I'm not joking
I'm Liu Xialai
Right, you must be my brother
What?
I didn't expect it to be you
Impossible
Absolutely impossible
We haven't seen each other in over ten years
What does he look like
I don't even know now
If you say so, then it must be
I had plastic surgery
We lived in City A when we were kids
After our father passed away
Our mother tried to raise both of us
But she couldn't manage it
She could only choose to take me
The two of us
Moved to Tui City to live
But our grandparents
Wanted
To keep the Liu family lineage in City A
So they kept you there
Then my mother took me to Tui City
Our mother passed away three years later too
So you really are
This is (Liu) Xialai
The proof of when you were adopted by the Cao family
Later I changed back to my
Original identity
Which is Liu Xialai
What's our dad's name?
It's
Dad Liu
Where's our mom?
Aunt Liu
Good little brother
What's your father's name?
Father Liu
What's your mother's name?
Mother Liu
You've grown taller
Of course
Very tall
Truly family
This tall
Look how thin you've become
You should eat more
Eat more
Brother
I'm a millionaire
You don't have to do this job anymore
No
Big bro has his own life
Understood
Now working in cleaning
Big bro quite likes it
Good
You take care of yourself
No problem
Thanks, big bro
Thank you
I never imagined
This reunion
So perfect
Alright
Just being alive is enough
Good, just being alive is enough
Big bro, you sit first
A tough man's tenderness
Really nice
Big bro
Maybe you should rest first
Right
Then big bro won't need to avenge you
Big bro
I think you're highly suspicious
No
Brother, not at all
Let me tell you
This matter really has nothing to do with me
You do seem like an honest person
To be honest
Because I've known for a long time
He's the one who "killed" my brother
"murderer"
If I wanted to "kill" him
I would have done it long ago
Why would I choose today to "kill" him
And in such a way
That all of you could catch me
Impossible
What do you mean by that?
That all of you could catch me
Or rather, let these Sherlock Holmeses
catch me
I should say
Alright then
Then there's nothing else
Anything else you want to ask?
Nothing else
Okay
If there's nothing else then
I'll go to work
Alright
Okay
Brother Hao
Brother Hao, go back now
Brother Hao, I'm sorry
Brother, I'll see you tonight
Little brother
When you leave later
No need to clean this up
I'll take care of it later
Sorry about earlier
My apologies
Okay
Thank you, Brother Hao
I also remember our parents' names
You should have said so earlier
Father Guo, Mother Guo
Our family is
This Hao the cleaner is quite touching
He took the cleaning job to find his brother
But I think
Although he's desperate to find his brother
However
Installing surveillance cameras
in other people's homes
without permission
to spy on their privacy
is really crossing the line
That's really unacceptable
Right
It violates people's privacy rights
And using such methods
could easily lead to criminal acts
Yes
And what he said about
waiting for the right opportunity
No matter what
this is essentially fighting fire with fire
Exactly
Such approaches shouldn't be encouraged
Agreed
Who should we question next?
Can we search Xiaomei?
Can we investigate her?
Can we search?
Yes, we can
We can search
No
I mean interrogate her
Question her
Right, I'll have her brought in
Good
Song Huo often enters Xiaomei's place
when she's not home to move things
because she gets many packages
And Xiaomei
specifically mentioned in her videos
that
this delivery guy is very kind
and very helpful
She trusts Song Huo completely
She allows him
to enter her home
when she's away
to deliver packages
But who can prove
that when she's not home
Song Huo didn't enter on his own?
Let's get back on track
I've already unboxed this one
Let me unbox it for everyone first
It looks absolutely beautiful
And this...
is also a gift I bought for myself
to celebrate that I've finally
earned my first 500,000
She said she earned her first pot of gold
her first 500,000
500,000
But this definitely shows that
it demonstrates
Xiaomei is quite vain
This video reveals too much
personal private information
Right
If people with ill intentions see it
they would exploit it
They absolutely would
And then immediately after
another photo was posted
Judging by appearance
this should be Song Huo
Yes
That's why Fang Xiaomei
drew that mark on the clothes
Because in this investigation report
it's clearly photographed
There are two stripes on that clothing
So Xiaomei also has a "murder" motive
Of course she does
Because she believes
Song Huo might have "killed"
her beloved big brother
"Killed" her beloved Moonlight
Right
Come
Xiaomei even brought a quilt
Myself
Did you come by e-bike?
Xiaomei
Right.
How could you...
I told you...
If you have any questions for me...
you'd better be quick.
Because I'm about to start...
my live streaming time.
I need to go live now.
We're already live streaming here.
Look at your audience.
Ask quickly.
Go ahead and ask.
Come on, ask away.
You all...
Main interrogator.
You searched her place.
No, you searched her room.
What should we say...
How could you still...
Didn't I just tell you...
not to touch anything in my room?
What's wrong with you?
Xiaomei, look at us.
Stop looking at the surveillance behind you.
Very professional.
Yes, very camera-savvy.
Sorry.
Occupational habit.
As you all know...
I'm quite famous in the streaming world.
Xiaomei, are you close with Song Huo?
You two are always at home...
laughing and joking around.
You're "sick."
What nonsense are you spouting?
The surveillance shows...
We all saw it.
Aren't you an internet streamer?
Don't you always do live sales?
I don't do live sales.
Those are all free.
They're all giveaways.
Right.
Exactly.
Why is this woman talking nonsense?
What's your relationship with Song Huo?
Yes, what's your relationship with Song Huo?
What kind of relationship?
No particular relationship.
He delivers goods.
He helps me pick up packages.
That's all.
Then why would you let him
when you're not home
enter your house?
Right.
Why did you give him your door code?
Exactly.
If I'm not home
and my package gets stolen at the door, what then?
Those are all things I bought
with my hard-earned money.
Isn't it safer to put them inside?
If you put them in your house
they'd be safe too.
You mentioned your hard-earned money -
how did you earn it?
Well,
Because we
do live streaming.
Yes.
Because I
No,
wait.
It's like this:
Part of my work
involves agricultural support livestreams,
but another part
includes taking some advertising jobs,
shooting some videos,
which brings in some income.
Your first
Your first 500,000 yuan -
how did you earn that?
Just by doing these things.
Exactly these things.
Yes.
The first time you
You should...
Let me change my tone.
The first time you
saw that hole on your door
the hole in the wall
how did you discover it?
I just noticed it one day when I came home
You didn't report it to the police after finding it?
I thought such a small matter
wasn't worth bothering the police with
But weren't you scared at all?
You two from Beijing Film Academy
What's going on?
What are you two doing?
Having a "magic duel" here, huh?
Because I was scared
Scared?
You were scared?
I was scared
So I called security
They helped me block it off temporarily
Told me to wait for materials
They'll fix it properly when the materials arrive
You didn't go in to check either?
Who would go in to check?
It's really strange
It must be something...
Who knows
Something scary inside
Who's "crazy" enough
to go in and look?
The six of us went in to check
Wait, hold on
Let me ask you first
This is your diary
Of course it was Bai Sanwan who found it
Has nothing to do with us
On Valentine's Day 2021
You and Cao Yueguang fell in love, right?
Right
And you say it so confidently
Then on February 14th the following year
He wanted to meet you
Why were you afraid to see him?
Is there a problem?
No problem.
Suffered quite a lot.
Is it because you hadn't had plastic surgery back then?
I've never had plastic surgery.
Can someone please control her?
Alright
I got work done
How is it?
I had procedures done
I'm sorry
You blame me for your procedures?
Of course, we shouldn't mock
These things are
Everyone has the desire to look beautiful
I think it's perfectly normal
The previous issue was
Why haven't you met him?
First
I think the time we've spent together
Hasn't been long enough
It's been a whole year
We just talk on the phone every day
I'm a conservative woman
So you gave your door passcode
To Song Huo?
Second, because before
Weren't there always those
Very strong filters?
I didn't want him to discover
What I really look like
But actually I shouldn't have done that
You should be more confident
There's one question though
Did you ever notice before
Whether Song Huo wore a watch or not?
I noticed something.
Seriously, that was way too much.
Let me tell you,
my boyfriend
previously mentioned
he was going to give me a watch.
He even sent me pictures of it,
so I knew exactly
what that watch looked like.
This is strange,
because just the other day I saw
it on Song Huo's wrist.
Moreover,
later his father told me
he had "died."
I was devastated,
so heartbroken
that I spent a fortune
hiring a private investigator
to look into this matter.
He said he investigated
my boyfriend and Song Huo
and found they had a physical altercation.
Then I noticed
that person was wearing
that exact outfit.
The next day,
when Song Huo delivered a package to our place,
I saw him in that same clothing
and he was wearing that watch too.
And we also discovered
Look
In your diary
You also noticed
Song Huo must be
the one who "killed" Cao Yueguang
But this watch
why is it with you now?
Because Song Huo "died"
Song Huo "died"
Then I picked it up
He "died" in that hole in your room
Seriously?
So you discovered Song Huo
wearing what appeared to be your boyfriend's
watch that was meant for you
So you...
Not just appeared to be
He was actually wearing that exact watch
So you confirmed
that was indeed your boyfriend's watch
So your boyfriend "died" again
So you kept relaxing him
making him lower his guard
letting him come and go freely in your room
so you could find the right moment
to "kill" him
Right?
That's not the case
Before my boyfriend went missing
he could freely come and go
from my room
She knew Song Huo first
Because Song Huo always helped her with deliveries
That's why Song Huo could enter her room
and see her phone
Right
That's how he saw Yueguang had five million
Exactly
Then he could rob Yueguang
Right?
You discovered
On the 15th
Cao Yueguang
was likely murdered
and all his money was stolen
And you found that his murderer
was most likely Song Huo
Yes
So now you hate Song Huo
Isn't that right?
You hate him to death
Since you hate him
did you consider killing him?
Of course, I wanted to kill him
Then tell us specifically about your crime process
How did you kill him?
What do you mean?
You hate him
but you chose not to act
Yet he's around
in your daily life
Right
You could easily have acted
Revenge is a dish best served cold
This is just the beginning
This morning
Between 10:30 and 11:00
Where were you?
After I finished my makeup this morning
Around 10:30
I was planning to go live
But
Around 11:00
I noticed there was a sudden power outage
Then I heard a cat meowing
Im terrified of cats
So I ran outside
And then I ran into you
So you left your room at 11:00
Right?
Yes
Xiaomei
Do you know whose phone this is?
It's mine.
Can't you see my photo on the lockscreen?
Why do you have so many...
...home door passcodes?
This is because...
This belongs to Song Huo.
After I found out,
I thought he was suspicious,
so I saved the pictures.
Isn't this yours?
It is mine.
Why do you have two phones?
Is it abnormal to have two phones?
One is for livestreaming,
the other is for daily use.
Do you have any other questions for me?
I need to go live now.
Did you know
that Moonlight has actually been protecting you all along?
Moonlight "died."
No,
he didn't "die."
He didn't.
What do you mean?
Look here.
Hello.
Do you know me?
How would I know you?
Didn't we just meet today?
My name is Liu Xialai.
I don't even know your names.
Now,
I sent you a WeChat message.
To tell you
that I changed from Cao Yueguang to Liu Xialai.
I had plastic surgery.
I'm coming to see you now.
You're really strange.
I had plastic surgery, and so did you?
Are you "crazy"?
You're crazily imitating me, aren't you?
And what's really strange is
why are you pretending to be my boyfriend?
You're really such a weird person
No,
I previously transferred a lot of money to you
Are you saying that
we had some financial transaction?
Let me tell you,
I'm going to report this to the police now
What do you mean?
No,
I have records
Wait, let me explain for her
It was Song Huo
who made you think it was her
but actually it wasn't her
You've been communicating with Song Huo all along
So all your money went to Song Huo
That 120,000 is with Song Huo
Song Huo was deceiving both sides
Right
I didn't know
I genuinely didn't know
I don't even understand what you're talking about
I wouldn't ask you for money
This is very strange
Do you have anything to prove it's really you?
There's one thing that can prove it
This watch
I was the one who bought this watch
It's one of a unique pair
Because this watch was custom-made
and you can only customize one pair in a lifetime
I was really looking forward
to seeing this watch on your wrist
I do know about the watch
Isn't that right?
I also know your favorite song
called "A Beam of Light in the Darkness"
Am I right?
Wait a moment, stop singing for now.
Turn it off first.
The watch first, right?
Yes.
You don't want money, you want the watch.
So do you believe I'm Cao Yueguang now?
Put the watch on first.
That's how it is.
Let's sing now.
That's right, it's me.
Please sit down first.
Alright, okay.
Because he called me before.
Heard this song.
I thought the voices sounded somewhat similar.
But I...
I am...
Mei Mei Planet.
My WeChat name is Moonlight Treasure Box.
So it really is you.
Who else would it be?
Well then.
I believe you.
Thank you.
So you now have five million.
That's correct, yes.
Let's just take these five million.
And live off it for life.
Now I need to think about it.
Wait a minute.
You're saying...
Now that this person is "dead".
And then...
The suspects could be you.
Your girlfriend.
Or your brother.
Basically someone from your family.
Just your family.
So, one person from your family.
Must be named as the "killer".
For this case.
This is how it ends, right?
That's correct.
Either sacrifice a family member for justice.
Or sacrifice your "wife" for justice.
Right, or sacrifice yourself.
End it yourself.
Xiao Mei.
Did you know there's...
Another girl in your family?
Don't scare me.
Our home is so small.
How could another girl live there?
It's just that after you leave.
There's another girl present.
Are there any of your colleagues
or anyone else
or perhaps your password
other than Song Huo knowing it
does anyone else know?
I don't know
Then who is that woman?
I think we've asked enough questions.
Let's go back, Xiaomei.
You really scared everyone today.
I'll head out first.
Have a good livestream.
Good luck.
Remember to send me gifts.
Bye.
I thought you didn't want gifts?
Everyone, this is Xiaomei.
Actually, we later discovered...
that a series of incidents...
were all because of Song Huo.
He saw...
some of Xiaomei's private information.
Right.
Actually, Xiaomei didn't do a good job...
protecting her own privacy.
There are many new apps nowadays...
that when you click on them...
your personal information...
might get violated.
It gets leaked.
That's right.
Don't click on these apps.
Yes.
But there's another thing...
The abandoned electrical room...
First, it was definitely abandoned.
Suddenly...
Thank you.
it was activated.
Then we discovered...
that abandoned electrical room...
was deliberately set up.
Because behind the door...
we found a wire...
that could connect to the doorknob.
Right.
So that "killer"...
didn't need to be there at the time.
Right.
He just needed to set this up in advance...
and that's it.
When we were on the sixth floor...
wasn't the hallway also locked?
Don't be like this
Bro
The person who locked the stairwell
and the one who turned on the abandoned power room's switch
might be the same person
The electrician said it like this
He said the three circuits are independent
But all three circuits
can be controlled from the first floor
The hallway lights
Is it possible that earlier
were already turned off from the first floor
When Song Huo touched the door handle
it caused an electric short circuit
Which then led to
all the sixth floor lights turning off
But when the old man went to fix it
He clearly fixed everything
but found the hallway lights were still off
Then he learned that
that circuit had been turned off on the first floor
Right, we don't know who
turned off the hallway lights
or when they were turned off
But ordinary people wouldn't go to
the abandoned power distribution room
So Song Huo must have been lured there
Right
So did you two arrange to meet at the power room?
No, he didn't arrange to meet me
Then who was Song Huo meeting?
Let's go take another look, okay?
Okay
Come on
Let's go, everyone
Song Huo, how did you "die"?
Search for evidence
Where to?
Sixth floor
To Xiaomei's place
Let's go
There's another suspicious point
One more doubt remains
You're acting very strange today
Do you have multiple personalities?
Tell me
Are you all crazy?
You're saying the exact same things as Fang Xiaomei
You two must be connected
There's something going on between you
You're "sick"
What nonsense are you spouting?
Fine
We've come back to
Fang Xiaomei's room
This is a hidden camera
See? Right here
Yes, this is what captured it
This is the camera Hao the cleaner placed
Covered with this
Right, only this was on the sofa at the time
Look
Check for any clues
See how that person
appeared in this room
What's that sound?
Out of power
That's a phone dying sound
Whose phone died?
She has another phone
She's got a second phone
Ventilation duct
Here
Where?
Bro, slow down
I think
It's inside here
It must be here
There's a camera here
Another camera
Here's a camera
There's a passage inside
A very wide one
Then how do we get up?
We really can't climb this
There's a pair of jeans
Maybe we need to find the entrance
There's definitely a door
I think it's here
Are you sure there's something there, right?
Don't you...
Don't come rushing down
It definitely is
Alright, I shouldn't look then
I think...
Okay
I'm not worthy
Good
I don't deserve it
Outside
Check if there's anything in the hallway
No, look for...
Something like a vent opening
Ventilation duct
There's nothing back here
The entrance to the ventilation duct
It might be in the abandoned passageway
The secret passage is inside. Let's go.
How do you all get in like this?
Because we're small enough.
Ventilation duct
I don't think it's here
It might be over there
Then it's here
Where?
Here
Aim for that
Poke it with a stick
It can be opened
We need to go up
We'll need something to step on to get up
Do we need a ladder?
Yes
Ask Xiao He if he has a ladder
I'll contact Xiao He
Sealed in February 2012
You...
Are you guys inside?
Are you there?
Here
I've brought the ladder
Thank you so much
Here
Come help us pass it
It's big, be careful
Okay
Come on
Be careful
Watch your fingers
It's fine
Great
And this ladder
You need to fully extend it to be stable
Okay
Alright, be safe
So, who's going up?
Me
Going up
Did you give him the flashlight?
Yes.
There's a light.
We have a light.
Is it big?
Quite big.
When this camera's battery is low,
it will emit intermittent alert sounds.
Please charge it promptly.
Do you have a phone?
Even recording a video would work.
We'll give you all the clues
we can find first.
Look what this is.
Steamed buns, shaomai.
"I'm So Hungry" order.
It's a food delivery order.
What Mei?
Ms. Something-Mei.
Xiaomei.
Apartment B120.
Throw it! Let go!
Clothes.
Does this lead somewhere else?
Yes.
Where else does it lead to?
It can go to other places.
This looks like a bedroom
Don't you think?
Yeah, he sleeps here
It really does look like a bedroom
Check that piece of paper
See if there's anything underneath
Nothing there
Nothing on the edges either
Kinda gives off that "Parasite" vibe
What's below this?
It's directly
the hallway
stairwell
Got it, this is the spot
Where exactly are you?
We're in the stairwell
Right outside the door
the hallway
So he needs to keep
the hallway lights off
so he can escape through here
and won't be caught on camera
because the hallway lights are off
Exactly
Is this as far as you can go?
This is the end
Already at the end
Alright, we can go down now
Let's go
You can close this door
I can do it
Don't close the door
Keep it open
We need to leave it open as a marker
Leave it open
Should we go down?
Anything left up top?
No, we checked
Just confirming someone lives there
There are laid-out boards up there
Cardboard sheets
It's like
they're squatting here
Like a temporary living space
Actually, not temporary
They might actually live there
What was written on that paper just now?
You mean the takeout order?
One steamed bun and one shaomai
Three yuan
Deliver to
B120
Basement level 1
Let's go to basement level 1
Let's take a look at B120
Then let's go out
Is there nothing left in this area?
Let's go
Was there anything else suspicious earlier?
Nothing
Just that piece of clothing and the takeout order
Did you take the takeout order?
Took it
Got it
Whose clothes are these?
Let's check if there's anything in the pockets
I've already checked
Nothing left
Nothing at all
We're collecting evidence very thoroughly now
We've improved
At least we're not like last time
There is
Keys
There are keys
I told you
Good thing we took the clothes
B120
This is my first time here.
A hub for trends.
There's another section.
My noodle shop will open soon.
You should come when it opens.
B120
Does this move?
I suspect it's a real person.
I also think it looks like a real person.
What are you doing?
I knew it!
Take this! (kicks)
What's going on?
Angry
Thank you
Scan the code to get a free power bank
So you're just giving us power banks, right?
You want to hug her, don't you?
You want to hug Song Piaoliang
Give her a hug
Not you
Not me
You want to hug Bai Sanwan
He wants to hug Bai Sanwan
Come here
You only hug Sanwan
This means you two are suspects
What are you talking about?
Are you Miao Miao?
You're Miao Miao's personification, right?
Yes, he is Miao Miao
Goodbye
Bye bye kitty
Love you
He says he loves you all
Fragrant dried fruits
Delicious and affordable
Family tradition screen protectors
Boss, apply one for me
Here
This way
This is B120.
But there's one problem.
First, this lock
is practically useless
But the bottom part is broken, see?
Yes, indeed
What kind of place is this?
I "killed" Zhou Keke by dropping him
It's open
Do not approach the abandoned power distribution room
Disobedience will lead to "death"
Song Huo has "died"
One link leads to another
Are you or aren't you Fang Xiaomei?
I am Fang Xiaomei
You look like that person
She's a twin
The real and fake Monkey King
Quick, restrain her!
There's something wrong with her
The positions of the two rooms are
Exactly the same
This is incredible
This too
New place
Come
There's a secret passage here
This is Hao Baojie's house
This is my home
There's something in here
There's something inside
Look at this symbol
The one that threatened us
You all
Will all
"Die"
Hao Baojie
The evidence is irrefutable
The door outside is already locked
We can't get out now
This door is locked
This
Chase him!
He went down.
Exclusively on Tencent Video
New episodes every Thursday, Friday, and Saturday at 6 PM
Members get early access one week in advance
Every Saturday at 6 PM
Case Tracking in "Let's Solve It"
Every Sunday at 6 PM
Watch bonus content: "Apartment No. 11 Diary"
Midweek teasers, behind-the-scenes, and short clips
Daily updates to binge
A 360 deep dive into Apartment No. 11
Hurry and open Tencent Video
Search for "Let's Solve It"
Join the "Bulldozers" for immersive detective adventures