At noon on May 6th,
I received a message from my ex-girlfriend whom I hadn't seen in a long time,
from Jiajia.
I hurried to the Detective Theater on the eighth floor of the apartment to meet her.
After meeting her and getting ready to leave the theater,
I noticed the lights in the hallway had gone out.
I slowly felt my way out in the dark.
But in the pitch-black corridor,
I ran into some new neighbors.
They seemed to be heading in another direction.
I was curious too,
so I slowly followed them.
But I unexpectedly discovered
that Detective, who looked a lot like my girlfriend,
had been "assassinated."
It was only our first day living in this apartment,
and already two people had "died"?
To find out the truth,
we started investigating.
We discovered inside the theater
there were four identical auditoriums.
Between the auditoriums,
they could be connected by one-way doors.
But one door was off-limits.
This door couldn't be used.
Why?
We also found
the theater staff room.
Using the information on the "True or False Love" poster,
the information provided there,
I used the premiere date to unlock the door's code.
Inside we found
Zhenzhen's dating schedule
and boyfriend ranking list
Also discovered Zhenzhen was using multiple identities
to secretly date different boyfriends
With this boyfriend she was Tongtong
This one was Maomao
And shockingly, I was on this list too
That's me!
Could the girl who "died" in the theater
named Zhenzhen
actually be my ex-girlfriend Jiajia?
We compared
the theater's audience counter records
with the photos
of boyfriends in the staff room
for cross-reference
We discovered Cao Yangguang
Screenwriter Song
as well as me and Bai Sanwan
were all likely at the theater
during the time of the incident
So the four of us became
suspects in this case
Later everyone came to my room
Unfortunately
my "escort 1000 girls home" project
was exposed to everyone
Though my intentions were good
they still misunderstood me
"You're not from security"
And then there's Jiajia
who exposed my immature
novel to the public
leading to me being cyberbullied
This was also discovered
After the cyberbullying
I drew an X on her photo
I admit I hated Jiajia
That's why I marked
her photo with an X
Later we went to Bai Sanwan's room
to continue investigating
We learned that he and Zhenzhen
had briefly dated three years ago
Bai Sanwan, for Zhenzhen's sake
indirectly caused his brother's "death"
He rode this bike to deliver food
and then had an accident
Later, the two broke up.
Zhenzhen ranted online,
calling Bai Sanwan a "scumbag."
"Bai Sanwan, you scumbag!"
This year,
Bai Sanwan and Zhenzhen got back together.
It seemed they had reconciled,
but Bai Sanwan discovered
Zhenzhen wanted to expose him
for "causing the death" of a brother.
Bai Sanwan suspected Zhenzhen had been deceiving him
and wanted to ruin him.
He just wanted
to see her for who she really was,
what kind of person she truly was.
Later,
in the audience counter's
surveillance footage,
Zhenzhen was seen changing outfits
and entering different theater rooms.
But after entering Bai Sanwan's theater,
she never came out.
At that moment,
we spotted in the surveillance footage
a suspicious person
nervously running out of the theater.
A look at the face—
isn't that Teng Zhongjie?
Highly suspicious.
From then on,
the suspects in this case
became:
Cao Yangguang,
Screenwriter Song,
Bai Sanwan,
me,
and Teng Zhongjie.
This season will unfold over eleven weeks
telling the stories that occur in Apartment No. 11 of Tui City
Six players will move in as new residents
and live in Apartment No. 11
They will be drawn into bizarre cases
By forming the "Apartment Detective Team"
they'll visit different floors
befriend various long-term residents
solve their own identity mysteries
and uncover secrets behind the cases
The first six cases
will unlock one new resident's story each week
The complex relationships between new and old residents
will also come to light
Starting from the seventh case
all storylines will intertwine
As the truth is gradually revealed
every choice made by the new residents
will influence the story's direction
and the final outcome
In each case
the detective team must at the crime scene
identify the "victim"
and based on clues
pinpoint relevant suspects
Note:
Suspects aren't limited to Apartment No. 11 residents
or visitors
Suspects might even exist within the detective team
After gathering suspects
the team will interrogate them
and re-examine based on testimonies
finally voting to identify the "culprit"
Only the actual "culprit" can lie
Only by finding the real "murderer"
do players win
Players who vote correctly
receive a golden key
If a player is the "murderer"
and escapes successfully
they'll receive a golden key
Movie viewing backend system
Okay, watch
Room 3
Who is this?
Someone wants to enter
Me
Teng Agency
Ran out
Panicked
Scared, Teng the agent
What did you see inside?
What did you find?
And you clearly looked frightened
Baoyou, can you hear me?
This is Xiao He.
I can hear you.
How's your investigation going?
The suspects you wanted to question,
Cao Yangguang and Screenwriter Song,
I've already located them.
They'll be here shortly.
Since they all want to clear their names,
except for the "real culprit",
the others probably won't lie.
Moreover, they might have
evidence related to the case on them.
You can search them during questioning.
If there are suspects among you,
you can question each other too.
I've prepared the property's
monitoring room in the basement.
You can conduct
the interrogations there.
Additionally, I've set up a camera
so that
we can preserve video evidence
to hand over to the authorities.
Come to the property monitoring room quickly.
Please ask your questions
Excuse me,
First, why did you go to that room?
Going to that room...
When I was taking the elevator,
I saw Sanwan's figure
who seemed to have gone up
After that,
I wanted to go up and check
what Sanwan was doing there
About what time did you go up?
When I went up,
it should have been around 1:46
We had agreed to meet at 1
so I had already gone up at 1
I saw you at 1 o'clock
Then I did other things
After forty minutes,
you came up again
So I went up
After going up,
I opened the theater door
I turned left down the dark hallway
and felt my way forward
After about ten steps,
I felt something round
like a doorknob
After going up, you walked left about ten steps?
Yes
That was Room 1
But the video shows
he entered Room 3
But I didn't know which door number it was
Okay
After opening it, I went inside
After entering
I felt there were steps
So I walked down following them
Then I felt
I stepped on something sticky
Meaning those footprints on the ground
Were left by you
That's possible
But when I entered
I maintained my professional habits
I was wearing shoe covers when I entered
Indeed
So when I was leaving
Between the first and second doors
I carefully picked up the shoe covers
Rolled them up
Put them in a black bag
After pushing open the second door
I walked to the elevator
And threw them in the trash bin
Then I went down
After going down, I thought
About going to see so-and-so
To play with their dog for a while
While playing with the dog
I heard you screaming upstairs
That's roughly what happened
At around 1:40 something,
Zhenzhen "died."
There's one major issue:
Why is it that
the "blood" he found in Room 3,
but when we went there,
Room 3 had no "blood."
There was no "blood."
Only Room 1 had "blood."
You only went to this one room, right?
Right.
So,
so I think
there must be something wrong with the rooms.
Do you have any more questions?
If there's nothing else to ask,
should I just go sit back down?
Is there anything else you'd like to confess?
Anything you'd like to volunteer?
Then why didn't you tell us earlier?
You've been to that room.
I think
this doesn't seem that important.
After being in contact with her for so long,
did you notice any
significant changes in her personality?
Zhenzhen, I don't know her.
She's your tenant.
Yet you don't know her either.
No, I don't.
I rarely go upstairs.
Because usually
You see,
she's rented from me for three years.
All this time,
I've never once been to her place.
I can't appreciate
you young people's things.
If no one has
any more questions for me,
I'll go sit back down.
You can search me.
Body search.
Search Teng the agent.
Whatever.
Go ahead.
Got anything?
Just got these today.
Freshly collected.
Just some lousy membership cards.
Really.
Carrying all my belongings.
Sorry.
What's this?
Coupons.
This is my cafeteria meal card.
And this?
And a love letter.
Love letter?
This letter is from my sister Xiaomian
to Sanwan.
"My love for you"
Not Sanwan,
it's Sanhaiwan.
"I love your face,"
"with nose and eyes,"
"I love your noodles,"
"perfect texture, not sticky."
"I love riding with you,"
"perfect pace, super comfortable."
"Your bowl"
"can hold"
"my bowl of noodles?"
Where did you see this?
Then why isn't it with me?
It's with you.
My sister gave this to me
to pass on to you.
Just sit there then.
So Xiaomian likes her boss.
That's what this means, right?
You're having workplace romance?
No, we're not together.
Your sister is Xiaomian, right?
Yes.
Xiaomian likes Sanwan, right?
Xiaomian does like Sanwan.
She even
because of Sanwan,
quit her favorite job
to work at his noodle shop.
So with the "deceased" Zhenzhen,
do you have any grudge?
I have no grudge against Zhenzhen.
If you insist on talking about grudges,
I think my younger sister
is the one who holds a grudge against Young Master Guo.
She's angry that Xiao Guo follows her every day.
What she really wants is Sanwan to accompany her daily.
But Xiao Guo just happens to be that annoying obstacle.
So my sister never gets that chance.
No,
I wasn't talking about my sister.
I'm asking if it's possible
that for your sister's sake,
you would...
Then I'd have to "eliminate" Zhenzhen.
Because
he and Zhenzhen are a couple.
I haven't...
I haven't even solved my own problems yet.
Why would I take such a big risk
just to "eliminate" her?
Brother Teng,
Wait, then my situation is really strange.
I've actually been
quite good to Xiaomian.
I've never harassed her.
Actually, it's precisely because you're too nice to her
that she finds you annoying.
But why would she take this matter about me
and make it public?
Starting online bullying against me?
I must clarify this for my sister:
I just called her,
While she does find you annoying,
she didn't cyberbully you.
She didn't expose you
or reveal anything about you.
But it's already online
On that "Anti-Scum" alliance page
He's already listed there
Xiaomian definitely didn't do that
Xiaomian never lies to me
So that means Xiaomian didn't post it
Then it must be
Someone else using Xiaomian's account
Who would use Xiaomian's account?
It's possible
Zhenzhen used Xiaomian's account
Love rival
I don't think that's the case
Because during this period
Zhenzhen and I were still together
Right, you were with Zhenzhen
And Xiaomian likes you
Zhenzhen found out Xiaomian likes you
So she wanted to ruin me
What kind of logic is that?
You see
You wouldn't have guessed
No, I wouldn't
But Zhenzhen figured it out
Zhenzhen thought of it
Only then would it make sense
Actually, it's not very useful
No, I don't think Zhenzhen has
Any emotional
Feelings of love or jealousy
She just wants to
Eliminate all the "scumbags" in this world
She was once hurt by a "scumbag"
And now fears all "scumbags"
So the sequence must be
First you got exposed as a "scumbag"
Then Zhenzhen might want to expose you
Zhenzhen being with him
Must be because she found out
About him stalking Xiaomian
Right, but how did she know?
Then I think our current evidence
still isn't being examined thoroughly enough
I feel that
the computer we just looked at
still
wasn't examined carefully enough
Who can bring it over?
I'll go
You go
Kewuku
Sorry for the trouble
Okay, no problem
Thank you
Thank you for your honesty
It's my duty
To help everyone solve their problems
I also want
to find the real "culprit"
If it weren't for you
we wouldn't have come here
I have a small goal
to make my apartment's
occupancy rate reach 100%
I don't want any wrongful cases here
affecting my occupancy rate
Come
Let's take a look at this first
Thank you
The forum?
Look
Stalker
Posted by Xiaomian?
Then Zhenzhen replied below
Saying "Don't worry sisters"
"I'll help you get back at that scumbag"
See, she only did this after seeing
that he's a scumbag
That's why she did this
Yes, exactly
That's the sequence
Everything follows this order
Probably not Zhenzhen either
Then look
January 11th
The first one is you
The white one is
February 22, 2020
Who's the most recent?
The latest is
This real-name report
Right
This is February 3rd
February 3, 2022
Cao Tongzhuo
When was the screenwriter exposed?
The screenwriter wasn't exposed
The screenwriter hasn't been exposed
She didn't get to expose the screenwriter yet
Right
The call was made on May 3rd
Saying "Don't forget"
our previous agreement
"Don't interact with other guys"
Which was just yesterday
So the screenwriter is also suspicious
Because before it was posted
They could have stopped her
Right
I just want to ask about the screenwriter
If you don't obey
you'll be punished
I think we should question those two
First
Okay
Screenwriter Song first
Hello, President Ma
Come, Screenwriter Song
Please, this way
Over here
Don't ask for more money
"The Qiao Family's Descendants"
I've already sold it to Tencent Video
Be serious
What are you doing?
I have many things to attend to now
What exactly do you want?
What's this really about?
Judging by appearances
You don't have that much business either
Phone
Give it to me
There should be records, right?
Yes, hand over the phone
Let's see who you're calling
Help us search him, okay?
Okay
Nothing here
On my person
Look
This is all I brought today
Right
This is the same
Exactly the same?
Mine is identical
Then the Tencent producer
Contract
I'll send you the contract to review
Let's schedule time to discuss details
Sold "The Qiao Family's Descendants"
to Tencent
Check the time
This afternoon
1:04
Successfully registered as
Congratulations
You have successfully registered as
a member of the forum's "Anti-Scum Men" Alliance
group member
Your login username is Xiaomian
Don't mess around
You're Xiaomian
You are Xiaomian
Why are you impersonating Xiaomian?
Why impersonate my sister?
And even expose me?
You even said
Let me tell you all
Five months ago
when I first started pursuing Jiajia
he was also pursuing Jiajia
so I began observing him
following him
He stalked Xiaomian
and many other girls too
You stalked me too, right?
I was observing
You actually stalked me?
This wasn't stalking you
I was protecting Xiaomian
What's Xiaomian to you?
Why would I protect Xiaomian?
Weren't you pursuing Jiajia?
You've made enemies with both Jiajia and him
Yet you still want to protect Xiaomian
You're no saint either
He just wants to
I was afraid he'd harm other girls
He's trying to achieve his goal indirectly
So who is Jiajia anyway?
Jiajia
is the one he likes
She's my ex-girlfriend
She's my girlfriend
Jiajia is Zhenzhen
Zhenzhen
Who is Zhenzhen?
Jiajia is Zhenzhen
How is that possible?
My girlfriend's name is Jiajia
How can she be called Zhenzhen?
Have you been to this building today?
Yes.
What time?
I received Jiajia's WeChat message at noon.
What time at noon?
Around 12 o'clock.
She asked to meet at 1 PM.
At Theater 4 of Zhenzhen Theater.
Did you see her?
I entered the theater at 1 PM.
Waited a while before she arrived.
When she came,
she was wearing that outfit I really like -
the retro Hong Kong style.
But strangely,
she forgot she was the one who asked to meet.
Haven't we already settled this?
Why did she want to meet again?
So I didn't even get the chance
to discuss the plagiarism issue.
She just left.
So nothing was resolved.
Right.
Which theater did she ask you to meet in?
Theater 4.
After you entered,
did you turn left or right?
About how many steps?
Who remembers that?
Who remembers such details?
Why would I remember?
Because you're our gold medal administrator
During your meeting
did you experience a sudden power outage?
No
When your meeting ended
when you came out
was the building in a blackout?
When I entered the theater
the corridor lights were on
But when I came out
the corridor was dark
Don't know what happened
Do you remember what time you came out?
Phones weren't allowed in that theater
When I got my phone back after leaving
it was already 1:25
So you just met briefly
and then left?
Yes
Jiajia has been acting very strange recently
Five months ago
when we first got together
she was always well-behaved and obedient
But ever since she changed to that new WeChat
and phone number
she's been hot and cold with me
and even threatened to break up with me
By the way
you mentioned this WeChat issue
I just remembered
Tell her
not to forget
the agreement between you two
What agreement?
Isn't it about writing "The Qiao Family's Descendants"?
That was our joint creation
Weren't you writing
"Charlotte's Troubles"? No?
It's called "So Annoying"
"So Annoying"
That was plagiarizing his work
Yes, he copied it
I wouldn't call that plagiarism
That's called homage, understand?
Homage
The tribute only differs by four words
That still counts as tribute
Then
If she exposes your tribute act
and talks about it
exposes you
You'd punish her, right?
How would you punish her?
"Kill" her?
I didn't "kill" anyone
Then what's the punishment?
I never actually planned anything
Just empty threats
Right
After she changed her WeChat
you had a ten-minute call
What was that call about?
Just to confirm
whether she was really Jiajia
After confirming
she was indeed Jiajia
Don't know what happened
but she's like this now
What was she like before?
She used to be very obedient
a very compliant girl
24/7 without stopping
Suddenly
she turned into an ice-cold girl
Basically
The Jiajia you saw in Room 4
was she the Jiajia you knew
or a stranger?
It was the changed Jiajia
You saw a Jiajia too
I also waited before seeing her
We both waited a while
and barely spoke
She just said one thing to me
"Why did you ask me here?"
She asked you "Why did you ask me here?"
Yes
She asked me the same
She asked me too
"Why did you ask me here?"
I really shouldn't have gone up there today.
I should have gone to the foot massage place in the basement.
To get a foot massage.
My appointment was at seven.
Maybe we can go together later?
Do you have anything else to ask?
No, I need to go.
I'm very busy.
You're someone who...
spends every day paying tribute to classic works.
How busy could you possibly be?
Busy paying tributes?
Is there anything you'd like to confess?
What do you have to confess?
What could I possibly have to confess?
Alright then.
Screenwriter Song.
Why don't you go grab something to eat outside?
I'm really busy, please hurry up.
Honestly.
Fine, coming right away.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
The call was never hung up.
Indeed.
Actually, regarding Screenwriter Song,
I have a few things to say.
He essentially
plagiarized someone else's work.
It's a blatant
violation of someone's copyright,
an infringement.
Yes, absolutely.
It's intellectual property theft.
Calling it plagiarism
is giving him too much credit.
Of course.
Although he
published it,
he published it,
but it's pirated.
Just messed up four characters in the copying.
Right.
Should I call Cao Yangguang in now?
Okay.
Hello.
School heartthrob.
This is the school heartthrob.
Come on, let's do a pat-down first.
Do you agree?
Sure.
Take out your phone.
Do you have a phone?
Yes, I have a phone.
Hand over the phone.
The search is really thorough.
Inside pocket.
His wallpaper is really cool.
Let me treat you to
a lightly tea-scented,
refreshing grapefruit with real fruit bits - Grapefruit Four Seasons Spring.
Promise me you'll drink it
Real tea, real fruit bits,
and tell the truth.
Okay?
Okay.
Why am I so popular wherever I go
and well-liked everywhere
Thank you, miss
Maybe we should take it back
Take it back, don't let him drink it
I'm begging you
Please, I'm begging you
Spit it out
Sorry, I've already drunk it
Sorry
My apologies
What did you call him
An "average but arrogant guy," right?
No, a mama's boy
Mama's boy
This makes me so mad
Come on, what did he say
Yesterday at 5 o'clock
He said in the evening
What did you secretly photograph
Where are you
Let's meet and talk
Today at noon
Come to the 8th floor of Apartment 11 at 1 PM
Meet at Theater 3 of Zhenzhen Theater
I'll be waiting
Do you know this girl
Which girl
The girl who messaged you on WeChat
The name of the person who secretly photographed me
is Tongtong
Tongtong
Yes
She's one of my many admirers
When she filmed you
What were you doing holding those high heels?
I was cleaning the high heels
You think you were just cleaning them?
We need to show you the video
Were you really just cleaning them?
Do you enjoy cleaning both men's and women's shoes?
Not really
I prefer women's accessories
Because women's things
are always shiny
and particularly cute
Let me ask you
Whose were those red shoes?
Tongtong's
They were Tongtong's
What happened to those shoes afterwards?
Those shoes are now at my place
I kept them
So you're
this girl
Whether you like her or not
as long as you like her belongings
you can just take them, right?
That's right
Then why don't you go to
the women's department to clean them?
I think his behavior
is sneaky
If he's secretly taking others' belongings
for himself
then when the value reaches a certain amount, it's theft
But none of them said anything
Why are you in such a hurry?
Lock him up
Your attitude is completely inappropriate
Your attitude remains completely improper
I don't call it stealing
I'm just taking
They like me too
I'm just taking their things
No, this is illegal behavior
This matter has nothing to do with you
I don't want to say any more
Hey
Your earrings
So cute
You're so scary
I'll give you
I'll give you everything
Give you all
It's okay
Here you go
Anyway, the things I want
I always get in the end
What if you can't get it?
Up until now
There's nothing I couldn't get
If I can't get it
You just want to "kill" her, right?
That's not necessarily true
He made a call
At 1:15,
he called Tongtong
Tongtong didn't answer
Why did you call her
at that time?
Well,
it's because
at noon today,
Tongtong sent me a message
She asked to meet at 1:00
at Theater 3
So I went to Theater 3 at 1:00
I waited for a while
and Tongtong came to meet me
What did she say?
Because at that time I knew
she had secretly photographed me
Then
I was afraid she might know
my real secret
so I kept pressing her about it
"Do you know my secret?"
I know nothing.
She said she didn't know.
And,
she claimed I was the one who asked to meet.
I never asked to meet you.
Don't change the subject.
You're the one who invited me here.
Why did you ask me to come?
This is what puzzles me.
Because you've all seen the messages.
Clearly it was her who texted me
at noon.
But her expression seemed so genuine,
it made me feel
as if she truly didn't know
about this matter.
I really know nothing.
I won't bother you anymore.
Get out of my theater!
Then she ran out.
I quickly followed her.
When I reached the theater entrance,
I picked up my phone
and called her again,
but the call didn't go through.
What time did you meet her?
At 1 PM.
Right on time?
I arrived at the theater exactly at 1 PM,
but she came
a little later.
I'm not sure how many minutes later.
What time did she leave?
Fifteen minutes ago, right?
Definitely fifteen minutes ago.
He called at fifteen past.
Right.
Aren't you afraid
that she might reveal
your real secret?
This secret isn't actually
a real secret to me.
The reason I came to see her
was to find out
whether she really knows
my true secret.
If she finds out
about my real secret,
then everything is over.
Do you know what
then everything is over
your real secret
Why does he keep repeating himself
No, we just want to know
what the real secret is
The secret is out.
Can it still be called a secret?
That makes sense
Quite reasonable
You're right
But you know what
The person you like has "died"
The person I liked has "died"
Do you like Tongtong?
I don't like her
I just like the things she wears
Then let me ask you
In your opinion, this Tongtong
Is she
A little girl who clings to you
Or the very independent type
A strong woman
She seems more independent
I remember when she came to see me today
She was dressed all in black
And wearing black boots
Different from her usual pair that I love
The red high heels
Could there be more than one?
Twins
You mean
Two people
Yes, because remember
Xiao He mentioned before
Sometimes she would greet him
Other times she wouldn't
When I first met Zhenzhen
I thought she was
A very warm girl
But later sometimes
She would ignore me
Very strange
Could Zhenzhen be
There are two
Are there two Zhenzhens
Twins
I think that's possible
And I know
Jiajia has a
unique feature
Because when I first met Jiajia
I accidentally hit her
with a basketball and knocked her down
After she fell
her head hit the steps
I took her to the hospital for stitches
She has a scar
Jiajia is the one with the head scar
That "corpse" we saw earlier
did it have a head scar?
Didn't check
I forgot
No one mentioned it could be two people at the time
Do you know
if Tongtong has any scars?
Specifically if her head was ever injured
I genuinely don't know about that
When I met her
she was perfectly healthy
He only noticed the high heels
Were the high heels damaged anywhere?
The heels were perfectly intact
They looked beautiful to me
Do you have any interesting websites
you'd like to share with us?
Interesting websites
I'd like to share with you
Like those "scumbag" sites
Yes, the anti-"scumbag" alliance
What "scumbag" alliance?
I know absolutely nothing about that
I think this matter
is best left alone by you
This matter has nothing to do with the case.
Maybe we should put this aside for now.
Alright.
I think...
Although he did commit theft in this aspect...
He stole...
Right.
But he left at fifteen...
There's also proof that he was earliest...
If you've ruled out...
Because it was before that time...
Right, he definitely didn't do that.
So asking about...
his other private matters...
really isn't very meaningful.
He, since you're familiar with him anyway...
If in the future...
we live here...
and there are other secrets...
we can ask him again.
Then please go back now.
Okay.
You...
do you know me?
Do you know me?
Why do you know each other?
How do you know each other?
It's nothing.
No, it's nothing.
Does anyone have any other questions?
Alright.
Okay.
No questions here.
If there are no more questions, I'll take my leave.
My phone.
Here.
Here you go.
Thank you, miss.
This tastes really good.
Let's hurry up and go.
I don't want to investigate this case anymore.
Mom, I want to go home.
Guo Baoyou is coming
Let me tell you
He's the most suspicious one, actually Guo Baoyou
Zhenzhen "died"
Where did Guo Baoyou go?
You scared me
Stalker
This is Zhenzhen
I can explain
I can
What time did you see Jiajia?
Jiajia
It was around 12:50 for me
Definitely before 1 o'clock
Then I entered Room 2
Room 2
I waited for her quite a while
Quite a while
What time did you see her?
I can't say exactly when I saw her
I can only say
The time when I went out to check my phone
Because I didn't bring my phone into the room
Right?
When I went out to get my phone, it was 12:35
In the room, I saw her
After seeing her
I remember I spoke first
I said could you stop posting online
those terrible articles I wrote
and exposing them?
You deserve it
She didn't answer my question
Instead she asked me
She said
Why did you ask me to come?
I was surprised
You're the one who asked me to come
You tell me why I'm here
If there's nothing, I'm leaving
No
You...
She left, so I left too
Could it mean...
The one who made the appointment wasn't
I think it's very possible
No, so she (Zhenzhen) must definitely be
There are at least two people
If there are more, it might be three people.
Because there's also Tongtong.
Right, Zhenzhen.
Tongtong.
And
Mao Mao
Xiao Xiao
Jia Jia
Five
Yes, she (Zhen Zhen) has five names
But today, probably only three appeared
I think it's just two
Judging by personality
Because he (Guo Baoyou) was also said to be quite gentle
You also encountered two of them
The one I met was more independent
I've already mentioned this
Then we broke up
But after finally coming back
She (Zhenzhen) reverted to how she used to be
So
Therefore
Thus
Any more questions?
Nothing more to ask
The questioning is over
I think Brother Wan
You should at least
Go sit over there
Okay, no problem
You'll need to stay for a while
Because through the surveillance footage
we clearly saw
you entering that room
Come on, guys
Brother Bai
Tell us
The surveillance footage clearly shows
you went in when the lights were on
That's right
I admit
She went in when the lights were off
Then you came out when the lights were off
Correct
But she never came out
Yes, she never came out
But I really didn't see her
How long did you stay in the room?
Until I went out to make a call
From 1:00 to 1:50
you kept waiting for her in the room
Kept waiting in the room
Waited for fifty minutes
But you never saw her
Waited fifty minutes
before going out to call her
That's right
The lights were off when I left
But exactly when they went off
I don't know
But according to our footage
you must have seen her
Because after you entered
Zhenzhen went in
Brother Bai
You arrived at the theater at 1:00 sharp
Correct
Then you left at 1:50
Right
What time did you go upstairs?
I was outside at 1:35
I stepped on the "blood" at 1:46
So now we just need to
find a way to verify
everyone's departure times
This way
we can establish their alibis
What time did you leave Theater 3?
1:15
When I came out and got my phone
it was already 1:25
I went out and got my phone at 1:35
When I went upstairs
it should have been around 1:46
Okay
Here's how the timeline looks now
Song can be ruled out
because he left the theater at 25 past
Then Cao can also be ruled out
because he left the theater at 15 past
Guo can theoretically be ruled out too
because he left at 35 past
after getting his phone and leaving the theater
So if the crime occurred
between 35 and 45 past
then at that time
you were the only one present
making you the only one
with the opportunity to commit the crime
That's exactly what I'm talking about
I said it's because of Brother Teng
He was in Room 3
where the "bloodstains" were found
But when I went there
to my Room 1
there was nothing
I just checked the surveillance again
It clearly shows
him entering Room 3
And then
Wait, there's another issue
We just saw
the "dead" Zhenzhen
was wearing a red dress, right?
The Zhenzhen who entered your room also wore red
Right
Yes, that's what the camera shows
The camera shows someone in red entering
Right?
Logically speaking
she shouldn't have "died" in Room 3
because she was wearing all black, right?
Right
Yes, all the evidence points to him
I turned left down the dark hallway
After walking about ten steps
After going up, turn left
That's Room 1
But the video shows
him entering Room 3
Why?
The "blood" he found was in Room 3
But when we went there
there was no "blood" in Room 3
Only Room 1 had "blood"
So personally
I suspect
Could it be possible that
my room's location changed
or the camera's position changed
or the room numbers changed
There's something wrong
Look
First
You see
It's circular, right?
This is the inner ring
And this is the outer ring
Four rooms
Since there are two doors here
What I suspect is
When I enter Room 1
It starts rotating
It rotates
My Room 1 rotates to Room 3
And Room 3 rotates to Room 1
So when I enter
It rotates away
Then it rotates back
Zhenzhen enters
Let's assume
The central camera remains fixed
So this camera
Always faces this door
Which is Room 1
No matter what number it is inside
When it rotates here
For the camera, it's still Room 1
Yes, exactly
I think this line of reasoning should be correct.
Will it really rotate?
This room
It's difficult
Right
Although I don't have evidence
I'm just speaking from a logical perspective
to address this issue
So have you noticed
any changes inside?
Nothing at all
I think there are changes inside
One unlikely reason is
it must be outside
because after you enter
when you come out
its number wouldn't remain unchanged
since you wouldn't know
where it has rotated to
if you suddenly exit
you'd cause a complete numerical chaos
No
The room he first entered
might be Room 1
But what we saw
wasn't necessarily Room 1
when Zhenzhen entered.
Right.
If we assume this room
can rotate,
he entered Room 1,
but after rotation,
though we see the same door,
the interior has shifted.
There are two doors inside.
The camera
films the inner door, right?
No, it films the outer one.
The outer door.
But the issue is when he exits,
he still comes out
from this numbered door.
There might be a rotation,
then rotation back,
but how could it
perfectly time every
entry and exit moment
to coincide with
when it rotates back?
I have a suggestion
Let's go back to the crime scene
and search it again
About our earlier assumption
regarding the room's rotation
or the camera positions
or the door number placements
Didn't we have another box
that wasn't opened?
Right
And do you remember
we saw small footprints
cat's paw prints
Yes
And on that
that jar
was labeled as stage props
and was red
That puddle on the floor
was from the cat breaking it
Because the cat's footprints
led in that direction too
Right
What the cat broke
you said was dye, not "blood"
What you stepped in wasn't "blood"
Come on
Let's go take another look, okay?
Okay
Everyone should receive one
Wait a moment
Don't rush
I have a flashlight
It's probably just a tripped circuit
Wait a moment
I'll turn that light on
It's open
Zhenzhen just appeared
Zhenzhen was just here
Wearing a red dress
She didn't "die"
She never "died" at all
So there are two people
Zhenzhen just appeared
wearing a red dress
She didn't "die"
She never "died" at all
So there are two people
Let's go check the eighth floor again.
Is there anything else we need to look for?
Work schedule.
Where is the elevator's trash bin?
This isn't...
There are his shoe covers.
Let's first take a look at the crime scene
Crime scene
Check if there's a scar on the back of her head
Excuse me (for this intrusion)
Where on the head was hit by the basketball?
Quick, which one?
Isn't this quite clear? This one
This is the hairline
This one
No
I don't want to investigate cases with them anymore
No scar
Which means she's not Jiajia
Look at this
This one can move
This is it
I was just wondering what this thing is
I poked at it
A is A
And this part can rotate
She still lives here
There's a computer here
Theater performance props
Let's check another room
See if there's anything
Okay
Her A here
Let's go to number two first
Right
Pull this out
B
Look, it says B here
The previous one said A
This is B
Same thing
Are all the props identical?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven
There are seven
Same
Yes, seven in each room
Are the colors the same?
This panel is a different color
The last one was red
Right
Now it's yellow
The panels are different colors anyway
Come on, let's keep going
This one must be green
What color?
Blue
So they're primary colors?
Red, yellow, blue
Yes
What do you get when you mix primary colors?
Black
You can calculate that?
Yes
Red, yellow, blue
Red, yellow, and blue can be mixed
To make other colors
Right
Let's open D first
Green
She invited everyone to different rooms
Different colors
Right
Isn't this just ABCD?
What does this even prove?
It just proves they're different
First, I have another question:
Can this room rotate?
I think
the middle layer can rotate
I think it can rotate
I believe this wall with the door
can rotate
There's probably a gap in the middle
I got it
Let's stand on the carpet
and try pushing this thing
Right, because there's empty space there
Okay?
Come on, one person per side
One person each
Come on
One each
I'll count us down
No, wait
Hold on, bro
Do you want to go inside?
I'll go in
If you leave, you won't be able to reset it
Can I still get out?
Okay, let's rotate it first
Anyway, the inside is blue
We'll remember
Come on
Okay, three two one
Three two one
Three... two... one...
Wait a moment
Is it backwards?
Backwards, okay
Stand over here
Okay, one two three
Once more
One two three
It's moving
It's going
We can push it
It moved
It's moving
One two three
You go ahead
No
How long do we need to keep moving this?
One two three
One two
You call three
One two three
Pushed to the end
It's at the limit
This must be the end
I think there should be a switch
Let's look around
Here
One two three
Find anything?
There's a switch
Two switches
For corridor use only
This one's for theater use only
So one is controlled outside
And one is controlled inside
Corridor control switch
Don't stand here
What?
It can rotate anytime
Amazing
It's so impressive
The room isn't moving
It's this outer door that's moving
Moving this middle part
Right
That's why you can't feel it
Exactly
This is so cool
What did Zhenzhen do before?
Zhenzhen also studied some mechanics
Otherwise this thing would cost 500,000
Spending 500k like this is really impressive
We were just saying
No way
It couldn't be something like a turntable
Who didn't believe it earlier?
Sorry
Me
I'm sorry
We didn't think it would go that far
Wouldn't be done so extremely
Didn't expect it to be this extreme
Stop
It stopped
Just as I thought
So
Actually, it's already rotated
180 degrees
Guys
The moment to witness the miracle has come
Entering through Door 3 leads to Room 1 (A)
Still Room 1 (A)
If there really is a "killer"
We need to follow this rotation logic
To rearrange these people
Right
Bai Sanwan entered through Door 1, right?
Why does Zhenzhen go to every room?
Guo Baoyou
Door 2
Cao Yangguang
She asked to meet me at 1 o'clock
At Theater 3
At Hall 4 of Zhenzhen Theater
Zhenzhen must know about this
She came in and out
She could have orchestrated it herself
Here's how we see it
Right now, this is Room A
So I didn't enter Room A
This is Room 1
When I came to Room 1
it was completely undisturbed
So when he arrived
the room had already rotated to C
Right
Meaning you were in C
When you first came, you entered C
Exactly
I entered through Door 1
into Room C
Before you arrived
it had already rotated to that state, correct?
Yes
Then Teng Zhongjie entered through Door 3 into Room A
That's why he stepped on the "blood"
Correct
If we believe
he's innocent
then it must be Cao Yangguang across from you
who "killed" her
Because the only rooms
that were swapped were these two
Only these two were rotating
So actually
the "body" has always been
in Room 3 (Room A)
Because Room 3 (Room A)
was never entered by anyone
No one went in
Only our Teng Zhongjie entered once
Are you suggesting
that I did it?
It's not impossible
Teng Zhongjie was there alone
putting on an act by himself
Why would he
stand there
and try to lock us in?
With that overhead lighting
He looks suspicious
He looks like a "murderer"
This yellow button
is specifically for theater use
hasn't been used in the theater yet
Try pressing it
You take this
Three, two, one
Hold it down
It's moving outside
Brother Teng, pull the door down
Open the door and see
It's moving
It's rotating
There's something
Stop
Slow down
Agile movements
There's a note here
Here's a note
I feel like I'm in a martial arts movie
This is my younger sister (Jiajia)
Her recent favorite flavor
Many of her belongings
Have been replaced with related items
If I drink more of this
Will I understand her better?
Then what's inside this box?
There's a letter
The elder sister Zhenzhen is independent
And skeptical about love
While younger sister Jiajia
Always remains hopeful about love
Enjoying zero-distance romance
Using the sisters' two completely different
Perspectives on love
As inspiration
Younger sister Jiajia created
The play "True and False Love"
On stage
Zhenzhen and Jiajia
Play the same role
Through seamless costume changes
And special stage design
Creating complete surprise for the audience
That there are indeed two sisters
And the one who "died" wasn't Jiajia
Because there's no scar
It was Zhenzhen who "died"
And the key
We found the key to open that box
There was a box we didn't open earlier
Right
Let's open it
There's a note here.
Sister (Zhenzhen)
Four people want to meet you today.
1:10 PM
Cao Yangguang at Theater 1.
1:20 PM
Screenwriter Song at Theater 2.
1:30 PM
Guo Baoyou at Theater 4.
1:40 PM
Bai Sanwan at Theater 1.
Arrive on time.
This was written by Jiajia.
Right.
Then why are the meeting locations different?
Zhenzhen told me.
She asked me to come to Gate 1 at 1 PM.
I arrived at Theater 2 before 1 PM.
She scheduled with me at 1 PM.
To meet at Theater 3.
To meet at Theater 4 of Zhenzhen Theater.
Another big question is.
Zhenzhen didn't know.
That she scheduled with them at 1 PM.
To meet at the theater.
Why did you ask me to come here?
I didn't schedule with you.
She actually forgot she scheduled with me.
We just walked halfway around.
Let's walk around some more and see.
Right.
Brother Teng, close the door.
Brother Teng, come in.
It's fine, you guys keep looking around.
Let's go.
Then be careful, bro.
We can still look around.
The train has departed.
No need to see me off.
You came all the way to the station.
It was 1 just now, right?
Yes.
Outside the door was 1, correct?
Outside is 1.
Look
Everything
It's this door moving
The number is rotating
Right, only the middle
This middle door is moving
This bearing
This middle ring
There's another one
Another wooden crate
Quick
Did you get it?
Brother Teng
So near yet so far
Brother Teng thinks the subway journey isn't over yet
Combination lock
Four letters
I think it's related to what we just saw.
This one.
Because it says
This is my younger sister (Jiajia)'s
recent favorite flavor.
She's replaced many of her belongings
with things related to this.
If I drink more of this,
maybe I'll understand her better.
Then you should drink some.
Won't you understand her better if you drink it?
After drinking - "Ding!"
What's the password?
Could it be on the bottle bottom?
There's a poem on the bottom.
Immortals float jade cups,
Tea greener than moss.
True energy reaches the woods,
Fruits pierced by birds' pecking.
This riddle
must mean something.
So,
"Real Fruit Grains Ruby Grapefruit Four Seasons Spring"
Not only has light tea fragrance,
but you can chew real fruit pieces.
I feel refreshed after a sip.
Real tea, real fruit - truly delicious.
Now my thoughts are clear.
It might be...
It's "real tea real fruit".
The acrostic poem, right?
Let's try.
ZCZG
Real Tea Real Fruit
Awesome!
Well done!
Okay.
What could be here?
A bowl.
The bowl you gave her.
The bowl you gifted.
Zhenzhen.
You used this to confess to her.
Yes, when I confessed,
I said I'd make noodles for her forever.
This tablet computer.
Video
Take a look
Jiajia
I've told you a hundred times
Screenwriter Song doesn't love you at all
He's emotionally manipulating you
Controlling you, using you
"The Qiao Family's Descendants"
This script was clearly written by you
Yet it bears his name
What's mine is his
I'm no good at anything
No one will love me except him
I can't lose him
So don't try to stop me and Screenwriter Song
You've always had boys flocking around you since childhood
Love comes so easily to you
It's because of your presence
No one ever notices me
So don't ruin things between me and Screenwriter Song
As long as he loves me
I'm willing to give him everything
Look at yourself
See how pathetic you've become
Real love goes both ways
Not about control and suppression
If you keep being stubborn
You should know
I can make Screenwriter Song
just like other "scumbags"
lose everything and be disgraced
Don't push me
I'll do anything for Screenwriter Song
Zhenzhen has been running
the anti-"scumbag" alliance.
Right.
Who was the one that just "died"?
It was Zhenzhen who "died".
Yes.
She was working on that
Jiajia said,
"I'm capable of anything."
Jiajia is a love-struck fool, right?
For Screenwriter Song,
she turned against
her sister (Zhenzhen).
So,
there is no "killer" among us.
They couldn't even tell Zhenzhen and Jiajia apart.
They didn't know who to "kill".
Also,
"Real Tea Real Fruit Grapefruit Meets You"
I've fallen for
"Real Fruit Bits Red Grapefruit Four Seasons Spring".
I ordered two more boxes.
Here's the purchase record.
Where were they delivered to?
Have those two boxes arrived?
Did you take a kickback?
They've arrived.
I'll go check later.
The younger sister (Jiajia) actually always wanted
to understand her sister (Zhenzhen) better.
So she also followed her sister (Zhenzhen)
in buying this.
It wasn't the sister (Zhenzhen), right?
No.
There was a small note
from the sister (Zhenzhen)
wanting to understand the younger sister (Jiajia) better.
The sister (Zhenzhen) wanted
to understand the younger sister (Jiajia) more.
This is what the younger sister (Jiajia) recently
Arrest someone
Let me go
It's over for me.
My body still feels numb.
Me too.
That startled me.
No...
I'm sure I was scared by them
Why are you grabbing me?
Here, I'll grab her
You grab her
You do it
We need to talk with you
We caught up with her
Then let's go inside and talk.
Alright, let's go in
We'll go in first
Let's see what happens
You hold her
I'll hold her, I'll carry her
You hold her, don't let her run away
Carry her
Which room is this?
This is the one
Don't let her fool you
This person is full of tricks
Teng Zhongjie (proper noun)
That's quite frightening
That was really terrifying just now
This person runs pretty fast
Lower leg
Who shouted?
Just now,
it was you, bro.
You're the loudest.
It's over for me.
So beautiful
looks
You're really beautiful.
It'd be a shame if you "died."
"Died."
It's someone else
They're coming
You can sit down and talk
Three bowls
Keep an eye on that door over there—three bowls
I'll sit here
Right, we'll sit by this door
Don't let her escape
Do you know who I am?
Jiajia
You're Jiajia
That's right
Why were you in the surveillance room?
I noticed you were investigating
my sister Zhenzhen's "death"
So I wanted to hear what you've found
Why did you "kill" your sister Zhenzhen?
I didn't "kill" my sister Zhenzhen
You didn't "kill" your sister Zhenzhen?
Then how did your sister Zhenzhen "die"?
I don't know
Did you know your sister (Zhenzhen) "died"?
I only found out at 2 PM today
when I returned to the theater
I want to ask you
why did you tell your sister (Zhenzhen)
that four people would come
at different times today
to different rooms?
I never said that
You gave her a note
Then I understand
How many of you twins are there?
How many twins?
How many sisters are there actually?
Twins
How many sisters?
What note?
Let me see it
Is she trying to destroy evidence?
Cover her mouth
Give it to her
You hold it for her to see
How do you explain this?
Don't move
Put your hands down
Are you trying to stuff it in your mouth to eat it?
Did you write this?
The handwriting looks somewhat like mine.
But I didn't write it.
Did you arrange this meeting?
You didn't arrange it.
Not me.
I didn't write that note.
This person even forged her handwriting.
So you were the one who asked to meet me?
It wasn't me.
Because my phone was broken.
Your phone was broken?
My phone broke three days ago.
May 3rd.
Just got it repaired today.
The person Screenwriter Song contacted was...
Her sister (Zhenzhen).
That's why he said she became colder.
Right.
She also said three days ago she changed her number.
Added him with a new number.
Yes.
The "Anti-Scum Men" alliance website.
Did you create it?
My sister (Zhenzhen) created it for me.
Your sister (Zhenzhen) created it for you?
Before that...
On that website...
All the exposed "scum men"...
Did you know them all?
I haven't seen them all.
They all dated you?
No.
Have you forgotten we used to date?
I never dated you.
Weren't we the kind of friends who shared everything back then?
Crosstalk, skits, magic, acrobatics
Chatting about everything under the sun
But I only saw you as a friend
I wasn't in a relationship with you
You're overthinking it
That's more like it
You thought you were in a relationship
Because Sister Zhenzhen told me
You're a "pervert"
And told me to stay away from you
A real "pervert"
Good, keep your distance from him
I'm your fellow townsman
How could I be a "pervert"?
In China's entertainment industry
Is it easy to find fellow Tianjin people?
Tell me
about this matter
Is there anything else you want to confess?
The beginning of all mistakes
was because of
that bowl you gave me
The last day of 2019
You gave me a bowl at the theater entrance
Because before
I often saw
him coming to the theater for performances
But I didn’t know
he came for me
And that was also my
first time someone confessed to me
So
I accepted your confession
Do you remember when you confessed to me
what you said?
I'll make noodles for you for a lifetime
Right
But then what you said next
shocked me
You said
Thank you Zhenzhen
Yes
So it turns out
you've always liked
my older sister (Zhenzhen)
But I feel unwilling to accept this
Why is it that my sister (Zhenzhen) and I
look exactly alike
yet since childhood
no one has ever paid attention to me
So I concealed
my identity as the younger sister (Jiajia)
I admit I was selfish
but
because I felt
every day with you was so happy
that's why I hid the truth
I can understand
But
After we had been together for thirty-three days
you broke up with me
You said it was to make me
stay true to my independent self
But I didn’t want that
Later
you disappeared
I was heartbroken for a long time
and even fell into depression
Then I told my sister (Zhenzhen)
that you were a "scumbag"
So my sister (Zhenzhen) formed
an "Anti-Scumbag Alliance" for me
Then later
my sister (Zhenzhen) met you again
What I never expected was
this time
you fell in love with Sister Zhenzhen again
Sister Zhenzhen originally thought
that all my suffering
was caused by you
So she deliberately
approached you to get revenge for me
(no translation needed - continuation of previous line)
But unexpectedly
Sister Zhenzhen also fell in love with you
I originally intended
to clear up
the misunderstanding between you and Sister Zhenzhen
But
I never imagined
Sister Zhenzhen would suddenly "die"
So first I want to say I'm sorry
I feel a bit unnecessary
Please come back quickly
You can sing them a theme song
It's time for the interlude
(no translation needed - repetition of previous line)
Hurry
What I told you before
Now that you've heard her say it
You can easily connect the dots
What I said
was correct
That's exactly how it is
You truly loved her sister Zhenzhen
From beginning to end
With unwavering devotion
You just didn't expect
When you confessed your feelings
It wasn't to her sister Zhenzhen
How could I have known
Right, you probably didn't understand either
Yes
You had a big argument with Zhenzhen
Because of your relationship with Screenwriter Song
Yes
Because I told Zhenzhen
Screenwriter Song would treat me well
But Zhenzhen didn't believe it
So that day we had
a huge argument
I also think that day
I got a bit too emotional
I know Zhenzhen was just
trying to protect me
looking out for me
But that day
we really did have a major fight
I understand
Then who do you think "killed"
your sister (Zhenzhen)
I don't know
Would sister (Zhenzhen) have "committed suicide"
to help her younger sister (Jiajia)
and then frame him for it?
That's impossible
If she "killed herself"
to help her
why would she need to frame him?
I don't know
You know even though it's really
You know this part is really
Your sister is still fine
Don't pull this act
No
This part is really touching
But watching them, I just can't handle it
It's over
Are we family?
You're not
Born of the same root
What are you doing here?
Why the rush to torment each other?
After generations of descendants
You'd turn your back on family
Begin
You're so happy
Three bowls
Are you happy?
The person I truly loved has already "died"
Go keep her company there
You're not a good person either
Fine
What you lost was just love
But what she lost was her sister (Zhenzhen)
She suffered a double loss
Lost her sister (Zhenzhen)
Family love and romantic love
Right
But she has Screenwriter Song
She's not at a loss either
Screenwriter Song
We've found something
Are you actually two sisters?
I didn't know
About you being two sisters
Why keep it a secret?
Because we needed to perform
To maintain mystery for the audience
So you're from out of town, right?
Aren't you staying here?
You...
Yes
One ID card for two
Two rooms booked
Correct
What's going on here?
Here's the thing
First, regarding the handwriting
Someone who could forge her handwriting
Must be someone very close to her
I'm a "pervert"
Stop looking at me
To write a good novel
You fabricated all of this
I think it's Screenwriter Song
So it is Screenwriter Song?
Because Screenwriter Song co-wrote the script with her
So he's very familiar with her handwriting
Yes, that's possible
"The Qiao Family's Descendants"
I did write it
But I put his name on it
I think Screenwriter Song is the prime suspect
Let's follow the rotation order
Let's analyze this first
Okay
Jiajia
Have a seat
You sit
Sit down, you can't leave anyway
Sit here
Don't run
Sherlock Holmes once said,
when you have eliminated all possibilities,
what remains, however improbable,
must be the truth.
There's no escape this way either.
May 6th, 10:30 AM
"Suicide"
There's a "blood" mark on the door
Cat
So what we need to do now is
figure out how to reconstruct this "murder" method
Something's suspicious, let's go
Where's the "corpse"?
The bottle's gone and so is the person
Neither her sister nor her have "died"
Someone's pulling from inside, right?
Playing tough, huh?
She's over there
Hurry, let's go
What's she doing here?
Controlling all of this
The "killer" can go anywhere
When he was scaring us
He was standing right behind us
Then why didn't he call out to us?
Moreover
I might not believe you
The "killer" could be lying
You don't have to believe me
But the question is - what's my motive?
Can't the three bowls be completed?
This crime process
All three of us could be involved
This is clearly trying to frame me
Bai could also be framing herself
A scheme within a scheme
Even if you have just a 1% chance of being the culprit
You can't be completely ruled out
He's really highly suspicious
Tune in to Tencent Video every Friday at 6 PM
3 episodes released consecutively
Members get early access 1 week in advance
Non-members get one free episode daily from next Friday to Sunday
Every Saturday at 12 PM
Watch "Let's Start Reasoning" case tracking
Every Saturday at 6 PM
Watch bonus content "Apartment No.11 Diary"
Every Sunday enjoy more exciting unaired footage
Plus a wave of previews
Daily short videos to browse
Take you on a 360° exploration of Apartment No.11
Hurry up and open Tencent Video
Search for "Let's Start Reasoning"
Join the "Bulldozers" for immersive case-solving