=My Fairy Doctor=
=Episode 10=
Did you
see it all?
If you say a word about it,
I'll kill you.
I have a question.
What now?
How do you imprint
the rabbit on the fabric?
Rabbit?
Break the spell now!
Quick!
Hurry up.
Don't worry too much about it.
It is perfectly normal
for a wife and husband.
Rest assured.
I'll be responsible for you.
Cut the nonsense!
Just stay there.
So,
where are we going?
Qi.
You're up so early today.
Good morning, father.
Well,
I'm waking him up.
Tang Caichen.
Get up.
Father.
We have something to do.
So we'll be off.
Hurry up.
Oh,
look at this couple.
It's all your fault.
Now I have to sneak around
and my plans to go abroad
have gone down the drain.
I've been saving money for so long.
Maybe I can go with you.
Do you have an ID?
Can you afford a plane ticket?
In your dreams.
Since we don't have a solution,
why don't you try
to accept my existence?
I have no other choice.
What are you doing?
I want to cut your hair.
Our hair is from our parents.
We must never disfigure it.
If you want to fit in
with modern society,
start with your hair.
Do you like men with short hair?
I don't want to walk down the street
with a freak.
Fine.
Don't you dare lie to me,
or else.
Fret not.
I'll take you shopping for
some clothes after this.
Plus 538,
plus 3962
equal to 24,500.
It cost me
24,500 RMB in just one day.
Tang.
This is all my savings.
I may be new here,
but I will not remain a stranger.
Do not worry.
I'll pay you back
ten times the amount when I'm rich.
When is that?
In the future.
That's it.
You don't have any money, do you?
You should have
something of value on you
from the Tang Dynasty.
(Cixiao Pavilion)
♪Light up all the stars♪
♪Wish for staying with you forever♪
♪You're like the thriving Tang dynasty♪
♪No matter if we're fated or not♪
♪We still love each other♪