=My Fairy Doctor=
=Episode 25=
This is for Dr. Tang.
I will pass it to him.
All right. Goodbye.
Goodbye.
I should have
asked them to send
their birth date to a chat room.
This is tiring.
But then we wouldn't know
if the info was real.
Qizi.
Does our ancestor know
that we are looking for
a wife for him?
Did he approve this?
I make the call on this.
I didn't approve of this.
Pack up now.
I am not going on any blind dates.
Qizi.
Come with me.
I need to talk to you.
Do you really think I should
study Chinese medicine?
It takes hard work,
talent
and commitment
to be a doctor.
All three are indispensable.
Although you lack talent,
your hard work and responsibility
are enough to
make up for it.
Besides,
I can guide you.
Even if
you let Dabao attend my classes,
I can teach it medical theory.
Then I want to be your best student.
Divine Physician.
Let's begin the class.
From now on,
feel free to consult
the patients.
Even if they're terminally ill,
I can revive them.
Okay.
(National Medical Centre)
(The present-day Hua Tuo)
See?
Isn't it fun
to treat people?
Yes.
It's nice
to feel needed.
Don't get carried away
with a small achievement.
You still have a lot to learn.
Your prescription
isn't really impressive.
It's just acceptable.
We study medicine to save lives,
not to argue about the methods.
It's pointless.
You're right.
So
could you
also teach Badou a thing or two?
Qizi
is a girl after all.
If Badou receives your guidance,
he will be able to expand
our family's philosophy of medicine.
Moreover,
Badou is also a bright child.
Tang family's medical philosophy
was originally compiled by me.
It's up to me
who I pass it on to.
Besides,
Badou is not interested in this.
Father.
He is right.
I really think Qizi
is fit to be a doctor.
You can leave
this clinic to her with no worries.
I just
want to get rich overnight
and live a carefree life.
You brat!
Brat,
is that something you should say
as a son of Tang family?
You are so irresponsible.
What is our family motto?
What is it?
Self-improvement,
virtue and harmony,
medical ethics
and goodwill.
You always tell Qizi
to recite the family motto.
I think you should
evaluate yourself
and think about how
to improve your skills.
Go and reflect on yourself.
Kneel in front of the ancestors.
Yes.
(Ancestral Virtues)
I never thought I'd see this.
What goes around comes around.
Serve him right.
♪Light up all the stars♪
♪Wish for staying with you forever♪
♪You're like the thriving Tang dynasty♪
♪No matter if we're fated or not♪
♪We still love each other♪