=My Fairy Doctor=
=Episode 13=
You are my wife.
Can you stop saying
I'm your wife?
This is verbal harassment.
We have no other choice
but to stay together
since we can't be separated.
Marriage is based on love.
We can't get married because
we don't have feelings for each other,
do you understand?
So
how do we develop feelings?
Watch TV more
and learn from people.
Also, learn more modern languages.
I'm going to bed.
♪Wait until the moon is gone♪
♪The glazed tiles are dyed white♪
♪The water reflects the moon♪
♪The reflection of fate♪
♪The gentleman is like a painting♪
I'll be there this time tomorrow.
Are you crazy?
♪Oh♪
♪Red string connected us♪
♪to each other♪
♪I wish I could hold your hand♪
♪until the end of the world♪
♪Lightly draw the eyebrows♪
♪Wish for staying with you forever♪
♪You're like the thriving Tang dynasty♪
Caichen.
Do you want to eat fried chicken?
You mean
the food from the other night?
Yes, it's still warm.
What are you doing?
Put it down.
This is for my live streaming.
Give it back.
You should quit.
You've been doing this for over a year,
yet you only have a few followers.
What's the point?
You're wasting food.
So what if I have a small fan base?
I can gain overnight fame anytime.
Don't be jealous when I get
a lot of sponsorships.
It's easy to talk.
Hello, my fans.
I am your best buddy, Badou.
We meet again.
Today I will share with you
the everyday foods.
Fried chicken
and this.
Sweetheart cake.
This is what he ate yesterday.
I bought this cake from an old town.
I heard it's delicious.
Let me give it a taste.
Sweetheart cake?
Can you find
a sweetheart with that face?
You are so tan.
Is your ancestor Bao Zheng?
"We could be friends
if you blur your face."
I guess it's hard for you
to be popular.
What is this?
Why are there two Badou?
This is live streaming.
That is,
if you click this
little black box,
everyone in the world can see you.
The whole world?
Yes.
That's unbelievable.
(Totally unappetising. Eat on your own.)
The man behind you is so handsome.
I need all
the info about this guy
in three seconds.
Handsome guy.
He is my type.
Invite him to your live streaming.
We want to see him
instead of you.
Caichen.
Sit down.
Have a seat.
Come on.
Hello, fans.
The handsome guy is here.
Remember to
give a like
and follow my channel.
He has nice skin.
So
what should I do?
Anything.
Eat some fried chickens.
Drink the coke.
There are questions from fans.
Share us the tips
to fine skin.
Shall I speak to it?
Yes.
You can start with a tea facial mask.
Use lemon juice with red dates
to cleanse your face.
After that, pat your cheeks
with egg white or lotion.
Each individual's
skin type is different.
So it may differ.
(National Medical Centre)
(I don't believe it.)
(Even that old-fashioned man
can be famous.)
(With my ability,)
(I can easily gain fame, too.)
(Live stream invitation)
Hello, babies.
I'm Dr. Tang.
Today,
I'm going to share with you
beauty herbal soup.
It actually tastes good.
I put...
Why are you talking to yourself?
♪Light up all the stars♪
♪Wish for staying with you forever♪
♪You're like the thriving Tang dynasty♪
♪No matter if we're fated or not♪
♪We still love each other♪