[Episode 17]
Luckily, Mr. Zhu put in a good word
with your principal,
saying you're a promising student.
Otherwise, your re-enrollment paperwork
would have taken forever.
Once I'm back at school,
can you handle things at home on your own?
Of course I can.
Never underestimate your mom.
Pocky once read my palm
and said my luck is about to turn.
Benefactors and career success
are coming my way.
Him? He also told me
I'd become a scientist someday.
Totally out of left field.
I think he was quite accurate.
Don't worry.
Ye has already paved the way for us.
Besides, with Xuan Island reopening,
things will be better than before.
Supporting the whole family?
Definitely no problem.
You really think so?
Yes, really.
What are you worried about?
Look,
Grandma gets around fine with her wheelchair.
Liu Nian is helping me in the shop.
If anything else comes up,
Xi Xi and the others are there.
What's there to worry about?
When I say I can hold things up, I mean it.
You've got this.
Right, I've got this.
Mom.
It's a full moon tonight.
Can I come in?
Sure.
I got a herbal soak packet from Dr. Zhuang.
Soak your feet for 30 minutes.
It'll make your legs feel better.
Got a haircut.
Now you look more like a student.
- Come on. The water's just right.
- Okay.
It feels so good.
It's like my meridians have been unblocked.
What are you laughing at?
You think it feels like
braised pork trotters, too, don't you?
Exactly.
Mainly because
it smells just like it.
Come to think of it,
this packet does contain Sichuan pepper
and cassia twig.
Is Dr. Zhuang really treating my feet
like pork trotters to be braised?
He's not that absent-minded.
Sichuan pepper and cassia twig
promote blood circulation
and relieve muscle tension.
I really owe you one today.
Otherwise,
I don't know how I would've made it back
after those twenty laps.
Honestly,
you didn't have to.
Yes, I did.
A bet is a bet.
It's also
a punishment
and a wake-up call
for letting myself slack off lately.
How so?
To be honest, even with my English score added,
my monthly test results won't get me
into the university I want.
What's more,
in the Gaokao,
Cao Fan won't be my only rival.
So I need to readjust my study methods
and push myself harder.
Do you believe I can make it?
Of course.
So certain?
Why?
No reason.
I just believe in you.
In that case,
you can also believe
that I can get both of us
onto the honor roll.
I'm not like you.
I haven't studied for years.
I probably
won't get into college.
Where there's a will, there's a way.
How will you know if you don't try?
Don't waste your time on me.
Besides, I'm going back to school
not to get into college.
I know.
Just to get your high school diploma.
Exactly.
That's about enough. Any longer
and your feet will turn into braised trotters.
Lift them up.
Good night.
Morning, Xing Wu.
Morning, Qing Ye.
You look much more like a proper student.
Like I wasn't proper before.
Back then you were Mr. Xing.
Now, you're a student.
Which one is better?
- Both are good.
- You have to pick one.
Can't I pick both?
Dream on.
You evolved, right?
You've become much more outgoing.
You even crack jokes now.
No way. Give me a break.
Ever done Myers-Briggs?
What's that?
Though you were an introvert,
you're becoming an extrovert.
Introvert, extrovert.
Right now,
I'm a high school student.
Let's go.
Wait.
You're not a complete high school student yet.
Where's your ID badge?
Forgot to put it on.
Let me help you.
There.
- Is it level?
- Yes.
Perfectly level.
- Let's go.
Nice day, isn't it?
What are you listening to?
English.
Listening practice.
Listen with me?
I-I'm not interested.
So? Does it sound good?
Yeah.
What's the name of it?
I Promise.
Quite nice.
Try another one.
Listening material?
No.
You're listening.
Whatever you say.
Oh, by the way...
Getting used to it?
This uniform is so uncomfortable.
Qing Ye!
Look, who's this?
Who else could it be?
New sneakers.
New haircut.
Time to celebrate!
Don't step on my new sneakers!
- You want to lose a foot?
- Don't you know the saying?
Step on new shoes twice,
and no worries on your path.
Rub a new haircut once,
and you'll be smart and bouncy.
See? Since he heard you're coming back,
he's even stopped stuttering.
Y-Y-You bet!
I'm even planning to stick around
for another year. Grade four.
Don't say things that bad luck brings.
Then I'll be your all-around companion:
companion of study, food, and drink.
I'll stay as long as you guys do.
Enough of such words.
What if I already regret
going back to school?
- Too late.
- Y-You dare run!
- Wait for me!
Go!
Frankly speaking, I do admire Xing Wu.
For what?
Not many in Anzi County can turn down my dad.
But he did.
That's just how he is.
He sets his mind,
and he'll do it no matter the cost.
I wish I could be like that.
By the way, Shu Han,
you don't have to pick me up
after school anymore.
Why? Got other plans?
I'm staying for the evening study session
to review with Qing Ye.
You're pretty tired after work anyway.
I'll just take a taxi home.
Anyway, if anything comes up,
just call me anytime.
Okay.
Sorry.
I can't sign the contract.
Why?
If it's about the salary,
I can talk to Mr. Ye again.
It's no trouble.
No.
It's not about the salary.
I've decided to go back to school.
Back to school?
Are you serious?
What made you change your mind all of a sudden?
To get
a high school diploma.
Oh, come on.
If you just wanted a diploma,
you would've made it a long time ago.
It's because of Qing Ye, right?
Looks like I hit the mark.
Spill it. What's going on?
I want to protect her as much as I can.
Keep her from being disturbed.
So she can focus on preparing for Gaokao.
Xing Wu,
you're so good to Qing Ye.
You're even giving up
this job opportunity for her?
Fine.
But as your friend, I have to tell you,
someday, Qing Ye will leave this place.
She'll leave Zhazhating
to see father's places.
Maybe by then,
she won't even remember this place.
I know.
You can walk this stretch of the road with her.
- I know that too.
- So what?
Then what about later?
What about the future?
It doesn't matter to me
whether she's still here later,
or whether she remembers this place or not.
I can only control the present,
making sure she goes through her time here
smoothly and safely.
I've always been by your side.
If one day,
you're tired of being a student,
you're always welcome to come back as Mr. Xing.
I'm busy. You can see yourself out.
I won't walk you.
[China Sports Lottery]
Qing Ye,
could you do me a favor?
Go ahead.
Could you give this to your brother, Xing Wu?
Thank you so much.
Wu,
I heard that you used to be
a beast at shooting games.
They called you the Sniper King.
Could you carry us in games after school?
I used to play games, but not anymore.
What? Are you all about studying now?
No wonder you're doing so well.
Always first in physics.
- Got any tips to share?
- Yeah. Share with us!
- I want to hear it too.
- Why crowing around?
Because I'm into it.
That's all.
That's so vague. Elaborate a bit?
Instead of asking me,
you'd better drill on practice problems.
We do grind problems,
but with the same practice material,
why do you always score higher?
- Yeah!
- What kind of problems do you solve?
- Don't you use the Five-Three Workbook?
- Right. Are you taking private lessons?
- A tutoring class?
- You must be secretly studying every night.
- I don't want to hear excuses.
- Grinder.
Didn't expect you to be this popular
right after returning to school.
Of course.
I'm just that attractive.
- Indeed.
- Yeah.
Look, Wu just transferred into our class,
great at games,
great at studies, and handsome, too.
He is so excellent.
Simply excellent.
No wonder everyone admires him.
Speaking of it,
someone gave you yogurt.
Yogurt?
Who is the "someone"?
- Break it up. Everyone, break it up.
- Let me have a look.
Go on.
So there's yogurt.
If you're not drinking it, I will.
Thanks.
Where did you get it?
It's Xing Wu's.
Who told you to drink it? It wasn't for you.
Well then, was it for you?
I bought it. I gave it to Xing Wu.
Here, take it back.
Get lost.
"I bought it. I gave it to Xing Wu."
Going for a late-night snack?
Not going.
Qing Ye. Late-night snack?
Have some?
You've already torn it apart.
Qing Ye.
Here.
I didn't find problems in English,
but found out
some new problems in math.
This question type is quite new,
but it's still related to functions.
Look at him, Ye Ying Jian.
Ever since the monthly exams ended,
he's been sticking to Qing Ye every night.
Can't even chase him away.
If I weren't incapable of studying,
I'd squeeze right between them, shove him out.
Don't bother me.
Go find Hu for a snack.
Hu?
Forget it. Let me tell you, class just ended,
and he's already vanished.
Before he left, he said something like
"I-I-I'm not going."
"I-I-I've got other important stuff."
"Be kind to your hands."
Smells so good.
Thank you.
It was supposed to be a show for four:
You, Qing Ye,
me, and Hu.
But what happened?
I'm still the nameless one.
Like an empty-nester.
Take your time for your cousin!
Xing Wu, I heard you know how to fix phones.
Mine is broken. Could you take a look?
- Mine is broken too.
- Mine too.
- Okay.
- You're so kind.
I'll take them back and check.
Then I'll let you know in a few days.
That would be great. Sorry for the trouble.
- You're welcome.
- Thanks.
- Volunteer.
- It's "volunteer," right?
- Your vocabulary is actually enough.
I find English lessons easy now.
I just wrote down that word at the time.
I'm heading off.
Bye. See you tomorrow.
Bye.
Had fun studying English, huh?
Had fun chatting with them, huh?
You've been busy.
- Not bad.
- Got to open it up and see.
Of course I do.
Open each one and check carefully.
Each one.
So there's more than one?
Yeah, quite a few.
Didn't expect to be this popular.
Just enjoy it quietly.
I can't enjoy it alone.
It's all thanks to you. I should share the joy.
What do you mean by that?
Treat you to a late-night snack.
Got a few phone repair jobs.
Everyone gets a cut.
Happy with the money.
So it's about phones?
What else did you think?
Nothing.
Wrong way.
This way.
What do you feel like eating?
Whatever. Anything is fine.
I'm so full.
Next time, I'll definitely not eat this much.
I wonder who kept saying,
"Good. Delicious. Yummy."
- Where did this rain come from?
- Here, over here.
Seriously, no warning at all.
It just pours whenever it wants.
Probably a passing shower.
Comes fast, goes fast.
Shoot, no umbrella.
Wait here. I'll go back and get one.
Forget it. It's only a few steps.
Let's run back together.
Are you kidding me?
It's not like
we haven't been caught in the rain before.
Wait a second. I'm getting my jacket out.
Scoot in.
Come here.
Come on.
- Got a good grip?
- Got it.
You sure?
Ready?
Three.
- Two. One.
Oh my!
Don't move.
Go inside. Don't catch a cold.
Okay.
What's Xing Wu
doing now?
What are you thinking about, Qing Ye?
You should go to sleep.
Grandma.
You're still up?
Ye.
Come in.
Aren't you awake too?
I want to wind up this yarn before I sleep.
Let me help you.
Good.
Like this, right?
- Yes.
- Like this.
Pull it straight.
- Okay.
- Good.
You're up so late.
What's wrong? Something on your mind?
No.
Not really?
Alright,
maybe a little.
Tell me about it.
It's just that
lately I feel
all mixed up inside.
I keep thinking about one thing,
trying to
sort it out.
There's this person
who makes your emotions
go up and down wildly.
Grandma, do you know that feeling?
Well, that means,
when he's happy,
you're happy.
And when he's unhappy, you get worried.
- Is that how it feels?
- Yes!
Grandma, I feel like
my emotions
have become unstable.
I know this isn't right,
but I just can't figure out what's going on.
You know,
if you try to make everything
in life crystal clear,
then it would be quite boring.
In one's life,
if everything is perfectly right,
then it's all wrong.
I think you're
doing just fine.
It's no big deal.
It's okay. Don't worry.
Grandma,
you are a philosopher indeed.
A philosopher?
What philosopher?
It's a title.
It means you're perceptive and wise.
Who gave me that title?
Your grandson, Xing Wu.
Oh, he's talking nonsense.
Fang!
Xing Wu!
- Help! Fang!
- Xi Xi? What's wrong?
Please help me!
I need your help!
- What happened?
- Hu is missing!
Missing?
When did you find out?
Just now!
Don't panic. Come inside. Come in.
Take your time.
Tell us about it.
Yesterday, I scolded him a bit,
and then he got upset.
- What's up?
- Wu.
- Has Hu contacted you?
No.
That's it. He must have run away from home.
Auntie, don't panic. Take your time.
What's going on exactly?
I scolded him a bit yesterday.
He got upset and talked back,
and then we ended up arguing.
Hu doesn't seem like the type to argue.
I know, yesterday not only did we argue,
he even slammed the door and left.
I said to him,
"Fine. Don't you dare come back!"
That was just angry talk.
When I get mad at Wu,
I say way worse things.
I thought he just went out to clear his head.
But this morning I checked:
he wasn't in his room.
The blanket was still folded.
I realized he never came home last night.
[Hu]
Did you call him? Try to reach him?
Well...
His phone is with me.
To avoid online romance, I took his phone.
Online romance?
No way. He is such an honest and simple kid.
How could he? Don't overthink it.
You have no idea
how mature kids these days could be.
Wu,
unlock his phone for me.
Let me check.
Auntie, I can't.
I can't unlock it.
Then what should we do?
Where to look for him?
I'll go with you to the police station.
Okay.
Wu. If he contacts you, let me know right away.
- Sure. No problem.
- Let's go.
- You two watch the shop.
- Yes.
Take your time.
Why didn't you just unlock it?
That would be a total betrayal.
Besides, that's an invasion of privacy.
But what if he runs into danger?
It won't come to that.
I know him.
He probably has a hidden problem.
None of you has seen him?
All right.
I got it.
If you do see him, call me anytime.
Okay.
I asked a few friends.
None of them has seen Hu.
Internet cafes, arcades,
Even in hotels, nobody's seen him.
I also asked our classmates.
No one has any news of him.
Lately,
Hu has indeed been acting a bit off.
Yeah, something's off.
But in what way?
In so many ways.
Ever since the start of this semester,
I've felt something was up.
He often wouldn't walk home with me
after school.
Whenever he's free, he holds his phone
and giggle like an idiot.
One time, I even caught him
chatting with someone at an internet cafe.
Why did you show up all of a sudden?
My mom went to the police station with them.
I haven't eaten. Thought I'd come for a meal.
- Are you full?
- Yes.
- Thanks.
- Wait.
I was saving it for later!
Don't worry.
Men destined for greatness
don't sweat the small stuff.
I'm not like my mom.
She makes a big deal out of everything
and even went to the police.
Oh, come on,
Hu isn't that fragile.
I reckon he's just hiding somewhere
to get some peace and quiet.
So, according to you, once he clears his head,
he might give us a call, right?
You never know.
- Hello?
- Wu.
Hu!
Hu, where are you?
I'm in Changdao.
Changdao?
What are you doing there?
It's a long story.
Dude, you left without your phone,
and didn't come home last night.
Your mom is going crazy looking for you.
Don't tell her I'm here.
Please don't.
She went to the police.
By now, she's probably at the station.
Wu,
why didn't you stop her?
It's not that I didn't try.
She wouldn't be stopped.
Hu,
we can keep your secret,
but you have to let your mom know
that you're safe.
She's about to die of worry.
Okay, I'll tell her.
When are you coming back?
Hard to say.
Things are pretty complicated here.
Bro, I'm not done yet.
Hello?
Young man. I'm in a hurry to deliver goods.
O-O-One more minute. Just one minute.
- Alright. Make it quick.
- Thank you.
Mom. It's me.
Get it boxed up and shipped out.
You have to take a boat
to get to Changdao.
Are you going for him?
Then I'll go with you.
The ferry runs only three trips a day.
We might not make the morning one.
Tell me a family here without a boat.
Fuzz.
Here you are.
Have some water.
I have
a wild guess.
- What?
- Look.
[There's something I wish for]
This is Shi Min's Moments Post.
This photo
is identical to Hu's Moments cover.
So it was Shi Min all along.
I'm not sure.
But Shi Min told me before
that she boards at school
because commuting is too much trouble.
She has to transfer three times.
Her home is on Changdao.
Look at you, Sherlock Holmes.
Well, girls have a certain intuition
for this kind of thing.
Who's good with who and who's not,
we can tell right away.
Then should you call Shi Min?
Right, I'll call her now.
[Shi Min]
Hello, Qing Ye.
Hello, Shi Min.
Have you been in touch with Hu?
He's with me right now.
Send us your location right away.
His mom is freaking out.
She's already gone to the police.
Let's set off.
How?
You drive.
Don't judge a book by its cover.
Hard to find a Zhazhating resident
who doesn't know how to drive a boat.
[PRC Yacht Driver's License]
Then let's head out.
Let's go, Captain.
Hold on tight.
Let's go.
Thank you. We'll cancel it.
Hurry, hurry.
What's wrong? Hurry up.
Slow down.
Go to Changdao. He's there.
How did you know he was in Changdao?
I overheard someone on the phone with Hu
mentioned farms and oysters.
Around here, only Changdao has oyster farms.
That's true. But Changdao is huge.
Are we going to search door-to-door?
Fine, door-to-door it is.
I'm to blame.
I shouldn't have yelled at him yesterday.
Boys are tough. So what if you yelled?
I...
I didn't just scold him, I hit him too.
You laid hands on him?
I just slapped his back,
poked his head, and pulled his ear.
That's nothing.
That's not even considered hitting.
I also said,
"Look at you, you can't even speak clearly.
What girl would ever like you?
If you don't study hard,
what's going to become of you?"
That was really hurtful, right?
- Yes.
He wouldn't do something stupid
like jump into the sea, would he?
Don't say that. Yu Fen,
does your husband go out to Changdao often?
Yes. Let's go back to Zhazhating now.
Head to the dock,
and have him take us there by boat.
Hurry, let's go.
- Take care!
- Hurry!
Oh my god.
Wait, no. Where's our boat?
Yeah, where is it?
Oh no. Crap.
The key is gone too.
Seriously, who was it?
Who took our boat?
I don't even need to think twice.
Our little rascal took it.
Fuzz! I'm going to knock you into next week!
Come on.
- Catch a ferry at the dock.
- Go, go, go.
Honey, go ahead with your work. We're leaving.
It's just up ahead.
It's vast out here.
Careful, cousin.
- Massive.
- Excuse me, coming through.
Everyone's bundled up.
How are we supposed to find him?
I've asked around.
This is the Shi family's seafood farm.