Hello?
[Qing Ye, it's me.]
[Mom said you had dinner with her.]
[You're back in Beijing?]
Yeah, back.
[Congrats.]
[You're back to normal life.]
Thanks.
[You don't sound too happy.]
Do I?
Maybe,
I'm still getting used to it.
[No way.]
Yeah.
Zhazhating has fewer skyscrapers,
the lights aren't as bright,
and the air always carries
a hint of the sea.
By all rights,
I should be happy to be back.
But…
[But you miss that place.]
You're right.
Wu,
dinner's ready.
Come eat.
[Hurry up, we're late.]
[Coming!]
[I haven't done my hair!]
[Three minutes till late.]
[Late means time-out.]
[Alright.]
[Move.]
I've been running around lately,
didn't really get to
look after Ye.
She didn't even get
her favorite red bean zongzi.
I thought
she'd stay through Lantern Festival.
Didn't expect her to leave in such a rush.
What are you all
so down about?
Ye
just left
our little dump,
she's back
in her rich nest.
That's a good thing.
What's there to mope about?
Good thing.
Yeah.
I just feel
the house is missing someone.
Feels empty now.
People come
and people go.
Just like the seasons.
Spring sunshine and blossoms,
so wonderful.
But it doesn't last.
We also have hot summers and cold winters.
Can't live missing spring forever
and forget the rest.
So,
just live your life well now,
spring will come again.
The ones who leave,
you'll see them again.
Eat up.
Finally home.
Everything's cleaned up.
The old nanny's back too.
Need anything, just ask her.
Okay, thanks, Mr. Sun.
Ye, you're back.
Welcome home!
Come in!
Long time no see, ma'am.
Come in.
Alright.
Enough.
Careful, it's hot.
Call me when you're done.
Okay.
[Is this still alive?]
[Come take a look.]
[It is!]
[The welwitschia made it!]
Mom.
Take this.
What's this?
My pay from lately.
Not much.
Give it to Auntie Shanxi
for rent.
I've got money.
Keep it.
School's starting soon.
Then college after that.
Save the money up.
Where'd you get money?
When Qing Ye's dad left,
he lent me some money.
A hundred grand.
A hundred…
I know what you're thinking.
But it's not like that.
Don't worry.
I didn't squeeze him for it.
And I'm not
some money-grubber either.
This money,
he offered it himself.
He didn't ask for it back,
but I wouldn't agree.
It's all in writing,
clear as day.
No matter how long it takes,
I'll pay it back
Don't worry.
So…
Does Qing Ye know?
I think so.
Probably she was the one
who asked her dad to give the money.
Look at them,
a hundred grand,
and no sweat to them.
If it were us two,
who knows how long we'd have to save?
Worlds apart.
Keep it safe.
Money doesn't come easy.
Ye,
your dad headed back to work.
Tons waiting on him.
School starts tomorrow,
I'll take you in the morning.
Get some rest.
- I'm off.
- Okay.
Bye, Mr. Sun.
Mom,
I'm home.
Gaokao's only
one semester away.
We're heading
into the final sprint.
I hope everyone
gives it everything
and fights
for the best future you can get.
Class starts.
Mom, how's the color?
Sir,
thanks for the hard work,
have some water.
Here.
Sir,
have some water.
Grandma.
Sir,
have some water.
Thanks.
Sir,
here, grab a bottle.
Thanks.
Have some water.
[It's alive, it's Welwitschia.]
[Tough as nails.]
[It can survive in the desert]
[for ages and ages.]
Class,
I've handed out
my 20 key
scoring tricks.
Memorize the steps.
From now on,
if you get a similar question
and don't know how to solve it,
just plug in the steps.
Remember,
Math
can be memorized by rote learning too.
If you're unsure in the exam,
don't leave it blank,
write whatever you can!
For English,
review vocab and grammar.
Cram as much as you can.
Don't leave either essay blank.
Memorize some stock phrases
and hit the word count.
Get studying.
Last-minute cramming still helps.
Every point counts!
The last holiday
before the final showdown.
You've got three days.
I hope everyone
gets good rest
and resets their mindset.
But,
don't relax too much.
We've worked hard for three years,
I hope everyone
leaves no regrets.
Go all in for the exams.
Go to the city you want
and get into the university you want.
Keep it up.
- Keep it up!
Where do you want to go?
I just want the provincial
normal university,
close to home.
Wu, what about you?
Beijing.
Son,
tell your grandma dinner's ready.
One more dish and it's done.
My boy's great.
I love the way you're now!
So focused.
Look at you now,
like those ancient scholars
studying for official exams.
Like
"Burning the midnight oil to the extreme."
Is that how it goes?
Yes.
Alright.
Then study hard
and call your grandma for dinner later.
Take a break.
Okay.
Grandma.
Grandma?
Dinner's ready.
Wu,
I don't wanna eat.
No.
You haven't eaten all day.
Come,
I'll carry you downstairs.
Come.
Alright.
Thanks, sweetheart.
I'm no lightweight.
You're lighter than a kitten.
Time to eat!
Grandma, have some soup.
Mom,
with how hard
Wu's studying now,
a top university
is a sure thing.
I'm telling you,
our ancestors
would be smiling down on us.
Then the biggest credit goes to Ye.
She got Wu back to school.
Yes,
Grandma is right.
But we still need
to stay calm.
For the gaokao I can only do my best.
Don't think about top universities.
I don't agree.
Why can't we aim high?
Well,
you have to dare to dream.
Hope gives you motivation.
Your mom's right.
I really believe in my grandson.
Come,
have an egg
and get full marks.
Thanks, Grandma.
Grandma, let me.
Full marks.
Mom,
you should have an egg too.
Stay 100% healthy!
Okay.
Here's some more good news.
Our Xuan Island salon
is almost finished being renovated.
Once Wu's exams
are over,
I'll get the house sorted
so we can move back home.
Good.
I'm also thinking of
going to a better barbershop
in the city
to learn
and sharpen
my skills.
In the future,
things will turn around.
Grandma,
It'll only get better.
That's great.
Tomorrow's the 15th.
Let's go
thank the Dragon King and Mazu
and honor our promises.
I wanna see the sunset too.
Sure.
I haven't been out in a while.
I'll go with you.
Forecast says heavy rain tomorrow.
How about
we go together the day after tomorrow,
once the weather clears up.
- Sure.
- Let's go together.
Good.
It's settled then.
Okay.
Alright.
The day after.
That works too.
Works too…
Wu.
Xing Wu!
Coming!
Wu.
What is it?
Grandma won't wake up
no matter how I call.
What do we do?
Grandma.
Take her to the hospital.
Okay.
Come on.
Slow down.
Doctor.
How's my mom?
The patient's elderly.
Based on post-op indicators
and her condition,
her bodily functions
are very weak.
She can't tolerate
aggressive treatment.
We recommend hospice care.
Prepare for the end.
Mom.
Grandma.
I…
I can't make it.
Mom, don't take that off.
It hurts so much.
I…
No intubation.
No resuscitation.
Lanfang.
Guodong…
Mom, you wanna see Xing Guodong?
I know,
he's gone.
How did you know?
Once
you came back very late.
And you were in a bad mood.
I knew
he was gone.
[Leaving so soon?]
[Yes, Mom.]
[I'm going back to town for something.]
[I'll be back in a couple of days.]
[Alright.]
[Take good care of yourself at home.]
[Okay.]
[Be safe.]
[I will.]
[I remember once]
[I said I was going to town]
[and shut down the salon
for a few days.]
[Actually]
[I got a call from the police.]
[They asked me to identify a body.]
[Guodong owed a lot of money.]
[To escape debt,]
[he hid on a ship.]
[He drank,]
[got drunk,]
[missed a step]
[and fell into the sea.]
I don't blame you for hiding it from me.
Guodong
caused us so much trouble.
He made our lives
a living hell.
Lanfang,
Wu.
Thanks to you both,
all these years,
I've finally had a good life.
I have no regrets.
Wu.
Grandma.
Wu,
from now on,
you've got to work hard.
Got it?
I will.
I will for sure.
Good.
Wu.
Why are you here?
I told you not to come,
just stay home and study.
You never listen.
We came to see Grandma
and you too.
How is Grandma?
She's not very clear-minded.
Awake only sometimes.
Even when she wakes up,
she may not recognize people.
Oh right.
The school issued exam passes.
I brought yours.
And the teachers
also gave prediction papers.
Review them again
before the exam.
Thanks.
Wu,
should we
tell Qing Ye about this?
No.
Don't tell her anything.
Remember that.
Alright.
[Grandma!]
[I found a big snail!]
[So big!]
[You're amazing!]
[Let's look over there.]
[There's some here too, yeah?]
Grandma,
Xuan Island's almost renovated.
When you get better,
we'll move into the new house.
Didn't you say
you wanted to thank Mazu
and the Dragon King?
And the sunset.
Look.
The sunset.
So beautiful.
By then,
we'll all live a happy life together.
I've already lived
a blessed life.
Even though
we're not blood-related.
Having a daughter
and a grandson like you,
I've got no regrets.
Grandma.
Grandma,
I brought you to see the sea.
I know
I'm not your biological grandson.
To everyone else here,
you're just an old lady
who loves crafts.
But I know,
when you were young,
you went to school.
But you had a hard life.
Your husband died early,
you raised
Xing Guodong alone.
To survive,
you farmed,
worked as a fisherwoman,
even as a sailor.
You suffered so much.
Even though we're not blood-related,
and you knew
I'm not your real grandson.
But you've always treated me
better than anyone else.
Since the day I can remember,
I've always considered you
my real grandma,
my closest, dearest grandma,
and my benefactor.
Every time I was at my lowest,
you were always by my side,
pulling me back from the edge
of the cliff.
I remember when I was little,
once
I secretly bought a piece of candy.
Xing Guodong kicked me away.
I just cried on the ground.
You helped me up
and comforted me:
"Wu,
be good.
Don't cry.
Have some candy
and it won't feel bitter anymore."
I also remember when I
got seriously ill as a child.
I had to go to the hospital
for injections every day.
Xing Guodong thought
I was a waste of money.
Only you…
But you couldn't bear to take a car.
So you carried me.
It was more than ten kilometers
to the county town every day.
And you carried me there again and again.
But look at you,
when you were sick,
you didn't want treatment.
When you broke your bone,
you refused to get surgery.
You were old, and your legs were weak,
you still wouldn't buy a wheelchair.
Fine,
then I'll make one for you.
I used a chair and wheels
to build a wheelchair for you.
But when you sat in it,
didn't you notice?
It's nowhere
near as good as a real wheelchair.
Last time I bought you
a new electric wheelchair.
You said it was
I was being careless
with money.
But do you know how happy you were
sitting on it?
At that time,
I realized
you always wanted
to go out and see the world.
Grandma,
you always said
"Let's go gather shellfish."
"Let's go see the sea."
"Let's honor our promises."
"Let's worship Mazu
and the Dragon King."
"Let's watch the sunset."
After that,
you never went out again.
Grandma,
in my next life,
I still wanna be your grandson!
In my next life,
I'll still be your Wu!
I promise
I won't let you
suffer like this again!
[Nice.]
[Really nice.]
[After all, I made it myself.]
[Come.]
[Take one each.]
[Grandma,]
[this flower steamed bun is so pretty!]
[Your Auntie and I]
[went to the Sea Goddess temple]
[to pray for it.]
[Eat it and you'll have sharp mind]
[and clear eyes,]
[and get good grades.]
[Thank you, Grandma.]
Kids, do your best on the exam!
Try to get a good score in the exams
and bring honor to our Zhazhating!
- Sure!
- Bring honor!
Thanks, Dad.
Don't be nervous.
Stay calm.
Don't stress.
Show your real ability.
Exactly!
Believe in yourselves!
What does this mean?
Mom, what's this for?
"Go for gold" charm!
Right!
Life should have a little ritual.
We even wore cheongsams today.
- Cheongsam's on, luck is on!
It's the kids' exam day.
Why are you so excited?
I'm nervous!
Can't you tell?
Nervous?
Don't be!
Son,
listen up.
Just take the exam casually.
We don't expect
that much from you.
Maybe I'll be the dark horse!
I'll give it my all.
Listen,
just do your best.
The bus is here.
Come!
Good luck!
Don't take "just casually" literally!
Do your best!
Really, it's fine!
Take your time!
Make us proud!
Good luck, Wu!
Good luck!
Exams are over!
Ye.
Dad.
How's the study-abroad
application going?
Once it's ready,
send it to the agency right away
and let them handle it.
Dad.
There's something
I want to talk to you about.
What is it?
I think
I might be okay with not studying abroad.