=Detective Qin II=
=Episode 6=
You were the first to find the body.
- Take away.
- Okay.
How can you arrest people at will?
What's wrong with it?
Ghosts claim lives, right?
Nonsense!
The troupe leader
was certainly murdered.
And I have heard that
you made a fuss as soon as
you entered the theater.
You insisted on drawing the curtains.
Therefore,
I have enough reason to suspect that
you
are the prime suspect
in this murder case.
Take me back to the station?
Let me be beaten into submission
to settle this case?
I don't care whether
you are the prime murderer
in this murder case.
I, He Hongfeng,
just dislike you people
who deceive with trickery.
Detective He.
You seem very confident about this case.
How about I read your fortune?
Okay.
I want to see
what pearls of wisdom
we can expect from you.
You must have been an army recruit.
Did you desert and run away here?
You must have spent numerous money
to become this captain, right?
By the way,
you need to get your stomach fixed.
It's not good to put it off.
I'm not a deserter.
Thus, everything else is accurate?
You checked me out.
It's just simple face reading.
Deceptive talk. Take him away.
Since you want to arrest him,
take me away too.
I am with them.
Miss Shen, you...
Yes, and me.
You...
Take them all away.
How about Mr. Shen...?
Upon arrival,
you should serve Miss Shen well.
Go.
Step back.
Alright.
Further away.
Turn your head.
The face-reading was really amazing.
Can you teach me?
He Hongfeng's right hand
has thick calluses
on both sides of his fingers.
This is caused by
years of pulling the trigger.
But policemen also need to hold guns.
They use pistols.
He Hongfeng's left palm and four fingers
also have obvious calluses.
This is left from
holding a rifle for a long time.
When he came close to me,
his right collarbone was sunken.
It's caused by the recoil from
years of rifle use.
Therefore, he's not just a soldier,
but a veteran.
Then how do you know he's a deserter?
I heard that
Sichuan Warlord Liu Xiang
once established an army,
called Shenji Army.
Each of them wore a medal
with a swastika pattern engraved on it.
I noticed at his waist,
he also wore one.
Only the inscription
on the medal was scratched.
Most of this unit died,
so if he is not a deserter,
he must be hiding something.
What about the stomach disease?
He has bad breath.
You're sick too.
I don't have bad breath.
Brush your teeth carefully.
Miss Shen, take care.
Slow down.
Sir, he is here.
You really treat here
like your own detective agency?
Do I?
This shabby little place
is worse than my detective agency.
Just ask me quickly.
I need to get back to sleep.
The police station's food is so good.
Delicious!
Don't just stare.
Go ahead and enjoy it. Don't be shy.
You... How did you get to know Qin Yang?
We've been neighbors since childhood.
Three years ago,
my parents entrusted me to him.
And then they never came back.
They are tomb raiders.
They probably died in some tomb.
I'm sorry. I...
It's okay, I'm not upset.
They say grave robbing is a sin.
They must have foreseen this result.
Over three years,
I have sought to be his student
to learn various skills.
Then to find their remains
and bury them.
Although he refused,
this doesn't hinder his status
as a hero in my heart.
He? A Hero?
Why are you going to theater?
Just to watch plays.
Is it illegal to bring two girls?
You are so shameless.
From the beginning, I disagreed
to let Miss Shen follow you.
This is what you've been
giving me a hard time for.
If it weren't for the
fifty dollars each month,
I wouldn't want my little broken temple
to accommodate such a young lady.
Think it carefully.
Do you think Qin Xiaoyang
is just for the money?
Or else?
Actually, he is a very
great and kind person.
However, he has run the
detective agency into such a state.
There used to be quite
a few people coming to him.
While he only takes on
some strange cases.
Faced with many poor people,
he also chooses to help for free.
Even with that,
it's not like he can't pay the rent.
I don't know about that.
Maybe...
He's saving money to get married.
Are you still eating that?
Here you are.
Stop the nonsense.
Tell me what you know.
If I were you,
I would focus on checking
the truth behind the
Wutong's death three years ago.
I don't believe in
female ghost claiming lives.
It's up to you.
However,
maybe someone who's
been dead for three years
does come back for revenge suddenly.
Get me some water.
(Honest and just)
Did He Hongfeng give you a hard time?
I'm helping the police with a case.
Why would they give me a hard time?
Where do we go next?
♪Applause rises for your wedding day♪
♪As I watch, a side character steps in♪
♪You two hand in hand, intimate♪
♪Not to disturb, is my only decision♪
♪As long as you are happy♪
♪Who isn't giving you an embrace♪
♪Keep smiling, maintain decorum♪
♪Tears linger on the rainy farewell day♪
♪Can't let him see through, our past♪
♪Quietly step back a little♪
♪Shift my gaze, and then realize♪
♪My rainy day, is right before my eyes♪
♪Smiles witness, your wedding day today♪
♪Even if I'm missed at the grand finale♪
♪Forgive my mid-show exit♪
♪Turning around, eyes turning red♪
♪After years, I can finally say goodbye♪