What should we do?
Oh!
Guys, can't we just stay in the truck?
Hurry!
Hurry, Guys.
What's that? Isn't it car No.1?
Yu Jeong, you move with me. The rest of you, search the area.
Get in position.
What's going on? Weren't they all eaten up by the spheres?
Hey, don't jinx us!
It's because I'm scared.
What about the others?
What the fuck is going on?
Oh?
What?
Platoon Leader!
Over here.
I think they all managed to get away.
They must not have gone far.
Deok Jung and Il Ha. Go down the road and be on guard.
Bo Ra and Na Ra, please guard the right.
Ae Seol, Ha Na and Yu Jeong.
You're with me.
- Go back to your positions.
- Yes, Sir.
I'm so scared. Oh, gosh. I'm scared.
What's that?
What do you mean, you punk?
That fluttering thing over there.
Oh, fuck. Damn!
Platoon Leader! Spheres are here! Spheres!
Everyone, ready to fire!
What do we do?
What...
Fire!
You motherfuckers!
Oh, right!
You motherfucker!
- Get in the car now! Hurry!
- Damn it!
Jun Hui, can you reach it?
Fuckers!
Shit.
Jun Hui, can you reach it?
Hui Rak, hop on now!
A little more. Hey, can't you get it?
- Hey, hey, hurry up!
- Get on now!
Hey!
Hey, everyone is on.
Okay, let's go!
I'll start the car!
Hold on tight!
Jang Su...
What are we going to do?
What about Hui Rak?
Damn it!
Oh, fuck!
You motherfucker!
Fucking Idiot. He pretended to be strong.
I remembered how weak this fucker was against the cold.
I don't know. I wasn't sure but...
Are you laughing?
Hey.
Oh, Fucking Idiot.
Did you think I was going to hold your hand?
Let's go!
What a fucking asshole. I'm the one who saved you. Why are you acting cool? What a bastard...
Hey!
By the way, why did you do that earlier?
What?
Just cut the act, Asshole.
I have no idea.
Anyway, we really don't vibe.
I thought I'd never see you again!
Do you want some water?
♫  Welcome to the K-Mars, it's colorful every night  ♫
♫  Those demons are always  ♫
Hey, I really thought something happened to you.
You don't even know the half of it. We barely managed to survive.
Hey, we didn't have it easy, either.
- Right, Kim Deok Jung?
- It was legendary.
Hey, hey. It's not enough to talk about our story for two nights and three days.
Jo Jang Su.
Am I wrong?
Three nights and four days.
- What's with him?
- What's wrong with him? All of a sudden?
That's lame.
Jo Jang Su is so fricking boring.
Hey, we missed you.
- Why, why?
- Please go wash.
I took a shower... four days ago.
Why?
If there was water...
- It's because of the water.
- You got to manage to survive.
What?
What's wrong with you?
You, too.
What is with you?
What's this? Isn't this Tae Man's?
I got hurt.
Not really! She's just exaggerating.
- Right!
- Don't get hurt.
How is your injury?
I'm okay.
Let's go get some treatment right away.
What about you? Are you okay?
Do you have any injuries?
No, I'm fine...
That's a relief. I was so worried.
What?
I'm so glad that...
everyone's okay.
Ah, yes.
I know, right?
Thank you so much...
for coming.
♫  I broke down at the unfamiliar sight of the bleeding  ♫
♫  When the world forces us to choose  ♫
♫  We follow our instincts (Be loyal to them)  ♫
♫  And become animals  ♫
- Hyeong!
- Hey!
- Guys!
- Hyeong!
Hyeong! Hyeong!
Hey, is everyone okay?
Didn't you get hurt?
- I didn't.
- Are you okay?
Hyeong, you look much older than before.
I got older while waiting for you guys.
- Are you all right, everyone?
- Yes.
Oh! Guk Yeong Su?
- You're back.
- Hey!
Then were you hoping we wouldn't come back?
What a selfish punk.
This punk would have clapped if we hadn't made it.
He'd rather have thought that there were fewer competitors left.
Stop it.
Yeong Su!
Did you clean up everything alone for the other kids?
Thank you for your hard work.
Yeong Su was...
worried about you, too. So please don't resent him.
Attention!
Good job coming back alive!
This is the male barracks and that is the female barracks. Go back to your positions!
Are we going to rest here?
Even though we barely survived?
You can't help it, even though it's uncomfortable.
Placement is... on a first-come, first-served basis.
Go back to your positions!
What did he say?
Damn, that sly punk!
Hurry!
Thank you.
Daebak. It's so comfy.
I really wanted to take a shower. We have everything here.
Loyalty!
You did a good job.
Go to the headquarters.
Hey, look at this!
Hey!
Why?
- Stop it!
- Give it here!
Hey, I said I don't like that.
- Hey, get him! Get him!
- What, you punk?
Come here!
I said stop!
Hey, throw it! Throw it!
You deserve a wartime death penalty!
Leaving without permission, using unauthorized equipment, and disobeying orders.
Is it not enough?
I'm sorry.
Sorry?
Is that the face of a person who is actually apologetic?
- I'll just...!
- Lieutenant Colonel!
Next time, you'll be just shot to death.
Anyway, you managed to bring the kids safely.
At least we have something to report in front of the superiors and parents.
Thank you.
You crazy punk.
Get out.
That stupid punk. I can't even send him to a military prison.
Shall we send him to a military prison?
What are you talking about, you punk?
Just try doing half as much as him!
He looks like a real ajeossi!
And you guys are ajummas.
Take a video of this.
Hey, stop filming, you punk!
At least you recognize good looks.
This is better than I thought.
Sun, how do I look?
He said this is the biggest size.
Stop filming, Fucking Asshole!
You guys look good.
I love it, love it.
They look pretty.
I'm jealous.
They say we're no longer trainees.
We're recruits now.
But it feels weird...
now that I'm wearing a military uniform.
The memorial service is done now.
A lot of people couldn't come back.
Wu Taek and In Hye...
I still can't believe that
they are not here with us anymore.
We should shave this part well so that
your face shape looks different.
It's torn here.
Let me show you.
Look at this. What should I do?
- What are you doing?
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
You pervert punk!
Why, why, why?
Why, why? Is something wrong with my face?
I'm sorry!
- Ugh, my period just started!
- The thin one, the thin one.
How's your feeling, So Yeon? Are you okay?
Yes, I'm completely healed.
You all almost died because of me at that time.
I also almost died because I was so sorry.
But what if the scar doesn't disappear?
Wow! You're so cool!
Don't mention it!
- Isn't it heavy, Su Cheol?
- No, it's not.
Su Cheol, you must be so strong.
This is nothing.
Fighting, Yeong Su!
Fighting!
Oh! Yeong Su!
You should do some work, too.
Hey, how long have we been here?
I don't know, you punk. Hurry up!
When I first came here, I thought, "Fuck yes, I'm saved"
But this just turned out to be another place to do military training.
Put it in properly!
Would this happen if you helped it properly?
But aren't they just making us shovel too fucking much?
Digging drainage channels, digging trenches,
and digging fucking much for the encampment construction.
Damn, what the fuck. That's fucking screwed.
Hey, Sun Yi! I ate dirt. Sun Yi!
But Chi Yeol...
We'll be taken to the shelter before we take the college entrance exam, right?
Then we don't have much time left.
I didn't even start Math 2.
Can you study this situation? What the...
- Hey, it's gone.
- What?
My undies!
Oh, gosh! Hey, you guys took them, right?
- Oh, it's not me. It's really not me.
- Stop lying!
Such pervert punks!
Hey, here it is. It's so dirty!
I heard we're going to be discharged soon.
Is it true? Yes?
- Oh, Yu Jeong!
- Yes?
Did you hear anything?
Everyone is asking me, but I have no idea.
Yu Jeong.
You look really tired.
I'm fine.
Class President! Class President!
What are the side dishes for dinner?
- Class President!
- Yes.
Hey, Deok Jung. Are you playing over there?
- Are you holding it?
- Yes, but is this how we do it?
Geez, three people sleep in this small place?
I think it will be even too tight for two people.
Hey, hey, hey!
This is not a tent, but a rag.
Damn it! We're screwed, man. Wang Tae Man will alone take this entire tent.
Hey, hey, stop complaining.
Compared to other training, this is fun.
Think positively as if we're camping.
Oh, shit!
This is not going in! Fuck! What a piece of shit! Damn!
If it doesn't look good after opening up, then you will get to disassemble and reinstall it again.
It's a tent where we will sleep for real. So don't play around, okay?
Do it right!
- Sun Yi, since we're done with this, please watch out not to trip over it.
- Oka...
Hey! Lee Sun Yi! Hey! Class President!
Please come here. I don't want to be in the same group as her. Please change my group.
Wow, it's good that at least she's not asking her to breastfeed her.
Geez. Come on. Get in there.
The boys from Yongnong High School looked handsome.
They asked me for my number.
But you don't even have a cell phone.
How about the boy in Class 1 whom you dated before?
We're done already. He's not in the training.
How can I meet a guy who hasn't even fired a gun?
Men who haven't gotten military training aren't even men in my eyes anymore.
What a bullshit. Hey!
You do it. I can't do it anymore.
Hey, if you can't, how can I do it?
- Oh, gosh.
- Let me try.
Wow, Lee Na Ra!
- Hey, No Ae. Hold it tight!
- Wait, wait.
Oh, gosh. What's wrong with this?
One! Hey! What are you doing now? Seriously?
S-Sorry, sorry.
Hold it properly! Oh gosh!
Hi, Bo Ra.
Hey, No Ae.
Why don't you just leave?
- Why?
- I'm saying this for you, Idiot.
What's good for you if you stay here?
Are you crazy about college, too?
No, right? Whether it is college or whatever.
It could be dangerous if you're here.
I'm not going to leave.
All of my friends are here.
You don't have any friends!
Ae Seol does have a friend.
Gosh.
Forget it. I shouldn't even...
Don't be nosy. Know when to join.
What does nosy mean?
Hey, Lee Na Ra. Do you think you're something since you shoot well?
What is it to you what I say to No Ae Seol?
Since only to Ae Seol, you...
You must think you'll do fine on your own.
But do you think you'll still be fine if there's someone around dragging you down?
You don't even know any shit.
But you don't know, either.
It's not easy for me to do it well, either.
- What?
-  It's hard for everyone, but they are all trying hard.
Ae Seol is trying, too.
As you can see, most of the mid-sized spheres, except for some, have fallen.
It appears that only about 20% of the mini sphere fragments have been neutralized.
And unfortunately, about 50% of our military forces
were sacrificed in this process.
Currently, most of these spheres are concentrated in the city center.
In the outskirts of this area, relatively low numbers are distributed.
It seems that this is because this sphere is eating people as food.
So since they eat people,
there are a lot of these concentrated in a crowded place, right?
Yes, you are right.
And after it was discovered that this sphere was vulnerable to cold,
it is said that the U.N. is currently developing cryogenic lethal weapons
in addition to the existing DU ammunition.
How long are we just supposed to wait?
We're low on personnel.
It will get cold soon, so wait until then...
Then if the large sphere falls this time, we will all die.
We'll have to stop those monsters somehow
until the main force finishes clearing the spheres.
Hey.
What are we going to do with student reserve forces?
The military and the people are
well aware of your hard work.
Many sacrifices have been made, but
you are the proud sons and daughters of the Republic of Korea,
who are protecting this country from the threat of strange creatures.
So, please be proud of yourself.
- Hey.
- To end this war faster...
What's he trying to tell us with that long introduction, huh?
By any chance, are they going to send us home?
- Really?
- No way.
I'm nervous about this.
We will deliver important operational details now.
At 07:00 on the ensuing day
the 2nd platoon recruits of Seongjin High School 3-2
will carry out an operation to remove the sphere in Iri-eup.
- What?
- Operation?
What's this? Is he saying we're going to war?
- No Way!
- They said they'll send us home.
What does the ensuing day mean?
Tomorrow.
Be silent, everyone!
Second Platoon Leader.
Our second platoon will leave the current area at 7'o clock a.m. the following day.
We will join the first Battalion of the 3rd Brigade in the Iri-eup area and
be scheduled to be deployed in...
the operation to remove the sphere.
The goal of this operation is to move from Iri-eup
to Maesong-si through nearby densely populated areas and remove...
as many spheres as possible.
As you know, the situation isn't good.
Most of the nation's infrastructure has already collapsed and
the loss of troops is so great that
riflemen are desperately needed.
Don't forget that you're a soldier, too.
Excuse me, what about the college entrance exam?
I really need to take the college entrance exam.
Is he crazy?
Once we're done with the operation, everything will be on schedule.
If the operation is completed successfully,
not only you will receive extra points for the college entrance exam,
but everyone will also return to their family's arms.
You are dismissed!
Fuck. The vibe did feel off for some reason.
I asked the other kids.
They said we have the most people in our class, so we go out first.
So annoying...
Who were the bitches who were excited about being discharged?
I can't swallow the rice.
This is my first time seeing you not eating.
Well, it would be weird to have a good appetite in this situation.
Do you mean the final letters?
How can I deliver this to kids who
are already scared...
I will deliver it to them.
Just leave it.
If you do this, you'll be in trouble again, Platoon Leader.
Platoon Leader.
It's just because... everyone writes these before they go off for a mission.
And cut a little of your nails or hair and put it here.
This is...
for a funeral in case they can't retrieve our bodies.
W-W-What?
So it means we're going to die?
No, it's not that...
Why are they being so scary?
It's just a formality.
So why are they asking us to do something formal?
They're asking for this because it's dangerous.
Aren't we going to be discharged?
Why are they sending us out for the operation again?
I also have no idea, but...
Hey! If you don't know, ask them again.
Ask them if we have to go on the operation.
- Yu Ha Na.
- She's the class president, isn't she?
As Class President, why don't you even ask them about it?
And fuck! How could you just accept this just because they give it to you?
Hey! Why are you fucking yelling at the class president?
You couldn't even say a fucking word in front of Lieutenant Colonel earlier, you punk.
What, Fucker? She's the head.
Then she has to act on our behalf.
Are you fucking trying to get extra points on the college entrance exam or what? What the fuck!
- Just do it by yourself.
- Fucker, what did you say just now?
Let go of me. This motherfucker!
Shit!
Stop fighting!
Hurry and explain!
This motherfucker!
Hey, Kim Yu Jeong. Doesn't this bother you?
Aren't you scared?
Oh, fuck. This is bullshit!
Class President, I don't think this is right, either.
Fuck...
Jang Su. Actually, I became a class president
for the student record.
At first, I had no
sense of duty or responsibility.
You're the class president and
I'm the vice president because of a difference of one vote.
Did you know that?
It makes me feel relieved.
I don't think I could have done it like you.
Hey, Kimchi, are you sleeping?
No, I can't sleep.
Do you remember when we made a popularity ranking
for girls at the beginning of our school?
Yes, I remember that.
Was the number one Cha So Yeon back then?
And the number two was Ha Na?
Hey, after the girls found out later, they all got angry and went crazy.
I was fucking scared for real.
Right.
Hey, but these days, they don't wash and wear makeup.
So I can clearly see how they've changed.
Wow, I think this is the real fear of war.
Oh, I'm scared.
There are also some girls who haven't changed.
- Kimchi.
- What again?
At that time, we just had class,
went to a game room, and played around.
Every day went by without thinking.
I didn't even imagine that we'd be like this.
You crazy punks, you are so talkative. I can't sleep.
Oh, did we wake you up? Sorry. I'm so sorry.
Who can sleep right now?
It's hard to fall asleep because I think I need to sleep.
Hi!
Hey, you're not sleepy either, right?
Isn't it too cruel?
Our kids...
Oh, where did it go?
Everyone is here.
How can we sleep?
It's tomorrow. What should we do?
Oh, damn! I'm fucking scared.
It's on the outskirts, so it won't be too dangerous.
Hey, why would they ask us to write a goodbye letter if it's not dangerous?
But they said they'll let us go if it's done safely.
Fuck. We just have to trust them and go.
If we can make it through this safely...
I miss my mom and dad.
Me, too.
Oh, fuck!
Mom.
I want to eat my mom's kimchi jjigae.
Mom...
I miss my mom.
- I miss my mom.
- Shh!
Hey, hey, hey.
- Oh, it's hot.
- Aigo.
Hey!
Kim Deok Jung.
You guys...
I'm sorry.
We couldn't sleep. We'll go back to our place right away.
I should go to sleep. Please.
Guys...
I heard you didn't even eat dinner.
Sergeant Kim.
Yes.
Go bring them all here.
Yes, Sir.
- What's this?
- I don't know.
- It's bread.
♫  I play game, if this is hell, then let's say I came here on a school field trip  ♫
♫  After running around happily  ♫
♫  Travel voucher to take as a souvenir. The worst of worst. After enduring it  ♫
♫  I'll invite you to our graduation ceremony  ♫
♫  After all this time passes  ♫
♫  Will the ground that was soaked with rain turn into nourishment? Or will it bloom into flowers   ♫
♫  I already miss the blackboard with names of friends  ♫
The magic of hardtack becoming a cupcake.
Wow!
♫  I've never seen beyond the school gates  ♫
♫  No matter how much I think about it, there is no answer  ♫
Oh, Platoon Leader. Here!
Wow!
The smell alone is something else.
You must have been very hungry.
♫  But I didn't think I could do that in college  ♫
Catch!
But was the hardtack this delicious? I always threw it away because it was so dry.
- Tell me about it.
- The hardtack mountain is daebak, too.
Now, just looking at the hardtack will make me salivate like Pavlov's dog.
Hey, it's the dog of Flanders.
Or was his name Patrasche?
You should just be a dog.
Not Jo Jang Su!
Hey...
Oh, my gosh...
Hey!
Look at them!
- Hey! Who's playing with food?
- I don't know, Ajeossi!
Hey.
Hey! You can't pick up on the mood, can you?
- What?
- Won Bin...
Let go of me!
Kim Won Bin.
♫  Welcome to the K-Mars, it's colorful every night  ♫
♫  Those demons are always asking me how much I can take  ♫
♫  I can't sleep because of the sun  ♫
♫  Where is the face I can rely on no matter where I am?  ♫
♫  I can't find it right here where I am  ♫
♫  I want to shout out to you in this chaos  ♫
♫  I saw a heart that seemed too damaged (I saw it)  ♫
♫  I broke down at the unfamiliar sight of the bleeding  ♫
- We're a mess.
- I'm covered in it.
- Look at you.
- You look worse.
Aren't you too childish, Platoon Leader?
You look like you're having even more fun than we are.
- You're too much.
- That's right.
What did you do before you came here, Platoon Leader?
I was in a combat unit.
No, I mean before that.
Were you in college?
Do you have a girlfriend?
You guys...
I won't answer any questions that have nothing to do with training. Okay?
The platoon leader has a girlfriend.
- No, he doesn't!
- Wow.
What's your plan after this war is over and
we all return? Are you going back to college?
I said I'm not answering questions that have nothing to do with training.
It has to do with training.
If we know more about you,
our platoon members will become more efficient.
- Yes. Just tell us.
- Tell us.
Tell us.
Tell us! Tell us!
Tell us!
You guys!
I was in the ROTC, so I came here after graduating from college.
(T/N: Reserve Officer Training Corps - A college program to recruit and train military officers)
I still have about a year left in my service period. But I'm not sure if
I'll just get discharged or apply for an extension.
That's it!
Extension? Why would you do more of something like this?
That's what I'm saying. Isn't it too tough?
- It's definitely better to go out into society.
- True, true.
Society is tough too, Guys.
Since I'm also still young, I don't know too much, but
even going out into society is like going to war.
If the entrance exam is a local war, then is society a world war?
This moment...This is the happiest moment...
Excuse me...
When will this war end?
Will we...
be able to go back home?
They said they'd let us go home if we complete this operation.
Can we believe that?
Please don't think we don't know anything since we are kids.
- Please tell us the truth.
- What if we trust them and get betrayed again?
I don't know when this war will end,
but you all just have to keep one thing in mind.
We will definitely survive until the end.
I can't end this war,
but I'll help you finish it well,
without anyone getting hurt.
I can promise you that.
First Squad. Shooter. Jo Jang Su.
Assistant Shooter. Guk Yeong Su.
Second Squad. Shooter. Kim Yu Jeong.
Assistant Shooter. Wang Tae Man.
Search Team. Jo Yeong Sin. Kwon Il Ha.
Sniper. Lee Na Ra. Observer. Do Su Cheol.
After arriving in the operation area, the assault team will be on alert.
During the movement, the two people in the search teams act as advance guards at the forefront.
Yes, Sir!
This is a sphere detector.
Sphere detector?
Is it detecting spheres?
Hey, it's called a sphere detector. What could it be for?
Is it a prototype?
- What's that?
- It's a product that hasn't been fully developed yet.
That's right. Since it's not perfect yet,
you should not rely too much on the sphere detector.
What is the detection radius?
It's one kilometer in undeveloped land.
In the case of the city center or town,
the detection radius will be 500 to 700 m.
So...
Always be alert.
Yes, Sir!
That's it!
Let's see. Let's see.
It looks like the higher ups aren't just sitting around doing nothing after all.
Tell me about it. Why didn't they give this to us earlier?
Class President, look!
Oh, what's this? Why can't I get any signal?
Because there are no spheres!
This idiot. Oh, gosh.
Three minutes to go! 2nd Platoon!
Get in the vehicles in squads! Implement!
Implement!
Hey, Deok Jung!
Oh, yes.
Platoon Leader.
We need equipment to clean this up.
Let's search the area first.
Hey! Walk properly.
How does this work?
Nerds are different.
Most of us just say this is fucking interesting.
We don't care how it works.
It's not because I'm a nerd, it's because of my family's genes.
It's a good gene.
Boom!
Gosh! Just go first.
You go first!
Did you set the fire selector to safe?
What?
Yes, I did.
Don't shoot me in the back of the head.
To set the fire selector to safe, you just have to turn this a little bit.
- I'm scared.
- I'm scared, too.
Hey, No Ae. Hurry!
Okay.
Class President. Why do you keep looking back?
We need to be on the rear guard.
Hey, then just walk backward.
Would that be better?
Are you okay?
Oh, geez.
Thank you.
Are you really walking backward because I said so?
You're more foolish than I expected, Class President.
Wow.
I don't feel well.
What's with me?
Let's see.
I know well about women.
Hey, Yeong Su, you should not do that.
Then what should I do?
To do well...
be manly and cool.
Na Ra, be careful.
Okay.
Ha Na, be careful.
Fuck off!
She told me to fuck off.
Are you anxious?
For what?
That couple shot.
Feeling like a romantic drama.
And a man who's just watching from here.
Hey. Just be quiet.
I'm already disturbed enough.
Hey, since we're going like this,
doesn't it feel like we're on some kind of operation?
Hey, hey, hey. We're on a real operation right now. Focus!
Show yourself, spheres!
- Oh! Get out of my way!
- Oh! My goodness! My goodness!
Wu Hui Rak. What's going on?
It's n-nothing.
Platoon Leader.
What's that?
- Oh, fuck!
- Oh! Daebak!
It's coke! Let me have a sip!
I'm going to save it, so don't even think about it and go!
You're petty! Please share!
You can't shake the coke.
But this is mine, so I can shake it.
Oh, shit!
I love it.
Oh, shit! We won't drink it since it's dirty.
Oh! Platoon Leader!
Kwon Il Ha.
Locate it.
It is 300 m southwest.
Oh, shit. Hey, why did you come here? What's with you?
What's that?
Platoon Leader!
- Platoon Leader!
- Here are the spheres. Hurry!
- Aren't those spheres?
Shoot! Hurry!
Shoot! Hurry, hurry, hurry!
I don't think I can.
Hold!
Second Platoon! Fire!
Hey! Left side! Left side!
One, two, three!
- Shoot.
- Got it.
Where is it?
Position yourself, aim, and fire!
- Die.
Hey, No Ae. Do it properly!
What should I do? Let me change the magazine and shoot it again.
Oh, it's hot.
Geez! Why are you touching it with your hands, Idiot?
Guk Yeong Su! Lee Sun Yi!
- Support on the right!
- Yes, Sir.
- Jo Jang Su! Wang Tae Man!
- Yes, Sir!
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Sorry.
Hey! This way!
Oh, shit! I can't fucking aim right.
No, No! Wang Tae Man!
Run away, Wang Tae Man! Wang Tae Man, hurry up!
It's fucking not aiming right. Jang Su! Jang Su!
Jo Jang Su, please help!
Save the DU ammo!
Fuck! Where are they? Where are they? Where, Class President?
Guys, over there!
Oh, fuck! Hey, I don't have a magazine.
Hui Rak, give me magazine. Hurry, hurry!
- What the fuck are you doing?
- Fuck! Fuck! What's this?
Why aren't they coming out?
That's what I'm saying.
Cover!
What's going on?
I don't see it.
No more spheres?
They all seem to be hiding.
- Where are you going?
- I'll go find and get rid of them.
Hey!
- What are you going to do by yourself?
- Let go of me!
What?
- Are they still here?
- What?
Come over here.
Hey! Behind you! Spheres are behind you!
Spheres!
It's coming.
Where did it come from?
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
Position yourself and guard your surroundings.
- Go back to your positions!
- Back to our positions.
Back to our positions.
Jo Yeong Sin.
Jo Yeong Sin! Locate the sphere.
Fuck!
What should we do now?
Find all of them and remove them.
Yes, Sir.
One, two, three!
Lady first.
You go first.
Oh, shit. Ouch!
Shit!
Hey! Sphere!
Hey, wait! Fuck!
Oh, shit!
Damn it!
What happened?
We removed three.
We just missed one.
Get out the way!
Oh, gosh!
Ha Na!
Let's go!
Let's go! Hurry!
I shouldn't have saved them.
Oh, shit!
Shit!
What the fuck!
Hey, you go to the left! And Kim Chi Yeol!
You follow me!
Oh, fuck!
- Na Ra!
- Stop crying!
Fuck!
Hey, stop crying!
Hey!
It's too dark. Shall we just not go in?
No. A sphere is detected. We have to get it.
- Oh, shit.
- Hey, just get the lantern out.
Okay.
Oh, fuck. Why do I always go first?
- Oh, shit.
- Oh, sorry!
Gosh! Hey!
Put it away!
I don't think they're here.
- Cha So Yeon.
- Yes.
Okay.
Oh, shit!
- There it is.
- Kill it.
I can't see it. I can't see it.
Kim Deok Jung!
Hey!
Deok Jung!
Are you okay?
Oh, I'm alive.
- I'm alive.
- You're fine.
- You surprise me.
- Is he okay?
Yes, he looks fine.
Oh, gosh. Hey!
Shh.
♫  I thought everybody wanna live peaceful. So I fought for equal rights and inner peace  ♫
♫  But ain't nobody equal, and this is the sequel. Don't sell it. Since not even one memory is worth anything. Respawn   ♫
♫  Rebirth, reborn. No matter what you say, the important thing is the basics  ♫
♫  There is no mercy for those who cannot keep it. You're on the list, ho   ♫
♫  Blood splatter on my soul. It is a luxury to hope that no scars are left behind   ♫
♫ Now, even in front of a grave, it feels more natural for me to be calm, huh  ♫
♫ The world is not easy, but it doesn't rest either. Time is ticking. I ain't got no time for sleeping  ♫
♫ So, I cannot rest and must stay awake. If you don't get it, then forget it. If you get it, then get it, ah ♫
♫  Santa Claus is dead  ♫
♫  The book of fairytale is closed, only thing in front of me is the reality, wake up, uh!  ♫
♫  I thought it was only in the movies, but in peace  ♫
♫ Hell already exists in the comments section ♫
♫ The world is yours but war's going on outside ♫
♫  No man is safe from. It's either death or survival  ♫
♫  Save the time to wake up the boy in you. Turn on beast mode  ♫
♫  If you don't take it away, you'll be taken away  ♫
♫  Get a hold of your mind  ♫
♫  If you miss it, you lose not only yourself but also your friends  ♫
♫  A crisis is a crisis because it comes suddenly. Wake up and get yourself together   ♫
♫  Miracles do not exist in reality. Even with gathered strength, it is selfish. It ain't joke   ♫
♫ It's a war. Gotta open your eyes yay-yea  ♫
♫  Nowhere to hide yay-yea  ♫
♫  Nothing is right, ain't it  ♫
♫  The war's on outside, everyday  ♫
♫  Get your as, get your ass, get your ass   ♫
♫  Get your ass up. In a game of snatching and holding back, the spoils go to the winner  ♫
♫  A crisis is an opportunity for learning. Pull it all, we never asked. That's Seoul's Code of Conduct. ♫
♫  Masquerade ball. I know that not everyone who is laughing is actually happy, okay ♫
♫  As tension sets in, my brain becomes addicted to that feeling  ♫
♫  I'm a slave for that, no cancelled. Time has already been pulled, and the bowstring has been placed  ♫
♫  I keep pulling twice as fast. If I can't stop anyway, I'll pull even more. I'ma go get the bag ♫
♫  Before everyone's breath becomes short, they think stages easily ♫
♫  I wake up from sleep hundreds of times and say it. I've put everything on the line. You better have something to pay ♫
♫  You'll be an adult at a blink of an eye  ♫
♫  Friends will leave, and it will repeat again  ♫
♫ Without time to be sad ♫
♫  Today's sun is blinding  ♫
♫  You forget your purpose and move like you're drifting in a tide  ♫
♫  When you look behind...  ♫