It's okay.
All the spheres have been eliminated.
What happened?
Is this a dream?
Is it?
There must be survivors over there too.
It's a boy...
Two people?
Don't step on him.
Don't step on him!
Hey...
I'm sorry.
Don't step on my friend!
Don't step on him...
My friend...
My friend... Don't step on him...
Don't step on him!
Hey, what happened?
I don't know.
Anything?
Fuck...
Excuse me...
Excuse me?
Platoon Leader!
It's not reacting to any spheres.
This way.
The smell...
Any survivors?
Everyone here must be dead.
I don't think there are any survivors.
I wonder if Mom and Dad are okay.
Guys, check over here.
This must've been the residence hall.
Are you guys the only survivors?
They said all we had to do is deliver the supplies to the shelter.
But when we arrived...
How about the commander?
I don't know. He disappeared.
Why did you guys stay here without a commander?
Because they told us to wait.
So we waited. We did what we were told.
But why...
I know it's tough, but please calm yourself down...
and let's talk after we wrap things up here.
Yu Jeong, take care of your new friends.
Aren't you guys hungry?
Do you want to eat something?
There...
Hamil High School, third grade, Kim Dong Hun.
Ae Seol, Hamil High School, third grade, Kim Dong Hun.
Jang Sun Yeong.
Jang Sun Yeong...
Did you see her eyes earlier?
They weren't focused. They looked empty.
This is horrific.
Had I been left alone, I wonder if I would've ended up like them.
Do you think we could survive?
It's a small shelter, but it's been completely demolished as if they were attacked by surprise.
The shelters are located in the outskirts, where there aren't any spheres.
And there are no traces of the spheres that have fallen outside.
I wonder how the small spheres attacked this place.
The spheres looking for food must have come here in droves.
How did they know that there was a shelter here?
Platoon Leader.
No Ae Seol is going to cause a major issue later on!
She was always weird, but she's really weird now.
She will cause a terrible accident if this continues.
You don't have to worry about Ae Seol.
She's doing very well, and she will continue to do so.
How much do you know about No Ae Seol anyway?
Just don't regret it later.
Because of that bitch...
Bo Ra...
No spheres, no spheres, no spheres...
But seriously, what are we going to do?
I heard their commander ran away.
I'm glad we have the platoon leader and Oppa Won Bin.
Right?
You guys must be starving. Hurry and eat.
What are you doing?
Why the gun...
I...
ran away.
My friends...
My friends begged me to save them...
But I ran away...
by myself.
That's...
They all died.
No...
It's not your fault.
I did the same thing. When my friends died,
I was busy running away.
It's not your fault at all.
Please... put the gun down.
It's dangerous.
Yun Seo...
Please put the gun down...
Don't come closer!
Yun Seo.
That's your name, right?
I know it was tough...
and scary.
From now on,
we will protect you.
So put that...
gun down.
Yun Seo, please put the gun down.
Please...
You said we would be okay.
You said we just had to do as we were told.
You told us to wait.
And then you'll run away again anyway.
Yun Seo!
Extra credit points?
Who the hell cares about all that?
What the hell!
I don't believe you anymore. Because of all you guys,
because of you grownups, they all died.
My friends all died...
You guys killed them all! You guys killed them!
No!
- What was that?
- Shit!
What was that?
Wasn't that a gunshot?
Where? Where?
I'm so sorry...
Won Bin...
Oh, no...
Wake up! Kim Won Bin!
- Oh, no...
- Bring me the hemostatic!
(T/N: A substance used to stop bleeding after injuries)
Bring us the hemostatic! Hurry!
Fuck!
Won Bin...
No...
It's not my fault...
The grownups...
It's all the grownups' fault.
It's not my fault.
It's not my fault...
It's not...
Wild Goose, this is Seagull.
Over.
I—
Will Hyeong be okay?
Fortunately, the bullet went through his shoulder.
- It's not life-threatening.
- Seriously...
But we still need to treat him quickly.
I'm fine. So don't worry too much.
- Hyeong! Are you okay?
- Geez...
I told you I'm okay.
Just stay down.
Thank you.
You guys can go now.
Deok Jung, what time is it?
Ten o'clock.
It's time for his painkiller.
I'll give it to him. Good work.
I won't go. I want to stay with him.
- Come on.
- Why...
- Hurry and come.
- Are you sure he's okay?
He will be okay!
Aigo.
P-P-Platoon Leader...
P-Please be gentle...
I want to punch you, but I'm holding back.
Who the hell do you think you are to put yourself there?
If something happens to you, what will happen to the kids?
I'm not confident that I could do it.
That female student... Don't blame her too much.
She must be so confused and afraid.
She must feel so betrayed by the grownups
whom she trusted would protect her.
And I'm one of those grownups.
So where do we go from here?
I will have to do my very best.
How is Ajeossi?
He's okay.
What a relief.
Hey, what if those guys shoot at us, too?
Hey! Be quiet!
They could hear you.
I'm just nervous about it!
- That, that mouth of yours!
- Shit!
But you know, I do understand her.
I felt like she was saying out loud what was in my head.
Platoon Leader wants all of us to gather.
We will retreat first thing in the morning and return to the base camp.
Can we go back? How about our mission?
I can't guarantee your safety here.
While I can't even determine how many spheres are out there,
and if they were to attack us all at once,
I don't think we could handle them.
Platoon Leader, including what happened last time,
wouldn't you be in big trouble if you keep disobeying the command?
I have determined that your safety comes first at the moment.
I'll take responsibility.
So you guys don't have to worry.
Sentinels, be sure to stand guard securely. The rest of you, go to sleep.
We'll be on the move as soon as the sun rises in the morning.
That's all.
Is that what's going to happen?
What's going on here?
It's going to be really tough for him.
It's so sudden.
Are we really returning?
Let's just go for now.
If this is what a shelter looks like,
I wonder what our school is like right now.
But if we return, wouldn't Platoon Leader be disciplined?
What if he goes to the military prison?
Military prison?
This is punishable by execution.
Execution?
No way...
Hey. Don't say such an ominous thing.
Now that I think about it, Platoon Leader sure is a rebel, isn't he?
He's doing that because of us.
But you know...
- What happens to our extra credit points if we fail our mission?
- What the fuck?
We can only get our points if we succeed in our mission.
Fuck, that asshole sure likes to blabber bullshit so consistently.
But still, what if they don't send us back to our parents for not completing our mission?
Hey. Someone might face execution. Do you really want to worry about that?
No, I mean, I'm just...
Let's think positively.
Although it could be dangerous, we're returning. That's a good thing.
The culprit is ultimately at the crime scene.
My cola!
Fuck, I definitely put it here!
- Park So Yun.
- What?
- It was you, right?
-  What the hell? Don't accuse an innocent person!
What are you staring at? Shit!
I think he drank it already. Shit...
Fuck! Who took it!
Hey! Shit!
What are you doing?
Move! Move!
That's enough, Asshole!
Hey, did you see it? Did you?
Where are you going?
Cha So Yeon.
It's bedtime. Why aren't you sleeping?
W-Well, I just...
I was just worried about returning.
It's not something you guys should worry about.
Did you come here to say that?
Excuse me?
Actually...
I wanted to say something to you, Platoon Leader.
To say something?
Platoon Leader,
I actually...
Platoon Leader...
- Kim Deok Jung.
- Gosh, you scared me!
What's going on?
T-To the restroom...
- Go ahead.
- Thank you.
Why don't you hurry and go?
You need an amazing amount of focus to do that...
What did you want to say?
It's nothing. Goodnight.
Wu Hui Rak?
I wonder what happened.
That Kim Deok Jung, Shithead.
She's back.
So annoying...
Hey, did you confess to him?
No. I don't think it's time.
Seriously...
I'll do it when we return.
What's so attractive about the platoon leader?
The love in the midst of war is meant to be beautiful.
What the hell? Crazy Bitch.
Na Ra, you don't have to be so intense about it.
Okay?
Yeah, right.
I'll stand guard. Why don't you rest for a little while?
I'm okay.
I guess she's okay.
Should I tell her?
No, I'd be a psycho if I told her at a time like this.
But still...
wouldn't it be my chance to tell her when we're alone?
Hey, you know...
Huh?
Well...
by chance, do you...
do you like...
d-do you like...
Do you have a celebrity you like?
It's a sphere.
What?
The detector isn't responding, though.
It's outside of the detector's perimeter.
It's about 2 km away from here.
Do you mean there was an exchange of signals?
I can't be certain, but I saw a light flash from a large sphere in the sky.
The sphere that looked like the leader lit up, too.
And after that, they started moving toward somewhere.
It looked like they were communicating with each other.
If that's the case,
they exchange signals and
a few of them would go off somewhere and come back.
That would be the pattern, right?
Do you think they're looking for something?
- By chance...
- Reconnaissance.
That's right. It's as if they're doing reconnaissance.
They're watching to see where we're moving to.
They're much more intelligent than we give them credit for.
They went as far as this area.
I wonder what's there.
I heard there's a shelter there as well.
Our platoon leader said that.
That there's a small shelter there too.
Wait a minute. If so,
they received their order from the large ones in the sky,
and they decided their next target would be the shelter in the area.
Gosh, that makes no sense.
Because there is...
-  a lot of food for them there.
- Pardon?
A shelter that's supposed to be a safe hiding place
has just become a place where their prey congregates.
To make it easier for the spheres to find them.
Geez...
We have to notify the troops who are in that shelter.
But our communication line has been cut off.
So what do we do?
As for us...
we'll make our retreat in the morning as planned.
- How about that shelter?
- We can't handle that many.
Let's return as quickly as possible and find another solution there.
But what if the spheres attack them before then?
At their speed, it will be too late even if the support troops show up.
What are you guys talking about? What do you want us to do?
That's right! It's an order, so we have no choice.
Don't we get to go home only if we kill all the spheres?
Didn't you see the Hamil High kids? Do you all want to die?
He's right! It's too dangerous.
Sun Yi, you're scared, too, right?
I'm scared.
But I'm sure someone's parents must be over there.
Who will protect them?
If we leave, they'll just send other kids.
Seongjin High came after Hamil High,
and another school would just follow after that.
From how I read the room, I think it's been decided.
Thank you.
I get to laugh thanks to you.
For some reason, doesn't it seem like the kids have matured drastically?
Wow! I'm so proud of them.
Is this how a parent feels watching their children grow up?
How old are you, seriously?
I'm forty-one years old.
The pain traveled.
It's going to be hectic from now on. So stay alert.
What are you talking about? I'm a patient.
You're not exempt.
Platoon Leader, isn't that too much?
- I said no exemptions.
- But I got shot! Seriously...
Attention, everyone.
To seek out and eliminate every single sphere
spread out all over the town is too dangerous.
That's right.
So we will gather
all the spheres in Mesong City College here
and eliminate them in one blow.
- But how?
- In one blow? How?
Eliminate them in one blow?
- How, how?
- Is that possible?
Everyone,
listen carefully to what I'm about to say.
Be careful.
Oh, that!
Why, why, why?
Hey, this is it, right?
I think this is it.
First, combine the DU ammunition and the dynamite
to make DU explosives.
Gently, gently...
Hey, be careful!
Be careful.
Careful.
Shit...
It's okay.
- Platoon 2, attention!
- Attention!
Find each assigned installation spot and install the explosives carefully.
After the installation is completed,
quickly make your way up to Seolbonggwan rooftop and stand by.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, Sir!
Each unit, to your position.
Loyalty!
Unit 1, restore power in the mechanical room.
Once all the power is restored, everyone else
will install DU explosives in the main building.
Unit 6, until the DU explosives are installed,
observe the spheres' movements,
and signal the units, so they could complete their mission.
If the spheres show even the slightest unusual movements during the mission,
report to me immediately.
Su Cheol, what are they telling us to do after making the explosives?
What were you doing, not listening to Platoon Leader?
My nail broke. So I was distracted with that.
Install the explosives, then lure the spheres, and then...
And then?
That's simple!
Do you think that's simple?
If we fail to install the explosives, we die.
If we can't lure the spheres, we die.
If we can't kill them all in one-blow, we die.
And if we get distracted during the mission like you, we die.
How about it? Is it simple?
Where? Where do I need to stand guard?
Deok Jung.
- Kim Deok Jung!
- Wait a minute!
- Leave me alone.
- Take it!
- Jun Hui.
- So Yeon, hold this.
Geez, what did you learn?
Do you think this is easy? Shit...
Once we're done installing all the DU explosives in the main building,
we'll close off all the doors to the outside.
Then quickly move to Seolbonggwan rooftop and stand by.
We have to put the explosives here, right?
Yes. Give it to me. I'll do it.
But what's this smell?
I've been smelling something similar to the spheres from earlier.
The spheres' smell?
Their unique fishy smell.
What's with this atmosphere?
Guk Yeong Su, do you like Cha So Yeon?
What do you mean? No.
Look at this punk. You really must like her.
Hey. Stop it.
Hey, Cha So Yeon, how can you say the guy who likes you stinks?
That would hurt his feelings so fucking badly. Isn't that right?
Stop it.
Hey, what the... I don't smell anything.
Cha So Yeon, smell him again.
Fuck it! Stop it!
You motherfucker, you're insane.
- Hey.
- Is now the time for this?
Are you guys out of your mind?
Hey. I'll see you later, you fucker.
After we lure all the spheres and lock all the doors,
we'll detonate the DU explosives and eliminate all the spheres.
The spheres started moving!
What?
Where?
Hold it.
Platoon Leader, the spheres are acting weird.
I think they're about to move.
Are they already moving?
Fuck.
Hey. Let's hurry.
The others.
How about everyone?
They're not done installing the explosives.
How about the others?
- Hey, did you hear the radio?
- Yes, I heard.
How could they be here so quickly?
What do you mean? We just have to do it faster!
Hey, go, go, go!
Are they already on the move?
This is weird...
What are you doing? Run!
Before the spheres arrive at the shelter, we have to make them come toward us.
How many more to go?
We still have quite a few left.
If we don't lure them now, the shelter will be attacked. They could probably cover this distance in 10 minutes.
Ten minutes...
We will wrap this up in ten minutes and move out.
Platoon 2, begin luring the spheres.
Yeong Su, can you do it?
Yes, I think it's possible.
We'll now begin Operation "Lure the Spheres."
Everyone, wrap up what you're doing in 10 minutes and go to Seolbonggwan.
What is he saying?
Shit!
Move, move! I'll do it!
Hurry!
We don't have time.
One, two, three.
Fuck! It's too loud!
Hey, my hands are trembling. This isn't working!
Hey, let me try!
Help me.
Is it not done yet? We have to go now.
Done, done!
- Hey, is it done?
- Yes.
Do I really do it?
- Do it!
- Shit!
What are you doing? Hurry up and break it!
They're almost here! Hurry!
Hey, where are the others?
We have to go!
Let's go! We have to go! Let's go!
Let's go!
Platoon Leader, we have to leave now.
I have to connect everything. I'm almost there.
We'll do the rest.
Wrap up the hall area.
Let's go.
I'll help you.
They started to swarm over this way.
Why aren't they coming?
- Bo Ra!
- Guys, where are the others?
Where? Where?
There are so freaking many!
We're fucked.
Platoon Leader, you have to leave now!
Run!
You guys go ahead.
Sergeant Kim!
I'll be right behind you. Be careful.
Class President, what are you doing? Hurry.
How many more to go?
We have a few more.
Fuck it...
We don't have time! Finish it now!
Hey, they went toward the main building, right?
I can't see them!
Hey, let's go down for now.
Seriously!
- What do we do?
- They can't be coming so fast like this.
Guys, come down!
Hey, what? What's going on?
Shit!
Go this way for now!
That way?
- Hey, what?
- What? Why are they going that way?
- Hey, just do this. Hurry.
- Shit!
Platoon Leader,
the spheres are nearby.
I'll wrap this up. Go to Seolbonggwan.
I'll help you.
The kids' safety comes first.
Take the kids. Hurry.
Please hurry up and come out.
Guys, let's go down first.
I don't want to. I won't go.
- Hurry and go.
- I don't want to.
Hurry!
I don't want to go!
Hurry and go!
Shit! Go! Go!
Shit. How many are there exactly?
Why are there so many?
More are coming.
Where is everyone else?
Oh?
Guys...
Let's go.
First of all, we get there safely.
Shit!
They should be here by now...
- Why aren't they here yet?
- Hey, hey, they're here!
Yeong Sin! Over here!
Yeong Sin...
Why is it only the two of you? How about the rest?
How about the rest of you? The rest...
Shit! What the hell?
Jo Jang Su, set up the computer.
How about Platoon Leader? Where is the platoon leader?
What happened?
Everyone...
until we hear from Platoon Leader,
we stand by here.
Why?
So Yeon, what happened?
So Yeon, where is the platoon leader?
Why isn't he coming?
Cha So Yeon.
Hey, what? What?
Platoon 2 of Seongjin High. This is your platoon leader speaking.
Platoon Leader.
Begin...
the detonation now.
What?
But you haven't left yet, Platoon Leader!
I'm out. So detonate now.
You must detonate now to eliminate the spheres.
Platoon Leader, no. Get out now! Now!
Platoon Leader, I'll be right there.
Do you all want to die now?
Kim Won Bin, come to your senses now.
If you don't detonate now,
we all die.
No... No, Platoon Leader...
Please hurry and leave now! Please!
Detonate now, Kim Won Bin.
I can't get out of here anyway. Are you going to have me die in vain?
This is an order. Detonate now.
It looks like the spheres will leave the building soon.
At this rate, it's really going to be...
No...
There is no other way.
But you promised...
You said you'd protect us to the end.
So, please hurry and get out of there!
Please!
I'm sorry.
For not keeping my promise
of keeping you safe to the end...
And...
for dragging you guys into this war as a grownup...
I thought you guys were just a bunch of kids who wouldn't listen to me.
But now that I think about it,
I'm so grateful to you,
and I'm proud of you.
Thanks to you guys,
I wasn't afraid of this war,
despite the fact that it seemed endless to me at times.
So trust and rely on friends who are next to you
to the very end,
and I hope you protect each other.
And...
don't die.
That's my last command as your platoon leader.
Begin the detonation.
That's all.
Platoon Leader. Platoon Leader! Platoon Leader!
No! No... This isn't happening. No! No...
- Give it to me.
- No...
Let go of me!
Platoon Leader!
Platoon Leader...
What do we do now?
Please answer me.
Platoon Leader!
- Don't...
- Please don't
Don't!
- Don't!
- Fuck! Fuck!
(T/N: Membership training: a retreat during which people from the same organization travel together for a series of group bonding and/or training activities)
Please don't do it...
- Don't do it...
- Don't...
No...
Please don't...
No! Please...
No...
Platoon Leader!
No!