I’d like to propose
that Petchprakai try adjusting its promotion.
If we promote it as
“vertical Likay,”
it should be much more interesting.
Do you think people will like our pilot?
Did you put up a notice for Guy’s series?
We’re on Guy’s team.
You got this!
I like dogs too.
Especially big ones.
We’ll get through this together.
It’s all gone.
Besides the clothes, is anything else missing?
The jewelry too.
Those were Father and Mother’s heirlooms.
No way.
Could it be those three?
Have they been acting strange lately?
They’ve been glued to their phones lately.
More than anything else.
You guys…
Are you sure you want to do this now?
They just split up.
Now is the best time.
They just called me.
Saying if I don’t pay them back,
they’ll come after us here.
I won’t risk anyone getting into trouble.
This is our only chance to get away.
What about these costumes?
Are you really sure
you want to take them?
At first, I wasn’t sure,
but this evening I saw P’Phet and P’Ploy
get by without costumes.
But we don’t have any Likay costumes.
No jobs, no money.
If we don’t go now, they’ll—
Think about it.
The whole house is chaotic right now.
No one will pay attention to us.
This is the only time we can leave
without getting caught.
Thank you for everything.
And I’m sorry for doing this.
They might not understand,
but if we stay,
they’ll definitely come after us.
P’Phet shouldn’t have to take the blame
for what we did.
I’m sorry, P’Phet.
P’Ploy…
Pleng…
Guy…
If I ever have money,
I’ll come back and repay everything.
Every baht.
Every costume.
Everything.
Let’s go.
Is everyone here?
I want to go over what’s missing.
Ping, Pong, and Chae aren’t here.
I saw them go shower a while ago.
They’re still not back.
Wait a second.
I just saw the bathroom was empty.
This feels strange. I’ll go check on them.
I’ll go with you.
Let’s go.
Now’s the time.
Thank you for everything.
And I’m sorry for doing this.
You’re still awake, P’Phet?
Why do you look so pale?
Hey—
The things…
Where did everything go, P’Phet?
It’s not just the things.
It’s all the memories of this house.
Ping, Pong, and Chae have left our troupe, Ploy.
Then you should report it.
This isn’t a small matter anymore.
No.
They’re our family.
We’ve been together for years.
I don’t want anyone going to jail.
This way.
Family?
Look at what they did.
Is that what family does?
P’Phet…
Your kindness
might bring the whole troupe down.
I believe there must be a reason
that pushed them to do this.
So…
what are you going to do next?
Then we have to let everyone know, Ploy,
that the Petchprakai Troupe
is not something anyone can mess with.
P’Phet…
What are you going to do?
Don’t tell me you’re posting it on Facebook.
I’m not exposing anyone.
I just want everyone to know that
our Petchprakai Troupe
is not something anyone can hurt
and walk away from.
P’Phet…
Have you really thought this through?
I didn’t mention anyone, Ploy.
I’m just posting what actually happened.
That we were robbed of what mattered most.
And I want everyone to know
that no matter how many times we fall,
we can always get back up.
Anyone trying to hurt our troupe,
once we find them,
we won’t let them get away with it.
This troupe is our home.
Even if someone betrays us,
I will protect it.
Hey…
Are you awake?
I don’t know when it started,
but my heart races when I look at you.
At first,
I thought I just liked you on TV.
But being this close,
it’s not just that anymore.
If you like me that much,
then don’t run away.
Was I sleep-talking?
So you finally said it.
This morning,
it felt like someone woke me up.
Like they were saying something sweet.
Crazy.
No, not really.
Who would say something like that?
But it’s strange…
it sounded like you.
The tone was like someone
who’s been secretly in love for a long time.
Don’t say that.
I just want to know if it’s true.
True…
or not?
So this is how you tease me now?
Then
you owe me an answer.
Let’s eat.
Okay.
Usually,
Ping, Pong, and Chae would sit there
making everyone laugh every morning.
♪ Turn it into a bong ♪
Hey—
But now…
it’s so quiet it feels empty.
It’s not just the laughter that’s gone,
it’s like the whole spirit of the troupe is gone too.
Even without them,
we still have to keep going.
Hey—
I went to look into it.
I asked everyone from the pork seller
to the fish seller.
I questioned the whole market like it was a big case.
But no one has seen Ping, Pong, or Chae.
But one lady was acting nervous,
saying her bananas were gone.
So I had to go full undercover.
I helped her search for them from under the pan to behind the shop, and unbelievably,
and ended up with fried bananas.
I failed the case—I couldn’t find them.
So Detective Pleng Chai
closed the case.
But—
it turned into a banana case.
I tried to search for them.
I really tried , but I couldn’t find them.
So I ended up helping her find bananas instead.
Fried bananas.
P’Phet…
I think Pleng’s got something.
Even when he jokes, it’s funny.
It feels natural too—interesting, right?
Yeah, true.
We’re missing a comedian now, right?
Yeah.
Someone who can lighten the mood.
And he’s standing right here.
Looks like our banana case detective
should try something new.
What do you mean?
You want me to investigate someone?
Banana Case Part Two?
No.
I want you
to try being the comedian.
Me?
What do you want me to do?
Stand there frying bananas on stage?
No.
Not that far.
I just think if you really try,
you might make everyone laugh like
they did before.
If everyone wants me to do it,
I’ll try frying bananas.
Not fried bananas.
(Phet Thae) It’s a “banana joke.”
(Ploy Ying) Ha! (Pleng Chai) Ha!
It’s “eat bananas,” idiot.
Ha!
Wanna try some? Fresh out.
(Phet Thae) Yeah, I’m hungry.
(Pleng Chai) Ha!
What is this?
Hey, our new comedian.
News travels fast.
Figures, coming from the social police.
Of course.
But please,
don’t call me that.
I’m not confident yet.
Here.
Hey, hey—
add some sugar first.
Is it good?
It’s good.
Water—
Here—
Try this.
How do you choke on just bread like that?
That was close.
Not sure if you’re funny,
but watching you eat bread already is.
You’re laughing too hard.
Ow—
Don’t stress.
Don’t worry, okay?
You may not be as good as those three yet,
but I think
if you just be yourself,
it’s already charming.
Finish eating and go help P’Phet.
Stop sitting around—give me that water.
Okay, okay—go help P’Phet.
Hey you—
You still say “I love you” so stiff.
Look me in the eyes.
Okay.
I…
love you.
I love you.
Got an answer yet?
What answer?
That thing.
That thing?
What are you talking about?
This is all we have right now.
Let’s keep practicing.
Okay.
I’ll leave it for now.
I’ll come back for that answer.
You’re still not answering?
Hey—
Practice.
Come on.
Where are you stuck? I’ll help.
Then try saying this line.
P’Phet,
our expenses this month
are higher than what we make.
There are costume and equipment costs,
stage, transport, and electricity too.
If we don’t manage this properly,
then soon
we’ll all be exhausted.
I know it’s not easy,
but we’ve come this far.
We can’t stop now.
We have to keep going.
Not just for the work,
but so our troupe can keep standing.
We can’t carry this on our own anymore.
I think we need more help.
Yeah.
I think so too.
If someone could handle the work side,
find sponsors,
or help promote us more,
maybe…
Mr. Tohr might be able to help us.
Mr. Tohr?
The other day,
I saw someone from the Payusin troupe
posting complaints,
saying he’s very strict about money
comment: booking agents these days are
extremely tough about money.
I get that precision matters,
but this is harsh—really harsh.
And there are many conditions.
It’s a shame the troupe
hasn’t shown their full potential
because someone controls everything.
When it comes to selling each job,
everything has to go through him.
And the other day,
I heard him complain about it myself.
You know how we feel.
But right now, what I’m most afraid of
is that our troupe won’t make it.
Everyone has already given it their all.
Both acting and performing on stage.
If no one comes in to help with the work side,
Ploy and I won’t have the energy left to rehearse
or take care of everyone like before.
Maybe having Mr. Tohr step in
can help us get through this.
At least,
it would keep the troupe going.
So…
I’ll try calling Mr. Tohr.
If Guy were here right now,
he’d definitely think the same as me.
I’ll head back first.
Please take care of the coffee sponsor for my troupe.
Of course. I’ll handle it.
Safe travels.
Okay.
Oh, Phet Thae, Ploy Ying.
Hello, Mr. Tohr.
Hello.
Ploy and I
I have something I’d like to ask
for your help with, sir.
What is it? Go ahead.
Well…
Right now, our troupe
is having trouble competing for jobs, Mr. Tohr.
So we’d like to ask for your help.
Sure.
If it’s for the Petchprakai Troupe,
I’m more than willing to help.
Thank you very much.
Um, about the commission,
what percentage would you take?
Well…
For others, I take fifteen to twenty percent.
For you, I’ll start at ten.
I’ve known you since you were young.
We’ll help each other out.
I’ll start handling things from tomorrow.
This time, our troupe will rise again—
stronger than before.
I’ll take care of everything.
Sponsors, bookings, promotion,
PR—everything.
The overall direction too.
This time, I want all of you
to work like real professionals.
Yes, Father.
I promise, no matter what you plan,
I’ll do my best.
The Petchprakai Troupe
will definitely stand on stage again.
Good.
Stop, stop.
Stop.
That’s enough.
What are you doing?
This has no artistry at all.
From now on, our Petchprakai Troupe
won’t be just ordinary Likay,
but a professional team.
Rehearsal starts at exactly 9 a.m.
Lunch break is exactly 30 minutes.
No more, no less.
After rehearsal,
no going out anywhere.
Put every piece of equipment away
don’t leave a single one out.
This feels like military school.
So no more evening market trips.
If you don’t want to stay, don’t follow this.
If you do want to stay,
you still have today to choose.
Tomorrow, you won’t.
As for you, Pleng Chai,
after university,
come straight back to rehearse, not go play games.
On weekends, come rehearse too.
Let me tell you something.
Being a Likay comedian isn’t easy.
Phet Thae.
Keep the rehearsal going.
Yes, Mr. Tohr.
Everyone, let’s continue rehearsal.
Let’s work on the show
for the next performance.
Come on, keep practicing, it’s nothing.
Don’t overthink it.
Keep the same rhythm—the “serng” beat,
just slow it down.
Try doing it yourself
so you’ll know what the pressure feels like.
I’m really worn out these days.
You’re making everyone uncomfortable.
P’Phet…
Comment: Why so extreme?
Isn’t that overdoing it?
Have you noticed?
Lately,
our place has gotten really quiet.
I feel it too.
Back then, in the evenings like this,
everyone would sit here, talk, and laugh together.
But now, everyone just goes to their own rooms.
It’s like waiting to clock out.
It doesn’t feel like home anymore.
It feels more like a company chasing targets.
I know it’s not the same.
But we chose this path, Ploy.
If we want the troupe to survive,
we have to accept some changes.
I believe
it’ll turn out okay.
Even if right now…
it doesn’t feel the same.
I hope it turns out well.
Because if it doesn’t,
we might lose the whole troupe
and ourselves along with it.
Before, we could eat whatever we wanted.
Just tell P’Ploy Ying and she’d let us.
Now it’s boxed meals—every meal is the same.
Yes.
And we have to finish within thirty minutes.
It feels less like family
but more like company employees.
The Petchprakai Troupe used to be full of laughter.
Now it’s just rules—nothing but rules.
I feel the same.
This place doesn’t feel like home anymore.
Yeah, P’.
The Petchprakai job—350,000.
It’s confirmed for next month, right?
Yes, I’ll sort it out with the troupe.
About the actors’ photos,
you want to add more? No problem.
As for the extra amount,
I’ll settle it soon.
Okay.
Just please don’t tell anyone yet.
Alright.
Thank you very much.
Three hundred fifty thousand…
Why did he tell P’Phet it was only 300,000?
That’s a fifty-thousand difference.
Damn.
That’s clearly cheating.
This job should be a hit.
We got another sponsor.
I’ll handle the details with the client.
P’Phet, P’Ploy—
I need to say something.
Right here, in front of Mr. Tohr.
What is it, Pleng?
Why are you talking so loud?
The job Mr. Tohr just took—
he got it for 350,000.
So why tell P’Phet it’s only 300,000?
The extra fifty, you kept it yourself.
Isn’t that cheating?
Pleng, what you said is partly true.
The job itself is 300,000.
But the extra fifty thousand
is an add-on package from the client,
for taking actor photos beforehand.
Then why didn’t you say so from the start?
Why hide it?
Why let me find out myself?
Because it just came up.
No one had proposed anything like this before.
This is the first time.
Sigh…
What is this?
I haven’t even explained yet,
and you’re already accusing me.
Pleng—
Mr. Tohr might not actually be cheating us.
Calm down.
Let him explain first.
Why, P’?
Every time I say something,
why do you never believe me?
Am I not important enough?
You used to be my whole world.
But today,
not one of you believes me.
P’Phet—
If I’m really wrong,
then prove it.
If I’m telling the truth,
one day,
you’ll understand.
Pleng—
Pleng!
Wait for me!
Don’t go yet!
P’Ploy—
I love this place like home.
But if no one trusts me here,
then it’s not home anymore.
Pleng, listen to me first.
Don’t worry about me.
I can take care of myself.
This time,
let me go my own way.
Pleng—
wait for me!
Pleng!
It’s so late—why are you calling?
Guy…
I…
I just left home.
And…
I don’t know where to go.
Are you…
okay?
Not really.
Come to me, I’ll send you the location.
Okay.
Thanks, man.
Are you okay, Pleng?
Make yourself at home.
Don’t worry about me.
This place isn’t big,
but there’s always room for you.
So?
Thank you so much.
Pleng—
If you don’t want to talk, that’s fine.
But if you need to vent,
I’m always here to listen.
You’ve grown up, huh.
Waiting alone at night to come to Bangkok.
Back then,
you’d freak out over a blackout.
I’m still scared of ghosts,
but now I’m more scared of reality.
Listen to me.
Ping, Pong, and Chae
stole P’Phet’s valuables
and ran away.
P’Phet won’t press charges.
He said
they might have their reasons.
And then
there’s Mr. Tohr.
Remember him?
Yeah.
At first, everyone was happy
that he came to help.
But I heard it loud and clear—
he closed a deal for 350,000.
But told P’Phet it was only 300,000.
When I found out and told them,
He said that extra fifty thousand
was just his commission
for landing the job.
Whatever that is.
Damn.
This is serious, Pleng.
What did P’Phet and P’Ploy say?
What do you think?
They didn’t believe me.
They believe everyone but me.
Then
you don’t have to prove it to them.
Just make sure you know
that you’re telling the truth.
Come on.
Let’s go upstairs.
Sorry to bother you.
P’Phet…
I didn’t want to do this.
I just wanted you to trust me once.
It’s late.
You’re still awake?
Not really sleepy.
Gross.
It’s all messy.
Hey—
This Game Boy—
you still kept it?
Damn.
P’Phet gave this to us when we were kids.
I still remember.
We fought over it until it almost broke.
Come here.
Back then, believe it or not,
I never beat him.
That’s why I got into gaming.
And
why I still want to stream games.
Pleng—
no matter what path you choose,
don’t forget
you’re not alone.
Yeah, thanks.
By the way,
you and that person—
how far have you gotten?
Tell me.
What?
How did this become about me?
Hey—
I just want to know.
Tell me.
Give me an update, come on.
Hey—
Just a bit.
Nothing.
Alright.
I’m going to sleep.
Okay.
You’re not telling me?
No, it’s not that—
I told you before, you just don’t remember.
Wait, let me try again.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
What are you doing? Why so slow?
You have fifteen minutes—finish and go rehearse.
Understood?
Clean this up already—I’ve seen it since yesterday.
Why leave it for days?
What were those three told to do?
Yes, this is Petchprakai Troupe.
A job? How much is it?
Yes, that works.
Stop, stop.
The rhythm’s off—don’t rush the drums.
Let’s do it again.
How many times do I have to say this?
What is this?
Why keep this?
To worship it?
Even a knife.
These aren’t expensive things,
but every piece,
comes from Father and Mother’s hard work.
They remind us that our family
is still together.
Phet…
I want you to remember this,
our family stands
because we help each other.
One day,
you’ll lead the Petchprakai Troupe
forward.
Not because I say so or because you’re the eldest,
but because you
are the heart of the troupe.
I promise,
I’ll take care of our family the best I can.
No matter how hard it gets,
they’ll always be my home.
♪ Everything changes ♪
♪ Hearts change too ♪
♪ We begin to lose strength ♪
♪ Growing weary ♪
♪ We will rise and fight ♪
♪ Believe me, my child ♪
♪ As time goes by ♪
♪ It passes on ♪
♪ Hold on to memories ♪
♪ Remind the heart ♪
♪ I will make it happen ♪
♪ One day ♪
I have good news.
This year, our village fair is coming back.
Honestly,
I think the issue between you and Guy
has been weighing on you for a long time.
What did you gain from being mad at your family?
I miss home.
Fight on with me.
Ploy…
Fighting alone is lonely.
Yeah.