=A Dream Like The True Love=
=Episode 6=
Do you find me dirty?
No, no.
What no?
It's okay.
I don't know why,
but this sleep was so deep.
Was it
because of drinking wine?
I put datura flower
in your porridge.
They're roadside flowers.
A small amount can calm the mind.
But excessive amount
can cause deep sleep.
Last night,
you had a nightmare?
Last...
Let's forget
about last night.
Baoyin...
Baozhu.
You are...?
Brother!
So you are their brother.
Yes, our big brother.
Su,
this is my neighbor, Luo.
He works in a restaurant kitchen.
He delivers to me too.
He's nice.
It's what I should do.
Didn't you say the croaker sold well?
Here's more.
They're hard to find now.
I just mentioned it casually.
Thank you.
And the snacks for Baozhu.
Here.
Have you eaten?
Come have some.
I'll get the money.
Okay.
Su,
don't go.
Su, what brought you here?
Weren't you...?
I came for
the festival.
Su...
Baozhu,
try some of this.
Baoyin should've
told me you were coming.
So I'd
have bought some
nice food
to treat you.
Are you two
close?
Of course!
Look.
Baoyin even sewed this for me.
She's so nice.
All the neighbors...
Luo.
Do you still have to go to work?
No rush.
Su...
You two chat.
I'll go.
I'll...
No.
Su!
Take care, Su.
Really handsome.
Baozhu's handwriting
is elegant
with a good structure
and has improved a lot.
When completed,
this piece can serve as a model
to be circulated.
Class dismissed.
Go home.
What?
Give it back!
Just this?
Is it really not well written?
Give it back!
Give me!
No.
Didn't the teacher say
it would be circulated?
Let me.
Give it back!
- Let me have a look!
- Let me!
- Give it back!
Here.
Take care.
Baoyin,
bad news!
What's wrong?
(Madam He)
Baozhu got into trouble at school.
Apologize to Lord Shen and Lady Shen.
Not my fault.
She pushed me.
Why can't I push back?
If I didn't,
they'd think I'm too scared.
They will definitely bully me even more.
I want them to know
that I am not someone to be bullied!
Quite sharp-tongued.
Mister, is this
how your student behaves?
Admit your mistake!
Why?
They hit me.
I fought back!
I'm not wrong.
Nonsense.
Who said so?
I did.
Baoyin!
Lord Shen,
I'm her sister.
Her attending school is never easy.
How could we
cause trouble?
Your little sister
is not only domineering,
but also scared my girl like this.
Tell me,
who is to blame?
Of course, your daughter.
Was she afraid of Baozhu,
how could she be so rude?
That's unreasonable.
As the magistrate,
can't you tell right from wrong?
The government founded the girls' school
for all girls.
It aims to expand girls' minds,
make them smart
and help them form good connections.
By acting like this,
are you against this goal,
and even the government?
Does the Prefect
know about this?
You...
Never mind.
I am the Magistrate
and won't argue with street thugs.
You all,
behave yourselves.
Don't go.
Your daughter should
apologize to my sister.
Let there be forgiveness.
He's let you go.
With no power or influence,
you should know when to stop.
Baozhu,
are you fine?
If only Father and Mother were here,
how would I suffer such grievances?
My father was a Registrar.
You did nothing wrong.
We may have no power,
but we won't be bullied.
Neither causing trouble
nor fearing trouble.
I taught you so.
You did it well.
Lady,
Headmaster wants to meet you.
There's a carriage for you.
Come with me.
The Headmaster?
Meet me?
Please change your clothes.
To meet Headmaster,
I have to get changed?
Please just do it.
Don't keep him waiting.
Headmaster,
she's here.
♪In a dreamlike haze,
our joys and sorrows blend♪
♪When the glory's gone,
this love will never end♪
♪We met and knew
in life's uncertain flow♪
♪Pledge a lifetime of deep affection♪
♪In this moment, hand in hand,
we'll roam the ends of earth♪
♪Through countless trials,
the devoted heart remains unmoved♪
♪Wishing to gaze long,
as our hair turns white, love deepens♪
♪Wishing to stay close,
with a heart-lamp through the night♪
♪Through every storm,
through every breeze♪
♪I'll stay by your side♪
♪With two hearts entwined,
we brave all barriers♪
♪Vows endure through endless years♪
♪As in the start, we dove in this dream♪
♪Every storm and every breeze♪
♪A witness to our love♪
♪Stars may shift, but love endures♪
♪No matter how brief our time,
we hold on tight♪
♪With you, my heart is complete♪
♪Every storm and every breeze♪
♪A witness to our love♪
♪Stars may shift, but love endures♪
♪No matter how brief our time,
we hold on tight♪
♪With you, my heart is complete♪
♪A dream like the true love♪
♪Through all eternity♪