=A Dream Like The True Love=
=Episode 3=
(Su Mansion)
Yuniang is my elder sister.
Go away!
This is Miss Wen Qiongniang.
Ms. Yuniang is her sister.
I dare you to make a move!
Wen family was raided.
No more Miss Wen.
Ms. Yuniang is pregnant now.
If the fetus is harmed,
you'll be in serious trouble!
Go away!
- Yuniang!
- Go!
I am Qiongniang.
Go!
I'll fight you if you dare touch her!
I dare anyone to harm her.
Heaven is watching what people do.
There'll be divine retribution.
Yuniang!
I am Qiongniang, Yuniang!
Go!
I am Qiongniang.
Don't go.
Qiongniang.
Tell your master
driving dogs into a corner
will surely backfire.
Open the door!
Is anyone there?
Is anyone there to help my lady?
(I understand Yuniang just wants
to look after herself.)
(But I can't be ungrateful.)
(The Wen family never treated me
as a servant.)
(Mr. Wen Junior even saved my life.)
(I must protect Qiongniang.)
Thank you for the rescue.
Miss,
(Luo Teng)
no need for that.
It was a small effort.
I see you got wet in the rain.
I brewed medicine.
Drink it while it's hot.
Did you encounter any difficulties?
To be honest,
our family encountered a mishap.
We couldn't find our relatives.
Right now,
only we two are left
to rely on each other.
If you really can't find a place to go,
you can stay here for the time being.
This room of mine happens to be empty.
In that case,
just consider me
renting this room from you.
Talk about it later.
We should look out for each other
every day.
It's getting late.
Drink the medicine
and rest early.
Mother.
Qiongniang.
Don't be afraid.
I am here.
Baoyin, my sister
doesn't want me anymore.
I want my father.
I want my mother.
Qiongniang, don't cry.
We have a place to stay now.
Everything will get better.
It will all be fine.
I don't want to.
I miss my parents.
I miss my elder brother.
I want to go home.
Qiongniang.
Qiongniang, don't cry.
Qiongniang, look.
Look, what is this?
Look.
A person's life
is like this glass ball.
When placed in the dark,
it becomes dull and dark.
No one pays attention.
When placed in a bright place,
it can reflect multicolored radiance.
If there is no light,
we
have to light ourselves up.
We can still shine out light.
Once lit up,
the road will be smoother.
People
must keep moving forward.
Right now, it's a bit tough.
But I promised Mrs. Wen to protect you.
So I won't leave you behind.
I'll stay with you
and treasure you
like the apple of my eye.
My name is Baoyin.
You can be called Baozhu.
I listen to you.
I'm not used to sleeping here.
I didn't bring your personal clothes.
I made a pillow for you
with old clothes.
The buckwheat you're accustomed to.
You go to sleep first.
I'll watch over you here.
Baozhu, hurry and sleep.
There's
no suffering man can't endure.
As long as we are alive,
there will always be hope.
(The Wen family has fallen.)
(I must take good care
of Baozhu to survive.)
(I'm strong.)
(I'm not afraid of hardship.)
(I learned a few characters
during half a year in the Wen family.)
(I also learned accounting.)
(I rented a bamboo raft.)
(On the Bian River,)
(I started a business
selling small dishes.)
(Profit is enough
to keep us fed and clothed.)
(Drunken Shrimp
Orchids and Chrysanthemums)
Today's promotion: holiday benefit.
Buy two, get one dish free.
Spend ten coins, get two coins off.
Don't miss out as you pass by.
Don't miss such a great opportunity.
Spend ten coins, get two off.
Come on.
Hold on tight.
Buy and take it with you.
Don't go home empty-handed.
The Su family moved out
of Bianyang overnight.
The tree falls, the monkeys scatter.
Afraid of being implicated.
But how did I hear
that the Wen family was not executed
for the charges?
They were just imprisoned.
Imprisoned?
Who did you hear this from?
Wait a moment.
Excuse me.
Where is the Wen family imprisoned?
Baoyin, I am scared.
Sir,
let me out.
Go back.
Behave!
Do you want to eat?
Baozhu.
Don't be afraid.
I am here.
Baoyin, I am scared.
Baozhu, don't be afraid.
I am here.
Be quick, just an hour.
Qiongniang?
Qiongniang.
- Qiongniang.
- Father, Mother.
Mother, Father.
Qiongniang.
My Qiongniang.
Baoyin.
Mother.
She is my sister.
I am no longer called Qiongniang.
I am called Baozhu.
Baozhu.
Please forgive me.
I dare not let her use her real name,
in case they come to get her.
I had to let her take on my surname
and give her the first name Baozhu.
Get up quickly.
You did nothing wrong.
My Wen family was entirely convicted.
Only Qiongniang was left.
If it weren't for you,
she might not be able
to stand here alive today.
I am too indebted to thank you properly.
What harm is there in being her sister?
If our Wen family
ever rises from disgrace one day,
you will stand as our daughter.
I don't want a noble status.
Back then,
you treated us servants as family.
For me, the Wen family
has given me a new life.
I just want to protect my family.
Just consider it me repaying a favor.
Where is my brother?
Why is he not here?
I heard the soldiers went
to the academy to arrest him.
But I don't know where he is being held.
Poor Su.
I don't even know if he's alive or dead.
Mother, don't be afraid.
Baoyin says
there's no hardship
that can't be endured.
As long as you live well, there is hope.
Our family will eventually reunite.
Right.
Hurry up.
Time's up.
Sir, Madam, rest assured.
I will protect Qiongniang.
Hurry up.
Baoyin.
- Mother.
- Qiongniang.
Qiongniang.
- Father, Mother.
Father, Mother.
Qiongniang.
- Qiongniang.
- Father, Mother.
- I won't go!
- Qiongniang.
- Mother.
(Three days later)
Little gadgets.
Get one.
Baoyin, it turns out today
is the Shangsi Festival.
Yes.
The days have become confusing.
Didn't realize today
was the Shangsi Festival.
Baoyin, there are
so many river lanterns here.
Many people are making wishes.
(Hope for my benefactor,)
(Mr. Wen Junior, safety and peace.)
(Wishing for the Wen family to reunite.)
Baoyin, it's so lively over there.
Let's go have a look.
Bravo!
The Eldest Princess's here.
She is the late emperor's
most beloved youngest daughter.
I heard she holds
half of the Tiger Tally
and is in charge of Bianyang.
Even the officials are wary of her.
This pleasure ship is so beautiful.
The Eldest Princess
is accustomed to luxury.
This is the largest pleasure ship
in Bianyang.
I've heard the Eldest Princess's husband
kept a mistress.
She then sent someone
to have him castrated.
No wonder
she kept so many
young and handsome toy boys.
As long as they're men she fancies,
none can escape her grasp.
Baoyin,
who is that man by the princess's side?
It's my brother!
♪In a dreamlike haze,
our joys and sorrows blend♪
♪When the glory's gone,
this love will never end♪
♪We met and knew
in life's uncertain flow♪
♪Pledge a lifetime of deep affection♪
♪In this moment, hand in hand,
we'll roam the ends of earth♪
♪Through countless trials,
the devoted heart remains unmoved♪
♪Wishing to gaze long,
as our hair turns white, love deepens♪
♪Wishing to stay close,
with a heart-lamp through the night♪
♪Through every storm,
through every breeze♪
♪I'll stay by your side♪
♪With two hearts entwined,
we brave all barriers♪
♪Vows endure through endless years♪
♪As in the start, we dove in this dream♪
♪Every storm and every breeze♪
♪A witness to our love♪
♪Stars may shift, but love endures♪
♪No matter how brief our time,
we hold on tight♪
♪With you, my heart is complete♪
♪Every storm and every breeze♪
♪A witness to our love♪
♪Stars may shift, but love endures♪
♪No matter how brief our time,
we hold on tight♪
♪With you, my heart is complete♪
♪A dream like the true love♪
♪Through all eternity♪