=A Dream Like The True Love=
=Episode 16=
Make way!
Everyone, make way!
Shameless!
Good he's caught!
Hit him!
Make way!
Mr. Wen!
It's me!
Buddha Temple...
Go away!
He deserved to die!
Get lost!
Make way!
Lady.
Master!
Don't speak.
Follow me.
Did Ruchu say where the decree is?
Sir,
the guards are too vigilant.
Given the situation,
the Eldest Princess doesn't have it yet.
Well, you may leave.
Yes.
Master,
why was Mr. Wen Junior sentenced?
Earlier he left with the Eldest Princess
without telling me.
Suddenly his life is in danger now.
I need to know the reason.
So I can explain to his parents later.
Please let me know.
Well,
since you're here for him,
you must be loyal and righteous.
Then I shall tell the truth.
As His Majesty is seriously ill,
my sister
intended to rebel.
As the Crown Prince's confidant,
Ruchu had to stay by her side,
and find the right time to act.
It happened abruptly.
The future is uncertain.
That's why he couldn't
tell you the truth.
(No wonder
he said those heartless words.)
Master,
when will he be executed?
Is there
a way to save him?
Ruchu has an imperial decree.
But when meeting with us,
the Eldest Princess's men took him
and the decree was missing.
As long as Ruchu
keeps the decree's location secret,
the Eldest Princess will not
do anything to him.
I have a risky solution.
I wonder if I can try it.
Who are you to break in?
How dare you.
I am the Eldest Princess's
personal maid.
By her order,
I need to interrogate Wen Su now.
I have this royal jade.
How dare you stop me?
We are sorry
for offending you.
Please.
Kill me if you want.
About the imperial decree,
I will not reveal anything.
Mr. Wen Junior.
Who let you in?
Do you know what this place is?
How can I leave you alone?
I have met with Head Monk Fahui.
They shouldn't have involved you.
All was my choice.
If Head Monk Fahui didn't tell me,
how could I know what you really think?
That day,
I said harsh things.
I didn't mean it.
I understand.
What a touching romance.
Su, I never knew
you are so considerate.
What happens between you and me
has nothing to do with Baoyin.
Let her go.
If you're unhappy,
come at me.
Which part of you
has not been flogged by me?
I am tired of you.
I want to try something new.
Where is the imperial decree?
If you don't say,
I'll make your lover drink this.
Since I'm here,
I'm ready to die for him.
I was
saved by you.
Today, I'll repay you.
We owe each other nothing.
Wen Ruchu!
Don't you want to know
where the decree is?
Kill me,
and no one will know where it is.
Don't push me.
I cherished your talent,
and intended to spare your life.
But you took advantage of my kindness.
Since you're so devoted to each other,
you can choose.
I can only let one of you leave.
I had
studied arduously for over a decade.
I was well-known for making the list.
I devoted myself entirely
to my homeland.
Humiliation
and torture.
I can endure them
along with blood and tears.
But there is one person
I must protect.
Don't be afraid.
Mr. Wen Junior.
Mr. Wen Junior!
You gave your life for a villager.
Wen Su,
you truly are a love-struck fool.
The decree is hidden outside
the palace wall at south gate.
It is hidden
outside the palace wall at south gate.
Outside the palace wall at south gate.
Alright.
How is Wen Su?
You must save him.
You must save him!
♪In a dreamlike haze,
our joys and sorrows blend♪
♪When the glory's gone,
this love will never end♪
♪We met and knew
in life's uncertain flow♪
♪Pledge a lifetime of deep affection♪
♪In this moment, hand in hand,
we'll roam the ends of earth♪
♪Through countless trials,
the devoted heart remains unmoved♪
♪Wishing to gaze long,
as our hair turns white, love deepens♪
♪Wishing to stay close,
with a heart-lamp through the night♪
♪Through every storm,
through every breeze♪
♪I'll stay by your side♪
♪With two hearts entwined,
we brave all barriers♪
♪Vows endure through endless years♪
♪As in the start, we dove in this dream♪
♪Every storm and every breeze♪
♪A witness to our love♪
♪Stars may shift, but love endures♪
♪No matter how brief our time,
we hold on tight♪
♪With you, my heart is complete♪
♪Every storm and every breeze♪
♪A witness to our love♪
♪Stars may shift, but love endures♪
♪No matter how brief our time,
we hold on tight♪
♪With you, my heart is complete♪
♪A dream like the true love♪
♪Through all eternity♪