[You Have My Heart]
[Episode 3: The Life-and-Death Wager]
The spiritual power is not enough.
Now that the tree heart's right before us.
Master, you may take it whenever you want.
Why does Lady Fufeng
keep following us?
There were bran and grease
in the wine merchant's fingernails.
There was grease on Widow Liu's neck too.
It came from a sesame flatbread.
Thank you, My Lady.
My Lady,
did you happen to find
a discarded flatbread at the crime scene?
I wasn't paying attention to that.
Xiqianhua only collects corpses
and suppresses evil spirits.
We don't pick up trash from the roadside.
What about the autopsy records?
There was no mention of it either.
How was this crucial clue overlooked?
May Lady Fufeng protect us.
What's written on this?
[Huge bounty for clues on the echo demon]
It's a reward notice.
My Lord,
is there really a silver reward
for providing clues?
Of course. Please, have a seat.
Here's thing, My Lord.
That day, I went to Nanqiutou Road
to buy sesame flatbread from that shop.
And I saw a figure there,
sneaking around
and acting suspiciously.
Does that count as a clue?
It does.
Thank you, My Lord.
Ma'am!
Mind your own business.
His annual salary is only 30 taels,
and he even lent 5 taels to us.
His Lordship has truly emptied
his pockets this time.
Who knows if it'll help?
Where there is a will, there is a way.
According to a beggar boy named Rat,
he learned a nursery rhyme
from a child in red.
Old things return,
shifting within the heart.
Not their rightful owner—
calamity will not cease.
He was given a sesame flatbread
in exchange for memorizing it.
A sesame flatbread and a nursery rhyme...
Hu, Deputy Magistrate Shi.
Find that beggar boy Rat immediately,
along with the child in red
he mentioned.
-How are we supposed to find them?
-This...
Send more men
to search the mountain at once.
And we need to find
Village Chief Zhou as soon as possible.
Dead or alive, we must find him.
Search the mountain?
Right.
You...
But we don't have enough men.
I only have one day left.
Master.
He noticed that lead.
A sesame flatbread and a nursery rhyme.
From such seemingly trivial details,
he managed to trace
the source of all calamity.
But in this wager,
he has no chance of winning.
The villagers said
that on the day of the incident,
they saw Village Chief Zhou
running into the mountains in a panic.
Perhaps he really is hiding here.
But the mountain is huge,
and it's raining now.
I'm afraid we'll freeze to death
before we find him.
Over there.
Sir,
have you seen
Village Chief Zhou Ming nearby?
What are you doing
in the mountains so late at night?
Village Chief Zhou Ming!
Zhou Ming?
Hold the candle. Prepare for the autopsy.
Another death?
Hurry up. Hurry up.
Deputy Magistrate Shi, what are you doing?
This was an unnatural death!
We must inform Lady Fufeng immediately.
It's the rule of Yin-Yang Crossing.
If you beat this drum,
will Liu Fufeng hear it?
Young Magistrate,
this Liu Drum is connected
to the earth veins of Yin-Yang Crossing.
Of course Lady Fufeng can hear it.
Three beats mean emergency;
five mean death.
Beating it five times
means it's a murder case.
Five beats.
A murder case.
The three-day agreement is due.
According to the examination of the scene,
there were no signs
of a struggle near the body.
The terrain around the scene
was flat and open,
and none of Zhou Ming's
valuables were taken.
Based on this,
it is concluded that while fleeing,
he was startled
and died of sudden heart failure.
There's another possibility.
He committed suicide
out of fear of punishment.
Lord Bai solves cases
with remarkable efficiency.
Are you suggesting
that after murdering Widow Liu,
the killer fled in fear,
lost his way in the mountains,
and was frightened to death?
Not exactly.
In the wine merchant's sudden death case,
both victims ate sesame flatbread
before they died.
And Zhou Ming had also
eaten sesame flatbread before his death.
Isn't that just common travel food?
What's so unusual about it?
You seem so obsessed with this flatbread.
Were you a starving ghost
in your previous life?
This piece of paper
is even less unusual.
Because it's nothing more than
oiled paper used to wrap flatbread.
The most important thing right now
is to find the shop owner
that sold the flatbread.
Then the case is already clear.
You've identified Zhou Ming as the killer,
and now the killer is dead.
Based on your six months
of experience as an official,
do you consider this case closed?
No.
Another clue suggests
that a beggar
learned a nursery rhyme
from a child in red
in exchange for a flatbread.
But so far,
that child in red has not been found.
This case is full of unanswered questions.
It cannot be closed.
Lady Fufeng,
I lost our wager.
You are indeed a man of honor.
Knowing a task cannot be accomplished,
yet admitting defeat openly.
In that case, Lord Bai,
will you fulfill the bet right now?
I was only fulfilling my duty.
Never mind.
The three days are up,
and the case remains unsolved.
I will keep my word.
My life is yours to take.
I've finally found it!
The perfect vessel.
And now...
you're mine.
What have you done to me?
Didn't you want to gouge out my heart?
You'd rather die than break your word,
and rather break than bend.
I've actually begun
to admire you a little.
I consider you've passed the test.
I'll allow you to stay
and serve as a magistrate.
The other day,
you said you'd gouge out my heart.
Now you're talking about admiration.
Being so fickle,
you really are like a demon.
About the three-day agreement,
do you know why you lost?
Not because you are foolish,
but because
you have no one at your disposal.
Aren't you looking for him?
The child in red.
With Xiqianhua's support,
you'll have both the authority
and the manpower
to find the real source of all calamity.
So my life is yours to take,
and yours to spare as you please?
Lord Bai,
before you came here,
you must have prepared for the worst.
Now, not only am I sparing your life,
but I'm also reopening the county yamen
and helping you investigate.
By that logic,
it seems you're the one
getting the better deal.
Whatever Lady Fufeng says, goes.
I just don't understand
what it is you truly want.
What I want
is the stability for Yin-Yang Crossing.
Of course,
once this matter is settled,
I'll write that recommendation letter.
Master.
We've tried so many methods.
Why can't we retrieve that half heart?
Because he is not Bai Han.
How can you be so sure, Master?
Lady Fufeng,
the evil power has finally been sealed.
Bai Han,
defeating the evil power
was my own desire.
I never did it to earn your gratitude.
Fufeng,
you need to let this go.
No.
This surge of evil power
threw Yin-Yang Crossing into chaos
and implicated you as well.
I'm sorry.
From now on,
you'll have to rely on yourself.
Fufeng.
You...
This half of my heart
contains half my cultivation.
Today, I give it to you.
Don't!
Fufeng.
I'm giving you my heart today,
not only to restore your spiritual power,
but also because I hope
you'll stand beside me
to guard Yin-Yang Crossing,
suppress the evil power,
and protect the spiritual energy.
I, Bai Han,
hereby swear
that in this life,
I will never fail you.
It's a promise.
A hundred years have passed.
Bai Han likely cannot withstand
the tree heart's spiritual power.
I don't know
what wicked method he used,
but it seems
he used Bai Shanjun
as a vessel to nourish the heart.
We need to find another way
to take the heart.
For now, I'll keep him here and observe
to see what Bai Han is really up to.
[Yin-Yang Crossing Magistrate's Office]
Be careful.
Watch your step.
Don't go this way.
There are still more over there.
Don't break them.
It's so heavy.
What is this?
Slow down.
Let's go.
Careful.
This way.
Put it here.
[Perspicacious and impartial in judgment]
My Lord.
Take a look around.
Lady Fufeng is so thoughtful.
She specially allocated funds and manpower
to renovate the county yamen.
She even said Shuan is smart,
so he can stay here as an errand boy.
Greetings, My Lord.
Easy there. Don't break it.
Put it here.
Lad, you are
quite a character.
Impressive enough to convince me to come
down the mountains and be your constable.
Then let's get to the bottom
of this case first.
I hope all my esteemed colleagues
will work with me
to keep Yin-Yang Crossing stable
and share Lady Fufeng's burden.
Deputy Magistrate Shi,
search the entire city for this child.
We've found this boy
just this morning.
Bring him in.
My Lord.
My son went out to buy candy two days ago,
and came back completely unresponsive.
Please get up first.
Has he seen a physician?
Yes.
The physician said
it was caused by corruption
and told us to seek help from Xiqianhua.
I've already hung a wishing plaque.
I wonder if Lady Fufeng will help him.
Candy?
Wasn't he buying sesame flatbread?
Sesame flatbread?
I don't know.
I only asked him to buy candy.
Whispers echo in the forest,
each cry like weeping.
-Mimicking human speech, it drains away vitality.
-Whispers echo in the forest, each cry like weeping.
Mimicking human speech,
it drains away vitality.
The smell is strong.
Old things return,
shifting within the heart.
Not their rightful owner—
calamity will not cease.
Why does it smell so strange?
Whispers echo in the forest...
It seems Lord Bai has found a new job:
practicing medicine and saving lives.
Why don't you save him, Lady Fufeng?
I can't.
This is a poison originates
from the Yin-Yang Crossing.
As long as we find the source of it,
it can be cured with the proper medicine.
Lord Bai, you've read
countless medical books.
Have you ever seen a case
matching these burns
left by the corruption?
This corruption
consumes the mind and destroys the body.
Decoctions are useless.
The fact that this child
still has a breath left
is already a mercy from the heavens.
Not their rightful owner—
calamity will not cease.
My Lady.
Does the corruption
really exist in this world?
You and I are
practically in the same boat now.
There's no need to manipulate me
with stories of ghosts and gods.
Whether I'm manipulating you or not,
you'll find out soon enough.
Fengling, go get today's case files.
Yes, Master.
Make sure they're archived.
Your hand.
What for?
To see how much longer a stubborn fool
like you has left to live.
I don't want you dying in front of me.
It's bad luck.
I didn't know
Lady Fufeng could read palms.
I suggest you be careful
while investigating, Lord Bai.
Don't let that evil power taint you,
corrupt your mind,
and make you just like him.
If that happens,
I really won't be able to save you.
I mean...
Take care of yourself.
Whispers echo in the forest,
each cry like weeping.
Mimicking human speech,
it drains away vitality.
This is the tune
of the legendary echo demon.
But the last few lines...
Old things return,
shifting within the heart.
Not their rightful owner—
calamity will not cease.
Old things, heart, not its rightful owner.
It sounds like the heart you mentioned.
That magistrate...
Isn't the heart in his chest
the other half of your tree heart?
But this nursery rhyme
started spreading two weeks ago.
Bai Shanjun hadn't arrived at that time.
What if we look at it from another angle?
Not their rightful owner—
calamity will not cease.
Perhaps it means
the half of the heart that I hold
doesn't belong to me either.
Could all of this be connected to Bai Han?
Fate has already been set.
This nursery rhyme
is aimed at my tree heart.
Even if that little magistrate
had nothing to do with this previously,
the moment he walks into this trap,
there's no escaping it.