~ Revenge Note 2 ~
Our beautiful school gives, shares and cares
Sinu Real Estate
Please think about it and let me know.
I'll get you a good deal.
Thank you.
Have a good day.
Sinu Real Estate
Are you still going to run the café after you get married?
Not too long ago, someone came
to inquire about your café and was very interested.
Gi Jun says that after we get married,
I should just go to the cultural center instead of working.
But I think I might get bored.
The café is not making much profit. Shouldn't you hand it over
when someone who's interested is looking at it?
He was a nice-looking young man.
I think the ladies in the neighborhood would flock in if he took over.
Really? Should I sell it?
Welcome.
I'm calling you because I miss you.
Has my baby eaten lunch yet?
You don't need to be on a diet.
Excuse me.
Please close the refrigerator door.
I'm going to give you a scolding if you don't eat your lunch, okay?
Excuse me. You need to pay for that before you drink it.
Excuse me.
I'll text you later.
Aigoo.
Are you afraid that I might take this without paying?
How much is it?
1,300 won (≈ $1.20).
Why is it so expensive?
Isn't this "buy one get one free"?
650 won (≈ 60¢) should be enough.
But I'll give you 700 won (≈ 60¢) for it.
Sir, you can't do that.
Then I'll have to pay with my card.
All right.
Here's your card.
Oh my. It's so pretty.
I know, right?
Of the three,
I think this place has the best food.
You think so?
Yes.
It's so nice to see the wedding hall
and to be able to have lunch together.
Wow.
Two, three, four. And one...
- One, two, three, four.
- Two, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four...
- Five...
- Oh my!
- Oh, I'm so sorry.
- It's...
- I was...
- Oh my goodness.
Is it all right for us to be doing this?
- Don't you think it's a bit too soon?
- What do you mean?
We need to make reservations early for famous wedding halls like this one.
So maybe we can set the date
about six months ahead of time.
Well, what if I suddenly change my mind
after setting a date?
Jeong Ah, please don't change your mind.
Ouch, that hurts.
Mr. Choi,
I'm already old to have a baby,
so let's hurry up and make reservations.
Yes, we need to do that.
- Let's go and make a reservation.
- Let's go.
- I think I'm blushing.
- Gosh.
- No way.
- Are we really getting married?
Is this real?
I think it's real.
Our P.E. teacher is dating our French teacher?
I don't think they're just dating. I think they're getting married.
They used to fight all the time.
Maybe they got attached to each other after fighting so much. My gosh.
You've improved so much in just one day.
I was so slow yesterday, wasn't I?
I'll do more today, so you can slow down.
Gosh.
You even pick up dishwashing fast because you're smart.
You want to wash my hands too?
I'm sorry. I thought it was a plate.
This is revenge for yesterday.
Hey, come on. No revenge, please.
Don't do it.
- Why not?
- Don't.
Hey, stop fooling around and hurry up.
Gi Jun,
I think the money will be ready by tomorrow.
Let me have your bank account number.
Money? What money?
You said you needed cash
for your investment in Paris.
I told you not to worry about it.
No.
I want to be there for you
when you're going through difficult times.
Since you need it quick, I applied for a loan
and I'm going to sell the café as well.
I will also have the deposit money from my sister, so it'll be all right.
I'm not
a poor woman, you know?
This is so frustrating.
Gi Jun.
Don't think of it as money.
Think of it as me giving you my heart.
It's my heart of love for you, Gi Jun.
Thank you.
Hey baby, will you close your eyes for just three seconds?
Here?
Come on.
Hey, baby.
You are a woman
that makes me want to be a better man.
Would you marry me?
This is a ring
that my mom has treasured for years
to give to her daughter-in-law.
You're the first woman that I've wanted
to give this ring.
Gi Jun...
That makes me so happy.
Oppa, where are you? I miss you.
Oh no, what shall I do?
I have an urgent business situation to attend to.
Gi Jun, it's all right.
I'm mature enough
to understand the importance of business.
Banquet Hall, 10th Floor
Break time is already over.
It's time to go back to work.
Oppa, are we really getting married?
I can't believe this is happening.
Are you my aunt's boyfriend?
Yes, I am. You can call me Uncle.
It's like a dream to me too.
My baby, you must be tired.
Maybe a little.
It's all right. We're going to get a massage.
Of course. Let's go.
What's wrong? Do you know them?
He looked like my aunt's boyfriend.
He was linking arms with another woman.
No way.
Maybe you're mistaken.
I'm sure of what I saw.
It's a twin.
My girl.
- I'm so tired. Move over.
- Why you little...
It's so heavy!
Oh, my shoulders.
What is this? A diamond?
A diamond?
Did he propose to you?
Haven't you seen a diamond before? You're such a country girl.
Of course I haven't! Let me see.
How much is this?
Price of an apartment building.
This is a very special ring. There's nothing like it anywhere.
Gi Jun's late mother left it
for her future daughter-in-law.
Of all the women he met,
he said I was the only one he wanted to give this to.
I'm so happy!
Your boyfriend must have watched way too many dramas.
I'm getting goosebumps.
Are you sure this isn't fake?
The diamond seems a little too big.
How would you know? You've never seen a real one before.
Can I try it on just once?
Are we really getting married?
It's like a dream to me too.
Aunt Seon Hui, can you show me a picture of your boyfriend?
Yes, show us.
Here, you can take a look at my Gi Jun.
There isn't one clear picture of him.
It's because Gi Jun
always wants to kiss me.
I feel like I've seen him somewhere.
Here, this is his new name card.
CEO Sa Gi Jun
He's a CEO.
Oh my. He's really something.
I need to go for skin care now.
Give it back to her.
Let me have it.
My goodness.
I'm going to look at more dress designs.
Mom, I saw something at the wedding hall where I'm working.
I saw a man that looks just like Aunt Seon Hui's boyfriend.
He was arm-in-arm with another woman.
I just saw him for a moment, but he really looked just like him.
Goodness, don't be ridiculous!
It must be someone that looks like him.
Wait a minute.
When did you go out and get a part-time job?
You barely went up five places on your final exam.
Now you think you're a top student?
You should study harder, not work!
I shouldn't have told you.
Don't you think we should get a bigger TV?
I don't watch TV.
Why?
I'm only going to watch you.
Gosh! You're just too sweet!
You love me so much.
We should get a king-sized bed, right?
What kind of bedding do you prefer?
As long as we're here, we should just get everything we need.
Our new apartment is empty anyway,
we could just have it delivered in advance.
No.
I'll take care of all of our furniture and electronics.
You trusted me enough to invest in me.
I really want to do everything for you.
All you need to do is just move in.
Really? I'm so touched.
Excuse me for a minute.
He's so handsome.
Excuse me.
Excuse me?
Gi Jun!
I'm here.
I thought that an angel had come down from heaven!
My goodness.
You're so silly.
You're so silly!
Hold on.
- Come on, no hitting.
- They're really something else.
You're so silly.
Wait, I think that man has been here before.
Come on!
Hello.
Who are you?
I work part-time here.
So?
This is really important to me...
I mean, this is important to my aunt.
May I check
if my aunt's boyfriend is on the reservation list?
Ask your aunt's boyfriend yourself.
Please leave. I'm busy.
Did it work out?
She won't show it to me.
I think I'll have to tell my aunt honestly.
- You're here.
- Yes.
Your aunt asked me to fill in for the day.
Ji Na!
Hi.
- Hello.
- So you're Ji Na.
We'll live close by after we get married. Come visit us often, okay?
Are we really getting married?
It's him.
I'm positive now that I'm seeing him again.
Here, this is my first allowance to you as your uncle.
Gosh. You're not her uncle yet.
Take it, Ji Na.
It's all right.
What's wrong? Take it, Ji Na.
I think Ji Na is sad that her aunt is getting married.
She must be jealous of Gi Jun.
- It's all right. Take it.
- Aunt, I'm leaving now.
Hey.
Are you done?
Yes, I was just wrapping up.
Thanks for always helping out my aunt.
Can I ask
why you don't like your aunt's boyfriend?
Well, to be honest,
I saw something strange while I was working at the wedding hall.
I saw him talking
to another woman about getting married.
I really hope I'm mistaken.
I think the person you saw was
your aunt's boyfriend.
I saw him at a club once.
No way.
I was really hoping that it wasn't him.
Reservations
Let me try it this time.
You can do it!
Hello.
How can I help you?
This is for you. It's for a bargain.
A bargain?
My uncle is trying to get married without the family's consent.
I only know the place and nothing else.
If I could know the exact time, I could bring my father to the wedding.
I see.
Oh, my gosh.
How come she's so nice to Je Yi?
I normally can't do this. But seeing that you have such a kind heart,
I'll do it for you just this once.
What is your uncle's name?
It's Sa Gi Jun.
What did she say? Did she tell you?
You were right. Sa Gi Jun.
The wedding is this Saturday at 3 p.m.
The bride's name is Seo Geun Ae.
What a player!
He's seeing them both?
My aunt likes him so much.
What's going to happen to her?
That's right.
My aunt said she was getting a loan today.
A loan?
Then it must not be cheating, but a scam.
Please pick up.
Hello?
- Aunt Seon Hui, where are you?
- I'm at the bank.
Hang up. I'm getting a loan now.
No, wait! Aunt Seon Hui!
She hung up. What do I do now?
Let's run.
Aunt Seon Hui,
please don't send the money!
Thank you. Have a good day.
Thank you.
Ji Na
Why isn't she picking up?
She's not picking up?
The loan has been approved.
Then will you transfer
the 200 million won (≈ $180,000) to this account?
Have you received any voice phishing phone calls asking for
personal information in the name of a prosecutor or financial official?
Gosh.
I'm not foolish enough to fall for such a thing.
I'm sending the money to my husband.
All right, then.
I had to ask you as a part of the process.
Here you go.
Aunt Seon Hui!
Stop! Don't send the money.
It's a scam!
What?
I told you. That's why I was making sure.
Oh my.
This is amazing.
Goodness.
Isn't it?
What's the estimated value?
Maybe about...
About... 8,000 won (≈ $7.00)?
I'm sorry?
Aunt Seon Hui!
Are you all right?
How could this be so well-made with just plastic?
It's really amazing.
Gosh.
Goodness.
Forget him.
Don't waste your tears on that idiot.
Just think that you stepped on a big turd.
You know...
I still can't believe it's true.
Maybe the wedding hall was reserved
by a man with the same name.
And the ring...
Maybe he has his own circumstances.
He said that the ring was passed down by his mom.
He might have never known that it was fake.
Get a hold of yourself!
No, it can't be.
Just for me,
Gi Jun contracted to buy an expensive house.
I shouldn't doubt him.
A house?
Hey. What is the address?
What if that's a scam too?
No way.
Property Purchase Contract
So the contract hasn't been signed yet?
All right. Thank you.
It's a scam.
There hasn't been a deal yet because the house is so pricey.
He made a fake contract as well.
No. This can't be true.
Gi Jun.
You can explain everything, right?
Gi Jun!
Please talk to me!
- That punk! Stop looking at his picture!
- Gi Jun...
Oh my gosh.
I know him!
It's him! This punk!
He came to the real estate office before
and asked me whether your café was on a monthly rent.
He also asked about the monthly profit. It's the same guy.
It really is him!
He approached you knowing that you had money.
He's a con artist!
Calm down.
Sa Gi Jun...
I'm going to ruin you.
Will you be the Revenge Goddess?
Enter target's name
I know the returns will be tenfold if I invest that sum.
You're the first woman I've wanted
to give this ring to.
Are we really getting married?
It's like a dream to me too.
Sa Gi Jun
I want to be there for you
when you're going through difficult times.
Gi Jun...
You can explain everything, right?
Revenge Note,
please get revenge
for my aunt.
We will proceed with the revenge.
My babies...
Come on out. I'm calling you.
Come on out.
My goodness.
Gosh.
What is this?
You have been selected as a revenge target.
Revenge?
Who's getting revenge?
I've cheated so many people. I can't remember who's who anymore.
Baby Kim said she would send 200 million won. I wonder why she hasn't yet.
After I get this one,
I should lay low for a while.
What's wrong with this?
I've tried on this tuxedo more than ten times.
This has never happened before.
My goodness!
Oh my gosh!
Excuse me. I'm so sorry,
but would you unzip this for me?
It won't open. I think it's broken.
Goodness me.
You're crazy.
I'm serious.
It's really broken.
Hey, I could just...
What is this? This is so irritating.
Hi baby.
What are you doing, darling?
I'm doing business of course.
I can explain everything.
Did you call me?
Baby!
Me?
Baby?
- Hey.
- You bastard!
Hey, Sa Gi Jun!
Baby, baby, baby. How many babies do you have?
Are you a ten-armed squid?
How dare you cheat on me?
You deserve a beating!
Asshole!
Wait!
Baby!
I'm going to hit his face.
Did he wet his pants?
It stinks. Gosh.
You really are something else.
How could you do this to me?
Did I look that easy to you?
Hey. Give me back my money.
I worked hard for that money. Give it back, you slimeball!
You will pay for this today!
I'm going to kill you!
Wait!
Look over there!
- Get him!
- Hey!
- Get back here!
- Get him!
- How dare you?
- Hey!
- Oh my!
You scumbag!
I knew what kind of vermin you were
since you caused trouble at my store.
How dare you mess with my sister-in-law?
You're going to pay for it today! You little—
Ouch.
- Gang Dong.
- Seon Hui.
Thank you.
Here! Over here!
It's him. Come over here, please!
Get up.
You low-life bastard!
Hey.
You just got out of jail and you're already pulling this?
Jail?
That rascal has committed fraud 13 times already.
What? Did you just say "13 times"?
Thank you for reporting him.
What?
So you've been in jail, not Paris?
- Let's go.
- Wait!
Baby...
Get moving.
Don't cry.
Ji Na,
let's just have a quiet meal today.
We'll put off the birthday party for now.
That's fine with me. I'm just worried about Aunt.
She acts so smart all the time,
but she fell for that scam.
He's the bad guy.
He messed with her heart to get her money.
Ji Na, happy birthday!
Can you come up to the roof for a minute?
How did you know?
Thanks. I'll come up after I eat.
Your revenge is complete.
Thank you, Revenge Note.
No matter who the Master might be, I can't live without you anymore.
Please don't suddenly disappear on me.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Oh Ji Na ♪
Thank you.
Happy birthday.
Sit down.
And...
this is for you.
You got me a gift?
Wow, it's so pretty!
- Do you like it?
- Yes.
It looks expensive.
Did you use all the money you made from the part-time job to get this?
It's not that expensive. Don't worry.
Thank you.
The bracelet is so pretty
and the cake looks delicious too. Thank you.
She's on the roof.
Take a look, Ji Na
Watch it.
To Ji Na.mp4
I like you a lot!
I like you a lot.
Was that you, Ji Na?
I like Seo Je Yi
Epilogue
I found it!
I'll take this one.
This must be for your girlfriend.