~ Revenge Note 2 ~
Our beautiful school gives, shares and cares
No matter how I see it, Ji Man looks suspicious.
What in the world am I imagining?
Let's not worry about it.
Ban Yi Deun
How is Yi Deun?
Well... He's fine.
Where did it go?
What? Are you looking for something?
No, it's nothing.
Darn it.
Ban Yi Deun
What in the world
happened to me?
He's a devil dressed as an angel.
I experienced hell today.
What is this? "Devil"?
We're back to school.
The devil was at it again today.
I'm sorry.
Nobody knows and I want to tell them all
that they're being fooled.
Sorry.
It's okay. It's not because of you.
Did it happen then too?
When they were together...
The devil was the worst at the nurse's office today.
Darn it!
Will this ever
come to an end?
The devil is
so powerful.
Yi Deun went to the nurse's office
during the last gym class.
Mr. Choi, I don't think Yi Deun is feeling good.
I'll take him to the nurse.
Then
is Ji Man the devil?
Hey. Do you have a problem?
I'm asking you.
Hey,
don't be scared. I won't hit you.
Nurse's Office
You feel dirty, right?
Darn it!
Yi Deun, what's wrong with you?
Please...
save me.
Hand it over.
I don't want to.
Is everything written in here true?
Do you think it would be?
Of course it's not.
Yi Deun is a bit...
What do you call it?
He's a bit sick. Mentally and physically.
You're not even the type to care about others.
So hand it over and go on with your day.
I heard you transferred here after causing trouble.
Gosh, it won't do you any good
if you cause a scene here.
Worry about yourself, not me.
What would you do if I exposed this?
Yi Deun made it all up.
You better not show that to anyone!
Seo Ro Bin!
Hey!
Darn it.
Hey, I don't feel sleepy today.
Ji Man, are you checking up on Yi Deun?
Yes. They say he's recovering,
so I'm going to check on him.
You're doing so much for Yi Deun.
Shouldn't we give you an award or something?
What do you mean, award? It's something I should definitely do.
Let's go.
You're so nice.
No, I'm not.
You know Ha Ji Man, the class president?
What kind of guy is he?
I'm not sure.
He's just the class president.
He gets good grades and treats his classmates well.
Everyone likes him because he's nice.
Are you sure
he doesn't have another side to him?
The class president?
You might as well call Rok Hui a boy.
Stop the nonsense. Let's go.
Medical Checkup Front Desk
You startled me.
Why are you here?
I'm worried about what you said earlier
about Ji Man.
You're not the type to say things like that.
Is there a reason why you said that?
I'll explain later.
It's such a relief
that he wasn't hurt badly.
It's all my fault.
I said I would be by his side.
I can't believe that happened.
No.
You've always been there for Yi Deun.
I'm so thankful for you.
I think the class president is crying.
It's all acting.
He could totally be an actor.
What?
He's coming this way.
We're back at school
The devil was at it again today
Is this all true?
The devil mentioned here is the class president?
I think it's all true.
Then we should do something about it.
Let's go.
Hello,
I am Yi Deun's classmate,
Oh Ji Na.
This is Seo Ro Bin.
You must be here to visit Yi Deun.
It's such a shame
that he's still sleeping.
Actually,
we're here to tell you something about Yi Deun.
- Would you like to read this?
- What?
What's that?
This is Yi Deun's notebook.
You should take a look at it.
Please don't be too shocked.
Why would I be shocked?
Hi, oppa Je Yi.
Hi, Sa Na.
Oppa, where's Oppa Ro Bin?
He's visiting someone at the hospital.
Ji Na said she was visiting someone at the hospital too.
Are they together again?
Oppa,
I really want things to work out with you and Ji Na.
So, good luck!
Fighting, fighting!
Sure, thanks. Fighting.
Look at this.
You can read all the things
that Ji Man did to Yi Deun.
Please. Get your facts straight.
Ji Man's name is never mentioned there.
Ma'am, Yi Deun's mother is only suggesting that it's Ji Man,
based on the circumstances—
Ms. Maeng,
don't butt in, stay out of it.
Even this time, he was with Ji Man
when he fell down the stairs.
Ji Man definitely pushed him.
Do you have proof that my son did that?
Don't accuse someone without any proof.
Principal,
you know what my Ji Man has done for Yi Deun all this time,
don't you?
Of course I know.
Because of Ji Man's great personality,
I even recommended him for the service award.
What?
You're giving him the service award?
Ma'am.
I am positive
that Ha Ji Man would never do such a thing.
You can't be like this after reading some things
written in a notebook.
If you keep acting this way,
it won't be good for Yi Deun.
Principal, this is absurd!
- Ma'am—
- Ms. Maeng!
Stay seated.
By the way,
Ji Man's award won't be canceled or anything
because of this, will it?
My Ji Man worked so hard to get that award.
Don't worry. It won't be affected at all.
Those who can, can, and those who can't, can't.
That's my motto.
I will always support students like Ha Ji Man
for having a good influence on our school.
Right.
Excuse me.
Hello.
You're the one who visited before.
Yes.
I wanted to ask how it went.
Well...
Yi Deun's mother!
From reading what Yi Deun wrote,
he seems to be mentally unstable.
He should get some psychiatric treatment while he's at the hospital.
What did you say?
Yi Deun is like this because of your son.
You do know that Ji Man's dad is a lawyer, don't you?
We'll sue you if you say anything,
so watch out.
Ji Na,
thank you.
Don't worry too much.
I'll be going to see Yi Deun now.
Unbelievable.
I have to do something about this.
I experienced hell today.
Will you be the Revenge Goddess?
Enter target's name
Will this ever
come to an end?
Ha Ji Man
Save me.
Target meets all conditions.
We will proceed with the revenge.
You have been selected as a revenge target.
I'm a target for revenge?
Who sent this?
Is it Yi Deun?
Gosh, what a fool.
- Darn it.
- Are you all right?
I'm so sorry. It was an accident.
Are you all right?
Does it hurt a lot?
Class President, what's wrong with you?
Are you hurt somewhere?
No, it's just...
Go to the nurse if it hurts.
By the way, the math thesis was due yesterday.
Why didn't you turn it in?
It was such a good opportunity for you. What a waste.
What? I sent it to you, Ms. Maeng.
You did? I didn't get yours though.
There's no way.
I definitely sent it.
Failed to send mail
No way.
Aish—
Teacher Maeng, can I just turn it in now?
Sorry, but rules are rules.
Class President...
What's wrong with him?
I'm scared.
Hey, was it you?
Were you the one that told Yi Deun's mom?
So what if I did?
So you did.
You're in big trouble now.
Do you think I would let this go?
Do whatever you want. Move.
Just wait and see, Seo Ro Bin.
Why are you here?
When did you wake up?
They said they would let me know.
- How mean of them.
- Stay away.
Because you
just had to write those things in your notebook,
I almost got in trouble.
Of course
no one believed it, though.
Why? Do you feel wronged?
Yes.
I feel wronged.
That's why
I'm not taking it anymore.
Then,
what are you going to do about it?
Are you
depending on this?
Are you?
You pitiful boy.
Delete
Stupid and incompetent people like you
do these things.
Deleting that
won't get rid of the things you've done.
Hey, be quiet.
Do you want me to break your legs too?
Yi Deun,
my dad is a lawyer.
Don't you know what that means?
No matter what I do,
I won't get in trouble.
Also,
when I think about all the trouble you've caused...
So,
if you don't want to get hurt more,
say that everything in your notebook was made up.
Okay?
Listen to me, all right?
[Chatroom comments]
Hey, what is this?
- Turn it off right now.
- I don't know.
I didn't do this.
Darn it.
Yi Deun, you damn...
Boramae Hospital
How are you feeling?
I'm okay.
Why did you want to see me?
I wanted to thank you.
You might not know this,
but you gave me courage.
I don't know what's going on,
but chin up.
The brightest star shines in the darkest of nights
Let's stop this.
Anyway, you're pretty smart.
Ha Ji Man got in huge trouble.
Weren't you the one who did that?
Me?
No.
Sure, let's leave it at that.
It's seriously not me.
Come to the park immediately
if you don't want your brother to get beaten up.
Sorry, Yi Deun.
Why isn't he picking up?
Please pick up.
Ha Ji Man, are you just losing it now?
Look at you now. You shouldn't have pushed that kid.
You can't make it obvious.
Shut up.
You can't be accusing me too.
It's seriously not me.
Yah, sure.
I saw your face that day.
- How dare you lie?
- How dare you?
Gosh.
Anyway, why did you call me over?
I'm on the student council. I'm not like you.
Well,
you said before
that you don't like Seo Ro Bin because he's arrogant.
Seo Ro Bin?
We can't have earphones in school?
All right then.
Hey, aren't you going to apologize?
Shouldn't you be apologizing?
I'll be sure to repay you,
so punish Seo Ro Bin for me.
Okay, I'd be down.
I've always wanted to punish him.
5 missed calls from Seo Ro Bin
- Hello?
- Hey, are you okay?
Where are you at the park?
What do you mean, park?
Hey, he's here.
- Seo Ro Bin.
- Was it you?
- Did you send that text?
- Gosh,
you're so fast.
You must be close to your brother.
What are you doing here?
How rude. You don't even recognize your seonbae.
I'm Song Do Min, Song Do Min!
I know. I was just checking.
You look like a rascal,
not a student council head.
You little...
You can just stop now and leave.
Hey. Are you scared?
You're full of beans because I went easy on you.
- You're dead meat.
- Do you fight with your mouth?
Are you nuts?
Hey, get him!
What are you doing here?
I knew you'd be doing this.
What is this?
He's not dead, is he?
- What are you guys doing over there?
- Run!
Damn it.
Stop right there!
Ro Bin, wake up.
Ro Bin,
wake up.
Somebody help!
Oppa,
are you all right?
Why do you ask?
You got a bruise here.
Really?
I'm all right. It's not a big deal.
Are you sad that my eonni only pays attention
to Oppa Ro Bin?
No.
Failed to send mail
Your revenge is complete.
When did you become so important to me?
You're up. Do you want some water?
Don't go.
Aren't you thirsty though?
You need to drink a lot of water to be healthy.
Ro Bin!
Ro Bin, what happened?
He's not hurt that badly.
Shut up.
How did you guys know I was here?
I swear I only told Bo Ra.
Of course we should come when a friend is hurt.
Let's take a picture.
Everybody gather round.
One, two, three.
Nice.
So Ha Ji Man did all this?
It's so shocking. How could the class president do that?
There's a petition saying he should be punished.
Even if his dad is a lawyer,
he won't be able to get away with it this time.
At the least, he'll be expelled.
That wouldn't be enough for him.
Hey, stop eating so much.
This is for Ro Bin. Why are you eating it all?
I'm getting a food coma now.
Ro Bin, move over a bit.
Hey, Ro Bin's a patient.
Never mind. You guys should just leave now.
Oh Ji Na, are you serious?
Are you Ro Bin's girlfriend or something?
But why did the class president push Yi Deun?
I don't know.
- Maybe he was angry.
- He dug his own grave.
Everything was revealed because of that.
I thought of something important.
Now that the class president is gone, shouldn't we elect a new one?
Why? Do you want to be class president?
Don't even think about it.
Why not? I would be good at it.
Rok Hui, you should be class president instead.
I'm not the class president type.
You're better than him though.
See? I'm the only potential candidate.
What are you saying?
Sin Ae would be better.
- That's true.
- You're right.
The more I think about it, the angrier I get.
Why are you suddenly acting abnormally?
Don't bother me anymore.
Are you rebelling now?
I wrote down everything you've done to me.
If you don't stop, I'll show this to everyone.
You're making me so angry.
Go ahead and try it.
Who would believe you?
Quit the nonsense and hand it over.
Give it to me.
Hand it over.
- Stay away from me.
- Hand it over.
Stay away.
Give it to me!
Hand it over!
Darn it!
I told you to hand it over!
Somebody,
please
save me.
Please save me.
You're Seo Je Yi, right? You were here once.
You're from Hanjong High School, right?
Hello.
Who are you here for?
My brother got hurt.
It's your brother this time?
It's not good to be at the hospital so often.
Do you want something to drink?
Young lady, go ahead and pick one.
Thank you.
- Je Yi, you too.
- Oh, yes.
Thank you.
How is the girl you came with last time?
Yes, she's doing well, thanks to you.
Really? That's good to hear.
This is for Ro Bin.
I'll see you guys later.
Are you close to that doctor?
Yes, I met him last time.
But how does he know Ro Bin's name?
I'm not sure.