~ Revenge Note 2 ~
Our beautiful school gives, shares and cares
Hey guys, look at us.
Are you ready?
One, two, three.
AOA Rocks
What is that?
It looks pretty nice.
Look at that.
Oh my gosh. The shirts came out great.
You guys are newbies.
You can't just write the name Mina.
I wrote that I'm her future husband. Do you understand?
- What is that?
- That's cute.
I'm amazed.
As expected from the president.
- You're amazing.
- They've gotten worse these days.
You made the placards, right?
They need to stand out so that the members can remember us.
Ta-da! What do you think? Isn't it great?
I made one for Jimin.
How does it look? Isn't it amazing?
It's all right,
but you need to highlight the word "heart"
in order to catch their attention.
Mina, it's me, your future husband!
You're the best.
- Now that's shocking.
- Everyone will stare at him.
- Oh my. As expected from the president.
- I admire you.
- It's so cool.
- Hey, be quiet.
My goodness. What kind of class are we having today?
- He looks great.
- What's going on?
Right. My outfit is a bit strange today, isn't it?
The last performance evaluation before summer break is dance.
- What?
- Dance?
I can't dance. I have no sense of rhythm.
Can't we just do boxing or something?
I will now make a demonstration.
Pay attention and watch closely.
Please come out.
Oh my gosh.
Her clothes look a bit strange.
- Are they a couple?
- They look good together.
- She's so pretty.
- No way.
Swing Dance
Bluetooth Audio
The sound is great.
Don't they look like professionals?
Yes, they do.
- Date!
- Great!
- You are amazing!
- Oh my goodness.
The performance evaluation will be on easy moves,
not difficult ones, so don't be nervous.
Then... Boys and girls each make a line.
Where are you standing? I'm going to be first.
You can't switch places with anyone.
The person next to you will be your partner.
What? You're my partner?
Sorry. I have a lot of sweat...
Oh Ji Na, switch places with me.
The teacher told us not to.
Is it because you want to dance with Ro Bin?
Do you like him or something?
What are you talking about? Hurry and switch places then.
Let's learn the basic steps then.
- Mr. Choi.
- Yes?
I don't feel well. I don't think I can participate.
All right, Yi Deun. You can sit out this time.
The boys can move up one spot.
Darn it. What the heck is this?
Now face each other.
Here are the moves. Three, four.
One, two, three, four.
You need to hold hands.
Don't be shy. You're supposed to hold hands.
It's just dancing.
Can you stay on rhythm?
I'm trying my best.
Hey, why are your hands so sweaty?
Are you nervous because you're holding hands with me?
Hey, I just have a lot of sweat on my hands.
Put on some gloves then.
Ji Na.
I'll see you later.
Did you see the way they were holding hands?
It was so fast. I had no choice.
Hurry up.
Aren't you hot? Drink this.
Thanks.
It's actually my mom's birthday soon.
Could you help me pick out a present? I don't know what to get her.
Sure, I can help you with that.
I've bought a lot of gifts for my mom and aunt.
Then do you want to go shopping later?
Sure.
Out of all the gifts I got for my mom and aunt,
I think they liked scarves the most.
Scarves?
I thought he was the one.
I'm sorry.
I'm at the airport right now.
I suddenly got transferred overseas.
I can't ask you to wait for me.
I guess this is the end of our relationship.
- Take care.
- Oh no.
This can't be happening.
Gi Jun,
I can wait for you.
Welcome...
Gi Jun.
How have you been?
What brings you here?
These are lisianthus flowers.
In the language of flowers,
it means unchanging love.
I came back because I couldn't stand it anymore.
I'm sorry for being so late.
Oh.
I was in a rush coming back from Paris, so I could only get you this.
- What is this?
- This is sold only in Paris.
It is limited edition perfume.
Miss Seon Hui, I thought the fragrance would go well with you.
It's quite luxurious.
It's so nice.
It's so luxurious.
Anyway,
I guess it isn't very busy at this time.
Business isn't doing so well these days.
Monthly rent?
Big deposit?
If you paid a big deposit for this place, it must have been expensive.
Would it be around 200 million won (≈ $180,000)?
I paid a big deposit.
If business isn't doing so well, you can just come to Paris with me.
Don't get stressed out about it.
I need to go back to work now.
I'll be back.
Let's see each other every day.
Yes.
You should at least eat kimchi with it. How pitiful.
Thank you.
Oh my. Your cooking is just so good.
It was sent by your mother.
Oh.
It's been so long since I've had a home-cooked meal.
Are you still good at making that squid and radish soup?
Can I come eat it sometime?
You only need to put out one more spoon.
Don't even think about it.
Only in your dreams.
Gosh.
You need to shave.
You look so messy.
Before summer break, you need to turn in your list of extracurricular activities.
- Yes.
But there's someone who didn't sign up for any yet.
Seo Ro Bin,
since you transferred here in the middle of the semester,
I'll give you some extra time.
Make sure you join one and turn in your list.
Yes.
Enjoy the rest of your day.
- Goodbye.
That's why you should've listened to me.
Since you need to join something, go ahead and write down your name.
AOA Rocks
Hurry up.
President An Mi Nam
Now, before we begin our meeting,
we will present a membership card to the newest member of our club.
Seo Ro Bin, please come up to the front.
I don't need it.
No, you need it.
I don't want it.
Before we begin our activities,
we will recite the lyrics of AOA's newest song
with a reverent attitude.
Bingle Bangle
"Hey, baby"
"Come on, don't be shy"
"Tell me about yourself"
"This fantastic feeling"
"Your eyes are nailed on me"
"I can tell but I act like I can't"
Next, we will learn the choreography
of AOA's new song "Bingle Bangle."
This is the most important part.
Shake your hips
Bingle bangle
Give a short bounce to your hips,
and make sure your hands are like a cat's.
Five, six, seven, eight.
♪ Shake your hips ♪
♪ Bingle bangle ♪
♪ Bang bang ♪
That's right.
One more time.
♪ Shake your hips ♪
Ace, A.
Of, O.
Angels, A.
AOA rocks!
We're done, right? I'll get going.
Urgent Notice
There's an urgent notice. We need to go to the Internet café.
You need to come too.
It's first come, first served, based on comments.
- Help us.
- No thanks.
- I'm going to leave this club.
- Please help us out.
Just help us comment. I'll pay for the games.
You can post one comment and then play games.
Please.
Come on. Please.
Let's go. Help us. I'll buy you snacks.
Come with us.
Are you ready?
Seo Ro Bin, come on. You need to loosen up your hands too.
No thanks.
I'm going to write one line and play games.
We have five seconds left. Five, four,
three, two, one. Go!
Darn it.
- Did you get it?
- No.
I didn't get it either.
Gosh, I failed again.
- Me too.
- Same here.
Robin Hood
Number 98, ID Robin Hood?
- Isn't this you?
- Yes, it is.
- We got it!
- Oh my gosh!
- You've got some lucky hands.
- You're amazing.
This is great.
Let's go now.
Where?
They're handing out tickets in front of the agency's building.
We need your student ID.
Come with us one last time. Please?
I don't want to.
I'll give you my student ID. That's enough, right?
You need to be there in person.
You and I look completely different
from head to toe.
Please.
Come on.
This is the last time.
No, I don't want to.
Nothing is working out for me.
- Don't cry.
- Don't be sad.
It's really the last time.
Thank you.
You're such a good friend. Thank you.
We can't go because we have to go to the cram school,
but our president is in your hands, Ro Bin.
Hidden Entertainment
Psychic Baby Jimin
Thanks for leaving a comment. Thank you, buddy.
Mina, Mi Nam
What's that?
I stole it from my dad.
He goes around taking pictures sometimes.
That's a nice camera.
I'll take pictures and upload them, so you can look at them if you want.
The quality is on another level.
Hey, I'm looking at the manager's social media account,
and it looks like the members will be stopping by today.
- No way.
- Oh, my gosh.
Then we can see them today?
- We'll see our goddesses.
- I'm so nervous.
- What do I do?
- Oh my.
Their car is here.
Nuna Mina!
Nuna Mina, I'll make you happy.
You remember me, right? I can make you happy.
Let's be happy together!
- Hey, are you all right?
- Are you all right?
Yes.
He's so lucky.
Number 87.
Do you need any help? If you call out the number, I'll hand them out.
All right. Thanks again.
Number 88.
Wait, isn't that Maem Ma Ma?
She's the promoter of the fan club.
She's close to the agency employees.
She's close to all the members too. Isn't that amazing?
She's such a successful fan.
- I'm envious.
- Number 93.
Here you go.
Number 98.
Number 100.
I'll really get going now.
Thanks so much, buddy.
You're Mi Nam, right?
Maem Ma Ma?
You know me?
Of course I do. You're known as the one who shouts, "I'll make you happy."
Really?
That's a very nice camera.
I'm going to take lots of pictures during these promotions.
Your effort will really cheer up the members.
Mina really liked what you said earlier.
She did?
Mina really saw me?
Of course. They're always watching their fans.
Hold on.
Hello? Oh, Mina?
Yes.
Even if you feel down, hang in there.
Feel free to call me anytime. Okay, bye.
Was that really Mina?
Yes. Out of all the members, I'm closest to Mina.
Oh my gosh.
Did Mina say she's feeling down?
Yes, Mina is struggling these days.
It would be nice if someone like you could help her out.
What? Me?
Save my number.
I think we'll meet again soon.
I'll see you next time.
Maem Ma Ma
Your mom is overseas? Where is she?
She's in Jordan right now.
Jordan?
Where is that?
Is it a cold country?
No, it's probably hot since it's a desert.
Oh, it's a desert.
There's a lot of dusty wind there,
so I think a scarf would be great, as you had suggested.
I know, right?
My mom always covers her face with a scarf when it's sunny.
She doesn't want to get freckles.
Shall we choose one then?
What do you think of this one?
No, no.
My mom likes colorful ones.
What about this one?
It's pretty nice.
I think you look better covered up.
What did you say?
I'm just kidding.
- What about this?
- This is nice too.
- What about this one?
- It's cute.
One, two...
Three... One...
Why is this so hard for me?
Ro Bin will scold me.
Three...
One, two, three, four.
One, two...
Ji Na, let's go.
You're here.
Aren't you hungry? I'll buy you something yummy.
Okay.
This tonkatsu* looks good.
(Japanese dish: a breaded, deep-fried pork cutlet)
Let me slice it for you.
Eat up.
Ro Bin is so lucky.
- Why?
- He has a hyeong like you.
I wish I had an oppa like you.
Eat up.
Thanks.
There's only one piece left.
- You can have it.
- No, you can have it.
Then let's play rock-paper-scissors. The winner can have it.
Okay.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Nice.
How sad.
The last piece is always the best.
What was that? I'm full.
Are you feeling sick?
Why do you look so tired?
Today was really exhausting.
Don't talk to me.
Come to the rooftop. We need to practice.
One, two,
three, four.
three...
Why can't I do this?
Okay, one, two...
One, two, three, four.
When did you get here?
Don't laugh at me.
I've been practicing since yesterday.
No way. Are you sure you practiced?
I'm serious. I practiced until dawn.
That's amazing.
But you're still like this?
I don't know. I have no control over my legs.
I can't control them.
Relax your body and move along with the rhythm.
Watch closely.
That was great.
You're really amazing.
You're good at everything except studying.
It's not that I can't study. I just choose not to.
Stop showing off.
Here. Stand up.
Let's start.
One, two, three, four.
One, two,
three, four.
One, two, three.
Relax your body and move slowly.
Let's try this again.
One, two, three, four.
Why is this so difficult for you?
I don't get why you can't do this.
Let's try again.
- One, two, three...
- One, two...
This happened again.
What is this? It's a thief.
- Mom!
- Wait.
It's a thief! Mom!
Mom, it's a thief!
Wait!
Sorry, I made you get caught up in laundry again.
This is Mina's private social media account.
She's struggling these days,
so I think it would be nice if you could be her secret friend.
Mina will respond if you send her a DM.
Her agency can't know about this, so keep it a secret. Got it?
Unbelievable.
This is really hers.
I'm the fan who always shouts, "I'll make you happy."
I know. You're Mi Nam,
who's always cheering me on with the loudest voice.
Will you be my secret friend?
You can't rest.
I'll get you water,
so keep practicing and don't rest.
[Epilogue]
- Two, two, three, four. One...
- Two, two, three, four.
- One, two, three, four.
- One, two, three, four...
- One, two, three, four, five...
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- I...
- No.
- Oh my.