~ Revenge Note 2 ~
Our beautiful school gives, shares and cares
What do you want?
Can't you see that I'm talking to the chairwoman?
Yes, I see that very clearly.
Principal,
take a look at this.
What is this?
If we do this famine experience,
I get some free pocket money.
My goodness, this is so good.
W-W-What on earth is this?
H-How did you...
- W-Wait a minute.
- The money...
W-W-Who put that in my room?
Who installed a hidden camera?
Go Jin Sang, you can't trust him.
I can watch him with this.
- Why are you—
- Are you crazy?
- W-Why are you doing this?
- How dare you install a hidden camera?!
Do you want to screw us both over?
Fine, I did it. It was me!
Do you think I would've done this if you weren't so sneaky?
- Have you lost your mind?!
- Oh, my!
The principal is trying to hit a student's parent.
You awful jerk!
What is this?
Oh, my. What are you doing?
Get away!
How dare she install a hidden camera?
She must have lost her mind.
What do you think you're doing?
What's going on?
What's going on? Move!
- No.
- We won't move.
What? Get out of the way.
You little...
Do you all want to be expelled?
What are y-you doing here?
You're not a teacher anymore.
It's all over.
Now, stop it.
What do you mean, it's over?
The hidden camera video from your office has already been leaked,
and the Board of Education is investigating everything.
What are you talking about? It's all fabricated.
The evidence I have is enough
to get you arrested, Principal.
H-How dare you speak such nonsense?
Move!
I told you to move!
Don't mess with our kids!
What's going on? What are you both doing?
You need to come with us.
W-What...
What do you think you're doing?
Do you know who I am?!
- Let go of me!
- Stop.
Why are you doing this?!
I'm a Women's College graduate.
Which police station are you from? Let go of me!
- You can come with us and talk.
- Oh, no!
Honey,
they are dragging me somewhere!
Can you believe what the principal did?
How could he?
Unbelievable. How could this happen?
Everyone, our school is on the news.
- What?
- Oh, my gosh. Let me see.
- I can't see.
- Let me see, too.
- Go away.
- Gosh.
- Look.
- Mr. Go, the principal of H High School
in Seoul, has been detained
for illegally hiring a teacher
after receiving tens of millions of won worth of money and goods.
Mr. Go is suspected of hiring a teacher
in return for tens of million won given to him by Ms. Lee,
the parent of one of the students.
It has been further revealed that he accepted bribes
from a school lunch provider to manipulate the prices of ingredients
and to allow the use of low-quality ingredients.
He overworked me, saying he would promote me to a full-time position.
He then told me to make a donation.
And he always messed with the students' lunches.
Mrs. Lee, who asked Mr. Go to commit these illegal acts,
is also being charged for bribery and fraud.
On a good day, he would insult me before I left work.
He wouldn't hit me on those days.
Mrs. Lee, the wife of the CEO
- of the school lunch provider in question,
- Get rid of the camera.
is also revealed to have repeatedly
- assaulted her driver.
- I'm from Golden Spoon Foods!
This is one of the many cases
these days involving the abuse of power.
There is a growing voice calling for severe punishment.
Hey, Geum Su Ji, isn't that about your mom?
What are you talking about?
She's not my mom.
She just looks like her.
We all know what your mom looks like.
The school lunch provider mentioned in the news
is your dad's company.
Don't tell me you knew about our lunches being spoiled
and didn't say anything about it?
No, that's not true. I got sick after eating the food, too.
You two were there, right?
Tell them.
I don't know about that. You were originally going
to eat the lunch from the hotel.
That's right. You said you were sick of it
and switched lunches with me.
You two aren't going to take my side?
Do you think you can get away with it by saying you didn't know?
It has to do with your family, so you should take responsibility, too.
Her parents are at fault.
It's not Geum Su Ji's fault.
Are you seriously taking her side right now?
So what?
Are you all trying to gang up on me or what?!
I can leave this lame school
and go study abroad!
- Isn't she crazy?
- My goodness.
- I can't believe her.
- My gosh.
- Look at her audacity.
- Why is she the one getting angry?
Geum Su Ji probably won't be able to come back to school, will she?
She won't be able to come back right away this time.
I feel like Geum Su Ji really didn't know this time, though.
Hey! She deserves it for all that she did in the past.
Since the principal's wrongdoings have all been revealed,
Teacher Maeng would be able to come back, right?
Of course.
Oh, my.
- It's her!
- Teacher Maeng.
- Yes!
- It's Teacher Maeng!
Stop it. You're embarrassing me.
- We're so happy.
- We're glad to have you back.
Are you happy even though we're going to do a lot of math?
- Yes!
A lot of bad things happened these past few days,
but let's stay strong and work hard.
Let's open up our math books then.
- Yes.
Everything has worked out,
and Ms. Maeng has returned, too.
So let's have a toast.
- Cheers.
The drinks are going in.
How long are you going to make me dance?
Drink up.
It's a perfect time for drinks.
Apparently, the money that the principal has pocketed so far is enough
to buy a house in Gangnam.
That is ridiculous. Heol!
I saw it coming,
but I didn't know it was going to be that much.
How could an educator of kids
do such a thing?
I know, right? I'm glad it all worked out,
but I feel quite bitter.
He really lives up to his name.
He's so obnoxious, isn't he?
He makes me ashamed to face my students.
I know.
When I think about the kids who didn't see this coming,
I feel so bad for them.
That's right.
By the way,
how did the hidden camera video
from his office get leaked?
I know, right? It's so fascinating.
Who leaked it?
Gosh.
Where's Mr. Choi?
Is he fashionably late?
No, he should be here by now.
I'm here. Were you all waiting?
Mr. Choi, this is great.
You have returned as a full-time teacher.
Congratulations.
He was always meant to be a full-time teacher.
There were just twists and turns along the way.
Congratulations, Mr. Choi.
I'd like to announce one more thing
on this good day.
We're getting married.
Congratulate us.
Oh, my gosh.
When did you start...
How could you surprise us like this?
I had a feeling all along.
Congratulations, you two.
Thanks, Maeng.
I'm sorry. As an apology,
I will treat you all to two rounds of drinks today.
Two rounds?
You're now an engaged man and a full-time teacher.
You have so much good news.
You should take...
A love shot.
- Love shot.
- Gosh.
- Don't do this.
- Love shot.
- Gosh.
I'm so glad Teacher Maeng is back.
When she walked into the room,
the kids all clapped,
and I almost cried.
I think Je Yi is really cool.
Je Yi figured out the password to the hidden camera video,
which basically solved everything.
He's pretty amazing the more I think about it.
I was the one...
who found the hidden camera video.
What? Are you getting jealous?
No.
- I think you are.
- No, I'm not.
By the way,
isn't this a pretty sweatshirt?
Yes, it's cute.
I know, right?
I knew you'd say that,
so I got you one, too.
Taking a picture of us in matching couple sweatshirts is
on my bucket list.
It looks so good on you.
How can a guy wear this?
You don't want to wear it?
Fine then. Don't wear it.
Ji Na!
Where are you going?
How can I wear this?
She'll get angry if I don't wear it.
You put it on.
It looks great on you.
Let's take a picture.
What's going on?
Why is this eonni looking at him that way?
Eonni Sin Ae,
come sit here.
Sa Na, you're here, too.
Hi.
It's obvious.
She likes him.
I guess this clueless oppa doesn't know yet.
Shall I help them?
Eonni and Oppa, I have to leave now
because I'm busy.
- Did something happen?
- Yes.
Aunt is stuck in the bathroom without any toilet paper.
Eonni, look after Oppa Je Yi.
Oppa Je Yi, you should grab some food with Sin Ae.
I'll get going.
A courageous woman wins at love.
Love is right under your nose. Don't let her get away.
Sin Ae, can I take a look at your science notes?
I forgot to bring my notebook.
Here. I was just using them.
I like Seo Je Yi.
It's the handwriting from that note.
What's wrong?
Did I get something wrong?
No. You have nice handwriting.
Do I?
Can I help you?
I'm fine.
Did I make you wait?
No.
I can't believe he's in a suit.
He sure looks happy.
Is he about to confess his love or something?
Do you think I'll be able to do well?
Of course.
Then do you think
I can confess my love?
- Of course. Do it before it's too late.
- I can't believe this.
Hurry and confess your love.
Gosh.
I'm so nervous.
Do you really think it's okay?
I said it's fine.
Then...
I'll do it.
Everyone,
I'm about to confess...
my love today.
Confess?
Even if it gets a bit loud,
please be understanding.
- Please...
- All right.
It's okay.
I can't believe this.
- How brave.
- You are.
I better leave...
before I get hurt.
Eun Hui.
I love you, Eun Hui.
I love you more now
than the day I met you.
This was...
meant
for me?
Do you like it?
I made this myself
just as you like it.
Do you like it?
You made this yourself?
The florist taught me
how to make it, and I did it myself.
So that's why...
you were always with her?
Congratulations.
Congratulations, Mom.
What's going on?
What do you think?
Dad prepared a surprise event for you.
I found out today, too.
Eun Hui...
I have one more thing for you.
What is it?
How...
The cake is
totally my taste.
From now on,
I will never...
give you financial stress.
Trust me this once.
Eun Hui...
Will you accept
my second proposal?
Mom, accept it.
Only you would get two proposals from the same man.
Oh, my gosh.
You should've told me beforehand.
How can I accept a proposal looking like this?
You still look pretty anyway.
Whatever.
Is this real?
Of course, it is.
I'm sorry about that time. I didn't know.
I'm sorry, too. I couldn't tell you then.
How much is this?
Two, four, six, eight, ten,
Twelve, fourteen...
There's so much.
Hanjong Elementary School 32nd Reunion
- It's been a while.
- Dae Gil.
Yeong Min.
Seon Hui, over here.
How have you been? Have you been doing well?
Yes. It's nice to see you again.
- What about you?
- I'm just
taking care of the kids.
I'm so busy.
Are you married?
No, not yet.
If you can afford to, it's better to live by yourself.
Don't get married.
Getting married is digging your own grave.
Good to see you.
I'd rather get married and dig my own grave.
If you know of any nice men,
introduce me to them.
Hi.
Who are you?
You don't remember me?
Hold on.
Hello?
You don't remember him?
It's Kim Yi Dong.
Kim Yi Dong?
He was so little back then.
He has grown so much.
I know, right?
He's one of the few single men here.
Really?
There was a guy like that in our class?
Let's drink.
It's nice to see you all.
Why aren't you married yet? You don't lack anything.
You have a boyfriend, right?
Of course, she'd have one.
Gosh, what am I supposed to say?
They'll look down on me if I say no.
If I say yes, they won't introduce me to guys.
No.
I don't have one.
Oh, no.
It must be hard to meet guys now.
That's true. Guys want to date younger girls.
Why would they want to date an old woman?
How could you call her an old woman? It's embarrassing.
No, I mean...
You look young on the outside,
so you don't look that old.
In my opinion, Seon Hui looks ten years younger than you all do.
Oh, my. That's going a bit far.
Seon Hui doesn't look any older than 32.
She's still so pretty.
Come on. She looks older than 32.
Anyway, it was nice to see you all.
It's no fun here. Let's leave.
- Why?
- What's going on?
- Who is that?
- Is it her boyfriend?
What's going on?
That's her boyfriend?
I was actually going to leave
because it was getting uncomfortable.
Should I be grateful, since you helped me?
I wasn't trying to help you.
I actually meant it.
You're still really pretty and charming.
Hey.
Do you really not remember me?
I'm sorry.
We never saw each other after elementary school.
I don't really remember.
We saw each other recently.
What?
Where?
It was on Gangbyeon Expressway, at Yanghwa Bridge.
I'll take you home. Get in.
Kim Yi Dong.
He does look familiar.
Why do I feel so comfortable, as if it were my own home?
We're home safe. Let's take a proof shot.
- What in the world are you doing?
- One, two, three.
- Snap.
- What are you doing?
Gosh, you're so handsome.
- One, two, three.
- You have good taste.
Wait...
Have I been in your car before?
Do you remember now?
Oh, my gosh.
When I was drunk
and taking photos...
Was that you?
Yes.
You actually remember.
I didn't know at first,
but after seeing you two or three more times,
I could tell it was you.
Don't drink so much.
Do you think I can get married?
Why not? You've met him already.
We saw each other recently.
He's roaming around.
He keeps on roaming around.
It was on Gangbyeon Expressway, at Yanghwa Bridge
I see that he has a certification from the government.
I think it's fate.
I guess I've been drinking all this time in order to meet you.
Next time you're drunk,
don't call any other taxi. Call me.
I'll come wherever you are.
Well...
- Surprise!
What's going on? You scared me.
The banner was specially made at the place
that makes banners for AOA.
Every moment spent with you two dazzled.
Remember this member forever~ ♥
You didn't have to do this. It's embarrassing.
We know you like it.
Yes, I love it to death.
You guys made it really pretty.
- Good job.
- Yes.
You know how loyal we are.
Loyal.
I missed three classes of hagwon.
We prepared a gift for you.
Photo Album
As if you're going to the cafeteria.
♫ Was it from that day? Was it since then when I started to yarn for you ♫
♫ Was it from that moment? Everyone except us knew it ♫
♫ I follow your gaze without realizing it ♫
♫ I can hear how you feel ♫
I'm so touched.
Thanks so much.
♫ I follow you ♫
Here.
This is my gift.
You're going to miss these when you go to the States.
You're thankful for my thoughtfulness, right?
Yes.
I'll think of you whenever I eat it.
Ro Bin, you seem so much happier now.
- Do I?
- It's true.
It surprises me too these days.
Do you remember when Ro Bin first transferred here?
Of course, I do. He was so cold.
I was scared of him.
Did he change this much
because of you?
Is this the power of love?
- Do you want a slice of pizza?
- Sure.
By the way, Sin Ae,
do you want the reference book I used?
Are you okay with a used book?
Of course, I'm okay with it.
It was used by the top student of our school.
Of course, I would want it.
What's going on? Why are you blushing?
I'm getting suspicious of you two.
N-No, I'm not blushing.
Then why are you stuttering?
I smell something fishy here.
Stop. Sin Ae is getting flustered.
I think you're blushing, too.
- What are you talking about?
- How suspicious.
When are you going to stop eating?
- It's so good.
- It was so fun at Grandma's, wasn't it?
- Yes.
- Eat up.
- Look at his face.
- This is good.
- Who ate it?
- Not me.
- We couldn't catch any fish.
- How did you know I ate it?
- That's right.
- Oh, my gosh.
Ji Na.
Here.
Thanks.
You fixed this?
I did fix it,
but I had to reset it, so you might've lost some important files.
That's all right.
There was something important in there,
but I don't think I'll need it anymore.
Anyway, you're amazing, Je Yi. Thank you.
Let me head back now.
- Look at this.
- Okay.
Bo Ra put that on you. It's too much.
I was holding the camera.
Who wants cake?
- Me.
- Thanks.
Me, too.
Revenge Note is back.
Without this,
I thought I wouldn't be able to do anything.
I don't think I'll need it anymore.
I have my precious friends who are always there for me.
Someone else will need it more than I do.
Just as I needed it before.
Reinstall the Revenge Note?
No.
Revenge Note has been uninstalled
Revenge Note has been sent to the next person