Those Haruhi's can't live with such a
I'm not sure if I should be using the
Fireball here, but I'm sure it's a good idea to use it.
I'm not sure if I should be using the Fireball here, but I'm sure it's a good idea to use it.
Welcome to the Back to the Future
Next, let's welcome today's challenger, Wang Mi Xia and Wang Wan Yi!
The match begins now!
Mr. Ye, it's time!
Mr. Ye, don't worry.
We'll use the speech recognition feature later.
Wang Yi, the match begins now!
The match begins now!
It's okay, Mr. Ye.
You've done a great job.
We have a lot of prizes waiting for you.
This is the free membership card for the rest of your life.
That's great!
Come on, Mr. Ye.
Let's take a picture together.
Today, many parks and communities in Jinchuan City are holding the first poetry contest
called Back to the Future.
The new song of the competition is related to a game called Back to the Future.
The game is a unique design that merges the poetry elements and the game's unique gameplay.
It has attracted a lot of attention.
Back to the Future lets the game and traditional culture create new sparkles.
Games are all about the red water.
Games that can encourage entertainment and make people progress.
Tenda has always been based on this concept.
It's a game that can bring players more positive meaning.
This time, we not only developed a poetry contest program,
but also held many offline events in the city.
In order to let players and other groups join the competition,
the public is loved by the poetry and painting.
How is it? Is it okay?
Don't say that. Brother Bao is quite good at it.
Really?
He's much more energetic than usual.
But I feel a little awkward watching myself on TV.
Sister Liu Yuan,
I have been constantly contacted by people to give me the authority to hold the poetry contest.
I have also been contacted by people to give me the authority to hold the poetry contest.
There are many university clubs, various communities, and senior universities.
There are also many people who signed up online.
There are many more people who signed up online than expected.
We have to hurry up and test this program.
Okay.
Let's get started.
I am sorry, Mr. Pei.
The traffic of the test project is mainly concentrated in the community of old people in the school community.
It developed to the end of the month in the existing trend.
We can only go back to the original.
It's much worse than the previous god-given contract, The King of the Valley.
It's our fault.
You mean,
I can't meet each of your demands?
I think you are right.
I have no other people to think of other than the god-given contract.
I don't have that much luck.
I'm going back to the book this month.
Just for the sake of it.
It's mainly because I'm proud of your strategy.
I...
What strategy?
Did you forget?
When I asked you to promote the game,
you said you would increase the budget.
You made me bold to spend money.
So you're doing activities in Jinchuan?
Yes.
Okay.
Lu,
did you put a lot of effort into this project?
You were always setting up a personnel department for me.
No, Mr. Pei.
He didn't work overtime.
He's really a fast and good programmer.
Yes.
Mr. Pei, I found out later that you're different from other bosses.
So I thought I'd work hard.
But don't worry.
I won't work overtime.
I promise to complete the job.
Because it's not hard for me.
Mr. Pei, you said you had to cut back on the project.
You had to spend all your resources.
You know that Ruan Guangjian and the others worked hard.
The original work is really great.
Mr. Pei, Ruan Guangjian is here.
Mr. Pei, I have to apologize to you.
I did draw a little bit of a blur.
I'm sorry.
I really thought you were a bad...
No, no, no.
A common boss.
So I taught him how to do business.
I didn't expect you to give me so much.
I'm really sorry to my partner.
So this time, I'll do my best.
Guangjian was also in the low-life.
He was suspected of being a fake gang member.
He thinks it's worth it to create a good work.
I think Lin Wan's ink painting style is very compatible with the poem.
I have a lot of inspiration.
Thanks to Mr. Yuan's help,
Now the original painting, the cos circle, the ancient style circle are all alive.
Completely out of the circle.
I'm not going to do it.
Go!
Where are your glasses?
Thanks to you, I made some money.
The next day we met in the telephone booth,
I had a close-up eye surgery.
The eyes are better, the painting is faster.
The problem is that we're mixed up with that game.
It's so difficult.
It's a combination of five words.
I'm full of hatred. Who wants to play?
Mr. Pei, you're right.
This time, in addition to traditional game players,
There are a lot of people who are self-sufficient.
We turned our heads and tried to drive the whole Minggu Poetry Club to learn the hot spot.
The public opinion has become positive.
Why didn't you tell me about this earlier?
The data in the background is not deep.
We thought you knew.
Look, Mr. Pei is here.
Thank you.
You see the beautiful scenery,
Do you only say the word,
And the word,
Or,
It's so beautiful.
But we can also say,
The color is not clear,
The blue and gray are full of Jiangcheng.
You can praise the deep and dark,
Outside the river,
And recently,
The game of the fatherland has turned its head.
The game of the ancient poem,
The prelude of the country's blood.
Let more people realize,
In addition to the Internet usage,
We have so many precious poems and great speeches.
Let us continue to be true romance.
This is not a joke.
Mr. Pei,
You're happy here alone.
Do you think I look happy?
You,
Didn't you just be happy?
Then you think it's happy,
Then it's happy.
Mingwan,
It's like this,
I'm like your parents,
I really hope you can return to life.
Don't do this game of turning your head again.
It has no future.
Why?
Did my parents come to you?
Mr. Pei, don't worry.
I will never give you trouble.
I know the boss is worried about his employees.
There will be no trouble.
But I'm not like this.
It's not easy to get back to work.
I plan to make an English version.
To be discovered internationally.
No, no, no, no.
Don't do it.
You see, you are already so powerful.
You're still working so hard.
You have to leave some room for your future self.
It's not that exaggerated.
Yes, very exaggerated.
Mingwan, I'm begging you.
You go home.
You must not stay here.
Mr. Pei is right.
I will go home in a few days.
Go back and ask them.
What are their good opinions about the return mountain?
No, I'm going home right now.
I'll book a ticket for you.
Wait, Mr. Pei.
My parents are in Jinchuan.
They saw me too busy recently.
So they came to see me.
Mr. Pei, where are you going to celebrate this time?
By planting Fried Chicken Spring,
we will place a set aside for next time.
Next time, I will go there for a generators.
I'll introduce it.
Mr. Pei.
I will take care of your business fee this year.
I have meeting for the pre- sytuational basis.
There is någonting wrong.
I'm a poor man.
My work is too
humane.
Why no one is watching?
Forget it.
I have to pay back.
I can't allow it.
Hello, Ma Ya.
What's going on?
We have to celebrate.
I have booked the restaurant.
I'll go.
Eat lobster.
But this is delicious.
Oh, Mr. Pei.
The one at the TV station in Jinchuan
is not here.
I'll go.
Mr. Pei, the TV station in Jinchuan
wants to shoot a video of the case.
When do you have time?
I'll ask you to meet the person in charge.
Let's talk about it.
Mr. Pei, our website has opened.
I'm thinking about doing some
subscription projects.
We can't just go to the center.
What do you think?
I've earned so much money.
I just wrote the new project.
Why don't you give me a new project?
You don't know my project.
How can I surpass you if you keep going like this?
Who are you asking me?
How do I know?
Ask Xing Zhezhu.
You help me persuade him.
I told him he wouldn't listen.
He just gave me a blank look.
If you keep going like this,
we can't afford to spend 20 million.
How much is Xingzhu's account?
20 million?
Why didn't Xingzhu tell you?
Before, our boss in Shulanjiansen
saw the business model and spent 20 million.
What's wrong with Mr. Pei?
He's happy.
Right?
We're in a hurry today.
Let's take a photo to record this happy moment.
Okay.
Hello, beautiful.
Come here.
Okay.
Let's take a photo together.
Make life easier.
Yeah!
The End
What?
Li Shi spent 20 million on Shulan?
God,
please forgive me.
From now on,
you're the only one who can eat meat and drink soup.
We'll work together.
That's it.
Mr. Li,
this is the first time I've seen you
give so much to others.
You know what?
Business is
broad and broad.
Only then can it be
open and fair.
I'll go.
Okay.
Get the car ready.
The food is ready.
Please enjoy.
This is the one I just caught.
It's fresh.
Thank you.
Go take a shower.
Okay.
Mr. Li,
I appreciate your kindness.
Can you not treat me to dinner next time?
Can't you just give me a change of clothes?
I'm not going to eat.
I'm going to eat.
Can't you just give me a change of clothes?
You still like to joke around.
I'll treat you to dinner in the Ming family.
You're a total connoisseur.
Now I'm here in your unknown place
to catch your fish.
You're used to it.
I'm not joking.
I've just been hit by
a serious problem in my life.
I can't hold on for a few months.
I really don't want to.
I'm going to lose my mortgage.
You've been eating so much today.
How many months did it take me to open up?
I didn't expect Mr. Pei to be so honest.
It seems that he really takes me as a friend.
Mr. Pei,
in fact,
it's normal that the funds can't be transferred.
Sometimes I don't have enough cash.
It's nothing.
Just right.
Now the 20 million loan of the number of exercises
should have arrived.
I hope I can solve Mr. Pei's
urgent problem.
That 20 million
is yours.
Answer.
Did I say
I want to cooperate with Mr. Pei?
And Mr. He also wrote
that in addition to this 20 million,
all the profits of the gym
will also be shared with Mr. Pei.
Don't get excited.
Actually, I came here today
I...
I mainly want
Mr. Pei to tell us
what our next
investment plan is.
What is it?
What other garbage investment projects are there?
It's the kind of
that can save my life
and at the same time
compensate your 20 million.
You know what? You don't know.
Now these projects are too common.
They are not enough to save me.
I need to be the kind of god.
The bigger the project, the better.
I seem to understand.
Look, Mr. Pei,
you don't have enough money now.
But you still
want to have a project that is stable and stable.
It's not interesting.
What you want to challenge now is
to make a big profit, right?
Okay.
I'll tell you all my investment tricks today.
Buy the father, don't buy the daughter.
Ask for the loss, ask for the gold.
Mr. Li, do you know
what other investment projects are there?
It's the kind of investment
that can save my life.
I really think of one.
Mr. Pei,
why do you like this place again?
Isn't this place good?
The square is ten miles away.
There will be no obstacles
in this building.
The project is set up by the developer
as a city landmark
with a high-end apartment, high-quality housing,
a modern commercial district, and a
Where is the park?
Just under our feet.
Just under the park.
A little bit under the ground.
Here.
This is a problem.
The information says
that the transportation is convenient,
a land is high,
and the price is high.
There are two buildings
in the building.
The basic facilities are good.
There are no people.
In the future, the fish will be...
Mr. Pei, I really want to buy this.
Or you can see.
I bought it.
I bought all the buildings.
Mr. Pei.
You are really
extraordinary.
Mr. Pei.
No, Mr. Pei.
I thought you asked me to talk about the house in the house tomorrow.
Why did you set up another apartment?
The house in the house tomorrow is my personal.
The one in Tenda is my family's.
If I don't set up a family's apartment,
how can I install my own personal apartment?
Mr. Pei.
Your ambition is really admirable.
If you are not the boss,
I thought you were the boss.
No, no, no.
I mean, you gave me such a big project.
I will not let you down.
This is our design plan
for the decoration style of Tenda apartment.
Let me show you.
This is the cream and hard style.
This is the designer and
this is the golden and glorious style.
Of course, we also have the new Chinese and ancient style.
It's too traditional.
Then, I will remember it.
Mr. Liang.
Is there a possibility that
Tenda's apartment is more than
all the apartments in the market?
We have to give the user a 100-inch 4K battery
and a full set of professional sound effects,
a screen and a projection, and many other options.
We also have to buy a game console for the user
and interact with the automatic brightness.
We can automatically clean the machine
and charge the smart lock.
We also have a massage sofa
with all the functions and all the smart home appliances.
The AI human body sensor system
you mentioned last time.
Mr. Pei.
If we add these things,
will it be very expensive?
For the experience of the user,
we have to pay a high price.
Mr. Liang, don't worry about the high price.
This time, we don't ask for the best,
but the most expensive.
Okay.
And don't worry.
This time, Tenda will definitely not ask for your salary.
Okay.
Mr. Pei,
is there a price for hardware?
Both soft and hard wear are on the same level.
Then the apartment will be sold out.
Look,
our soft and hard wear are very luxurious now.
But for hardware,
we have to focus on contrast.
The more we break through, the better.
Okay.
I've decided.
We don't stick to the wall.
We don't lay the ground.
We don't brush the paint.
The wall and the ground.
We are all mud.
We walk in that kind of bad style.
What people see is the wind of the broken wall.
It's a sight to see.
Mr. Pei,
is this kind of decoration style
too advanced?
I'm worried that
many customers can't accept it.
How can someone not accept it?
I...
I have a friend
who lives in the wrong room.
He's still living in the wrong room.
We Tenda are always like this.
We only attract people who are equal and fair.
We will never force them.
And designer Liang,
you must remember to strictly improve the user.
You must keep the original position of the apartment.
Okay.
No, no.
Mr. Pei.
In the future,
how can we introduce to customers
the contrasting style
of the apartment decoration style
you mentioned?
This apartment
is four sides of the wind
and four corners of the house.
Four sides of the house?
It's called four sides of the house.
Designer Liang,
you will have a hard time in the future.
Mr. Pei.
Don't worry.
Hurry up and spend money.
Don't worry about spending money.
Tenda will pay for you.
Don't save money for us.
Okay, Mr. Pei.
Let's go.
Mr. Pei.
I finally caught you.
Do you have time now?
Mr. Pei.
After the feedback test was officially introduced,
I made a new game planning plan
MMORPG.
The name is God's Mountain Sea.
Please have a look.
No hurry.
You worked overtime every day
because of the feedback test.
You worked very hard.
Other bosses might ask you
if you did well.
But I only care
how much you sleep.
If you have time,
you can go to the gym and rest more.
I read online that
many people with insomnia have been cured.
No need, Mr. Pei.
I don't have insomnia.
I'm not tired.
I just want you to see
my plan.
The game here is very promising.
I can feel your enthusiasm.
But Tenda has already
released four games so far.
Each one is popular.
It's really a pain.
I often ask myself
if we really have the potential
to create a lot of games.
Can we carry these?
Mr. Pei.
Every game made by Tenda
is very impressive.
But you will think twice.
It's already over 99% of the total number.
But the development of Tenda games
has stopped.
I think the top priority
is to...
is to think about
what kind of games
players like now.
Think about how we can
create a game
that is innovative
in the cross-generation.
Mr. Pei.
Do you not want to
develop new games at all?
How is that possible?
Don't worry.
I will definitely look at your plan.
You should also
think more,
and do more.
Don't say that.
Mr. Pei, my computer!
Is it because my idea is too immature?
So Mr. Pei is not interested?
I don't think it's possible.
I have studied your plan
of the Godly Mountain Sea carefully.
As the chief test-taker of Tenda games,
I will tell you the game instinct
that I brought from the mother-in-law.
The Godly Mountain Sea
is based on your current idea.
If you can come up with this idea,
it will definitely work.
I also think
that I want to play
your plan.
Do you really think so?
But Mr. Pei made me reflect
and make me more innovative.
That's because he didn't look at your plan.
How can your plan be innovative?
What can you reflect on?
As long as he looks at your plan,
he will think that
you made this game.
That's what he wants.
Thank you, Brother Bao and Xiaolv.
I was almost out of confidence.
I'm quite touched
to hear you say that.
How about we play the plan together?
With Brother Bao playing with me,
and Xiaolv's technical support,
we can definitely make Mr. Pei
do something.
Okay.
No, I don't work overtime.
I was found out by Mr. Pei
when I worked overtime last time.
If I'm found out again this time,
it will be troublesome
if I have to work a lot.
I have to be a big waste.
I have to work hard.
I have to be a big waste
to not let others use me.
I know I don't let you work overtime.
But can you...
No.
Brother Bao,
we don't have a second brother
who is at the top level
and has the best skills in the world.
We have to be prepared.
We have to make this game
for 60 years.
Really?
If we don't have
a genius like Xiaolv,
we can't make
the Godly Mountain Sea as perfect as we thought.
Yes.
What a pity.
Wait.
I'm interested
in the Godly Mountain Sea.
I can help you
during the time
when you are working
and taking a bath.
Don't thank me too much.
Cheers.
The four-billion-yuan-yuan
is my last wave.
I can't let the previous
cycle of life and death
be over again.
I can't let the previous
cycle of life and death
be over again.
These four-billion-yuan-yuan-yuan
can always find
my Godly Mountain Sea.
No.
I have to set up
a door that can't be controlled.
Mr. Pei.
What's going on?
I told you to recognize me.
Take her and turn around.
What?
Turn around.
It's about the same secret.
Don't expose it.
Xiaotang.
You've had a hard time
during the time
when you were working.
I observed
that you were working
in the same room
with the same person.
I saw that you were working
in the same room
with the same person.
I saw that you were working
in the same room
with the same person.
I observed that
although you don't
like to talk,
you have a low sense of presence,
but you are actually
a trustworthy person.
So I thought for a long time
and decided to give you
an important task.
Are you ready?
What are you going to do?
It's all here.
Let's go.
Mr. Pei, please come in.
The four-bed apartment
has reached the standard of intersection.
The walls and the ground
are all pure cement.
The furniture and the shop
are top-quality.
The whole house is also equipped with a self-contained button.
It has reached the experience of living in the house.
It's a perfect match.
Mr. Pei,
the whole house can be controlled
by AI voice control.
This room is designed for you.
It has set the scene command.
You can try it.
Flying yellow,
hit!
Mr. Pei,
did you mean this?
It's great!
Mr. Liang,
your design this time
is too in line with my requirements.
Thank you.
Cui,
I will leave the rest to you.
Mr. Pei,
I am grateful for your trust in me.
Thanks to you,
I am already the general manager of the university.
It's like a dream.
I'll confirm it again.
What are your requirements for the rental of this apartment?
For example, the price.
We four apartments only rent and do not sell.
Only rent.
Only rent and do not sell.
Yes.
In order to ensure the needs of the user,
We four apartments prohibit the rent of the apartment.
In addition, we will provide the user with 24 hours of cleaning service and housekeeping service.
For example, these home appliances are too fast.
We will update them regularly for the user.
So the apartment is one-time payment for ten years.
One-time payment?
If that's the case,
Is your price a little bit high?
For example, if you want to go all the way to the high end,
Then these rich people in Jinchuan have a lot of options.
The point is that you don't let customers decorate themselves.
Then they don't really have to choose these four coins.
Designer Liang, tell Xiao Cui
The concept of our four-coin apartment.
There is a four-coin meeting.
No opposite, no opposite.
That's right.
So our apartment must strictly follow environmental standards.
Look, our apartment has just been renovated.
It must have a lot of space.
So we have to put it down and get more wind.
President Pei, we didn't renovate it at all.
And these furniture are all environmental materials.
Actually, it's been on for a long time.
According to you, I also found a professional company to get rid of the rights three times.
Far below the standard.
Really don't need to put it down again.
That's not good.
We should implement it according to the mother's standard.
Everything is for the children.
President Pei, we have to blow the wind.
Xiao Cui, you are the manager.
You have to go to all departments to go into the internship.
Participate in the work of each department.
Play your role more.
The specific content can be done according to what I said.
President Pei asked you to work in our game department.
That's right.
President Pei said my main task is to go to all departments of Tenda.
What do you think?
I think it's a good idea.
My main task is to go to all departments of Tenda.
Do you need my help?
Tang, you are not in line with my profession.
You can't write code.
I don't need your help.
Xiao Cui, I have to criticize you.
Tang is a manager.
He is here to learn.
Do you understand?
You have to be a little better.
Tang, it doesn't matter if you can't write code.
You can play games.
You come and play games with us first.
Okay.
Thank you, Brother Bao.
The requirements for computer configuration are high.
This is the top computer I bought.
You feel it first, okay?
Okay.
Your game department is different.
The keyboard and screen of the computer can be folded.
Hey!
I didn't fold this!
Brother Bao, let's play together.
Son, let's go pick you up.
Well, how about we change the action?
Slowly, spread your waist.
Especially those who are always sitting.
Come on!
The waist can't be moved.
Mr. Ma.
I found that your eyes are dry.
Your lips are also dry.
Really?
This should be a damage to your kidney.
What? You said kidney?
Yes.
But it doesn't matter.
The expert said that you only need to drink water once every half an hour.
It will be relieved.
I will remind you.
Mr. Ma, it's time.
It's time to drink water.
I can't drink it.
Mr. Ma, stop playing.
Mr. Ma, it's time to drink water.
I can drink it myself.
You...
Brother Huang, do you think I need to do anything
for our Chinese website?
Our authors have poor data.
They are all depressed.
Please encourage them.
Thank you.
Encourage.
Hi.
I'm here to write.
How's it going?
I've been here for so many days.
I can read it more.
I can't get used to it.
I want to give up.
You write it?
I can't.
You really want to give up?
I want to give up.
But I want to be a good student.
I want to work hard.
I want to be a good student.
I want to give up.
Then you give up?
You've been writing for so long, the data is bad, you're not happy.
Then do you think you're not suitable for this job?
But I'm just writing, what else can I do?
You can do self-media.
Since you like writing, you can write scripts and make vlogs.
I think you have a future in writing.
If you're popular, you'll have your own IP.
Vlog?
Mr. Pei, do you think I have to continue with the training plan?
I've been following your instructions lately.
I feel like everyone is getting more and more out of shape.
They're all hiding from me. What should I do?
Xiao Tang, you've been working hard these days.
Next, all the actions can be done one by one.
Tell everyone a good news.
Four apartments can be rented.
Okay, Mr. Pei.
I'm sorry, Mr. Pei.
Guan Pei Sheng, which genius came up with this?
Du Jue Bei Zi, Guan Pei.
I have a 100-inch TV.
I also have a food court.
Four apartments cost so much.
I'm sorry.
I'll renovate my house tomorrow.
I'll be able to live there for a few days.
Come on, get ready
You'll be coming for a ride
Are you dreaming, Mr. Ma?
Mr. Pei even arranged the apartment for us.
Get down, get on board tonight
Let's all be on our feet
Go find a good boss.
I can drink water.
No, you say it.
You can't touch my computer.
Don't worry about the computer.
Let Mr. Pei give us a new clothes.
Mr. Pei, we're not going to the toilet.
It's hot.
What's this?
What's this, Mr. Sheng?
Welcome home
You're good at it.
Not only is it hot,
but it's too shy.
We can also say
A man with a face
He had a strong heart
He misfired at times
I love you more than the mountains
You want to ق ヤр Republicans
Went to Yang yesterday
I was nadie
If you feel sad
č89
Except of the coat ad
I can say
A man with a face
Thanks for watching!