[English subtitles are available]
This character, Ji Wuhuan, hasn't changed at all.
I mustn't give myself away.
Chief, disturbing your pleasure
was my dereliction of duty.
How did the selection of the paramours go?
Just him.
I’m leaving.
Xiaolian.
You too.
Me too?
Hurry.
Chief!
Chief.
Didn't you just pick one person earlier?
Why are you taking me along?
Chief.
Look at you.
You picked me in front of everyone.
Aren't you afraid of exposing my identity?
You are the spy Feng Nanxi
placed by Ji Wuhuan's side.
In this world,
I can only trust you.
Let me ask you.
Which month's 15th is today?
The seventh lunar month‘s.
No.
The Four Great Sects
will be here in just a month.
Ye Wuchen.
As long as I kill Ye Wuchen,
I can go back.
Chief.
Where is Ye Wuchen now?
Ye Wuchen?
Ye Wuchen, the eldest disciple of Xiaoyao Sect.
Haven't you heard of him?
The eldest disciple of Xiaoyao Sect?
Chief.
The eldest disciple of Xiaoyao Sect
is not Ye Wuchen.
If I remember correctly,
the eldest disciple of Xiaoyao Sect
should be called Sang Kun.
Sang Kun has become the eldest disciple?
What about Ye Wuchen?
I've never heard of him.
Oh no.
I seem to have deleted Ye Wuchen.
Ye Wuchen is not in this world.
Chief.
I can’t go back.
What should I do?
Go away now.
You don’t need me anymore?
I don't.
I’m leaving.
Oh no.
The story's plot is completely changed.
What should I do?
The only way to go back is gone.
Chief, it’s late.
I am here to assist you to bed.
Ye Wuchen is gone too.
Who are these people?
No!
What are you doing?
Chief.
You chose me.
What else can I do?
I'm warning you. Don't act recklessly.
Or is it that I, Shen Yu,
am unworthy of your favor?
Shen Yu?
Did I write about this person?
This is completely messed up.
If you keep doing this, I'll call for help.
Call for help?
Am I not enough
for you?
Master.
Did someone upset you?
Why aren't you staying with Feng Nanxi,
and why did you come to me?
Master, you misunderstood.
The chief scolded me
and kicked me out.
She said
the quality of the new paramours in our Moon Shadow Sect
is getting worse and worse.
She asked me to find more handsome men.
But why did she leave you in her bedchamber?
Couldn't she say these things to my face?
She knows you are my person.
No one can figure out the chief's temper.
Master, don’t be angry.
But didn't you feel
that something was off just now?
What do you mean?
The assassin attacked just now.
With Feng Nanxi's skills,
she wouldn't have needed help from a paramour.
Maybe
Chief did it on purpose.
Then why did she shout for help during the day?
Do you think
she is sufferring from Qi deviation due to practising Cloud Absorption Spell
and lost all her martial arts?
What are you doing? Don’t come over.
Chief, since you chose me,
it’s my duty to serve you.
She really lost all her martial arts skills.
Great. Feng Nanxi.
The position of Chief should be mine.
You deserve your current situation.
Why don’t I take this chance...
Chief.
I just want to remove your clothes.
If you think I did something wrong,
I can change.
I don't need it.
I’ll call for help if you keep doing this.
Chief.
I'm late.
Stop!
I don't think you're here to save her
but to kill her.
You pervert!
How dare you talk nonsense?
Ji Wuhuan.
As you can see,
he didn’t want to kill me.
Chief.
You may leave.
Yes.
I'll take my leave.
You too.
Get out!
Chief,
let me stay with you.
Are you forcing me to use Cloud Absorption Spell?
Cloud Absorption Spell?
This is... the Cloud Absorption Spell?
Do you want to eat something?
No.
I did hit you hard just now.
Are you alright?
As the Chief of Moon Shadow Sect,
why do you care about a lowly paramour?
I just don’t want to stain my chamber.
What are you doing?
Chief.
Someone is here.
It seems that you're surrounded by dangers.
You must need a confidant.
Are you really kicking me out?
Fine.
Since you are not interested in me,
I’m leaving.
He has a point.
I can't let anyone find out that I'm not Feng Nanxi.
I should keep up the act.