[English subtitles are available]
[Phoenix Lands in the World]
[This story is purely fictional]
[Episode 18]
[Moon Shadow Sect]
Feng Nanxi.
Chief Feng.
Senior Feng.
What’s wrong with him?
He must have lost his mind.
Senior Feng.
Give me the real secret book of Cloud Absorption Spell.
You know it.
That one is real.
But why is
my internal energy unstable?
You don't have enough internal force.
How can you blame the secret book?
Ye Wuchen.
I poisoned you to death.
Didn't you
drink that cup of tea?
Shen Yu.
You traitor to the righteous sects.
Today,
I will eliminate you.
What's going on?
[Ye Wuchen's Biography]
Shen Yu.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Let's go.
Bamboos.
One, two.
The moon.
The moon is so round.
Who are you?
Who am I?
You are Ye Wuchen.
My good disciple.
My arrival has changed the plot.
Feng Nanxi could have gone back after killing Ye Wuchen
at the wedding.
But why did I see the way back just now?
Is it because
Ye Wuchen is dead
so that the target has changed?
It's late.
What are you thinking about? Why are you still up?
Nothing.
You are so weak.
You should rest early.
I'm going to bed.
Ye Wuchen.
I poisoned you to death.
Didn't you drink that cup of tea?
Where have you been?
I couldn't sleep.
I went to the back mountain to take a walk.
Wuhuan.
You must tell me about such things
in the future.
I'll go with you.
Okay.
Wuhuan.
Do you smell
a strange smell of blood?
I...
What's wrong?
Wuhuan.
Xiaolian.
I want
to hug you a little longer.
If I kill Shen Yu,
can I go back?
Was the smell of blood last night from Wuhuan?
I have something to tell you.
Ye Wuchen may be alive.
What?
Shangguan Ye said
he poisoned Senior Ye with chronic poison.
But he couldn't find Ye Wuchen's body.
Senior Ye
has always been proficient in poisons.
Half of the books
in Xiangyang Residence
are about detoxification.
I find it
hard to believe
that Senior Ye died from poisoning.
Then why did I react to Shen Yu?
If that's the case,
Ye Wuchen might still be alive.
Chief.
Are you still going to find him?
I'm a little confused now.
I'll go and have some quiet time alone.
I'll accompany her.
If you're worried,
why don't you follow them?
What's the use of staying here?
Just now,
you kept staring at Ji Wuhuan.
You hesitated to speak.
I saw it.
My situation is different from yours.
But I think
since you came to Chief,
she has become more gentle.
In the past,
she always had a long face.
But now,
she has more smiles.
It's like
she has turned into a different person.
Wuhuan.
Why are you here?
You seemed distracted when we were eating.
Is something bothering you?
If you can't tell those two boys,
you can tell me.
There are things
you won't understand.
Perhaps the bystander has a clearer view.
Let me tell you.
I had a dream recently.
In my dream,
I wrote a novel.
It's about
the love story between me
and a hero.
But I need to kill this hero
to wake up.
What should I do?
You mean
you need to kill
the person you love the most.