[English subtitles are available]
[Phoenix Lands in the World]
[This story is purely fictional]
[Episode 13]
I'm afraid these will be my last words.
The men whose names are on the memorial tablets
in the confinement room didn't betray our sect.
Shangguan Ye has abused his power for personal gains
and frequently sent the Dark Division's disciples
to look for secret treasures for him to improve his power.
He has committed many crimes like setting fire, killing, and looting.
Master was worried someone would find out what he did,
so he made the Moon Shadow Sect his scapegoat.
If the Dark Division's disciples attempt to disobey him,
they will be killed.
Shen Yu.
What are you doing?
Hurry up.
Ye Wuchen, hurry up!
I've been waiting for you.
Coming.
What do you think of this sachet?
Not bad.
Take it.
No need for that.
Shen Yu,
don't you know
most of the businesses on this street
are owned by the Moon Shadow Sect?
Chief.
Xiaolian?
Chief, let me see if you're hurt.
I'm fine.
Why are you still with her?
She colluded with the Xiaoyao Sect
and almost got us killed.
Chief,
Wuhuan has realized her mistake.
She won't do it again.
I promise with my life.
What's wrong with her?
She suffered a bit these days.
She has been dispirited this whole time.
In my opinion,
why don't we let her manage a shop?
She needs to find something to do.
Otherwise,
she'll always focus on other people.
You're right.
By the way, Chief,
speaking of shops, you came at the right time.
I...
I happen to have something to do.
I'll meet you later.
Chief, let's go.
Wuhuan.
[Huishan Milk Powder Shop]
Xiaolian went to deliver goods with Ji Wuhuan.
He left me here alone.
It's so boring.
Why hasn't Shen Yu come back yet?
Come and take a look.
I want sunset on the mountain,
mist on the shores,
the sound of a flute,
and a boat.
You are... Senior Ye.
Tell Master
I'll wait for him
near the Xiaoyao Sect at midnight tonight.
What exactly did you do just now?
Nothing.
The order is wrong.
The method can be found
in the Manual of Making Mary Milk Powder.
Smell it.
Our Huishan Mary Milk Powder
is fragrant, right?
Yes.
It smells so good.
This is top-quality milk powder.
It's so fragrant.
I want to buy milk powder.
Shen Yu
is still hiding something from me.
Who on earth are you?
Stop playing tricks.
How did you know Wuchen's secret code?
Shen Yu?
Master,
does Senior Ye's death
have anything to do with you?
You appeared at the door of the Xiaoyao Sect when you were a baby.
You were just an abandoned baby.
I raised you
and taught you martial arts.
But now you've become a woman's dog.
Senior Ye's letter has told me everything.
You want to convict me with just a letter?
If you have a clear conscience,
why did you come here to see me?
Shen Yu,
I knew something is wrong with you during the day.
Where did you go?
I couldn't sleep, so I went out to practice swordsmanship.
You're not lying to me?
No.
It's not a white lie either?
Of course not.
Fine.
I trust you.
But don't go out at this hour again.
I was worried about you.
Okay.
I'm going to bed.
I'm so sleepy.
Nanxi,
give me three more days.
I will tell you the truth.
Before that,
let me be Ye Wuchen for a few more days.
Master,
I'm curious about the reason why Feng Nanxi
wants to find Ye Wuchen.
She even disbanded the Moon Shadow Sect.
It seems Shen Yu has approached Feng Nanxi
by pretending to be Ye Wuchen.
In other words,
Feng Nanxi still doesn't know
Shen Yu's real identity.
This...
Master,
there is one more thing that is very strange.
The Xiaoyao Sect has always been heavily guarded.
How did Feng Nanxi
manage to come and go freely before?
I haven't figured it out yet.
You may leave.
Could it be...
there is a secret passage?
Time for breakfast, Nanxi.
Nanxi.
Get up and eat.
What's up?
I'm not hungry. I want to get more sleep.
Be good.
I'm not hungry.
I want to get more sleep.
You can get more sleep after eating, okay?
Are you... okay?
I'm fine.
Are you okay?
Xiangyang Residence.