THIS DRAMA SERIES IS FICTIONAL
AND IS NOT RELATED IN ANY WAY
TO ACTUAL PLACES, PERSONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, SETTINGS AND EVENTS
You look happy.
Since when did this place
become freely accessible for just anyone?
I'm not just anyone.
I'm your son.
Yes.
The sole reason
you've been able to survive
in Kangoh is because you share my blood.
That was your only excuse.
- I met with CEO Park Sajin because...
- I want you out of Kangoh now.
You will be terminated
tomorrow morning at 9:00.
After that, you will be issued a notice
to be kicked out of Kangoh Group.
Why?
Why can't it be me?
I have the abilities
to make your dreams come true too.
Abilities?
Did you think those were your abilities?
Not Han Taeoh's?
Is that why you stole him?
If it were Taeoh instead of you,
I wouldn't have had
to split Kangoh in half
the way I did now.
I did everything in my power
to gain your approval.
So why haven't you acknowledged me
for a single moment?
Did you kill Inju
because I didn't acknowledge you?
My son! Your brother!
You killed him.
Kang Inha is a hollow shell.
Baek Inha!
That's who you are.
Put everything you have
in your hands down.
Go back to your old life.
If you go back and live quietly,
I won't make you pay
for your crimes.
What if I don't want to?
What?
I'm not the one that killed Inju.
It was you.
The person who made me this way
and killed Kang Inju!
In the end, it was all you.
You're finally showing your true colors.
Go back to being Baek Inha?
Now?
I can't do that.
I wasn't asking you.
If I tell you to leave, you leave!
That's the law of Kang Joongmo and Kangoh!
I'm different from my mother.
I won't give up that easily
without even trying.
There's nothing you can do.
I don't know. Is there really nothing?
Get out of my sight
before I call security!
Will you kill me too?
I don't want to see you, so...
Father, did you know?
I've come too far to turn back.
This wouldn't have happened
if you had acknowledged me...
a little sooner.
I wish...
you had reached out this hand
a little earlier.
Kang Joongmo's Kangoh is gone.
Kang Inha's Kangoh is about to begin.
How's Chairman Kang?
I just got the call
and I'm on my way to the hospital now.
I'll call you when I get there.
OPERATING CENTER
What's going on?
What happened?
I don't know.
I found him on the ground, passed out.
But why did you go to the office
at that time?
Why are you alone?
Where's your husband?
HYEWON
What?
RESTRICTED AREA
How's the chairman?
It's hard to tell you anything right now.
What do you mean?
He missed the golden hour
to take his heart medicine.
We'll have to wait for him
to regain consciousness.
It's all up to him now.
Mom!
Not yet...
Don't worry.
He won't go like this.
Sit down.
Wait, is there a hidden space?
KANG JOONGMO
Han Taeoh.
Who are you?
Han Taeoh?
Don't get the wrong idea,
I'm not here to confess.
You're a wanted man right now.
But you show up in front of a prosecutor?
I really didn't kill anyone.
So why would you tell me that?
What does that have to do with me?
I screwed you over.
I came to repay that debt.
What?
The night I supposedly
killed Kang Inju and Shin Bona.
Everything from that night was recorded
on Shin Bona's phone.
I really didn't kill anyone.
I'm giving you...
a chance right now, Prosecutor Ha.
Choose.
Will you take my chance
and return to the Seoul
or stay here and live a third-rate life?
INVESTIGATION ROOM 1
Great job.
Thank you.
This way.
ESCAPED CONVICT WANTED NOTICE
Find Han Taeoh right now.
SEONU WAN
Did I come to the wrong person?
Did I...
overestimate you?
Am I a joke to you
because I have no connections or money?
Do you think I'd do everything you ask?
I must be crazy.
I'm listening to this nonsense.
You are under arrest for escaping prison
and for obstruction of justice, Han Taeoh.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can
- and will be used against you in court.
- What does inferiority solve?
You...
- have the right to an attorney.
- Your inferiority will solve nothing.
It provides no consolation
to the deceased!
Catch the real culprit.
That's solace and peace.
You need to do that.
So, why? Damn it...
Why me? Why?
I told you.
I'm repaying my debt.
It's your last chance.
Choose.
Will you stay here...
or go back?
Ha Myeongjin made an entrance.
KANG INHA
DELETE
PERMANENTLY DELETE FILES?
Han Taeoh.
I think the chairman has him.
What were you thinking?
Why would you hold Taeoh?
He's not awake yet.
What happened to you?
I'll call you back.
Why are you so surprised?
What's going on?
Where's Han Taeoh?
Why are you asking me?
Because I know my dad was hiding him.
Tell me. Where is he?
I don't know.
Why do you think I'll know?
I don't care about this.
Really?
Then you won't care if I report this.
I'll tell them that the last person
my dad was with before he fainted
was Han Taeoh.
Han Taeoh. Where is he?
SEOUL EASTERN DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
EVIDENCE DATABASE
What if the video
isn't on the phone?
It's there. I'm sure of it.
What if it's not?
You can arrest me then.
I'm already standing
on the edge of a cliff.
CASE NUMBER 2023-1013
SHIN BONA'S EVIDENCE
EVIDENCE
Please.
Please...
ENTER YOUR PIN
Prosecutor, it's done. Check it.
NO PHOTOS OR VIDEOS
MY ALBUM
RECENT HISTORY
I already went through it,
but there's nothing.
Please...
Hey.
Hey!
Are you dead?
Inju!
I think he's dead!
Hey! I won!
Yes!
I'm the king!
Damn it!
What's this?
Do you want a drink?
Do you want drugs? Huh?
The weather's nice.
The perfect weather...
to go back somewhere.
You want to cut the video there?
Someone came in.
It's proof there was an accomplice.
It's a speculation.
Our job's to start with a speculation
and catch the culprit.
What if you can't?
Mo Gijun could escape
if something goes wrong.
You need to charge Mo Gijun first,
and then...
And then...
And after that...
Wait, do you know who it is?
- Han Taeoh.
- I'll help you...
catch the real culprit.
I keep my promises.
First of all, taking evidence like this
can cause problems for you.
Someone who should uphold
the law commits a crime?
That's why you should help me, sir.
On what grounds?
Come back with us.
Pack your bags and be here tomorrow.
I'll handle the procedural issues.
Thank you, sir.
ESCAPED CONVICT WANTED NOTICE
HAN TAEOH
CRIMINAL AFFAIRS DIVISION
I'm here to turn myself in.
ON DUTY
PROSECUTION SERVICE
Mr. Mo Gijun.
You're under arrest
for the murder of Kang Inju and Shin Bona.
What is this?
Let go of me. Damn it.
- Let's go.
- Yes, sir.
SECRETARY MO ARRESTED AS NEW SUSPECT
IN KANG INJU AND SHIN BONA'S MURDER
Seongju.
There will be no pardon
or amnesty for Han Taeoh.
We just need to keep going on our path.
KANGOH SECURITIES CEO KANG SEONGJU
Yes, Mother.
All that's left is Kang Inha.
That's right.
And he has no power without the chairman.
SECRETARY MO ARRESTED AS NEW SUSPECT
Things are getting interesting.
I don't have...
any money to hire an attorney from Milton.
Don't worry about money.
We have a pro bono program at Milton
to assist in free legal consult.
Are you using me
to promote Milton,
or are you trying to promote yourself?
Neither.
I'm only following the chairman's orders.
Chairman Kang Joongmo
could see everything clearly.
He asked me to help you
finish this matter.
Where shall I start?
Dad.
They caught the real culprit
who killed Inju.
So you have to get up, okay?
How's Chairman Kang?
Is he showing progress?
I know you met with my father.
Did he promise you something?
He said he'd give me Energy.
You didn't refuse him.
In my position,
it's more appealing
to stand with the owner
over the bastard child of Kangoh.
Energy.
I'll give it to you.
If you don't like the bastard of Kangoh,
you can help me become
the owner of Kangoh.
Someone of the Kang bloodline
to be your cannon fodder and shield.
I'll be that for you.
I don't know.
It's not that appealing.
I'll be honest with you.
If Chairman Kang
hadn't collapsed like that,
wouldn't you have been ousted?
If Chairman Kang wakes up tomorrow,
you're fated to leave Kangoh as planned.
Those chances are slim.
That's your wishful thinking.
You can never have Kangoh
as long as Chairman Kang's alive.
What if Han Taeoh returns to work
based on the court ruling?
Even if that happens, don't worry.
As of now, is there anyone who can help
Han Taeoh besides the chairman?
The one who made the ridiculous dream
of Royal Road a reality
was Han Taeoh, not your father.
Right.
If the time comes to make a decision,
accept Han Taeoh as one of our own.
Aside from our board members,
I'll gather as much stock
as I can for now.
Why now?
Why?
Why did you kill
Kang Inju and Shin Bona?
I was treated as less than human
for a long time.
There were frequent beatings
and verbal abuse.
That's why.
That's why I killed them.
You could've just quit.
- How could you kill someone?
- You don't know what it's like.
What about Han Taeoh?
Did you plan that too? Even perjury?
Yes.
You've answered "yes"
to all of my questions, Mr. Mo.
You created a falsely accused perpetrator
to take the fall
and even committed perjury
for the perfect crime.
And you're willing to admit to everything?
Where'd your determination
to not get caught go?
This wasn't your idea, was it?
I planned everything.
I did it.
Who planned this...
and ordered it?
No one.
Kang Joongmo's Kangoh is gone.
Kang Inha's Kangoh is about to begin.
KANG JOONGMO
Even if that time comes,
there's no need to complicate things.
Han Taeoh was falsely imprisoned.
Who will help him if Kangoh doesn't?
He was one of our own once.
He was more loyal than anyone.
Then...
as the division director of
the Future Strategy Office?
No.
As the planning and coordination director
of Kangoh Corporation.
- Excuse me?
- Yes.
There is no such department at Kangoh.
It's a new department
that I plan to make for CEO Kang Seongju.
Is it tomorrow?
Even after the darkest night
comes the dawn.
It's finally here.
Let's have a drink before you go.
You've never asked me to grab a drink.
You must want something from me.
Why Hong Kong?
There's an investment company there
called Gold H Investment.
It's a paper company
that I created to make Kang Inha
the chairman.
No one knows it exists, but me.
Not even Kang Inha.
I guess one more knows.
Me.
You're right.
Now that I know your secret,
will you kill me?
Do you want to gamble for real with me
before you die?
Not shooting craps
in an illegal gambling den,
but seizing control of the great Kangoh.
A real gamble.
He's coming.
Where is he?
- Why isn't he coming out?
- Was it not today?
Boss!
- Boss!
You've been through so much!
Tofu.
Boss! Have some tofu!
Hey!
Have some tofu!
Who the hell eats tofu these days?
Still, have a bite.
Let go of me!
Open wide!
Don't do it!
Don't!
Congrats on your release, Boss.
Is that you?
Hyangmi's daughter?
I knew your name sounded familiar.
Right?
Taeoh and I are on different pages.
I don't trust gamblers.
What?
- Gamblers?
- Hey.
I don't trust you either, Hyewon.
You're Hyangmi's daughter.
Yoon Hyangmi ran off with my money.
Since we're on the same page,
let's talk about work.
That's what I wanted. Yes.
Gold H Investment.
Michael Chang,
a Wall Street investment genius,
founded an investment firm
in Hong Kong in 2021.
Michael moved to the States
when he was young.
He graduated Cornell summa cum laude
and is an eccentric genius.
He was an active rower in college.
He fell in love with trekking
and works as a professional now.
Wait a second.
Who's Michael Chang?
I heard all about Gold H Investment
from Inmate 3866, so I know it well.
But he never told me about Michael Chang.
MICHAEL CHANG, 53,
AMERICAN, PROFESSIONAL TREKKER
Me?
Come on.
He's an old man.
He's not even
some friendly neighborhood guy.
He's an old dude from the outskirts.
Who are you?
Me?
Seonu Wan.
The ace
in this field.
There's something you don't know about me.
I'm a rabid dog.
A mad dog.
Woof, woof!
Do you have a death wish?
Who will kill me?
Ah. Mo Gjiun?
But he went to jail, didn't he?
Later.
Ah.
That's not loaded.
Don't waste your energy.
Wan!
Damn it!
Do we still have business?
Come on. Why would you say that?
Tell me why you're here.
Gold H Investment.
You had me fooled completely.
But you gathered shares
loud enough for me to hear.
- So?
- What do you mean?
You need my help.
BUY
TRANSACTION COMPLETE
YOUR PURCHASE WAS SUCCESSFUL
Sir, there's trouble.
Well, it is indeed an honor
to join your foundation.
Thank you.
Mother.
- Please, excuse me.
- Sure.
GOLD H INVESTMENT SHARE RATIO
Gold H Investment?
But, since when?
GOLD H INVESTMENT SHARE RATIO
Yes, sir.
Gold H Investment.
Look into it right now.
Yes, sir.
FUTURE STRATEGY OFFICE
DIVISION DIRECTOR KANG INHA
We're almost there.
You just need to come out
and pull the trigger.
Great job.
Thanks, Hyewon.
COURT
Your Honor,
I am not just here
to defend Han Taeoh today.
I am here
to give our country's judiciary
a chance to apologize for the wrongs
inflicted on an ordinary citizen
of this country.
I hope that the outcome of this trial
becomes an opportunity
for him and for all those
who cherish and love him
to have hope for a new life.
First, as a member
of the judiciary, I offer my apologies.
Defendant.
Will you stand for a moment?
DEFENDANT
Defendant...
Han Taeoh is innocent!
That is all.
That wraps up the retrial.
CORRECTION FOR A BETTER TOMORROW
DETENTION CENTER
HAN TAEOH FOUND INNOCENT OF MURDER
AFTER RETRIAL
Did you call for me?
Start monitoring Han Taeoh.
See who he's meeting
and what's being discussed.
Report every single thing to me.
Yes, sir.
KANG INHA KANGOH GROUP
KANG INHA SHOWS FRESH PASSION BY REJECTING
CONVENTIONAL CONGLOMERATE FRAMEWORKS
If Chairman Kang
wakes up tomorrow,
you're fated to leave Kangoh as planned.
Kang Inha is a hollow shell.
Baek Inha!
That's who you are.
Put everything you have
in your hands down.
Go back to your old life.
If you go back and live quietly,
I won't make you pay
for your crimes.
VIP PATIENT KANG JOONGMO
I'm sorry, Father.
You should've just died then.
If you had...
we wouldn't have go through this twice.