THIS DRAMA SERIES IS FICTIONAL
AND IS NOT RELATED IN ANY WAY
TO ACTUAL PLACES, PERSONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, SETTINGS AND EVENTS
I'm back, Chairman Kang.
If Chairman Kang
wakes up tomorrow,
you're fated to leave Kangoh as planned.
Kang Inha is just a hollow shell.
Baek Inha!
That's who you are.
Put everything you have
in your hands down.
Go back to your old life.
If you go back and live quietly,
I won't make you pay...
for your crimes.
VIP PATIENT KANG JOONGMO
I'm sorry, Father.
You should've just died then.
If you had...
we wouldn't have go through this twice.
How did you become such a monster?
- How?
- Don't act all high and mighty.
- Do you think you're any different?
- What becomes of you if the chairman dies?
You'll become a nobody. An invisible man.
You're crazy.
Snap out of it, Kang Inha.
Can't you return to being
the old Kang Inha?
Look who's talking.
Quit and go back to your place.
Didn't you say your life goal
was to get me to the top of Kangoh?
I can achieve that dream if you just
leave me alone so what's the problem?
Don't give me any more lessons.
The Kang Inha you know is gone.
Fine.
Do whatever you want.
However, you'll have to use
all your strength to stop me.
I know a lot things.
What do you know?
Everything.
I even have evidence to prove it.
Nonsense.
You can look forward to it.
You'll end up with nothing.
You'll ruin me
and take Kangoh for yourself?
Whatever the case...
who says I can't?
You?
I can't have the same dream
as you, Baek Inha?
Of course not.
You're not Kang Joongmo's son.
You seem to have forgotten.
You may be his son, but you couldn't
have had this dream without me.
Do you really think so?
Don't worry.
I won't stop you from dreaming.
Hey, Inmate 255.
You have a visitor.
Come on out.
Hello?
Who are you?
Gijun.
Inha.
I'm sorry.
I want to go there myself
to see if you're okay,
but there are too many eyes watching.
No.
You don't need to put yourself in danger.
Gijun.
Can I continue to trust you?
I'm almost at the top.
I can't be held back now.
I promised you.
I'll take the fall for all of it.
But, Inha...
I'm a little scared.
It's only a matter of time
before I get a death sentence.
Now that it's come to this,
I'm kind of scared.
Great job.
The average internal rate
of return is 27.3%.
When it's all done, it'll be 33.3%.
27.3% and 33.3%.
Gold H Investment.
It's a paper company I founded
in Hong Kong and never used.
This corporation will protect you
from hostile parties trying to acquire
the company's shares.
What about the funds?
For funds, if you can release a portion
of the overseas funds for finance,
I'll start the process
of neutralizing the opposing forces.
He took the bait!
It's a hit!
He bit hard!
What? He did?
Things are going to work out
pretty easily.
Kang Seongju made the request first.
He wants to meet.
Old man.
You need to get ready.
Well...
I'll try my best. What else can I do?
Don't worry about it.
With the shares at Gold H,
they won't be able to look down on you.
A little bit more to the left.
Looking good. Let's move this way.
Do you have time to talk?
You don't think...
Inju's shares are yours, do you?
- What do you mean?
- The shares you have
must only be used for the Kang family.
Who are you to tell me what to do?
With Taeyang's shares
along with my family's shares,
I don't think you're in any position
to tell me what to do.
I wouldn't have come
if I were scared of that.
I'm just telling you not to get any ideas.
Give that power to Seongju.
Is Seongju feeling urgent?
Did he ask you to say this to me?
He didn't ask me to do anything.
Then do you have something else in mind?
- What?
- If that's not it...
don't get involved.
Don't step in and get hurt.
Are you worried about me right now?
I'm warning you.
Don't forget your duty
as the daughter-in-law
of the Kang family.
Seongju, you take responsibility
for Gold H and bring them to our side.
Yes, I requested a meeting.
They responded right away.
Things are looking good.
Don't let your guard down
and strengthen the relationship
with the shareholders on our side.
It's time for the opposing shareholders
to come to our side now.
Do you think
they'll come over that easily?
In the end,
they're just fish living in Kangoh's pond.
They'll pick their owners
depending on who fills their bellies more.
We have to move faster now.
Okay.
I'll secure the shares Gold H has
in a few days.
Also, Congressman Jo
is working hard in the pits,
so they'll have no choice but to join us.
We can no longer tolerate
the sight of predators targeting Kangoh
from all around
just because your father's down.
We have to make a choice.
This is really the last step, Mother.
I'll succeed Father well.
Don't worry.
It's called Gold H Investment,
and it's owned by Michael Chang.
Michael Chang? Where did he come from?
He got a taste for money by inflating
and selling mergers and acquisitions.
He'll be allured
by a sweeter deal from either side.
We'll postpone the decision
and carry it out.
It could threaten PY Holdings.
What do you want to do?
Will you stand by
and watch Kang Seongju make a move?
Keep in mind, Mr. Kang,
I can let go of your hand whenever I want.
Don't make me regret my choice anymore.
What is it?
What are you doing here?
Michael Chang.
He called us to one place.
I'm surprised you're here.
Why?
- I don't deserve to be Kangoh's owner?
- Kang Inha.
What if I was qualified
as much as you were?
Did you forget your waiver?
What's the big deal
about a piece of paper?
Hey!
Are you insane?
No.
I'm perfectly fine.
I'm confident I can fight you
and win right now.
Hello, I'm Han Taeoh.
The co-CEO of Gold H Investment.
- I heard you wanted to meet me.
- We're here to meet Michael Chang.
Let's not waste our time. Let's go.
Gold H Investment.
I'm in charge
of all its domestic business.
HAN TAEOH
Gold H Investment Co-CEO
What are you doing?
Why did you call us all here?
Either way, each side wants one thing.
I thought it'd be good
to get everyone together and talk.
We could save time and effort.
True, it's not like we're strangers here.
Do you have anything to say,
Mr. Kang Inha?
I don't know.
We know each other so well.
I'm not sure how much I should say.
That's what troubles me.
Is this the best you can do to stop me?
Are you ready?
Do you think I'll let you get
what you want?
Inha.
It's already going my way.
Things will be a mess.
Ever since I was young--
Come on, boss!
- You don't have that kind of aura!
- What?
You can see the dignity!
Boss! What was it, Michael?
The name doesn't suit you.
Hey!
That's how it was in school.
- Back in school...
- Cheers.
Have a drink!
Weren't we like that in school?
- Yes, that's right.
- You don't know me?
Yes, that's right.
That's what it was like!
Why won't you ask?
Ask what?
How it went with Inha.
I don't want to know.
It's between you two.
What?
Just...
It feels like
the Na Hyewon I knew is back.
The one you knew?
The one's who's so busy
that she doesn't care about other people.
JISEON
Yes, Jiseon?
Why did you call me?
What do you think
when you see this?
- What do you...
- Whether it's people or paintings,
it's hard to figure them out
just by looking at their exterior.
Things can be overlooked and discarded
at one time,
only to be rediscovered later.
In other words,
it's about looking into the future.
How much power...
do you think I have?
I'll gift this painting to you.
Oh, right.
The hidden meaning behind the painting
is "cooperation."
Bye.
MOTHER
Yes, Mother.
Come to tonight's dinner.
Why so suddenly...
I just want the family to sit down
for a meal. Don't feel pressured.
Okay.
I'll see you later.
Cooperation.
Hey.
Let's not waste time. The person in need
should extend their hand first.
Sit down.
I didn't know it before,
but I can see why the chairman trusted you
so much, Mr. Han.
Thank you.
Shall we toast?
Shall we?
Watch me.
Watch how I steal your dream.
Excuse me.
What's wrong?
Don't worry about him.
Your stepfather killed your mother.
Is it true?
No!
Honey!
Please! Not Taeoh! Please! Honey!
Move!
Honey, no!
You and I are the same.
Once we go out into the world,
let's achieve all of our plans
and get revenge on those who ignored
and tormented us.
What a simple dream.
It's not my final dream.
I guess you could call it a giveaway
within that dream.
Yes.
Let's do it.
It's me, Commissioner.
Inmate 301.
Inmate 301!
Congrats, your temporary release
was permitted.
Here are your papers.
Here's some cash.
The most important thing.
Remember that we can find you
whenever we want.
Yes, sir.
I know you're a model prisoner.
But those are the rules.
Yes, sir.
Visit your parents' grave.
Yes, thank you.
CORRECTION FOR A BETTER TOMORROW
DETENTION CENTER
ONE UNREAD MESSAGE
Jisuk.
Seongju.
It's time to show our hand.
Open a press conference tomorrow.
KANGOH GROUP'S EMERGENCY PRESS CONFERENCE
Jisuk.
Jisuk!
Don't come near me.
Jisuk...
you haven't changed one bit.
You're so smart too.
You tricked the entire world,
and you put your husband in jail.
If I could...
I'd tear you limb from limb.
So, come with me
while I'm still asking nicely. Okay?
No.
I told you.
If you come with me now, I'll forgive you.
Forgive me?
You'll forgive me?
You killed me!
Whenever you stomped on Taeoh and me...
- Damn it.
- ...you killed our souls!
You stomped on us.
And what?
Forgive?
You'll forgive me?
Then just die.
Unbelievable.
Mother.
Even if Father woke up, he'd want this.
Everything's ready.
Let's go, Mother.
What's the matter?
Are you Jang Geumseok?
You're under arrest
for disposal of a corpse,
offering bribes, and embezzlement.
You'll need to be investigated.
Come to the station.
What?
Are you Moon Jeonghu?
You're under arrest
for disposal of a corpse.
- Come with us.
- I'll come later voluntarily.
- I can't today.
- Just a moment.
Come on. Take her in.
- Why are you doing this?
- What are you saying?
Tell us the exact charges
before you take them!
Hey, take those cuffs off!
Anything you say can be used
against you in court.
You have the right to an attorney.
- Don't you know who I am?
- Move.
- Now, now.
- Mr. Moon!
- What's going on?
- Can cops do whatever they want?
Mother!
You have
the right to an attorney.
- Seongju!
- Can you do this?
- You have to go!
- Hey!
- I'll take care of this! Go!
- Move.
- Hurry up and go, Seongju!
- Hey! Mother!
Go!
Seriously?
Get in!
I'll arrest you
- for obstruction of justice!
- Mother!
KANGOH GROUP'S EMERGENCY PRESS CONFERENCE
What time is it right now?
What's going on?
- What?
- Who is it?
FUTURE STRATEGY OFFICE
DIVISION DIRECTOR KANG INHA
Kangoh Group family's staged hit-and-run,
and the foundation's slush fund.
Will this be okay?
Tip off the police. Right now.
Yes, sir.
People who trust
and worry about Kangoh Group,
the shareholders, and employees,
how are you?
Some of you may not have heard
the news yet,
but I'm sure the majority are aware
of Kangoh Group's current situation
from the earlier reports.
INTERROGATION ROOM
Chairman Kang Joongmo
is still unconscious.
He's receiving 24-hour care
by the best staff in Korea
at Kangoh Hospital.
However, with false news
surrounding Kangoh Group,
it's been causing anxiety and distress
among shareholders and employees.
It cannot be overlooked any longer.
As of today...
I declare a state of emergency
for Kangoh Group,
and I appoint myself as acting chairman
until normalization can be achieved.
I intend to overcome this crisis wisely
and move forward.
This little rat...
He's trying to crawl in?
Along with our 400,000 employees,
and a company
that can represent our nation,
please continue to trust and support us.
We will rise again
to repay our fellow citizens.
Thank you.
- I have a question!
- Over here!
There will be no Q&A.
What?
Director Jang Geumseok was arrested?
Mr. Han.
Will you leave Kang Inha like this?
Of course not.
After Jang Geumseok's arrest,
Kang Seongju lost a lot of supporters.
All of them switched over
to Kang Inha and Park Sajin's side.
It's only a matter of time
before Kang Inha becomes the chairman.
Mr. Han! Where are you going?
You know, don't you?
You know I didn't kill your mother.
She's alive and well.
Go and tell her.
Tell her not to let her guard down
because I'm here.
I'll see her soon.
Please...
What happened to Mom?
Tell me what you know.
- Huiju, calm down first...
- I can't calm down right now!
I can't reach Seongju.
What gives you the right to hold
a press conference in this situation?
Huiju.
We're family, and I think of you
as my little sister.
Mother's in danger right now.
Don't listen to anyone else.
Just listen to me.
Then you'll be safe.
- What?
- It's almost over.
Join me and support me...
Are you trying to get me
to take your side right now?
If you were really family,
shouldn't Mom be your priority?
It's too late.
Kang Inha...
you're not the Inha I know.
You're crazy.
- The number you dialed--
- Damn it.
Is Chae Donguk picking up?
CENTER DIRECTOR CHAE DONGUK
CONGRESSMAN JO SUNDONG
CEO KANG SEONGJU
MANAGER YANG JIHOON
I don't know who it is,
but they were waiting
for the perfect timing to attack.
He's not of this world anymore,
and even if the statute of limitations
has ended,
disguising the murder
that Kang Inju committed as a hit-and-run
is a ticking time bomb.
Not to mention...
KANGOH GROUP KANG SEONGJU
I've become a complete loser
after trusting Kang Seongju!
Congressman,
it'll be safer to step back on this.
In your opinion,
which way do you think
Kangoh's succession will lean toward?
Don't you think it's leaning towards
the acting chairman, Kang Inha?
Kang Inha?
I've never met him before.
Congressman.
How about I help you get a leg up
with Kang Inha?
Chae Donguk...
Jo Sundong.
Hello.
You may leave.
Was it you?
Did you do this?
I'm sure you were flustered
with that sudden press conference.
I heard Mother was taken to the station.
I thought sending all of those reporters
home in that situation
would really put Kangoh in a crisis.
I made the decision on my own.
I'm sorry.
Are you mocking me?
Do you really expect me to believe you?
Who are you to make that decision?
Seongju.
In times like these, support me.
I heard the reporters at the station.
It's over for Mother.
That dishonor...
there's no guarantee it won't reach you.
Just give it up now, okay?
You're a cockroach
that sneaks in at the slightest opening.
How dare you say that to me?
Hey, Inha.
I never want to hear my family's name
out of your filthy mouth.
If you say one more word,
I don't know what I'll do to you.
Got it?
Get out.
Mom...
I refuse.
Mr. Kang.
Thank you.
Now that I've gotten the chance
to meet you,
you're a very reasonable man.
You flatter me.
I'll do my best to normalize Kangoh Group
and be a reliable support
for your future endeavors.
Yes, so you shall.
Now that you've secured your spot,
the launch of PY Holdings
will gain momentum.
You can look forward to it.
As long as the board meeting goes well,
Kangoh's best item will go to you.
I can promise you that.
Tonight's for celebration.
What's with all the business talk?
Cheers to the founding warriors
of Kangoh Group,
and the collaboration of the Blue House.
Cheers!
Goodness.
Yes, go ahead.
I looked into it.
He got a leave for two nights
and three days from prison.
He returned after a day.
Something's off.
We both...
lost our mothers.
I think it was by the same person.
I think we have something to talk about.
Send off your mother well.
Take care of the funeral.
I'll see you then.
Finally, it's tomorrow.
Hello.
Good morning.
- Hello.
Hello.
EMERGENCY MANAGEMENT COMMITTEE
CHAIRMAN KANG INHA
2023 KANGOH CO., LTD.
SHAREHOLDERS' MEETING
ARREST WARRANT
Mr. Kang Inha.
You are under arrest for the murder
of Kang Inju and Mo Gijun.
What are you saying?
Arrest him.
Wait a second!
- Get out, you two.
- Let go of me!
- Do you know who I am?
- Sir.
Get this off of me!