A magician
How could he be killed by his own act?
There was nothing unusual during the show
Then his prop mechanism must have failed
I examined your props that day
They had been swapped
The fake blade was replaced with a real one
The rope was also tampered with
So this was no performance accident
It was murder
Enough
What did you find?
I examined the magician's props
For a normal Sawing Illusion act
The blades have special mechanisms
Mechanism on - real blade cuts watermelon
Off - fake blade "cuts" the assistant
But his blade was switched
Fake one replaced with a real blade
By the time he realized
It was too late
What?
The magician's props were already
collected as evidence
I'll verify your claims immediately
If you're lying
I'll treat you as an accomplice
But if I'm right
I want to examine
the body of Boss Hu
who died at the nightclub
Also
bring the guillotine rope too
Officer Gu
I'm thirsty
Stay put
Go back
You promised to save me
Why aren't you coming?
Would he really abandon me?
Boss Hu was a nightclub regular
A week ago
he was found hanged at the nightclub
on the second floor railing
People said
he'd been cheated by the Japanese
lost a fortune
and had been depressed for days
No signs of others at the scene
We suspected suicide
Here's what you wanted
The magician's prop rope
Notice the pattern - familiar?
The patterns match
How do you prove it's not coincidence?
Officer Gu
I know something about magic
Magicians usually use
the cheapest hemp ropes
But this one was specially treated
Smoother
and more flexible
The killer wanted to tell us something
Officer Gu
Am I right?
You already know the answer
You're correct
When collecting evidence earlier
I specifically compared
the magician's prop rope
with Boss Hu's hanging rope
They're identical
Officer Gu
Look
These are two sections of the same rope
Boss Hu was murdered
The killer left us clues
Here's an idea
Let's play along with their game
Send me back to investigate the nightclub
You're
becoming more interesting
Want to stay and assist me?
These past few days
it's the Japanese Commander's birthday
Most of our police force
is stationed at his residence
I haven't allocated many officers
to this case
Inspector Gu
If you trust me
why not release Miss Bai first
She's been with me these two days
and just arrived in Ha City today
She couldn't have committed the crime
With her help
I can definitely solve this case
Do you know who I am?
Hurry, let go!
Why did you take so long to come?
Find anything?
Isn't this the Bai family's young mistress?
Have the Bai family pull some strings
and you could get out
I'm not the murderer
Why should I use connections?
You're lucky to have Laifu as a friend
Out of respect for Laifu
But Laifu
I'll only give you three days to find the killer
Otherwise Miss Bai here
remains a suspect
You...
Actually
you don't need to care about her fate
You're very capable
You could stay and help me
I could hire you as special consultant
Better than following her around
as a mere sidekick
Inspector Gu has quite the methods
First the slap
then the sweet date
Just some small tricks
I have many ways to handle suspects
I'm warning you
He's mine
Don't get any ideas
That depends if you can keep him
My patience is limited
But this offer
remains open to you
Thank you for your kindness, Inspector
We have guests coming
Boss, we're closed
I know
We're here about something else
You two...
Yesterday you made
a mess of my place
What do you want today?
The Bai family investigates
Bai family handles ghosts and spirits
Never heard they handle human affairs
We're not here for nothing
Let's talk
Girls, back to work!
Who did Boss Hu meet before dying?
Me, me, me!
After leaving my room
he died immediately
I know nothing about it!
Was Boss Hu acting strange that day?
Strange?
He said his chest was burning
I massaged his chest
What about the wedding cup?
Come, come
Why's it so hot?
Let me blow and rub it
No!
Too stuffy
Get away!
So hot!
Boss Hu...
Ziyan!
Ziyan is already dead
The girls say Ziyan never left
She's still in the nightclub
When did Ziyan die?
How did she die?
Just last month
That young witch used her youth
to steal other women's men
She was a vixen
Darn it
Tell us more
What's there to say?
Women like us
either die of venereal disease
or by men's hands
Who knows what illness she had?
Couldn't take it and hanged herself
Just like Boss Hu's hanging
I wouldn't know
Ask them
You...
Don't be afraid, everyone.
Young Master Lin is taking me out to eat later.
I'm going to touch up my makeup first.
I'll go to the restroom first too.
You all chat slowly.
We need to go practice our dance.
Let's go, let's go.
Yes yes, we need to touch up our makeup.
Sit for a while first.
Now look what happened.
None of them are willing to cooperate.
We'll just have to wait and see.
It's all your fault.
I spent all that money.
And got no information at all.
Give me my money back.
No,
aren't we investigating this case together?
The person is already dead.
What's the point of asking now?
Ziyan,
every grievance has its source.
I've never wronged you.
Please don't come after me.
Ziyan?
Who's there?
Who's over there?
Probably just a rat.
I'll get a cat tomorrow.
See if you dare cause any more trouble.
Let's go check.
It's haunted.
It's haunted!
Be your bride.
Break a willow branch.
Stay by your side.
It's Ziyan.
Ziyan has come for me.
It's Ziyan's ghost.