The journey of the eight girls in the Love Moment house
is reaching a turning point.
This will be their final audition for the miniseries
before each of them decides
who they'll walk out of this house with
to continue their story outside.
Right now, many of you might be cheering for June,
because she hasn't gotten a role yet.
Let's see if she can win it this time.
Hello, everyone.
-Hello.
It's our last week of workshops.
Everyone's improved, right?
Maybe not yet.
No, you've come a long way. Trust me, you have.
Since it's the final week, I want to confirm
what's at the heart of being an actor.
So today's workshop challenge is comedy.
It's hard.
Comedy is hard.
I'll go through the
theory really quickly.
People usually think comedy means overacting,
but that's not true.
Comedy depends on beats.
You need contrasting beats to create comedy.
That's all you need because you're already good.
Now I'm stressed.
Pair up and tell a story that has never existed in this world.
And in your storytelling, you must use a variety of beats.
You can improvise as much as you want
since your story has never existed before.
Use your imagination freely. Okay? Pair up first.
Who will help your comedy survive? Pair up.
Can we do ones-and-twos?
So that the groups are more spread out.
Ones-and-twos.
Oh, today's workshop is comedy?
Actually, making people laugh
can be even harder than doing drama.
Ones-and-twos.
-You're together.
-What's this?
You're with Hling.
Ones-and-twos.
Who's with Pai?
Pailiu.
June. Okay.
-June.
-Come, Dear.
Comedy's my specialty.
One pair at a time.
Okay?
I'll start each pair with an opening line,
like, "Once upon a time, there was a girl,"
and you'll continue right away.
Your smile is suspicious.
While you're performing, I'll clap,
and throw you a word to use.
Oh, my God.
Include that word...
-Sounds fun.
-Yeah.
naturally as if you planned it.
No shocked faces.
Who wants to go first?
Point them out.
-No.
-Point.
Them.
It's unanimous then.
Here's the prompt.
Oh, there's a prompt.
Once upon a time, there was a rabbit and a frog.
Oh, actually the frog's name was Lita.
The frog's name was Lita, and the rabbit's name was...
Wafer.
Oh, the rabbit's name was Wafer.
One day, the rabbit was walking to a house.
If I remember right, she walked into a house
and found five more frogs.
And they were all Lita's siblings.
How was that even possible?
Don't stop.
That's promising. Now, was their tone of voice high or low?
High all the time, right?
Is there contrast yet?
Not yet.
Gotta be brave to pull it out. Lita, think less.
Start talking rambling Wafer.
Hold on.
Reset first.
Ready?
Go on, continue.
You know what she found in the pot?
What?
All the frogs were boiled.
All the frogs got boiled inside.
So in this story, the frogs became stew.
The end.
What happens next?
It's over.
No, it's not.
You can't end it there.
No, because there's a twist.
Tell me.
After that she found frog stew.
It's fine, but she already ate it.
No, it's...
Wrap it up already.
Oh, yeah?
We were about to.
But Lita refused to end it.
Just keep rambling.
So I was being myself.
It was fun.
You have to help your two friends save face.
Got it.
Once upon a time, there was a girl in a cap.
That girl had bought her cap from Gap,
but just realized it was fake.
Really?
Yeah, she bought it from Nakhon Ratchasima,
but she ordered it from Lopburi.
How did she know it was fake?
Because after checking the item, she realized...
it wasn't authentic.
How did she check?
How?
Because they didn't truly love each other.
They were never real friends.
The caps?
-The caps and...
-Not being...
Who are not friends?
They used to be secret lovers.
The caps were lovers?
Girls, this is not a conversation.
I'm so confused how the caps became lovers.
You're telling a story. You have to understand it?
Make us understand it.
But right now, Dear's like...
"I don't understand."
I see.
I'm someone who rambles on.
So it came out kinda confusing
because I didn't understand it myself.
Hling and Neuanaow, come on.
I'm disappointed.
Once upon a time, there were thirty pigs.
That day I was walking, right?
Then a pig came and crawled right under my legs like this.
And you know what happened? I fell!
But I passed out.
Then I saw you...
Hling, open your body.
in my dream.
Huh? In your dream?
Yeah, you were riding a pig.
For real?
-You were.
-Really?
-And it pooped.
-Like this?
Oh, no?
No.
You were like this.
You know what's crazy, Neuanaow?
I also dreamed I was riding a pig,
but I was doing this.
-Really?
-Yeah, why did you see this?
No, it's...
-Finish the story.
-Actually my dream...
Let's go back to sleep. We might dream again.
Or we might be dreaming right now.
Wake up.
-Should we slap each other?
-Now?
So we'll wake up.
Girls.
You're ending with "Should we slap each other?"
No, just to wake each other up.
I see.
Oh, to wake each other up. Okay.
I just rambled.
Did this and that, moved around like...
I wasn't worried about the character because I was being me.
Alright, watch how the master does it.
Go. Here comes the Mother.
Once upon a time, there was a young duck herder.
Once upon a time, there was a young...
Duck herder.
Duck.
Okay, correct.
How did that duck walk?
Quack, quack, right?
No, it walked like this.
Was it that badly hurt?
It needs physical therapy.
No, then what happened to the duck? Explain.
My duck walked like this. How did your duck walk?
-My duck.
-Walked like this?
Guess what? When the duck walked like that...
What?
Its legs were broken.
-Huh?
-Its legs were broken.
How many legs were broken?
Two.
So how did it walk?
It used its wings.
Show me.
Like this.
-What if its wings were broken?
-Don't pull jokes on each other.
We shouldn't?
We love our school.
I wear a sarong, right?
So I go to school. We do a hand salute there.
You know what we say?
What?
"We won't love our school."
At all?
Yeah, "We won't love our school." So that means...
It means we're ungrateful.
Ungrateful. We love our school. In our school
we must love each other, so wanna love each other?
-Is that a good idea?
-Wanna love each other?
End the story.
-You wanna?
-Of course.
Let's go.
Hey!
Awesome.
They managed to wrap it up perfectly somehow.
I'm not good at comedy
where you just ramble like that.
I'm not that good at. Yeah.
Since this is...
the last lesson, I wish you...
I'm not saying this just for this audition.
I wish you success in the future, whatever you do.
May you be loved by everyone and the power that be.
Okay?
She's gonna cry.
No, I won't because my mascara will smudge.
I hope you get to do what you love for a living,
and once you...
have fans, one thing to never forget is
to keep developing your abilities
so you'll deserve the love people give you. Okay? Got it?
-Okay.
-Thank you.
I'm not gonna cry.
I will miss you.
The workshops are over. Now the girls must be wondering
how they will be paired up today.
Hello.
This is the final audition.
I dreaded hearing that.
-I don't wanna leave.
-So fast.
Right?
Do you still remember the first day we met?
I can picture it.
Yeah, I remember.
It's like a déjàvu.
We were all sitting here,
but I was the one who saw the big picture.
On the first day, you were still nervous.
No relationships had been formed.
No one knew each other. Everyone was shy.
That day we asked you to write
a love letter and express your feelings.
-Right.
-You remember, right?
That time has come again.
This is the final pairing for the audition.
The word "final"...
-I hate it.
-Yeah.
-Right? It sounds sad.
-It breaks my heart.
Are you crying?
Not yet or my lashes will fall off.
Calm down. I get it though because seven weeks have flied by.
It's quite a long time to live together in this house.
Many of you have shared good memories and great moments.
So this time, I'll let you guys pair up based on...
mutual agreement.
Today's rule is the girls have to decide for themselves.
It sounds easy, but it's actually quite a tough decision.
This time will this partner help me
win the role in the final audition?
Or am I choosing her because...
I feel comfortable with her,
I've already given her my heart,
and no matter what happens, I'll still choose her.
It's up to us who we want to pair with.
I still want to pair with Neua because right now I feel...
she's the only one I want to pair with
Alright, is anyone...
ready to go first?
-They're obvious.
-They're clear about each other.
This pair is quite obvious. Some pairs are already clear,
but maybe someone might change their mind.
Neuanaow and Lita.
Yes.
Are you sure? Anyone wants to break them up?
The question is "Can we?"
Yeah, can we?
They've been obvious since EP 1.
Judging from our hands, I think...
Okay, okay.
Leave them be.
Next.
Anyone wants to go next?
-We need to talk first.
-Can we talk first?
Yeah, talk first.
Let us process this first.
Right.
Nice, who do you have in mind?
Honestly...
I'd be happy to act with everyone.
Whether it's June,
Hling, or Pailiu. Any of them would make me very happy.
I'm okay acting with any of them.
So you want one of them.
I wanna talk first.
What about Wafer?
I actually want to pick...
these two.
Hling and Pailiu.
Maybe she means the one behind us.
No, she's joking.
I've talked to everyone quite a lot,
but sometimes when the conversations...
got deep, I could talk to them.
What about you, Dear? Who do you really want?
She's direct.
I've always been clear about this.
Yeah, she's always been clear.
Everyone knows. Even my fans know.
So who do you want to pair with?
-Point.
-Will it make her uncomfortable?
Say it.
I'm like, "Just say it."
-If you don't fight...
-Say it.
I'll spank you.
Pailiu.
I mean, I'm used to it, but not numb yet.
I'll keep fighting. I'm not giving up for sure.
She didn't pick you last time, yet you still...
I was heartbroken, but I'll keep fighting.
Attagirl.
She's got her heart.
Jeab, I have to be honest with my feelings.
Yes.
Okay, what about you, Hling?
I'm feeling a bit conflicted.
Why?
At first I had one person
in mind, but after some reflection,
I started asking myself what I really want.
Wait, who's that one person?
At first, it was June.
Then why aren't you sitting together?
-It's not serious.
-Is it me?
Is it my fault?
We were paired last week, right?
Yeah, we've been paired all along, but now...
I've started to hesitate
because I've been thinking more about the future.
I don't think about what happens here as much anymore.
I've been thinking what it'll be like once we leave.
And I've been overlooking
someone who's always been around me
but I've never noticed her.
When I was down, she's there.
Or when I didn't feel like doing anything.
When I talked to her,
she always seemed ready to, like, "It's up to you."
I never felt she demanded anything.
And I started to wonder, "Could this person be my safe zone?"
And who is that?
Not only is everyone in the house surprised, we are too.
But honestly, we have witnessed
some moments between these two.
Wafer, did you have an inkling?
No, but I...
I'm close with everyone, so I'm always
wandering around chatting with everyone.
That day I was mentally tired, kinda drained,
and I didn't feel like going on a date...
with anyone.
So I told her, "If you're paired with me,
is it okay if we don't go on a date?"
And she said yes. So it confused me,
like why was she agreed to pair with me
even when I didn't want to do anything?
And I genuinely wanted to help her.
So Hling must've processed that and thought, like,
"Why am I overlooking her?" I'm not sure.
And I thought, "Who else would even think like that?"
Because if it were me, I wouldn't either.
I was just ready to support her. I mean...
It was okay if we didn't go.
I just felt if she wasn't up for it,
I'd still be there to support her no matter what.
As long as she felt comfortable.
There was no pressure that she has to take me somewhere.
It was fine with me. I just wanted to support her.
That's all.
Aww, come here.
I'll give you the hug of the season.
Jeab, do it.
There, there.
Come here, come here.
Get up, get up.
Please sit.
Even I thought you two were an obvious pair,
like Neuanaow and Lita.
But this week I'm surprised that suddenly you're hesitant
and want to pick someone else.
June, how do you feel about that?
When I was listening to Hling,
at first I was like, "It's fine,"
because I've been feeling that
I was pulling her down basically.
-All the time.
-But I never thought that.
No, I really felt that way, so I thought, okay,
if she wants to go, then go. Like, it's fine, really.
Yes.
But I'm not hurt or anything. I even understand.
But her answer kind of hurts me.
You might not feel hurt or you just say
you're not hurt about cutting me loose.
So I'm a little hurt when June said that
she was ready to cut me loose and pick someone else.
I felt like she didn't realize how much I tried
when I taught her or gave it my all.
I really gave it my all, but I'm hurt that...
she said she was okay, but when problems came up,
she wasn't actually okay like she'd said.
So I feel hurt.
Okay, okay, I think I understand what's going on now.
So, June, who will you choose?
My other choice is Pailiu because we acted together in EP 1.
And I want to perform better than the first time.
You two were paired in EP 1, right?
-Yes.
-And have you been paired again since?
Never.
Oh, so you were paired just in EP 1 and...
So you want to try one last time
to see if you'll get to pair with her again?
Yes.
I understand everything now.
And I see the big picture of what's happening right now.
So take some time to talk to each other.
I'll come back when you're done, okay?
-Yes.
-Okay.
At first I talked to Hling about picking you,
but it seemed you didn't really want to pick me,
so I was like, okay, I won't pick you
because you don't want me anyway.
If I pick you, it might not work.
You didn't seem to want to pair with me.
But didn't you want to pair with Hling or Pailiu anyway?
No.
-I never...
-She never...
I never told anyone who I wanted to pair with.
She's crying again.
Sorry. Once she starts, she can't stop.
Tissue, tissue, tissue.
Sis.
Guys.
I have to tell you something. Do you know why?
Because I feel comfortable talking to you.
Let me be the middleman.
For me, right now my heart is empty.
Right now it's up to you, Pailiu, who you want to choose.
Because I don't feel like choosing anyone.
Like, my heart's not ready. I don't want to choose anyone.
I understand.
This EP is heavy.
Tears galore in EP 7.
This is just picking audition partners.
No, I think everyone's already thinking about that.
I get it. This is the last one.
But now that June's clear, I'm okay with her choosing Wafer.
Yes.
Good. I'm happy for you.
I'm not blaming you, but those words
-really hurt.
-You two are hurt
-You both are hurt.
-So...
when I sat next to you and you said that, I just...
I realized I have to make a tough decision.
Eh? Pailiu, why did you suddenly walk away
without saying a word?
I felt so uncomfortable. Like that situation was
so uncomfortable.
My chest was about to explode. My heart was
pounding so hard I couldn't stay there anymore,
so I ran off to the kitchen.
Dear's already made it clear.
What if you don't get paired today?
-It's fine.
No, I just...
I just wanted to show how I feel about her.
Yeah, you did great today.
If you didn't say it earlier,
I'd be like, "Say it. Say it."
Everyone kept nudging you.
Nice got up and followed her.
You can totally understand how pressured Pailiu must feel.
Not only because this week is the first time
many people want to pair with her,
but also because it's the final audition,
which makes it even more stressful.
I just wanted to say don't stress yourself out.
Just let it go, and...
Want some water?
No, I'm fine.
So I thought...
I'm here too.
Yeah, do this together.
It's just that I felt like...
I already thought that...
Wanna sit?
In the end, when...
-Let's sit.
I can stand.
No, no, come sit together.
Dear, you sit too.
Wanna use this for the vibe?
Kinda weird. You're too direct with that.
It's stressful when you have to choose
between three people, especially at the end like this.
I imagined that if I could keep going in this house,
I'd want to leave with you because...
I really imagined that because,
like I told you, if we got paired,
I'd want to go to Ocean World.
So I thought, when that happens...
Aww.
I'd want it to be you. Do you get it? Because...
I just feel I want it to be you.
But it's the feeling that...
But you can choose whoever, it's okay.
Yeah, I understand.
Are people actually rooting for you two?
-No.
-I don't know if...
No, no, no. Maybe it's because I'm someone who's...
Everyone has known this for a while,
but I'm not brave. I'm...
How do you say it? Too scared to show how I feel.
And too considerate. Like, I don't know
if showing it would make you uncomfortable.
-I'm sorry if I did that.
-No, don't apologize.
Yeah, but everyone kept telling me...
to be braver since we were in the last stretch.
So you don't need to stress yourself out because I just...
wanted to show you that I...
choose you, that's all.
-Yeah.
-I get it.
Maybe you want to be alone.
We're gonna step out.
Yeah, sure.
Now that June, Dear, me, all three of us choose Pailiu,
I figure she's got plenty of choices
and doesn't need to pick me.
Ooh, why are you all alone?
-Did you flee?
-It was uncomfortable.
So I fled.
Let's drink some water. Have you had some?
-There's some here.
-I see.
There's a glass here.
Water might help.
I'm so stressed.
Here.
Oh, thank you.
What should we do?
But I'm not here to force or pressure you.
I just feel that...
you've always been my choice.
Really?
I mean it. But back then Hling and I
agreed to pair up since it was almost over.
But now everything's changed, and when I saw the teaser...
I was like, why did I go in and hug you like that? Did you see it?
-I don't know if you saw it.
-I did.
So I felt that...
maybe we should give it another try, you know?
But that's what I thought to myself,
that maybe we should try again.
But it's up to you.
No pressure.
I get it.
-It's up to you. No pressure.
-I know.
I understand.
No.
I'm just worried that...
I don't want to hurt anyone.
I don't want anyone to feel bad.
But I believe that...
all of us are...
bracing ourselves.
Right?
Honestly, I'm taking a big risk, you know?
But...
Let's just do what we planned for, what we started.
Let's finish what we started properly.
At first I thought maybe I should leave the house alone.
I really did.
Don't think like that.
Hm?
You do it too.
No.
I thought about leaving alone because...
no one picked me. You get it?
That's a lie. A lot of people picked you.
But you kept picking different people the way you wanted.
No.
-Jeez.
-That's not true.
You were the one who hesitated. You were never clear.
At first you picked Nice. I was like, "Okay, Nice."
Then you picked Hling. Who would dare pick you?
Who would dare pick you?
No, I was...
I was gonna pick her but she suddenly changed her mind.
Serves you right.
See? It's karma. I'm so confused.
But now no one's picking me.
Now that no one's picking me, then what?
I walk back into the house alone, even though I came with you.
You dropped other people first.
Because in the second round,
when they asked those picking me to step forward,
you didn't, so I thought, "Okay, she's dropped me."
I did.
-You took one step.
-But many did.
Yeah. See?
Did I mess up?
Whoa, June is finally opening up
to Pailiu how she really feels.
It seems Hling choosing Wafer today
brought back all of June's memories,
possibly making her feelings clearer.
Got your heart broken by Hling, huh?
No, no. I don't want you to fix my broken heart.
I just... Please don't think that way.
That's funny.
But it's understandable.
I really am fine with everyone.
Right?
Totally fine.
Then we can do ones-and-twos.
I just feel it'd be nice if I get to pair with you.
I see, okay.
I'm okay even if I don't get to go.
Are you really okay?
Yes.
Are you sure?
I just don't get a date.
You want a date, right?
I wanna fall in love.
See?
See? You dropped other people first.
No, honestly, I've had you in mind.
Yeah? And then?
I've had you in mind.
All along.
And then what?
But you kept going to other people, never to me.
Oh!
Whenever I asked you who you'd pick,
you'd be like, "I don't know. I'm so torn.
I have so many people in mind."
-No.
-You were never clear about it.
But at first, I really didn't have anyone. I meant that.
Then Nice and I started drawing together and got close.
I saw that.
Yeah, I thought she was cute, but then I realized...
I mean we could be siblings for real, you know?
After that, I didn't know who to pair with.
As for Hling...
She said she wanted to teach me, so we paired up.
Then she changed her mind.
You get that?
-I do.
-And I was like, who do I really want to pair with?
Then when I saw myself...
what it looked like when I was with
someone I truly saw, it was... yeah.
I kinda wanted to try again.
It's understandable.
Shall we?
I don't know how to say it,
but I don't want to see anyone get hurt.
So I became a coward who's too scared
to show that I choose this person.
Now it's up to Pailiu to decide
who she'll pick as her partner.
Yeah, in that EP someone have to make a decision.
You won't get to act again.
So don't act.
-I mean...
-Do it together.
That's it.
Because we already did it.
We did.
Everyone did it.
Right.
Now we can act with anyone, but when the time comes,
use your real feelings.
Hello.
Did you figure it out?
Yes.
Have you guys decided?
There are four left.
Four left. I mean four people...
The last... The final four.
-Who still undecided?
-Yes.
-Wait, still?
-But I...
We're gonna do ones-and-twos.
Yes.
-Ones-and-twos?
-Yeah.
But I forbid it.
Why?
Harsh.
There are four left, so Naow and Lita are all set.
And...
Me and Wafer.
Hling and Wafer.
So now Pailiu has to choose between Nice, June, or Dear.
Yes.
And all three of you pick Pailiu.
So Pailiu, pick who you want.
Don't stress, bro. Chill.
Let's try pairing with June first.
-So you chose June.
-Yes.
At the time, I really sympathized with Pailiu.
I know she thought really hard.
Whoever she chose, I'd be happy.
Why June?
Because in the first round
when we acted together, we were too new.
So I want to try again now that we both
have more experience, to see how it goes.
With Dear, I already know
we'd work well together.
Nice too. She's talented.
I acted with her and she was a great acting partner.
And with June, from the first time, I feel like I want to...
improve on that.
Make it better.
Yes.
I feel like maybe she's had
feelings for me from the beginning.
It gave me hope right away.
It's like...
exciting and it made me think,
why didn't I choose her sooner? What was I even doing?
Even though Pailiu said she chose June this time
to improve her own acting,
I wonder if there are feelings involved.
Why does the atmosphere feel so tense?
Do you know the script we'll audition
with today is a romantic comedy?
You guy were just crying and stressed out.
The person you're paired with today
might not be the one leave the house with.
Or maybe you won't leave holding anyone's hand at all.
Let's focus on the present.
Alright, come get your script with your partner.
Lita and Neuanaow are still
together with no one trying to cut in.
And Hling and Wafer chose each other,
which surprised everyone.
Pailiu decided to pick June again today,
leaving Dear and Nice as the remaining two who had to pair up.
They've shed liters of tears,
but the girls have to switch modes quickly
to rehearse a romantic comedy.
And today's challenge is that it's not an ordinary rom-com.
It's a period fantasy.
Aside from acting skills,
the language in this script is definitely
a big challenge for everyone.
I'm still thinking... like, how goofy should I be?
Just act confused like you were just now.
Pailiu.
Let's read through the script,
then we'll get into this part.
-But this part's hard.
-Which part?
Do I have to act it out?
And you push me, right?
And then…
Ms. Yoong.
Farewell.
Ms. Yoong?
Ms. Yoong!
Yeah, that was great. Perfect.
Do it like that.
The end. Perfect.
Hey, you got better at acting.
Jeez.
You'll win this time.
I wanna act with you.
-Please.
-You'll win.
Let me have one.
Sure.
Let's go. Which part?
Hello, my name is Tia.
I'm 22 years old and a senior undergrad.
I was on a field trip with my friends.
Let me change something. Make it chattier at the start.
-Chattier?
-Try saying, "Hi, I'm Tia."
Hello, my name is Tia.
I'm 22 years old and a senior undergrad.
The light.
Is that the light that brought you here?
When you say, "That light," keep your eyes fixed on it.
Hold your gaze, June. Try it.
-That light.
-Hope.
Is that hope in your eyes?
The light.
Is that the light that brought you here?
Yes.
Then you must hurry back.
I won't, Miss.
Run.
If you're not safe, I'm not leaving.
That was good. Make it firmer. "I won't, Miss."
Try using a firm voice.
I won't, Miss. If you're not safe, I'm not leaving.
These aren't words we use in daily life,
so it was really hard for me.
But once I tried it, it was fun.
And the biggest surprise was June.
Ms. Yoong.
-Like this?
-Yeah.
You're pushed, right? So it's like...
"Ms. Yoong!"
"No!"
"No!" And...
Then...
I see.
"Ms. Yoong?" Something like that.
Yeah, like you don't wanna leave.
"I'm not going!"
I don't know.
Got it, got it.
Great job.
Great.
My lips are so dry.
I'm starting to have it memorized,
but the words still don't flow in my mouth.
Want some water?
Thank you.
"You may leave."
"From now..."
"Secure the area."
"So I can't let it go."
Ask ChatGPT for me.
For synonyms of "lifestyle"?
The word "lifestyle."
Ask for old-fashioned words similar to "lifestyle."
"Lifestyle."
You seem a bit crazy.
That was good. Your reactions were on point.
Don't change your voice. Use your real voice.
I think you're kind of crazy.
It's not surprising.
No. I don't think I'm surprised anymore.
You're definitely not a prisoner
sent by the Hanthawaddy kingdom.
Are you trying to say "kalamang" or "kramang"?
I'm trying to say "kramang."
-Yeah, correct.
-I thought of "kalamang."
Yes, correct.
When she says "kramang," you misunderstand.
I don't understand.
-"What kalamang?"
-So you're like, "What kalamang?"
There's no kalamang here. Something like that.
Not too strong, right?
Yes, keep it light, like a
bonus. It should be subtle.
Then you feel resigned. You can sigh quietly.
Yeah, like you're talking to an idiot. Yeah.
Dear, your acting flows better.
You just need to work on your reactions.
Like, "What does that mean?"
Then go to the next part.
The next part was good.
Try scene seven. The one in the forest. "Run!"
Nice, you stay here. Alright, one...
It's confusing now.
One, two, three.
You must leave this place.
No, I'll stay with...
-I'll stay...
-You can't. You must leave this place right now.
They're coming.
No, I'll stay until you're safe.
You can't.
Hurry back home.
This place is no longer safe for you.
I reacted too strongly.
I reacted like slapstick comedy.
At first I was like, "Hey! Hey!"
But Teacher said not to go that hard.
Just make it cute and a bit goofy.
Yes.
When I'm home, I don't really do anything.
I shoot videos and post it online sometimes.
I don't do chores. Our housekeeper does everything.
You see? When the lines are long,
if you deliver them all in the same way,
it ends flat. You just delivered them,
like, "I'm like this, like that."
Try...
-switching up more.
-Really?
When the dialogue is hard, you get stuck. Listen.
The harder the dialogue,
the stronger your emotion needs to be.
-Got it?
-But today we're tired.
Yeah, I know you're all worn out.
-I can't.
-You're done.
Push through it.
Go.
Come on, you can do it.
Sometimes I post dance videos online.
As for our chores, our housekeeper does them all.
As for my hobbies, I cook sometimes and I love snacks.
And I...
What are you rambling about?
You don't make any sense.
I definitely struggle with the language.
So I find it challenging and quite hard
given the short time we have.
I'll make you look pretty.
Do it.
Let's read through it.
It's Tia. Say the line.
Ms. Yoong.
No!
Ms. Yoong!
-Farewell.
-We're so serious.
Ms. Yoong!
Let's do it like this.
Since it's a rom-com.
You play the character who rambles.
Sure.
You can be yourself.
She really rambles.
Suddenly she talks about home. I'm confused.
This is really you.
"Oh, and usually, I just stay home,
watch movies and listen to music." You know what I mean?
Oh, got it. Just be me.
Chatty vibes.
When I rehearsed with Lita, I was super chill
because my lines were everyday speech. And...
she's like me, just rambling on and on.
My lines weren't hard, but Lita got really stressed.
I'm here.
-Teacher.
-Mama.
It's hard because it's..
But you usually enunciate.
If you enunciate, you'll be fine.
-I played a slave in a period drama once.
-Yeah.
I feel you must've had done that.
But it took me a whole week
to memories lines from a period drama.
Just memorize the keywords. Improvise the rest.
You can't memorize it 100% anyway.
Yeah, don't focus on... Perform for me.
Get up, girls. Can you get up?
It's not surprising if
you don't understand,
-because I'm from...
-Oh, she hits the stool too, right?
-You know "hit the stool"?
-Like...
Hit.
While sitting.
Yes, exactly.
As for my hobbies, I love cooking
and I love snacks. I love...
What are you rambling about? You don't make any sense.
We did quite well. Her delivery was good.
It was cute too when we rehearsed together.
I can't just leave you...
I can't just leave you like this.
Run and find your way back home.
Understand the script and don't focus on what to say...
-Yes.
-exactly, but...
Try to connect.
Try to keep the ancient tone.
-Keep the character.
-Yes.
In comedy, you act within your character,
what she's capable of.
Today's script is really hard.
But everyone's determined to do their best.
Because today is also the final audition.
Especially for June, the only one who's never been
chosen for the miniseries or gone on a date.
Macarons from...
I'm under so much pressure.
I'm probably the most stressed in the house
because it's ending soon.
And everyone else has improved. But what about me?
I want to go too. I want to go on a date.
I want to get out of the house and have fun. I wanna go...
somewhere with her, you know?
And the script for week seven's audition,
which is the final audition of the season,
is called "Because Love Calls."
It tells a story of Tia, an undergrad who accidentally
travels back in time to the Ayutthaya era
and falls in love with a noblewoman called Ms. Yoong.
The mood and tone of this story must be romantic comedy.
So not only do the girls have to memorize
long dialogues with an unfamiliar linguistic style,
they also have to make the judges smile,
which is no easy task.
This is the final audition.
And today, besides me and Teacher Prang,
we also have a very special guest judge.
You guys probably know him very well.
Please give a round of applause to Poramet Sukontakajorn.
Hello.
Hello, hello, hello.
You guys know him well.
He's the producer of this show and the director
of the miniseries on "Love Moment."
Today, he'll be joining as a judge and directing this story.
-Choose.
-Right away?
Which pair you'd like to see first.
Today is the final audition.
Do your best.
Unclutter your mind for now.
Just focus on this performance.
Okay then.
I want to see Dear and Nice first.
Who exactly are you?
My name is Tia.
I'm 22. I'm a senior undergrad.
I came to Ayutthaya on a field trip with my friends,
but I got separated from them.
Then there was a flash of light.
I walked into it and fainted. When I woke up, I saw all of you.
Are you tired from talking so much?
I didn't understand a single word you said.
Oh, it's not surprising that you don't understand
because I'm from the future, hundreds of years from now.
My lifestyle there... No, my way of life
was totally different from people in this era.
After listening to you,
if I think you are a prisoner of war,
I would be wrong.
The general of Hanthawaddy must be a fool if he sent you here.
Are you calling me stupid?
Yes.
No.
I mean...
Never mind.
Anyway,
stay here for now.
If you don't stay in the kitchen,
I'll capture you as a prisoner.
That's fine. I'll stay in the kitchen.
But how long do I have to stay here?
You told me
that light had brought you here.
If you encounter that light again,
it might be your way home.
What kalamang?
What did I say?
You said "kalamang."
I said "kramang."
Whatever a kalamang is, I don't want to know.
You mean a laundry basin?
You're going to do laundry?
No, Miss.
Then go take care of your chores. Come see me later.
Go back.
No, Ms. Yoong.
No, I'm staying with you.
You can't. You have to go back. You have to go back.
Ms. Yoong...
It's already too late.
-No, Ms. Yoong.
-It's where you belong.
You'll be safe there.
-No, I'm gonna stay with you.
-Go back.
Go back! Go back!
No, Ms. Yoong!
Cut.
How was that?
What I really liked was that...
Dear, your improvisation is spot on.
When you improvise, you know exactly
what to say and it's spot on.
Your body flows, so everything feels smooth and natural.
Meanwhile, Nice, in the second scene,
you're starting to get the hang of it.
I think you're better in dramatic or emotional scenes.
Great job.
Thank you.
Honestly, I think I gave it my all.
I'm happy and had fun with Dear.
Like in the past episodes, every time
I acted with her, we always had fun together.
Which pair should go next?
Lady Her and Wafer, please.
-"Lady Her and Wafer"
-Awesome.
Where did you come from?
Um, hello. My name is Tia. I'm 22. I'm an undergrad.
I went on a field trip to Ayutthaya
and couldn't catch up with my friends.
Then suddenly there was this bright light,
and when I woke up, I was here.
I saw you here. I don't even know how I got here.
What are you rambling about?
You don't make any sense.
Actually...
I...
I mean, I...
I came from a hundred years in the future.
My lifestyle just...
It just doesn't go well in this era.
So you probably don't understand me much.
That light!
That light...
is your way home, is it not?
Hurry and go back.
No! I'll stay here with you.
-I'll stay until you're safe.
-You fool.
If there's a way home, you must hurry.
No! I'm staying with you.
You're not safe yet. I'm staying here.
Why don't you go home?
Thank you very much.
But this time I can't be selfish.
I'm worried about you as much.
If it's truly fate,
we shall certainly meet again.
No, Ms. Yoong.
Run.
Run!
No.
Go now.
Farewell.
Ms. Yoong!
Cut.
You almost made me laugh, Wafer.
I don't know if it's because I looked at your face.
The timing between you two.
But something's missing.
It still felt too big for me. It could be smoother.
Great job.
The mood and tone of this episode are comedy, right?
But there has been some drama.
Wafer and I were crying so hard earlier,
so it's kind of hard to switch to comedy.
Like our minds still have
unfinished business with some people.
Which pair is next, Met?
Let's go with...
June and Pailiu.
June and Pailiu, please.
Hello, my name is Tia. I'm 22 years old.
I'm a senior undergrad.
I came on a field trip to Ayutthaya,
and I couldn't catch up with my friends.
Suddenly, there was a flash of light.
Then I woke up and found myself here.
And I met everyone here.
Hmm, but I don't really know how to do anything.
I eat, watch movies, listen to music,
and post some dance videos.
Wanna see them?
Dance videos.
Like dancing.
Dancing.
Lisa's dance.
Lisa.
And…
Oh, hobbies.
Mine are…
cooking,
eating snacks… burgers…
macarons, cheese macarons.
Hey, what on earth are you babbling about?
You don't make any sense.
I'm sorry.
It's not surprising that you don't understand.
Because I'm from the future hundreds of years ago.
No, hundreds of years from now.
And my lifestyle...
My way of life there is completely different from here.
From now on, you'll have to live here.
Here?
And what will I do?
I'd rather go home.
Didn't you say you can cook?
Then...
you will work in the kitchen.
But I don't want to.
Run.
No, if you're not safe, I'm not going anywhere.
Run. You have to find your way home.
I won't.
Go now.
That light…
The light.
Is that the light that brought you here?
Yes.
Then hurry back.
No.
Go back.
I'm not going if you're still in danger.
You fool.
You have a chance to go home. Why are you not hurrying back?
No.
Thank you very much.
But I can no longer be selfish.
If fate truly binds us, we shall certainly meet again.
No! Ms. Yoong!
Farewell.
No!
Cut.
June, I feel like you unlocked something
in yourself today with comedy.
Which I find more charming.
You're so much better than before.
As for Pai, I love the tone of voice you chose.
You made me want to keep watching to see what you'd do next.
Great job, both of you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
I think we've got a real shot,
because June was really amazing.
I... I was honestly surprised by her.
I think her audition was even better than the rehearsal.
You're the last pair.
Lita and Pailiu.
No, Lita and Neuanaow, the last pair.
Or...
Allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Tia.
I'm 22 years old.
Right now, I'm a sophomore.
Well…
I'll tell you what happened today.
I was on a field trip to Ayutthaya with my friends.
But I've got short legs. After a while, I fell behind.
I mean I couldn't catch up with them.
Sorry, I'm not used to meeting new people.
I'm talking too much.
I fell behind. And...
suddenly there was this flash of light.
Like a UFO.
And then…
when I woke up,
I'm here.
But…
What are you rambling about?
You don't make any sense.
No wonder you don't understand.
Because I'm from hundreds of years in the future.
Ms. Yoong.
Run away.
No!
I said run away.
If you're not safe,
I'm not leaving.
Find your way back.
Run.
That light is your way home, is it not?
Go now.
No!
I'm not going back if you're not safe. I won't.
Thank you for your kindness.
But I can't think only of myself.
If it's truly fate,
we shall certainly meet again.
Farewell!
Cut.
It got away, like...
I was about to get emotional.
It became...
It went the wrong way. The mood of the story is wrong.
But overall, I think your chemistry
keeps getting better and better.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
I was so nervous.
I kept thinking, "What if I forget my lines?"
I was scared I'd say the wrong words
since it's a period piece.
But when we started, I let all of that go and did my best.
We can really see everyone's progress this time around,
but in the end, only one pair will get the roles.
Let us three discuss it first.
We'll call you in for the results.
That was the final round of auditions.
How were they, Teacher Prang, Met?
The first pair, I feel like…
they tried too hard to be funny
to the point I didn't know what they were doing.
Like, what's the story about? I was totally lost.
They can be funny within their characters.
Wafer and Hling.
What do you think?
Overall, they were okay.
But they didn't...
impressed me, I guess.
They both seemed exhausted.
Like their energy was drained,
so the joy of acting wasn't there.
Even though I believe they could do it
with the potential they have.
Next, we have Pailiu and...
June.
Right. How were they?
I was actually surprised by June.
She's usually very quiet,
but today she was quiet in a way in the way that fit the role.
Just seeing her face made me smile.
And Pailiu keeps improving every time.
I really felt it today.
A huge leap in her development.
Yes, she's kept getting better every day.
And this week I still think she can go far.
She can adapt to all types of actors.
With someone like Pailiu,
she can take and respond to all kinds of deliveries.
So I feel that's her true strength.
And like Met said, she'll definitely go far.
And the last pair, Neuanaow and Lita.
I don't understand their interpretation.
But I feel they were off the mark in a different way.
This pair is the most natural.
Because Lita looks very Thai,
while Neuanaow looks very modern.
Her mannerisms, she's super modern.
But they over-planned the performance.
So who should we choose today?
I think we're all on the same page.
Let's call the girls in.
We've reached a conclusion on
who will get the roles for this final round.
But I want to say that every one of you did well.
You have improved much more than
you had in the previous weeks.
But of course it's not perfect.
There were some mistakes.
Maybe some of you had things on your mind today.
But today one person really surprised all the judges.
We didn't think she would pull it off.
But...
she did.
So the pair who won the roles today is…
June and Pailiu.
I've been waiting to hear this.
-Pailiu, thank you.
-You got it.
-Thank you.
-Congratulations.
June has really improved.
I was so happy. I turned to hug Pailiu.
I said, "Thank you, Pailiu. I got this because of you."
You truly earned this yourself.
It's not like we gave it to you
just because it's the last round.
Because there were parts you weren't perfect,
but there were parts that showed us that
this character fits you best.
-Got it.
-Congrats.
Thank you. Thank you.
Great job. Great job.
I'm so happy today.
Stand up and give each other a hug.
I'm gonna cry.
Leave all the past disagreements behind you.
Okay?
You can talk to each other. You're good now.
Make up, make up.
Come on, everyone, group hug.
We're all friends here.
Great job.
Congratulations.
Don't cry.
Be careful with your eyelashes.
Your eyelashes may fall off.
They're magnetic ones.
Thank you.
The crew's treating us to a nice meal today.
Yes.
Sit down first, sit down. Let's wrap up the show properly.
And the pair who got the roles today
will also go on a date by the sea.
A very special date by the sea.
Have fun on your date.
And next week will be our final week together.
We'll find out who leaves the house with whom.
See you all next week.
Goodbye.
Goodbye. Thank you.
Finally, June got the role.
And it's a victory she shares with Pailiu.
Give it your all on set, and enjoy your date.
I'm truly happy for you.
Action.
No, this one is...
It's okay, I can walk.
I'm telling you, I'm not just here for filming.
See?
I can handle hiking too.
I keep going.
Hey, I'm Thai. What's going on?
Let's share.
Whoa, it's huge.
Did you bring this with you?
It's not mine.
Stay still. Let's chop its head off, Ms. Yoong.
Hey, I'm Thai.
Duh. That's why Som said,
"Stay still. Let’s chop its head off, Ms. Yoong."
Hey, I'm Thai.
Don't do that.
Don't. I'm just here on a field trip.
Hey, I'm Thai.
What's going on?
Let me know what sound's ready.
I'm just here on a field trip.
Take her back to the house.
Cut.
Yes, Miss.
Want some lemon?
She's losing her voice.
Take her back to the house.
I felt both excited and pressured.
I really wanted to do better.
This is called cosmetics.
Get started right away.
Cut.
That was good. Do it again.
My legs are cramping.
Insolent.
It sounds Chinese.
Yeah.
Insolent.
It's the "hao." Hao. Ni hao.
This is June's first time acting in a series, right?
I think she did really well, but I felt bad for you because
it was her first time, and she had to do the hardest role.
I think this one was the toughest role.
How was your first shoot?
You saw it yourself.
It was a tough one.
-I felt bad.
-Right?
Yeah, you had to lie on the ground right away.
On the ground right away.
I walked through mud since this morning.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Before you saw me.
Yeah, I didn't see. I was getting into my costume.
Exactly.
You should rewatch the clip.
I thought you wanted me to join you in the mud.
Would you go if I asked?
-I'm telling you...
-Of course.
After the mud, we'll wash off at the water park.
Whoa, can I rest first?
Really?
-You might not be up for it.
-Let me rest first,
Let me take a nap, then we'll go.
When are we going? Tomorrow?
I think so.
Stop playing around.
Come on.
Who's playing?
We're working.
You're talking nonsense, Met.
Our director's talking nonsense.
I had to run. I fed you earlier.
You're exhausted.
You want encouragement.
What kind do you want?
Just encouragement.
What kind though?
I don't know.
Despite the tough roles,
the atmosphere on set is cheerful and fun.
But…
there's something going on with this pair.
-I'm scared.
-War... What are you scared of?
Of falling down.
Yeah, I saw that.
Just stand back a bit diagonally.
Handfuls...
That would be hilarious.
Handfuls of mud.
Set.
And action.
Let's go.
Run, Miss. I'll hold them back.
Run, Miss.
I ran off.
I ran off with a girl.
Keep fighting.
Cut.
Slate!
Working with June was a lot of fun.
I feel she's a fighter.
Because she had a lot of tough scenes.
And... I don't know... she's just so endearing,
that girl June. "That girl June."
So heavy. Wanna hold it?
No way.
How can I hold that? Goodness.
This is actually called an ant egg stick.
You know what that is?
Really?
Not really.
Hey, I'm giving it back. I changed my mind.
-We switched roles.
-It's pretty chill.
It's not that heavy. Wanna try?
Huh? No?
Where did he go?
Somebody, come take this.
The last one.
Want some?
I'm good. You take it.
I'll give you more.
Fine.
Adore her. Adore her.
You wanna pinch her cheeks.
Cut. Okay.
That's a wrap.
Alright everyone, that's a wrap!
Yay. The last episode of the miniseries was really tough.
But June and Pailiu will later
go on a date at a water park in Hua Hin
and stay in a private villa
with a pool by the sea. Totally worth it.
This last episode I got to film with June
was actually my own decision too.
I chose to go with her because...
What's the word?
Because something was unresolved in EP 1.
I feel I've unlocked a lot of things in myself.
I feel working with her was so much fun.
It actually unlocked something in me.
It helps me... It might help me make a better decision
when I have to choose the person to leave the house with.
Now back to the house.
Oh, you don't eat veggies.
-Yeah, you don't eat veggies.
-Especially pickled ones.
Oh, you're sleeping here, Jeab?
-I thought you left.
-Jeab.
Don't tell me you're a secret member?
I thought you left.
I wanted to let you know something.
It's something pretty serious.
What I want to tell you is…
you're going to the beach too!
But...
those two can't know that we're going to surprise them.
Okay.
Always have something up your sleeve.
Because we want you guys to spend quality time together
outside this house before you make your decision on
who you want to leave house hand in hand with you.
So have fun at the beach, share good moments,
and make the most of this beautiful experience.
Spending time together at a beautiful place
might help clear your hearts and minds.
It should help you make your decision next week.
I hope all of you have fun there. See you later.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
We get a free trip. I'm so happy.
(Bangkok, Phra Ram Ratchaniwet, Cha-am)
Wow, the villa with a pool the girls came to today
has such amazing atmosphere.
Hopefully they have good moments here
which will help them decide
who they want to leave the house with hand in hand.
So pretty.
The vibe is amazing.
Wow, it's huge.
I haven't gone out in so long. Seeing this is so refreshing.
-Yes.
-Right?
Feels like we're on a trip.
Like a whole new world.
Ooh, a new place. So bright and shiny.
I wanna live here.
So how are we gonna sleep tonight?
Let the couple sleep together.
We're planning on that.
What?
Well, Wafer and...
Hling, go ahead.
Yeah, the newlyweds.
Left or right?
-I'll take this one.
-Then you take this one.
-I'll take this side.
-I'll take that one.
Okay, let's go.
-Okay. See you in a bit.
-Wait.
You four gonna stay in that room?
Well, it's settled... It's not settled yet.
-Take your time.
-Stay together.
One episode left.
Go unpack and we'll meet later.
-See you in a bit.
-See you later.
Maybe we'll be a foursome.
Wait, really?
An open relationship.
Okay, shall we divide our tasks for today?
-Sure.
What are our tasks?
As for the seafood, I can't really tell if it's fresh or not.
I can tell. I know how to spot male and female crabs.
I can tell which one has eggs.
Okay, that's your job.
-Sure.
-Then I'll go get drinks with Neua.
And as usual, Nice and I will just watch.
-Yes.
-And we'll help plate the food.
Okay, that's settled then.
-Okay, so...
-Shall we split up now?
Before it gets dark.
-Shall we?
-Let's go.
Yeah, so our friends will have food.
-See you guys later.
Shall we?
We're here.
We're at Vana Nava.
Let's see.
Looks good on you.
So we're matching.
How are we not?
-This one.
-Which one?
-Got everything?
-Let's go.
Cute.
And for the first date...
No, I feel like whenever someone get to film
the miniseries with me go somewhere with me,
they always end up having to do something difficult.
Oh, it's an adventure.
-Really?
-Yes.
Okay, awesome.
I've never been here.
Why is my side going backward?
Why is it my side?
Today Pailiu is treating me.
Yes, whatever you
want to eat today, I'll buy.
But first, let me walk straight.
I don't really talk until I'm close to the other person.
But if we're close, I talk.
Yeah, true.
At first you didn't talk at all.
I'm quiet.
Completely silent, like...
I was so scared.
-I was...
-Really?
You're really quiet, but I used to be just like you.
I used to get an introvert result on the MBTI test even.
I didn't get along with people right away.
I had to be around them first.
And I didn't dare start a conversation.
If I sat next to someone, I'd get so tense.
It's not that I didn't want to talk. I did.
I just didn't know what to say,
or how to start, so I'd rather stay quiet.
-Yes.
-I was scared.
Exactly. But outsiders would think we're arrogant.
But we're not. We just don't know
how to start a conversation.
We overthink things in our heads.
Oh, we're stuck again.
Rock, paper, scissors.
And she's the one who asked me to play.
She's the one who wanted to play,
-but I'm scared.
-To challenge ourselves.
Never been so scared of a round of rock, paper, scissors.
Loser goes first, okay?
Oh my God, please.
In case heaven is real.
-Rock, paper, scissors.
Should you be in front?
Do it like this?
Like this.
Like this, right? How did they do it in "Titanic"?
They held hands.
Outer space.
June!
I'll follow you.
Pailiu.
Ready?
She's going.
One, two...
Pailiu!
Are you okay?!
Pailiu, are you okay?!
How much do you weight?
She's gone.
Before she went, she said, "June..."
-Then she went.
-Okay, ready?
-Yes.
-Okay.
Wow, Liu and June are having so much fun.
After using so much energy, they must be hungry.
-Come on.
-So hungry.
Haven't eaten anything today.
Yeah, we've been in the water all day.
-Yeah.
-Totally worn out.
But I had a blast today.
What did you like the most?
Getting to take you to play.
-I wasn't messing with you.
-Thanks.
-I wasn't. I just...
-I'm the victim.
-It was just fun.
I got you to try something new.
Thank you.
So how do you feel coming here with me?
Today was fun, but honestly
you surprised me since the audition.
The one that we both won the roles.
Because I'd never seen that side of you.
It was crazy to me. You were totally yourself.
You were bold, not afraid to act, not tense.
I found that very charming.
And you've improved so much.
-Really?
-Yeah, so much better.
I had to try and fight. And look, I made it.
Yeah, you did.
-And I got to play in the water.
-Great job.
I love it.
But there are so many people choosing you.
-It's stressful, honestly.
-Is it?
Yeah, I don't wanna hurt anyone.
I even thought maybe I should leave the house alone.
You can't do that.
Like, maybe I should just leave
by myself so no one would get hurt.
They might still be sad,
but at least it wouldn't be too painful.
I don't know. It's been weighing on me, but...
Yeah.
It's okay. Spaghetti will cheer you up.
Yeah, comfort food...
That was so loud.
-Wow.
-That was totally me.
Even though both of them seem so happy today,
they look worried about the final day
when they'll have to leave the house.
Take your time to think.
There's still some time to decide.
Better to fully enjoy this moment.
(Welcome to Pu Chak-Saphan Yok
Traditional Fishing Lifestyle)
Meanwhile, the other six girls split up
to do the tasks they were assigned.
Squid, right? They'd probably want that.
What do they want to eat?
Pailiu likes shrimp and crab.
And the others?
The others…
Maybe we get everything?
Let's just get everything.
How do you know that?
-Well...
-How do you even know that?
-No, we're together...
-How? I don't even know.
We're together a lot, that's why.
But I don't know about the others
since we've never eaten together.
-There's more.
-I'm giving you extra.
Wow, thank you.
You're the prettiest here.
Thank you.
Prettiest in the market, thank you.
Thank you very much.
-That one.
-Yeah.
-You'll grill it yourself?
-Yes.
We'll clean it for you.
-Thank you.
-Take out the ink.
Get the eyes out.
-Yes.
-Thank you.
They're gonna be so happy.
Yeah, we'll head back to the villa.
What drink do you want?
Water.
Just water.
Let's get the green drink.
Okay.
The black drink.
It's not here.
Let me hold that for you.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
Let's go.
We're not worried about the shoppers.
We're more worried about the girls preparing the grill.
Everyone will have food today.
-It looks...
-Yes.
It's starting to look good.
Looks like it'll work.
Blow it yourself?
Yeah, see?
See? See?
Yeah.
Feels like a scout camp.
It's coming!
Hey, hey!
We really lit the fire.
Wow, Wafer's really reliable.
So these two get to chill before everyone else.
The villa is ready. Are the other two girls ready?
The internet here...
Oh.
Guess where we are right now?
Eh? Where?
Not at the house?
At the market?
Nope.
Where?
We're in Cha-am!
Hello!
Have you been there long?
Just arrived.
Just got here.
-Having fun?
-We're all here.
I'll send you the location.
I'll send you the location, okay?
Meet us at the villa.
-Okay.
-Hurry back.
The villa's gorgeous. See you.
-Look.
-Okay.
Bye-bye.
Why are you pretty?
Eh?
-Eh?
-Eh? They're gone.
-Wow.
-What a surprise.
Yeah.
-When did they get here?
-Let's hurry.
Come on, let's go there.
What are you doing?
Touching up.
Wanna some lip gloss?
Let's go.
-Ready.
-Let's take pics.
Yeah, let's take some pics.
Stay tuned for the next episode,
where the girls spend time together
at a villa with a pool by the sea.
Enjoy the great atmosphere
and the final chapter of their hearts.
Who will pair up in the end?
And who will decide to leave the house alone?
Don't miss the finale of "Love Moment."
You can watch episode seven of the Love Moment miniseries
titled "Because Love Calls"
only on Kantana Motion Pictures' YouTube channel and WeTV.
Go watch it, rewatch it,
binge it from the first to the last episode,
and share it with your friends.
And if there's any story you'd like to see
developed into a full series in the future,
don't forget to let the girls and the crew know.
A goodbye kiss.
Goosebumps.
The final chapter of the hearts:
who will leave the house hand in hand?
Join us to sail the ships and get elated
on the finale of "Love Moment."
You definitely don't wanna miss it.