What kind of behavior
would be identified as a crime?
We have to judge it in legal terms.
For example,
did he do that on purpose?
Or was it an accident?
Anyway,
whether it was intentional or unintentional,
it's very important in legal terms.
In this case, he did it on purpose.
In other words, he did have the intention of robbing it.
It's essential in legal terms.
Well, my happy time has finally arrived.
Guess what we'll eat today.
Taichi's notes are still the same. They're like secret codes.
Huh?
But it's easier to understand than before.
Right? I will continue to serve you.
Hey, Taichi.
-What?
-How do you read this?
Well...
Oh, "burger."
"Burger?"
Yes.
I see, it's "burglar."
It means stealing, right?
Yes, that's right.
-It means stealing.
-Oh.
This is bad.
Hey!
Ah, Maya.
Kouhei, hide quickly!
Eh?
Don't worry about it. Hide first!
Hurry!
Why?
Oh.
Eh.
Okay.
Where's Maya?
Where is she?
Oh no.
What's wrong?
[Theme Song]
Bon Appétit.
It's delicious.
Why is it so delicious?
Big stuffed onigiri.
Hey,
can you stop looking at me like that?
I'm losing my appetite because of you.
Hey.
That's my onigiri.
It's a burglar. You're a thief.
What?
That belongs to Senior, right?
You have no right to judge me.
Oh?
My tamagoyaki.
It's delicious.
Taichi, why don't you take mine?
Can I?
Pick what you like.
That's great. Thank you.
Here. Take this too.
Ah.
Then you have nothing to eat.
I'm full.
-Don't starve yourself.
-I'm not.
Senior.
Is studying hard?
Yes.
I'm already in my second year.
The lessons are getting harder.
That's not what I meant.
I'm asking about your qualification exam.
Ah.
Huh?
What qualification?
You've started studying for the qualification exam, right?
Yes.
What are you talking about?
I've never heard of it.
I haven't told you yet, have I?
What?
I want to be a social insurance specialist.
Social...
Social insurance specialist?
What does that do?
Don't you know?
A social insurance specialist certificate
is a national qualification.
Specialist for...
labourers' social insurance?
Senior.
Do you want to work at a law firm in the future?
No.
I haven't thought of the details.
I just think
it might be hard to work and get certified at the same time.
So I'm taking the exam since I'm free now.
I see.
I don't know what will happen to my ears.
That's why I'm trying to master some skills now.
You haven't thought about anything, have you?
What?
"There's nothing else I want to do.
I shall go to college first," it's all over your face.
Hey, you!
Am I wrong?
You are…
You are not wrong.
I knew it.
Geez... Your words…
Hey, Taichi.
Huh?
Yasu wants you to go to the club room.
But I'm still eating.
You can eat later.
Huh?
I'll borrow Taichi first.
Hurry up.
Don't disturb my happy time.
You can eat later. Let's go.
Ah, Maya, goodbye.
At least let me have one onigiri.
Hey, hurry up.
Why?
I don't know. He said it was urgent.
Now?
By the way, carry your own stuff.
He's so noisy.
Really?
Maya, are you also like that?
Huh?
You can hear Taichi's voice, right?
No, no, no!
Besides, that's because he was too loud.
Yes, he was.
What's wrong with him?
He's acting strangely.
Last time, he rushed towards us while riding a bike.
Hey, he-he!
Eh? Ah.
That was awesome!
That time, Taichi's face...
What's wrong?
Senior,
you do laugh like this?
Of course.
He also scared me when we first met.
He suddenly rolled down from above.
What's going on?
Awesome.
Really.
Taichi is amazing.
N-Nothing...
I have a distorted personality.
I think it would be bad if Taichi's kindness was discovered.
Thinking that one day,
someone will notice his good side,
I feel restless,
actually.
Senior.
No, it's nothing.
[Film Research Club]
Ta-da.
[Director, Satoshi Yasuda, year one student at Kousen University]
[D/Z~ Dear zombie]
-What?
-What do you think?
[Gold Award]
[20th National Student Film Festival] [Winner]
-You're amazing.
-You won the gold prize in the first year.
Yeah.
Taichi, your role as a zombie is great too.
No, Yasu is the best!
Okay.
Amazing, Yasu!
You're really something.
You did it!
Thank you.
Why? Aren't you happy?
I'm happy.
You're overreacting. That's why he's embarrassed.
Is that so?
Yes.
What is this?
The movie director, Satoshi Yasuda, is born!
He's born!
You're exaggerating.
But I have to keep shooting for the future.
Future?
Yes.
I'd like to work in this field if possible.
-Okay.
-Hey, Yasu.
You look so stiff.
No, I don't.
You finally won the gold prize.
-What's wrong?
-Your facial expression...
-Your facial expression seems not right.
-What did you say?
I'm so happy.
With a bright smile.
Don't you agree, Taichi?
Yeah... I feel the same.
-Isn't it refreshing?
-Yes, it is.
I'm home.
You're back.
Hey.
Ah.
Grandpa.
Yes?
Grandpa,
when did you decide to become a carpenter?
Why do you ask?
Tell me. When?
Three years old.
What?
I decided when I was three.
So early.
You're amazing, Grandpa.
Be careful with your nails.
It's all your fault. No one asked you to be there.
What did you say?
What?
Do you like nails that much?
Hey.
-Here. Take all of them.
-No, I don't want.
-Here you are.
-You're terrible.
-Ha ha ha.
-You old man.
Are you kidding me?
[Open]
Thank you for coming.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
This is jasmine tea.
Here, this is coke.
Here.
Excuse me, Sakawa. Can you clean up here?
Okay.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
They're all amazing.
All of them are preparing for the future.
-Ah, I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
-Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
[Sign Language]
Eh?
Huh?
Ah.
I'm so sorry.
Okay.
Isn't it B?
It's C.
Why?
Hey!
-Yes?
-She's always with Sugihara.
Ah.
I think she has a problem with her ears too.
-Really?
-Yes.
Sure enough, similar people
are more intimate.
Who knows?
Why do I
always hear those words?
Senior.
I'm sorry.
I also said something like that before.
Something like that?
Are you ignoring me?
Do you think everyone is pitying you?
You brat…
Hey!
-Oh my!
-Let go!
If Taichi were here,
he'd get mad again.
Taichi...
is like a little boar.
Boar?
Rather than saying he's always frank,
it's better to say he doesn't know how to turn or dodge.
He won't turn back unless he hits the wall. He's just charging forward without hesitation.
Senior.
Even a boar
turns.
When it finds its next target,
it will go that way directly.
What will you do then?
The place I'm going is only five minutes away from here.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
I'm sorry for causing you trouble.
No, no, no.
It's my fault for knocking you down.
No, I hit you.
I didn't see it. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
Okay.
Are you a student?
Yes.
Second year at Kousen University.
Eh?
My relative has a child studying at Kousen University too.
Yes.
-Really?
-Yes.
-What's his major?
-Ah, well…
[sig-n]
Eh?
Shi…
Shigun.
Ha ha.
It's pronounced as "sign."
"Sign."
I'm back.
Oh, you're back.
Ah.
Can you put it here?
Okay.
Chiba.
Can you get him a cup of tea?
Ah.
Okay.
No need.
I'm leaving.
Please have a seat.
Okay.
Here you are.
Dig in.
Can I?
Well,
bon appétit.
Enjoy it.
It's delicious.
Chiba.
Yes.
Do you still have this cake?
Eh?
I want a piece of it too.
No, no.
Mr. Sai, didn't you eat just now?
But look how satisfied he is.
One more, please.
Alright, alright.
Thank you.
Ah.
Let me introduce myself again.
I'm Sai, the chairman.
[Chairman, Sai Seishiru]
Nice to meet you.
Eh?
Old man, are you the chairman?
What old man? You brat...
You're right.
I'm already an old man.
Ah. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
May I ask
what this company does?
Our company
is involved in the sign language business.
Sign language business?
Yes.
We mainly provide
sign language training services
with sign language interpretation.
Hmm.
We're very popular in the service industry.
In fact, our customers
[Sign language training, sign language lessons, sign language interpretation]
[Learn sign language to communicate with hearing impairers]
[Welcome all enterprises and teams]
have many chances to interact with people who can't hear.
However,
although the training course
only covers basic sign language,
through learning the sign language,
people will think about how to communicate with someone who can't hear.
Sugihara.
Good job.
This is Ms. Natsumi, the head of this office.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Okami Maya.
Hello, Okami.
Hello.
Excuse me.
I haven't learned sign language so far.
I see.
She's just like me.
That's totally fine.
I look forward to working with you.
Well done.
Very good.
Ha ha ha.
But
not everyone can use sign language, right?
Yes.
Do you have any measures to help those
who can't use sign language?
For example,
provide them subtitles,
just like taking notes.
Huh?
We don't have such services yet.
Our target is deaf-mute.
Deaf?
Ah.
In other words,
they can't hear anything.
For those people, sign language is their first language.
It's completely different from those with poor hearing.
Okay, enjoy your cake.
Thank you.
Eh?
Don't you think
it's strange?
Why?
What do you mean?
Because
if we categorize people like this,
it won't help those with hearing disorders.
Gosh.
Are you picking a problem with our company?
Anyway,
you think it's wrong to separate the deaf-mutes from people with hearing disorders.
I mean,
people with hearing impairment also suffer a lot.
So I don't think it's necessary to separate them.
I see.
This is an issue about idealism.
For example,
you mentioned subtitles just now.
The subtitles may be necessary for those who can't hear it.
But some people also think the subtitles make the screen narrower.
So they don't want the subtitles.
For example, we provide tactile pavements for those who are vision impaired.
But it becomes a barrier for those who sit in a wheelchair.
Once we satisfy one of them, it makes the other party unhappy.
We're not volunteers.
This is our job.
It's impossible to satisfy everyone.
Hey, do you understand?
I couldn't hear what they said anyway.
Kouhei!
I don't want...
to lose the chance of hearing that voice again.
Now you don't even tell me how you feel.
You won't understand anyway.
What do you mean by that?
I don't understand.
What?
If you keep saying it's hard,
nothing will change.
How should the tactile pavements not cause troubles
to those in wheelchairs?
Maybe you can solve it if you think carefully.
And the subtitles.
How should you prevent the screen from narrowing?
You might be able to solve it too.
Hey.
I...
I don't like giving up at the beginning.
If they think they're the only one who's different,
they must be very lonely.
Everyone is the same.
It's no different from being alone.
But
they can't experience the feeling
when people have the same idea
and laugh together.
It doesn't matter
whether they can hear it or not.
Isn't that what people do when they're together?
Is it that hard?
My...
name is...
Maya.
Try it.
My...
name is...
Maya. Did I do it right?
Yes.
My
name is...
Finger language?
It is to express the Japanese phonemes
by means of the fingers.
Ta... I... Chi.
You've turned it into "kitsune (a fox)."
-Really?
-That's "ki."
-Like this.
-"Chi."
Ta... I... Chi.
Ha ha.
Did I do it right?
You punk.
What are you trying to say?
I don't know anything.
I'm sorry for being so full of myself.
Excuse me.
Hold on.
Eh?
I understand what you want to say.
Do you want to work in our company?
What?
Huh?
Wait.
Mr. Sai.
Mr. Sai, what are you talking about?
[In the Next Episode]
Good luck.
Even if we're short-handed, you should find someone more capable.
What do you think if I drop out of college?
Ever since I met Taichi,
I'm glad I'm what I am now.
I'm fine.
[This drama is purely fictional. The names of all characters and groups in this drama are fictional.]
It doesn't matter if I don't have Taichi.