You…
-Ha-bin.
-Move.
I won't be framed for this.
-Ha-bin.
-Let go!
Wait. What was that sound?
Choi Yeong-min.
-Hey! Choi!
-Choi!
Hey.
Report to the situation room.
-Call the forensic team too. Quick.
-On it.
Detective Lee, notify the team.
Detective Park, with me.
Yes, sir.
Situation update.
We found Choi's body on the second floor.
The suspect may have fled the scene.
What happened there?
Why were you there with Choi Yeong-min--
Stop beating around the bush.
Ask me if I killed him.
What did you mean when you said
you won't be framed for it?
Was someone else there?
Have you changed your plan?
Are you pretending to trust me
to get me to confess?
I'm not pretending.
I'll believe what you say now.
So tell me.
There were two weapons.
The stab wound on the knee
was made by something pointy,
but not the one on the neck.
Why do you think
they used different weapons?
Maybe it wasn't a sole offender.
There's a chance that
one culprit used multiple weapons.
Looking at the tie marks
and how they knew where Choi was hiding,
they must have known him
and had everything planned.
What we can say for sure is
that they had a good enough reason
to find and kill the man in hiding.
Collect the DNA samples
and send them to the NFS immediately.
Yes, sir.
Explain what happened.
When I went back,
Choi Yeong-min was already dead.
Did you see who did it?
No.
How did you know
Choi Yeong-min was hiding there?
I knew it
because I followed him.
Alone?
Yes.
Why did you go back to him?
To ask him something.
Ask him what?
The real culprit who killed Su-hyeon.
Mom thought I did it,
so she buried the body…
and committed suicide out of guilt.
I get it.
But it wouldn't have happened
if Su-hyeon hadn't been killed.
What's your plan now?
Why did you get me out of there?
The body has been transferred earlier,
so check this instead.
We'll have to wait
for the autopsy to be sure,
but the cause of death
seems to be exsanguination.
The forensic team has confirmed
that the culprit used
two different knives.
Could there be two culprits?
I'm not sure.
Just because there were two weapons,
doesn't mean there were two--
The ripped wound on the neck
shows that the blade was dull.
Meanwhile, the wound on the knee
was made with a sharp knife,
which makes it a good weapon.
The person who attacked his leg
might not be the same person
as the one who killed him.
The forensic team must have missed it.
I'll submit it when I get to the station.
If there really are two culprits,
one of them might be a woman.
Is this Hansol Youth Shelter?
I'm calling from Yeonju Police Station.
We need the contact info
of Song Min-a's family regarding the case.
I already gave you
her aunt's phone number.
Do you know her father's phone number?
Both of Min-a's parents passed away.
What is it that you wanted to say?
Choi Yeong-min is dead.
Jang Ha-bin killed him.
What…
I saw it with my own eyes.
Now, we have an ace up our sleeve.
Her dad is a cop.
He's going to do anything
to prevent her from going to prison.
You don't have to worry anymore.
Are you telling me
to blackmail my student's parent?
Just so you know.
I'll take care of the rest.
One thing that bothers me is…
the woman you're seeing.
What about Seong-hui?
She knows what happened that day.
She won't do anything to hurt me.
She's not going to stick by your side
with the cops poking around and all.
Seong-hui has been through
a lot because of me.
Even if she tells the cops,
I won't blame her.
That single mom is clinging to you
because you're so naive.
You don't know what you're talking about.
You've got to nip it in the bud!
Say one more thing,
and I will cut ties with you again.
Mom.
Why are you up so early?
Where have you been?
I was just
meeting with Mr. Park.
A police officer came yesterday.
To our place?
He showed me Mr. Park's photo
and asked me if I knew him.
And?
What did you tell him?
CHOI YEONG-MIN CASE
EVIDENCE: NECKLACE
A woman's necklace was found?
Yes.
We also found a brick nearby
with bloodstains on it.
If that's Choi's blood,
it could have been left
by the culprit during the struggle.
Could this necklace be Kim Seong-hui's?
The culprit is likely someone he knew.
When did she get home last night?
She wasn't home last night.
Bring her in. Tell her
that we just need her for references.
-Yes, sir.
-What about Park Jun-tae?
He left urgently
after getting a phone call yesterday.
Have you reached out to him?
I called him, but he wouldn't answer.
And it seems like
Park Jun-tae met Song Min-a
on the day she died.
He met who? Song Min-a?
Yes. Also,
it turns out
Min-a and Mr. Park knew each other.
Where did you hear that?
From Do-yun, Kim Seong-hui's son.
What? Why are you telling me that now?
Can I help you?
Hello, Mr. Park.
Can we have a minute?
I can't right now.
I'll reach out to you later.
Should I wait in the teachers' office?
Choi Yeong-min is dead.
How?
You don't seem surprised.
Did you know about it?
How could I?
Are you suspecting me now?
Of what?
I never said he was killed,
and you seem pretty sure it was murder.
Did everything go okay with…
what made you leave urgently yesterday?
-Yes.
-Was it perhaps related to Choi?
-No.
-To Kim Seong-hui, then?
I'm not obligated to answer that.
I just wonder if she knows too.
Knows what?
Song Min-a.
You knew Min-a well.
I'm not sure what you're trying to say.
Why did you meet Song Min-a that day?
What is it that you wanted to ask me?
You once lived with my daughter, Min-a,
so I thought you might know something.
I'd love to help,
but I don't know anything.
I'm sorry, sir.
I know you knew her well.
Pardon?
I think there's a misunderstanding.
You must be Do-yun.
Get back inside.
I know you saw Min-a that day.
Stop racking your brain to figure out
what I know and tell me what happened.
I'm the one who should call the police.
A person died in this house.
Do I seem like I'm joking?
What happened that day?
I'll tell you!
I'll tell you everything I know.
May 11th.
That's the day Song died.
You met her, right?
I'm not sure. I can't remember.
I'm not asking this out of curiosity.
I know you did.
To tell you the truth,
I met Choi Yeong-min
after leaving the police station.
He threatened me,
knowing that I was being investigated.
Threatened how?
He knew that once people found out
I was involved in a case where girls died,
the rumors would hurt my career.
His ridiculous threat did upset me,
but he was fine until I left him.
Was it really a ridiculous threat, though?
Yesterday, Choi told me
that he'd turn himself in,
saying he knew who the culprit was.
And as soon as he said that,
he got murdered…
and the last person he met
before he died was you, so--
I saw Ha-bin there yesterday.
It looks like you already knew
that Ha-bin met Choi Yeong-min too.
Why don't you come
to the station and officially state…
that you saw her yesterday?
And…
you'd better stop avoiding the interview.
Please don't make us believe
that you're the culprit
Choi was talking about.
Because if you are,
we'll arrest you at all costs.
I'll see you at the station later today.
We got Choi's call log.
He kept calling Kim Seong-hui
while he was on the run.
After ignoring his calls for a while,
she finally called him back,
which was around 1:00 a.m.,
the estimated time of his death.
Is Kim still not answering your calls?
We couldn't reach her,
so I sent Detective Cho to her house.
What's this number? 7658.
Well?
Captain.
CAPTAIN JANG TAE-SU
Where's Captain Jang right now?
That new place?
-He's so cute, isn't he?
-I know.
-I've always wanted to try that.
-Let's go.
What a coward.
What a piece of trash.
I LOVE YOU, MR. PARK
PLEASE GET WELL SOON, MR. PARK
IT MAKES US SAD
WE LOVE YOU, MR. PARK
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING,
MR. PARK
You weren't home that night?
After having dinner, my son had a fever,
so I took him to the emergency room.
-You're lying. Tell me the truth.
-It's the truth.
The hospital must have the record too.
Are you saying that girl…
I mean… Min-a was home alone then?
That was…
after she left the gang.
A man living downstairs named Yeong-min…
Yeong-min was…
looking for Min-a then.
And that day,
I suddenly got a call from Min-a.
Hello?
Ms. Kim, is Yeong-min home?
Are you Min-a?
Yes.
I want to pick up the stuff I left there.
I rented a car, so it won't take long.
Okay.
Get here safely.
Do-yun's fever won't come down.
This won't do.
I'll take him to the hospital.
-Let me come with you. I'll drive.
-I can take a taxi.
Min-a is coming to pick up her stuff,
so let her in when she's here.
Do-yun, let's go to the hospital.
Jun-tae…
Nobody was home.
I had to take my child to the hospital…
so I told Min-a the passcode
of the smart door lock.
All her stuff was gone,
so I thought she came by and left--
Don't you try to fool me.
I know you saw everything that day.
I really don't know.
I really don't.
Well…
I did hear Yeong-min say…
that he was going to take her down.
But I was too scared of his retaliation
to say anything to the police.
I'm sorry.
So you think…
Choi Yeong-min killed her.
Hello? This is the police.
Ms. Kim Seong-hui.
Are you in there?
This is the police. Is anyone in there?
She's not picking up.
Keep trying.
This is the police. Hello?
Ms. Kim Seong-hui!
We need to talk.
Why didn't you tell me
you had a phone call with Choi?
Do you hear me?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Why would a suspect call the police?
He wanted to turn himself in.
And?
I waited for him
where we were supposed to meet,
but he didn't show up.
Why didn't you tell us about it?
Seriously, I don't understand.
I made a wrong decision.
What decision did you make
and how was it wrong?
I thought it would be better
to talk to him by myself.
You think you're so great, don't you?
I know you don't care about the team,
but if you told us that he wanted
to turn himself in
and made a plan to lure him out
we could've arrested him alive.
I'll take responsibility
for this mistake
after finding the culprit.
"Responsibility"?
Responsibility, my foot.
"It was Choi Yeong-min"?
All right, then.
Kim Seong-hui isn't home.
It's a bit sketchy
that she knew all three victims
and tried to call Choi before he died.
Check out what she was up to yesterday.
Yes, sir.
Captain.
Are you just going to let
Captain Jang off the hook?
He always acts like we don't exist.
We can't work with someone like that.
Other detectives can see that too.
What's up?
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
The reason Captain Jang
didn't tell us about the call with Choi
might be because of his daughter.
What does Captain Jang's daughter
have to do with the case?
Jang Ha-bin and Lee Su-hyeon
were close friends,
according to Park Jun-tae.
Officer Lee, can we talk first?
As you know, she was also involved
with Song Min-a before she died.
Her alibi has already been
confirmed for that.
Is there something else?
After interrogating Choi,
he definitely said
that he knew Captain Jang.
Wait.
Are you saying they knew each other
even before the interrogation?
Yes.
From where he's from
to the crimes he's committed,
I looked into everything,
but he had no overlaps with Captain Jang.
I think they got to know each other
through his daughter.
And?
We need to investigate Jang Ha-bin.
Sorry to interrupt…
but I think you should listen to this.
I'm sorry.
I have an urgent tip to report
but I don't know the detective's number.
It's Jang Tae-su.
Choi's phone records showed that
he called the police
before he contacted Captain Jang.
If they had known each other already,
he would've known Captain Jang's number.
He kept it a secret even after Choi died.
-There must be a reason--
-Of course, there is.
That's why he acted alone
and messed up the investigation.
Aside from everything else,
I think he should take
full responsibility.
For now,
we have to fix this first.
I understand what you're saying,
so let's revisit this
once the investigation is over.
Get ready
for an interview with Park Jun-tae.
Did you find something?
He admitted
that he met Choi Yeong-min yesterday.
Did you meet Park Jun-tae alone?
He's coming later.
But that alone isn't enough
to prove he's the culprit.
We didn't get to have
a proper meeting today.
Profiling is
about identifying the culprit,
not pushing a specific suspect.
You know that better than anyone.
He met Choi Yeong-min before he died.
That is the single most important fact.
Why did you meet Seong-hui?
What if she said I killed Min-a?
What were you going to do then?
Everything I could do.
There are
too many sketchy people around you.
Choi Yeong-min.
Jang Ha-bin.
And the woman you're dating.
They're all so sketchy.
Let me be clear.
Never meet Seong-hui ever again.
Song Min-a.
Did you really kill her?
You saw it yourself that day.
Why did you kill her?
Tell me!
Did you really kill her?
I told you. I killed her.
But why…
Why can't you say anything?
Why would you, an ordinary school teacher,
kill a person?
Why?
Maybe it runs in the family.
You…
You're not like me.
You're different.
What do you know about me?
I just know.
You didn't do it.
How can I help you?
I recently got pickpocketed around here.
He was riding a motorcycle.
It seemed like
he was caught by the police.
Do you remember the time and location?
In the alley near Mihwa Elementary School.
It was on the 21st,
and the police came around 2:00 p.m.
Could you sit there and wait?
Is there a female police officer here?
Do you need something?
Yes.
Give me a second.
Where did she go?
It looks like she left.
But she was here just now.
JUNG DU-CHEOL
What?
Let me ask you one last time.
Are you sure
that nobody saw you at the scene that day?
Someone saw you there.
Who is that?
What's this about?
Do you think
I'm the culprit, not that person?
That's not why I'm asking this.
Then why are you asking?
I'm afraid that I might not…
be able to prove it wasn't you.
That's why I'm asking.
Are you sure…
you told me…
everything?
I already answered your question,
and it's your choice to believe it or not.
Okay.
That's all I needed to know.
TAE-SU
Are you still suspicious
of what Captain Jang did?
You must think…
I'm overly suspicious.
"I wish my doubts were wrong."
I thought that's how you might be feeling.
When you truly want to understand someone,
but you can't…
you end up having doubts.
You can't trust your own judgment,
but you can't help it.
DAD
MISSED CALLS
FROM NOW ON,
ANSWER WHEN I CALL IF YOU WANT
TO KEEP WHAT HAPPENED
AT MOUNT DAEHWA A SECRET
FROM JUNG DU-CHEOL
TO PARK JUN-TAE
Jun-tae.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
Seong-hui,
we should stop seeing each other.
That's the right thing to do.
We should've stopped even sooner.
Is this because of Min-a's dad?
If you're worried about me--
He's my dad.
What do you mean?
Don't worry.
He'll never reach out to you anymore.
-Jun-tae.
-I'll be honest with you, Seong-hui.
I met Choi Yeong-min again yesterday.
After I left?
Why?
I was afraid he might call the police.
I didn't care if he reported me,
but I wanted you to be safe.
So I went to convince him.
But then…
This was near the redevelopment site
around the estimated time of Choi's death.
So there's a chance
she called him there and then met him.
-Yes.
-Okay.
Good. This should be enough
to get the warrant.
Request Kim Seong-hui's live location
and prepare to dispatch.
-Yes, sir.
Ms. Kim, you are under arrest
on suspicion of the murder of Choi.
-What?
-Arrest her.
-Yes, sir.
-Wait.
You have the right to an attorney.
You can request an arrest review.
-You can defend yourself later.
-No.
-Take her.
-It's a misunderstanding.
Yes, sir.
-Take her to the interrogation room.
-Yes, sir.
You met Choi Yeong-min yesterday, right?
Why did you call him?
I wanted to tell him not to call me.
That's why I called him.
Why, all of a sudden?
You had been ignoring his calls before.
You must've had a reason.
You met Choi Yeong-min yesterday, right?
Yes.
With Park Jun-tae?
Yeong-min kidnapped me.
Then he called Jun-tae using my phone.
That's why I met him.
Jun-tae came because of me.
Then what happened?
Nothing happened.
Really, nothing happened.
What time did you and Mr. Park part ways?
What time was it?
What is it?
Park Jun-tae is here.
No.
Make him wait in another room.
We need to interview her first.
Captain. But…
Park Jun-tae turned himself in?
Yes.
He even brought a knife,
saying that he killed him.
Jun-tae was arrested?
What did they find?
Jun-tae
killed Yeong-min.
That's nonsense!
Why would he kill Choi Yeong-min?
I thought you should know,
-so I convinced Jun-tae and called you.
-No…
No. That can't be true.
I saw her.
I saw everything.
That way.
-Go that way.
-Yes, sir.
-You go that way.
I saw everything.
CHOI YEONG-MIN CASE
EVIDENCE: NECKLACE
It's not residential,
so there was no movement for an hour.
But I wonder
why he came back after one hour.
What is it?
I went through more CCTV footage
to see if Park's accomplice was filmed.
A motorcycle?
Yes.
This motorcycle's route
overlapped a lot with Park's car.
I thought it was a coincidence
as they went in different directions,
but it showed up again after an hour.
Do we have footage
from after the incident?
Not yet. We should look into it.
So there are two people.
Good. Keep digging
while we interview Park.
Check the name of the motorcycle
and print a photo of it.
Let's go interview Park now.
-Yes, sir.
Your mom's necklace
had your DNA on it.
He's not answering his phone.
When did he leave again?
He left when we were checking
the CCTV footage earlier.
And he didn't say where he was going?
No.
The day Song Min-a died…
you went to Mount Daehwa, right?
I know
that you approached her
because of your mom.
You told her
you would give her phone back,
and met her at the mountain that day.
"Did you lure her out and kill her?"
Just asked me directly.
Why beat around the bush?
You might be an accomplice
of the murderer who killed her.
Or…
a witness.
What I know for sure is
that you got hit by the car
at the mountain that day
and jumped in front of another car
to make up an alibi.
If I was a mere witness,
why would I do that?
You're right.
That's why I suspected you too.
You can believe whatever you want.
I've been trying…
to put myself in your shoes.
If I were you…
would I tell my dad everything?
The dad who never trusts me
and the dad who lied that…
he didn't meet Mom when he did.
Would I have felt comfortable
confiding in my dad
after everything he did?
Thanks for understanding.
No matter how much you hated me…
you're not impulsive enough
to let that hatred frame you for murder.
Then why did you keep it a secret?
What makes you willing to risk
being framed for murder?
Then I've come to a conclusion.
It's because…
you don't want me to catch
the culprit before you do.
You want to catch the culprit yourself…
and kill them.
Who was the motorcycle rider?
You know
that I won't tell you.
Who is that person?
You can't arrest me.
What makes you think so?
Because the moment I get arrested,
you will be removed
from the investigation team.
Because you know…
that I will find
and kill the culprit at all costs…
if you fail to find them first.
MY DAUGHTER
Release Park Jun-tae.
Or your daughter's life is over.
I'll give you one day.
I did all that by myself.
But the crime scene
we've investigated suggests otherwise.
Park Jun-tae is lying.
You know that too.
When did you start suspecting
Captain Jang's daughter?
You must be Ha-bin.
I'm still scared…
he might hurt Ha-bin like that again.
Subtitle translation by:
Sunyoung Baek