♪The sun rests on the sea♪
♪The sky steals the night and day♪
♪The waves tug at my heartstrings♪
♪That's the petals' curtain call♪
♪The wind is blowing on my face♪
♪I'm stroking the fragile film♪
♪Memories spread under the streetlamps♪
♪The stars linger in the Milky Way♪
♪I've sung every song♪
♪You remember it all♪
♪I cried, you laughed♪
♪You said you would be with me♪
=Six Sisters=
=Episode 1=
(Fall, 1962)
(Tianjia'an,
Favorable Weather for Crops)
(Tianjia'an)
(Mrs. He)
Your dad said he'd pick us up.
(He Jiali, He's eldest daughter)
Why hasn't he come yet?
Forget it. We're not waiting.
Let's go.
(Tianjia'an)
(Self-reliance and relentless effort)
Grandma,
I'm hungry again.
Didn't you eat earlier?
I threw up on the ship.
Why did Mom and Dad come here?
What's wrong with our hometown?
They're supporting national development.
What does that mean?
So we can have food every day.
That's good.
(Chairman Mao's Quotes:
Be resolute, fear no sacrifice,)
(surmount difficulty, and fight for victory.
"Yu Gong Moved the Mountains")
I think we're here.
Jiali, knock on the door.
Be polite.
Anyone here?
This is your home.
Your mom and dad are in there.
Call them.
Dad, I'm Jiali.
I'm with Grandma.
Dad.
Open the door.
Changsheng!
(Zhang Qiufang)
Are you Mrs. He?
Changsheng and Meixin
went to the hospital.
Meixin is having a baby.
My mom told me to wait for you.
Changsheng asked me to give you this.
Look, Dad left it to you.
Hurry, take it.
What's your name, little girl?
Zhang Qiufang.
Qiufang, would you
take us to the hospital?
(Silence)
(Pharmacy)
Changsheng.
Mom.
Grandma's here.
Mom, you're here.
Is Meixin in there?
She's about to give birth.
Put your bags down.
Come here.
Jiali, you missed your dad.
Why don't you call him?
(He Jiawen, He's second daughter)
(He Changsheng)
You've shot up so much.
Dad.
Jiawen, call Grandma.
Let me carry you.
Grandma will carry you.
Jiawen.
Why don't you call Grandma?
Mom, I got my fortune told.
It's definitely a son.
Really?
Great.
Mom, you don't have to wait here.
The keys.
- You take Jiali...
- No, I'll stay.
Let's wait together.
(Model Worker, Reward)
Mr. Tang.
(Big Tang)
I know what you're worried about.
About Changsheng and Meixin, right?
(Zhu Deqi)
My gut feeling is never wrong.
He's had two girls already.
He'll have a boy this time.
Do you think He Changsheng
is that lucky?
From Jiangdu to Huainan,
I've been watching him.
This guy doesn't have what it takes.
(Operating)
Who's Liu Meixin's family?
I am.
Girl.
Changsheng,
it's ok. Boys and girls are the same.
This is the third girl.
What's wrong with my dad?
Nothing.
Meixin, have some.
Skip your recovery,
pay with your health.
Changsheng managed to get brown sugar.
It's hard to get these days.
He cares about you. Drink it.
(Liu Meixin)
If he cares about me,
why hasn't he come back yet?
He said something happened at work.
I know he's not happy with me.
I know he wants a boy,
so do I.
But fate had other plans.
Logically speaking,
boys and girls hold equal value.
Even Chairman Mao said,
"Women hold up half the sky."
It's my fault.
If I had
three or five sons like other women,
we wouldn't be afraid of anyone.
Changsheng is lonely deep down.
We have four daughters.
He is our only son.
Alright, let's say no more. Drink up.
Congratulations.
For what?
For having my third daughter?
(Zhu Laoda)
Why are you still thinking this way?
But look,
I left my hometown for this place.
Without a son,
how can I build a foundation?
Personally, I think
when you
reach a certain age,
you have to accept your fate.
You know, my wife died early.
So once and for all,
I gave up on that idea.
That is
my fate.
Come on.
Finally, you are back.
Look how sweet our daughter is.
She's quiet.
She's too hungry to cry.
Her mom is too hungry
to give her enough milk.
Look.
Here.
I'll get some fried dough twist tomorrow
and soak it for you to eat.
Have you contacted the school?
Jiali has to go to school.
Yes, it's all done.
Just focus on your postnatal recovery.
Don't worry about anything.
He Changsheng, listen carefully.
Don't think you can
pull a long face to me
for giving birth to a girl.
We're a production cooperative.
I'm not running it alone.
Are you clear?
Cooperative?
Sure, got it.
Changsheng,
need a hand?
No, thanks.
He, you're not fast enough.
Sheepskin and rabbitskin checked off.
When will you check the pig bristles?
Can they be stocked before lunch?
I'll hurry. It won't be a problem.
Hurry up
and do it well.
It's like
having babies, right?
You don't just have many of them.
You need a boy
to take over the business.
By the way, I heard
you had another girl.
Yeah, girl.
Congratulations.
Another girl.
How many are there?
The third or the fourth?
How many now?
Three.
Sit down.
Sir, sit down and take a break.
- Incredible.
- Freshly made.
Three.
Why did you make it so hot?
- It's my fault.
- Did you get burned?
I forgot to tell you.
(Class 1 Grade 3)
Let's welcome our new classmate.
(Unity, discipline,
vitality, and solemnity)
He Jiali,
would you introduce yourself?
May I do some martial arts?
Sure.
(Tang Weimin, Tang's first son)
Take the fourth row in the center.
Thank you, ma'am.
Take out your textbooks.
Turn to page five.
Move.
Your martial arts looked amazing.
None of your business.
Which gang are you with?
I'll count to three.
If you don't move, I'll hurt you.
I'll count for you.
One.
Help me! Come on!
I'm not done with you!
Stupid coward.
Mom, I'm home.
Is it Jiali? Get me a diaper.
Yes.
Jiali,
did you get it?
Jiawen.
This...
This is gone.
Mom, I'm home.
You're home.
Dad's home.
What's wrong?
You look distressed.
Anything happened at work?
We're from the same town as Big Tang.
Mom,
you know,
those old trivial matters,
why can't he...
Unbelievable.
We've held grudges against each other
for a long time.
He mocked me again
for not having a son.
Jiali, your dad is home.
Set the table for dinner.
This soup
is cleaner than a monk's diet.
It's been difficult these years.
Hang in there.
It will get better sooner or later.
I'll think of something
and ask Zhu Laoda
to get us more fried dough twist
and a couple of pork coupons.
By the way, today,
I made some lard dregs.
Jiali, go get it.
Go.
Won't you help Grandma?
I'll go.
Nothing.
No lard dregs.
Maybe
the rats ate it.
I'm so forgetful.
I forgot to make it today.
I'll do it tomorrow.
Mom, how can you make it?
We only got a little bit of pork skin.
Won't you admit it?
When you steal food again,
wipe your mouth clean.
I can smell it from across the table.
I didn't steal it!
I just saw it and couldn't help myself.
So you put it in your own mouth?
That's stealing.
It's not stealing.
Then what is it?
That's for your mom.
Apologize to Mom.
What did I do wrong?
Everyone is equal in the new society.
Why does mom get to eat everything?
Why can't we?
Only the landlord class plays favorites.
What are you talking about?
Do you want a beating?
Enough!
It's no big deal.
Changsheng, don't vent your anger
on your family.
Say no more.
Less firewood.
Your mom
isn't demanding preferential treatment.
She gets to eat the fried dough twist,
fermented bean curd,
lard dregs,
and the only egg.
We can only eat pickles, flour paste,
steamed corn bun, and soy sauce soup.
Why?
Because she gave you a sister
and contributed to our family.
Do you know how hard it is
to have a baby?
We should be united
as a family.
But dad doesn't unit with us.
He wasn't happy with my sister's birth.
He has his own trouble.
What trouble?
He just wants a son.
Smarty pants.
You'll understand when you grow up.
I need to eat more to grow up faster.
I don't have enough to eat.
I'll cook you good food
in a few days, ok?
Okay.
I'll apologize to Mom.
Mom,
I'm sorry.
Look.
Your daughter apologized to you.
You should be generous.
Today,
I was wrong, too.
He Jiali,
you're willing to apologize.
Learning from your mistakes,
you're a smart girl.
You're a girl.
A girl should act like a girl.
Don't be wild all day long.
You're our eldest daughter.
You should help out around the house
and help Mom
take care of your sisters.
Yes.
From now on,
whatever you want to eat,
tell Mom and Dad.
Don't steal food again.
I see.
Mom,
may you give Dad a son soon.
Did you teach her that?
No, I didn't.
What nonsense are you talking about?
You do want a son.
Why do you scold me?
(Fortune)
Who is it? I'm coming.
Who?
Where is the suspect?
Give me the suspect!
What suspect?
You...
Mrs. He, look.
His head is broken.
It's bleeding.
We must settle the score.
It's your granddaughter's fault.
She's only been here a few days.
She's like a mobster!
What are you talking about?
Who is a mobster?
That's a terrible thing to say.
What's wrong?
Changsheng,
(Mrs. Tang)
Your daughter hurt my son.
Look.
His head is broken.
You must give me an answer.
What should we do?
Jiali.
Jiali!
Did you do it?
Be honest!
- Not really.
- You're still lying!
Let her talk.
Yes.
They wouldn't let me go home.
They said they'd hurt me.
I gave him a little shove.
He fell over himself.
I don't know what happened then.
Yes, I did...
Don't talk!
Did you hear her?
Did you?
She gave him a shove!
Jiali,
apologize to Weimin.
Why do I have to apologize again?
Changsheng,
this isn't about apologizing.
It could be big
or small.
Today,
I'm going to be frank no matter what.
If your daughter
hurt my son's brain,
what should we do?
Tell me.
How can we still live our lives?
We have mercurochrome.
I think it's just a scratch.
I'll put it on him to sterilize it.
Mrs. He,
it's more than a scratch.
On the surface,
it's a scratch.
But what about his brain?
Is it hurt?
If it's hurt,
who of you will be responsible?
Jiali,
apologize.
I didn't do anything wrong.
They bullied me.
I fought back in self-defense.
Apologize!
I'm sorry.
Be more sincere.
Go shake hands with Weimin.
Come on. Let's make up.
I didn't tell on you.
Look, the kids have made up.
Weimin,
why couldn't you fight a girl?
My son
is always a good student.
He's never fought.
There are terrible people in this world.
It's hard for him when he sees
others have something
that he doesn't have.
Why are you so harsh?
She apologized. What else do you want?
It isn't enough!
I'll tell you what,
I'll get Weimin
some lard for his recovery.
Mom!
Weimin, here.
Lard, to help you get well.
Take it.
- Here.
- Take it!
Alright.
Any aftereffects,
I'll come back to you.
Go.
Remember to bring our bowl back.
Well done.
The lard is gone.
Stand in the yard for the night.
There, there.
Get inside with Grandma.
Grandma, where are we going?
I promised to get you good food, right?
Grandma, what's this?
Is it edible?
Common sowthistle, yes.
Jiali, here.
Later, we'll get some fiddlehead
and fat hen.
They're all edible.
Here.
Don't use too much.
Yes.
Mom, what's this?
Can we eat it? I've never seen it.
Yes, it's very nutritious.
Nutritious?
Not bad.
- Yes.
Look how your sister is enjoying it.
Jiali, don't just eat the food.
Have some soup.
Not bad, huh?
It's pieced together from cloth scraps.
But it's good quality.
Look.
Look at the lining.
Alright, alright.
How about this?
Tomorrow,
I'll set sail.
- I'll ask around when I get there.
- Okay.
But let's get this straight.
This thing
is a tough sell.
It's hard to trade for pork coupons.
You have to be patient.
No, I...
I can wait, but my wife can't.
She is eager to have pork.
If she doesn't,
her heart palpitates.
She says she has no strength
and doesn't feel well.
If I didn't get her any pork,
she would probably eat me.
Alright, you know,
here's a coupon for one jin of pork.
I got it for someone else.
You take it and get some pork.
Your wife's health matters.
Take it.
Okay, it's better than nothing.
Why are you still up?
Guess what I've got?
What?
Undo it.
- What?
- Take it out.
Just one? One jin.
We're lucky.
If it weren't for Zhu Laoda,
(Pork Coupon)
we wouldn't have this.
I'll try to get some more.
Don't worry. If I can,
I'll definitely get it for you.
Otherwise, how can we
run our production cooperative?
Soil fertility is important for crops.
Get out.
It's the seeds that matter.
Mom.
You're back.
Where have you been?
I got in line, but it was too long.
I didn't get any.
What?
Pork.
Mom, I have an early shift tomorrow.
Would you go redeem it?
Sure.
Is it pork? I'll go.
You naughty girl,
what do you think you can do?
She can do it.
She redeemed some other things.
Mom, Grandma, rest assured.
I promise to finish the job.
Come on. Let me see.
(Long live Chairman Mao
Strive for greatness)
(Develop the economy
Cooperative)
Hello, ma'am.
How much is the pork?
Where are you parents?
They'll be here soon.
I came to get in line first.
Here it is. Here's the pork.
In a day,
only ten people at most
can get some pork.
Nine.
Ten.
What should we do?
Not necessarily.
Let's just wait.
Hey,
why are you cutting in line?
We've been waiting for long.
Do you see it?
- What?
- Do you think it's a footrest?
This is my mark in line.
I was here before you arrived.
- It can't replace you.
- I had to go home.
- Got it?
- Got what?
You're being unreasonable.
I was telling you the reason.
She's unbelievable.
I can't believe there's such a person.
That's true.
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
Thanks.
Do you have any more pork?
In 15 days.
Leave, guys.
What should we do?
I can't believe it.
- Let's go.
- Little girl,
why don't you go home?
Sir, is there any more pork?
Didn't you hear me? It's sold out.
Look at how skinny I am.
Do me a favor,
would you?
That's all I have.
Do you want it?
This...
Why are you looking at me?
It's pork, too.
How much does this weigh?
Well,
I've never weighed it before.
How about this?
Make it two liang and write it down.
Next time,
I'll get the other eight liang.
Smart girl.
Okay.
Is it cooked?
Come here.
It smells good.
Have a taste.
No, thanks.
- Come on.
- No, I'm not eating it.
Look.
The pigs are fat.
But why do they get such tiny tails?
Why are you cutting it up?
Season it.
Put it in your mouth
and eat it up.
We must share it.
What a pity.
She went early in the morning
but came back with this.
And she used the coupon.
When push comes to shove,
girls just aren't as good as boys.
Jiali.
Open the door!
- Open the door!
- Who is it? Stop it!
Who?
It's He's first daughter.
Mrs. Tang,
give me the pork you got by cheating.
Who cheated?
Didn't I make it clear to all of you?
Why don't you understand anything?
Go back home.
If you don't give me back the pork,
I'm not leaving.
Are you blackmailing me?
What if I don't give it to you?
It's our pork.
I find your family is funny.
When you couldn't get any pork,
you sent a little girl to harass me.
Fine!
I'll see
what you can do to me.
Mom,
Dad let me come out and check.
He's waiting for you to bring the food.
What a bad time.
Coming.
When push comes to shove,
girls just aren't as good as boys.
Little girl,
do you really want to cut your braid?
Cut it and you can have it.
What I mean is,
it doesn't look good
if it's too short.
I don't want it to look good.
I want it short,
as short as a boy's hair.
Alright.
Okay.
I'm cutting it.
Jiali?
It's really you.
What are you doing?
Why are you sitting here alone at night?
And you cut your hair so short.
I didn't even recognize you.
What's wrong?
Who bullied you?
Say something.
Dad,
do you think girls are useless?
No. When did I say that?
Do you want a son?
Why do you ask?
Yes, I've always wanted a boy. Why?
Boys are different from girls.
Boys
can stay at home.
Girls can stay at home too.
Girls will get married eventually.
They'll join their husbands' families.
I won't get married.
Nonsense.
All girls will get married.
You'll also get married
when you grow up.
How can a family not have a boy?
Without a boy,
the whole family will be bullied.
Dad,
you can raise me as a boy.
I'm better than a boy.
I'll fight anyone who dares to bully us.
I'll protect you,
Mom,
Grandma, and my sisters,
ok?
Okay.
Why did you cut your hair?
Do I look like a boy?
Yes.
You look good.
Really good.
Did you go cut it yourself?
Do you want to go somewhere with me?
Where?
There's good food.
- Yes.
- Go.
Don't eat it all.
When you want to come,
we'll come again, ok?
Okay.
Ok?
You have to ask Mr. Zhu
and see if he agrees.
Eat as much as you want.
I can tell
you're biased.
Later...
Later,
she won many great battles.
At last, Hua Mulan became a general.
- Grandma.
- We're back.
What happened?
Come on. Let me see.
She had lice,
so she cut her hair.
It'll grow back.
There's hair all over you.
Hurry up and get changed.
Is Meixin asleep?
What happened?
She wanted to be a boy
so she could protect our family.
This girl
has a delicate mind.
(Early 1965)
(Never forget the Communist Party)
What are you doing?
Let me help you.
I can do it myself.
The water's deep. You may fall.
Give me.
Let's make a deal, then.
If we get two, one for each.
Ok.
Don't tell anyone.
Whoever says anything is a traitor.
You have my word.
I'm home.
Nice working together.
Weimin.
Why don't you come home?
What are you doing?
I got something in my eye.
Let me see.
Open it.
Do it.
(Tang Youmin, Tang's second son)
Mom!
What's wrong?
Mom, it hurts.
- Mom.
- What's wrong?
It hurts.
What happened to your hand?
What's wrong?
The turtle bit me.
- Give me...
- Where did you get it?
I caught it
with He Jiali.
With her again?
That little devil.
Get up.
Keep an eye on him.
- I'm going to see her.
- Mom, Mom!
Don't go.
- Mom!
- Let go!
Don't go.
- Mom, don't go!
- Let go!
- Don't go!
- Mom!
- What's wrong?
It's He Jiali's fault.
Look.
Youmin's fingers
got bitten!
Did she bite him?
The turtle bit him.
Where did you get the turtle?
I caught it.
You're lying. He Jiali gave it to you!
Turtle?
It's very nutritious.
Where did you get it?
I caught it this morning.
You caught it?
It's real meat.
Of course.
You're what you eat.
What do you mean?
You'll know when you eat it.
You can do it when you eat it.
Mom.
- Who is it?
- Someone is knocking.
(Follow the Party)
(He Jiawen, He's second daughter,
He Jiayi, He's third daughter)
We're from
the Market Management Office.
The people report
that you have a bourgeois lifestyle.
You undermine socialism
- and take the capitalist road.
- Take your sister inside.
Comrade, how can you say that?
We're working people.
- Yes, we...
- We...
- Exactly.
- We are the working class.
- That's right.
- Then what are you holding?
Well...
What's this?
It crawled in a couple of days ago.
When it was raining,
it crawled in through the door.
Comrades,
they undermine
the cornerstone of socialism.
You must arrest these bad guys.
Yes, arrest them.
Yeah.
Don't listen to her nonsense.
It isn't true.
No, she doesn't have any proof.
Of course I do.
Here is the witness.
Son,
don't be afraid.
Say it.
♪Thoughts linger with snowflakes flying♪
♪Warm memories never fade away♪
♪Those past stories and moments♪
♪Find their peace in silent years♪
♪The memories buried deep inside♪
♪Gains or losses, hope you're fine♪
♪Time takes people away♪
♪Leaving their loved ones behind♪
♪What can I offer you♪
♪Mountains, rivers, and clouds♪
♪What can I give back to you♪
♪My heart is restless♪
♪What can I leave to you♪
♪There are no fireworks in the city♪
♪How can I tell you♪
♪Flowers bloom in distant corners♪
♪What can I leave to you♪
♪There are no fireworks in the city♪
♪How can I tell you♪
♪Flowers bloom in distant corners♪