♪The sun rests on the sea♪
♪The sky steals the night and day♪
♪The waves tug at my heartstrings♪
♪That's the petals' curtain call♪
♪The wind is blowing on my face♪
♪I'm stroking the fragile film♪
♪Memories spread under the streetlamps♪
♪The stars linger in the Milky Way♪
♪I've sung every song♪
♪You remember it all♪
♪I cried, you laughed♪
♪You said you would be with me♪
=Six Sisters=
=Episode 33=
Hey, Xiaoling.
Don't touch anything.
The equipment is very expensive.
If you break it, in no way can we pay.
Fine, fine.
This is the employee manual.
It offers the workflow and guidelines.
- Read it carefully.
- Ok.
Later, someone will guide you.
Alright.
Don't worry.
Sharp eyes are my best advantage.
Sharp eyes aren't enough.
You must be patient and careful.
Oh, the internship period is six months.
You must pass the qualification exam
before you're officially hired.
Then...
Is there a salary for the internship?
No, according to the rules.
But Hongyu's brother
knows the boss very well.
He got you a salary.
Enough for meals, anyway.
Jiaxi, you're such a good sister.
Of course.
Xiaoling,
your job
is almost settled down.
Move out of Mom's home, then.
Don't worry.
I've found somewhere to live.
- Where is it?
- It's not far.
Near Jiawen's home.
A small bungalow.
That's good.
Work hard.
- Ok.
- Let's move on.
Sure.
Xiaoling.
- We're here.
- Welcome,
sisters.
This room looks good. Is the rent high?
No. It's a cheap house.
I just pay a little
and I'll take care of the house.
Oh, there's another room.
It's enough for you alone.
Yeah. It looks very big.
Right.
It just doesn't have a toilet.
I need to go out.
Just like when we lived in the north.
Right.
My life is getting even worse.
This one-family house is awesome.
It's quiet.
Well, you guys talk.
I go to the toilet.
Ok. Turn right and go down the street.
I know.
Sit, Jiali. Sit down.
I don't want to stain your bed.
Do you despise this house?
That's not true.
Be seated.
Look at me.
I've got a job.
I have somewhere to live, too.
I can even profit
from the rent difference.
Yes. Your life is back on track.
But Yangyang...
Can you think of a way for me?
When I saw two rooms
and two beds here,
I knew you wanted to get Yangyang here.
This place, you know,
is near his school.
It's convenient for him.
You're always careless.
Now, you can use your brain.
I can always use my brain.
Oh, poor mother.
Thanks.
Alright. Go check it.
Ok, Jiayi.
Please enter the password.
(Checking)
(Balance: 104,000 yuan
Available: 104,000 yuan)
The money is in.
Jiayi, good luck with your business.
From your lips to God's ears.
Now, we're even.
Yes, indeed.
Where will you move?
What? Will you offer a flat?
I live and eat in the hotel.
I even plan
to spend my last years there.
I have no flats.
Here. Take a look.
Don't touch the card
after touching my feet.
That's jinxed.
I love to see the number.
Let me see it. Hurry.
Come on. You'll see it like this.
When you have time these days,
tidy up our home.
Move big things to Xiaoling's house.
We'll take away the small ones.
Where are we moving, then?
Yan Hongyu, what's wrong with you?
To my mom's house.
Didn't we have a deal?
What if Jiali is upset?
Don't be scared.
Problems must be solved.
Sooner or later.
Jiali,
doing laundry, huh?
I have something to tell you.
You go inside.
I'll finish the laundry first.
It's ok. I can talk here.
Xiaoman's household registration
is transferred here.
She'll enroll soon.
In autumn, she'll go to primary school.
Her grandma said
she could live there.
But I think that's far and inconvenient.
I'll be worried
if her grandma looks after her.
So, maybe,
we have to move back here.
Ok.
Jiali, to be honest,
I don't just move back for Xiaoman.
I also want
to share your burden.
You took care of Grandma
in her last years.
You'll take care of Mom, too.
Sisters like us
all think you work too hard.
You've been taking care of this family.
You deserve some rest.
Besides, you should also
take care of Xiaonian's child.
You can't ignore your grandchild.
There's no hurry, Jiali.
We'll move before school begins.
Think about it.
Xiaonian lived here
when he went to school.
Now, Xiaoman will go to school.
How time flies.
This house is quite prosperous.
Just now, Jiaxi came,
officially informing us
Xiaoman would go to school in autumn
and they would move back.
She wanted us to get out now.
Did she really say that?
You must be exaggerating.
That's what she actually means.
Xiaoman will go to school.
That's exactly why
her registration is back here.
I'm not surprised.
The two of us
will live somewhere else.
Don't fall out with them.
When Xiaoling was back,
Jiaxi was really busy.
She offered a lot of ideas.
See? She moved Xiaoling out.
Now, she's kicking us out.
Don't say that.
Jiaxi's request is reasonable.
When she wants
to take care of Mom, let her be.
That's a good thing.
Mom must have pampered her.
Without permission,
she wouldn't dare.
Mom has a big problem with us.
So, we need an early plan.
What plan?
Rent a flat.
How about
we buy a flat?
Shall we live with Xiaonian?
Don't make more trouble.
Distance makes heart grow fonder.
When they got married,
we didn't live with them.
Our son and his wife
will just be relatives
who we sometimes visit.
We will
buy a small flat.
We'll stay there until we die.
We won't move out of there.
That's good.
But do you have money?
We'll think of a way.
What way?
Can you do magic?
I'll get the money.
(Always be alert
Huainan Detention Center)
Dad, did we get the wrong news?
Wait patiently.
When you see your mom,
give her the bouquet spiritedly.
It's been over a year.
Make her happy.
(Huainan Detention Center)
(Detention Area)
♪The sun rests on the sea♪
♪The sky steals the night and day♪
♪The waves tug at my heartstrings♪
Mom!
♪The wind is blowing on my face♪
♪I'm stroking the fragile film♪
♪Memories spread under the streetlamps♪
You've lost weight.
♪The stars linger♪
♪In the Milky Way♪
Go home.
We're going home.
Zhicheng,
take your mom home.
Let's go.
♪You laughed♪
♪You said you would be with me♪
Mom, when you were away,
I studied very hard
to give you a surprise.
Now, I've made progress.
I ranked third
from the bottom in my class.
Now I rank 37th from the top.
What's the truth? Be honest.
Fifth from the bottom.
With persistent efforts,
he made progress, anyway.
A little bit.
Mom,
Dad especially made the dishes for you.
Very delicious.
Jiahuan,
you must have had poor meals lately.
Try if they taste as good as before.
Dad, the wine.
Oh, yes.
Here it is.
Come on, son.
Let's raise our glasses
to celebrate Mom's safe return.
- Jiahuan.
- Here.
Drink the milk.
You're out here.
Don't think about it anymore.
The manager is dead.
It's all over.
Let it go.
But I'm innocent.
Of course, you are.
I'm not innocent
because he killed himself.
I'm just innocent.
I'm not involved in this.
I didn't know what he did.
I really didn't know.
- I'm innocent.
- I know.
I know.
I know everything.
I really do.
It's not too late to leave me now.
Don't be ridiculous.
I have nothing now.
And I'm nobody.
It doesn't matter.
I can't get my old job back.
I can't go back to work.
My previous efforts are wasted.
Everything's in vain. I can't go back.
I've lost everything.
- I'm not what I used to be.
- Jiahuan.
Jiahuan, I said it's ok.
I was laid off, too.
Jiayi and Ouyang rose again, right?
As long as we're alive,
we can start all over again.
So, this is how it feels
to be abandoned by destiny.
My family is gone.
My job is gone.
So is my pride.
I've lost everything.
You still have me.
And our son.
When our family sticks together,
nothing will be a problem.
Jiahuan,
get some sleep now.
In a couple of days,
we'll get remarried.
Why don't you leave me?
I couldn't live
without you.
♪What can I offer you♪
♪Mountains, rivers, and clouds♪
♪What can I give back to you♪
♪My heart is restless♪
♪What can I leave to you♪
♪There are no fireworks in the city♪
♪How can I tell you♪
♪Flowers bloom in distant corners♪
♪What can I leave to you♪
♪There are no fireworks in the city♪
♪How can I tell you♪
♪Flowers bloom in distant corners♪
♪What can I offer you♪
♪Mountains, rivers, and clouds♪
♪What can I give back to you♪
♪My heart is restless♪
♪What can I leave to you♪
- Take it.
- Mom.
It's for you.
It's ok.
Do you think
I'm a loser?
No.
Since you were born,
you've been my smartest daughter.
You are the first
college student in this family.
You're everyone's pride.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Mom, trust me.
I wouldn't do that.
I trust you.
Forget it.
What's gone is gone.
Pretend you had a fall.
Now, you rise again. Ok?
You'll live an ordinary life.
Just be safe and happy.
Right?
You're quite lucky.
Look. Fang Tao loves you so much.
All these years...
Aunt Xiaoling.
Give me a shrimp.
Shrimp, huh?
Don't eat too much.
Have a shrimp.
Give more to Jiahuan.
- Be careful.
- Thanks.
Thanks.
Let's drink.
- Try the beans.
- Ok.
- Eat more.
Jiahuan is free.
Xiaoling is back, too.
Now, we have a family reunion.
Hope we'll be better.
To better days.
- Better days.
- Jiahuan.
- Welcome back.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
Congratulations, Jiahuan. Cheers.
Jiahuan, how did it feel
when you were in there?
Xiaoling, have some pork.
It's really tasty.
Ok.
Xiaoling, you can get in there
and experience that.
I don't dare.
- Jiahuan.
- Eat.
Later, get remarried to Fang Tao.
What do you mean?
Why will you get remarried?
Did you divorce?
I missed a lot of exciting stories.
Xiaoling, have some shrimp.
Here.
We know you have a tongue.
How's your job?
I quit.
- Have some shrimp.
- No worries.
Adjust your mood first.
Then, we'll see.
Get her a shrimp.
- Where's Guangming?
- She doesn't want it.
- Guangming.
- He...
He'll have the exam.
So, I didn't invite him.
He'll come next time.
That's right.
I guess only Guangming
will be successful.
That depends.
All roads lead to Rome.
Which school is Feng in?
I'm in a vocational college.
That's right.
That's good.
We're satisfied.
Let me say something.
Jianguo and I
will move out, too.
Why?
Mom,
what's going on?
Xiaoman is going to primary school.
Jiaxi will move back in.
Yeah. Xiaoman's grandma is competitive.
Xiaoman has to go to HNU Primary School.
It makes sense.
A child
should have a head start.
When Mom is still strong enough,
she can help take care of Xiaoman.
She doesn't need to.
I'll take care of Xiaoman myself.
I'm not moving back to bother Mom.
Besides, I can also take care of Mom.
Hongyu said
we had a responsibility
to take care of Mom.
That's right.
Mom, where will you and Dad live?
How about you live with us?
Mom, our home is the stronghold for you.
Welcome back anytime.
Come on.
Have another drink. Cheers.
- Cheers.
- You guys drink.
Let's drink. Come on, Tao.
Cheers.
Who is she to make you move out?
She knows you have nowhere to live now.
She must be on purpose.
I understand.
Nonsense.
Xiaoman was registered here
a long time ago.
It can't be a sudden plan.
Just a matter of time.
Can't you restrain her as you did
in our childhood?
Why aren't you as tough as before?
You've grown up.
You're even mothers.
I can't restrain you
like I did in childhood?
The problem is she can easily move in
but won't easily move out.
I don't expect her to move out.
I just want her
to take good care of Mom.
Is she actually a caring woman?
Mom brought Jiaxi up. They're close.
If she takes care of Mom
when Mom's old,
that's ok.
We should give Mom some money
in case people gossip.
But you need somewhere to live.
My husband wants
to buy a small flat.
A pre-owned one.
We'll see. We can rent one first.
It's ok.
Jiali didn't say anything.
What would she say?
What could she say?
Her silence was worse than complaint!
She said she'd move out
in front of the whole family.
Why? So, everybody has to take a side.
Listen, Yan Hongyu.
Let's bet. Believe it or not,
this isn't over.
Maybe we can't move back there.
It won't happen.
It won't?
She won't make a scene.
But she'll make someone else do that.
Didn't you see?
Jiawen pulled a long face immediately.
Jiayi looked upset, too.
Jiahuan looked alright.
Maybe she is still confused out of jail.
Think about Xiaoling.
She wants something, too.
You think others don't want benefits?
Maybe they think we'll move back there
for Mom's house
and her pension.
We really want her house, don't we?
No!
I do this for Xiaoman's education.
Fine.
Let's not talk about this.
Since Jiali brought it up,
it's now on the calendar.
Jiali is in the wrong industry.
She should have been an actress.
Maybe she'd be the Best Actress.
Think about her big eyes.
When she stares with tears,
everybody will pity her.
But it makes sense.
I'm sure she thinks
she's sacrificed a lot for this family.
But she didn't expect
she and Mom
couldn't get along very well.
Mom didn't ask her to stay.
Alright.
Say no more.
Stop thinking. Don't go crazy.
Or you'll be too angry to sleep.
Stop thinking. Come on.
(Tianjia'an Civil Affairs Bureau
July 19, 2002)
Come on. Smile.
Ma'am, smile.
Ok.
(Marriage Registration)
I'm qualified to cook for you again.
I can only offer steamed buns and rice.
You don't want steak?
Then, I want sweet bean sauce on it.
(Fang Tao)
(Admission Ticket)
My heart is racing.
Come on. My heart races, too.
You're admitted
to Jiangnan Forestry University.
Jiangnan Forestry University?
Did he apply for that?
Yes.
Ok.
Where is this university?
At the foot of the Purple Mountain
in suburban Nanjing.
So,
it's not far from Sun Yat-sen Mausoleum.
It's a good place.
Yes. Good, indeed.
The air must be good.
Well done, son.
You're going to college.
Very good.
Jiaxi,
you should move out soon.
I'm waiting to renovate this house.
When it's cold,
the smell won't dissipate.
I'm more anxious than you.
Fine. Glad you know what to do.
I should go.
Jiayi, have an ice pop.
No.
I'm too old to eat icy food.
Stop cooling yourself.
Here. Have an ice pop.
Yan Hongyu, are you insane?
Do you think an ice pop will work?
I won't eat it.
It's so hot.
The fan doesn't even work.
I need the air-conditioner.
Don't be ridiculous.
We're moving away soon.
Soon?
You know what?
We'll have to wait.
I gave Jiali a hint today.
But she didn't seem to take that.
No way. She agreed last time.
Don't you know
she's a tough nut to crack?
If she doesn't move out, what can we do?
When tenants refuse to move out,
what can the landlord do?
Jiali and Jianguo
aren't that kind of person.
How long have you known them?
I've been getting along with them.
Mom, you should remind Jiali.
You know what?
Jiali is wicked.
Unless you make everything clear,
she'll always play dumb.
(Pickled Vegetables)
I gave her one year.
Do you know what I suffered this year?
It's so hard to send
and get back Xiaoman.
I can't do anything, you know.
Mom,
now I have to...
I really have to move in.
Look what a mess she has made
in your house.
When I move in, I'll tidy it up.
That day,
I looked in the kitchen.
The oil on the exhaust hood
can be this thick.
It's nearly dropping.
If it drops into the pot,
how can you eat the dishes?
I can't even imagine
how many cockroaches
there are under the stove.
That's true.
Jiali is really tolerant.
The kitchen is really...
If you knew it, why didn't you tell her?
You're tolerant, too.
Anyway, tonight, you will
tell her to move out.
I...
I can't force her.
You won't force her, Mom.
You just won't.
You'll remind her.
Besides,
she said she would move out.
A promise is a promise.
She can't regret it, anyway.
Let's wait.
Fine.
Anyway, if you don't talk to her,
I'll communicate.
Once I start my plan,
I won't just talk.
What?
Will you force them to move out?
People deserve different treatments.
I have to do something harsh
to someone as shameless as her.
It's dark. Stop reading.
Or turn on the light.
No need. I can read like this.
It's cloudy.
It's going to rain.
Get the clothes back.
It won't rain, says the weather report.
The weather changes fast.
The forecast isn't reliable.
Fine. I get it.
- Jiaxi.
- Jianguo.
The kitchen is there.
- Smash.
- They...
Yes, boss.
What are you doing?
Jiaxi, what’s going on?
Did you get these guys here?
Jiali,
Mom wants to have the kitchen renovated.
So, I got some guys here.
What on earth are you doing?
We take orders from the boss.
Go talk to her.
We still live here.
Don't touch anything.
I told you to move out.
Several times.
The kitchen is too old.
Time for a renovation. Smash!
- Ok.
Nobody move.
I said, nobody move.
- Guys, smash.
- Nobody move.
- Stay out!
- I'll call the police!
You may get hurt.
Get out of here.
Jianguo, be careful. Jianguo.
Jianguo, don't get hurt.
What's going on here?
Did you send these guys?
None of our business.
I...
I didn't.
You go out.
Be gentle, guys.
Mom,
sit down here.
Sit.
Jiali,
don't push it.
This is Mom's home.
It's her house.
She can do anything she wants.
She can live with anyone she likes.
You aren't in charge alone.
You know what?
All these years,
Mom has lived a hard life!
This kind of life has to be over!
Enough!
- Mom!
- Mom.
Is this your idea?
- No. Umm...
- Don't press Mom!
Mom!
Let's go.
Jianguo, Jia... Jiali.
- Mom.
- What's going on?
- Go inside.
- Why?
It's dangerous here.
Listen to me and go inside.
Go!
What the heck.
What's going on here?
Stop, all of you!
Liu Xiaoling, none of your business.
Stay out of this!
Mom.
Hope you won't regret it.
What happened, He Jiaxi?
He Jiaxi, are you insane?
Jiaxi, you...
You're going too far.
Mom,
I did all this for you.
Now, they're gone.
You won't be annoyed anymore.
Don't weaken.
Why did we leave?
We shouldn't have left like that.
Jiaxi dared to have the kitchen smashed.
Mom possibly approved it.
We should have left earlier.
That's why things are awful.
No way. I must go back.
Forget it. We're a family.
Don't make it worse.
What kind of family is that?
I can't let it go.
So,
we can't count on anyone else.
That's not anyone else.
That's my family.
And I promised to move out.
Why couldn't they wait?
Let it go, Jiali.
We have to rely on ourselves.
On ourselves?
Jiaxi doesn't even care for her sister.
Why didn't she rely
on herself 20 years ago?
Now, we're old and we're a burden.
So, we're useless.
Don't think like that.
Anyway,
you still have me.
- Let's not compete.
- Did I?
You saw that.
Mom listened to Jiaxi
and let her do anything.
Does Jiaxi show any respect for me?
For this family,
the elders and kids,
I've done so much.
In the end, they don't even respect me.
They even smash things.
Come on. Don't be angry.
I can't accept this.
I really can't.
Fine. I know you feel bad.
Come on, calm down.
Moving out?
Jiayi.
- Jiaxi.
- Here.
Are you moving out?
Or what? Staying forever?
Don't be so angry.
Where will you move?
Home.
Good for you.
What about Jiali? Moved out?
I'm not sure.
Anyway, Mom told me
to move back.
You've finally got permission.
(Huaishun Hotel)
The moment I entered the yard,
I saw Jiaxi
break in with some strong guys.
They swung the hammers
and smashed the kitchen.
Don't worry, Jiali.
I will
definitely avenge you.
I'll pack up and move in.
I'll give her a hard time. I...
No need. Don't make things worse.
Just go to work.
Don't say anything
if you see Jiaxi at work.
Fine. I should go.
I'm getting late. Bye, Jiali.
In my opinion,
Mom is to blame.
Without her support,
Jiaxi wouldn't dare.
When the mother is partial,
the whole family can't be harmonious.
Jiaxi is so terrible.
Without your help,
she wouldn't have come this far.
Yesterday, I couldn't let it go.
But today, I can.
I won't talk about contributions.
I have to admit I'm old.
Jiaxi never cares
for someone so useless.
That's normal.
I'm totally fine
when Mom lives with her.
Jiali,
don't worry.
Whatever happens,
I'll be on your side.
Jiali just moved out?
It's so heartless of you.
I really can't live very well
with Jiali and her husband.
We don't like the same dishes
and we have no common topics.
You have no idea.
Jiali can't get along with me.
She loves to talk back.
You shouldn't have
kicked her out anyway.
She contributed too much to your family.
Think about it.
Since your husband died,
without Jiali,
- her sisters would...
- I didn't
kick her out.
She moved out herself.
I failed to stop her.
Besides, she doesn't care for me.
Her grandma brought her up.
She's never close to me.
It's good to live separately.
Jiali is such a good daughter.
Come on. When she lived with me,
we both felt terrible.
Now, it's good. We won't be annoyed.
I'll put them by the door.
- Jiali is so good.
- Oh no.
- Put them down.
- I'll put them here.
Ok.
There you are.
You're here, Ms. Liu.
Greetings, Ms. Liu.
So, you're moving back?
Yes, I'm moving back.
My mother asked me to move back.
She can live with anyone she wants.
- It's convenient for Xiaoman.
- Yeah.
Ms. Liu, come visit us often.
Ok.
I'm going to Shanghai soon.
You're so blessed.
I should go.
Already?
- Fine.
- Be nice to your mom.
Take good care of her.
Don't worry. She will.
Rest assured.
- Leaving?
- Yes.
Be careful.
- See you, Ms. Liu.
- We'll talk later.
This old woman
always gossips in someone else's home.
- Not at all.
- She gossips about everyone.
Glad you're going to Shanghai!
In this case, neighbors will be quiet.
Shh. She hasn't gone very far.
Why are you being too harsh?
Am I being harsh? I don't think so.
Luck keeps changing.
Time for my luck to change.
Jiali can live here. So can I.
Mom,
what do you like to eat?
Hongyu will go buy it.
We'll celebrate.
Jiali, Jianguo.
What do you think?
I think it's a good flat.
It's cheap, you know.
The furniture is ready.
- Live here for now.
- Another room?
Yes. A bedroom in there.
Good. Good place.
Thank you, Xiaoling.
Jiali,
I'll always be on your side,
whatever happens.
Jiaxi is awful.
Forget it.
What's gone is gone.
Fine. You get some rest.
I should go.
Here's the key.
- Ok.
- Bye.
Bye, Jianguo.
Take this.
Is this your secret money?
Kind of.
(Certificate of Deposit)
Hey, Zhang Jianguo. How dare you?
You saved money under my nose.
I...
When Xiaonian got married,
I realized we needed a backup plan.
When we are old,
if we fall sick or something,
the money will help.
Now, it will help.
Look around.
We need a home, after all.
Is there more?
No.
No, indeed.
♪Thoughts linger with snowflakes flying♪
♪Warm memories never fade away♪
♪Those past stories and moments♪
♪Find their peace in silent years♪
♪The memories buried deep inside♪
♪Gains or losses, hope you're fine♪
♪Time takes people away♪
♪Leaving their loved ones behind♪
♪What can I offer you♪
♪Mountains, rivers, and clouds♪
♪What can I give back to you♪
♪My heart is restless♪
♪What can I leave to you♪
♪There are no fireworks in the city♪
♪How can I tell you♪
♪Flowers bloom in distant corners♪
♪What can I leave to you♪
♪There are no fireworks in the city♪
♪How can I tell you♪
♪Flowers bloom in distant corners♪