♪The sun rests on the sea♪
♪The sky steals the night and day♪
♪The waves tug at my heartstrings♪
♪That's the petals' curtain call♪
♪The wind is blowing on my face♪
♪I'm stroking the fragile film♪
♪Memories spread under the streetlamps♪
♪The stars linger in the Milky Way♪
♪I've sung every song♪
♪You remember it all♪
♪I cried, you laughed♪
♪You said you would be with me♪
=Six Sisters=
=Episode 10=
No, no.
Let me tell you.
Your hip needs
to be pushed up against this bar.
Try it.
It's easier this way.
Right, right.
In a moment, you go prepare
six poached eggs.
Looks like your dad really likes Weiguo.
Jianguo.
Have there been any updates on my work?
Don't worry.
Your sister and I
are keeping an eye on it.
We'll let you know
as soon as there's news.
(Family Tradition: Kind)
Coming.
What time is it?
Why haven't they come yet?
- Don't rush.
- Mom.
Mom.
- Jiawen is here.
- They're here.
Hurry. They're here.
- Jiawen, come in.
- Mrs. Chen.
Come on, come here.
Jiawen's gifts.
Mrs. Chen, this is a gift from my mom.
(Homemade)
Thank you.
Jiawen, come here.
Sit here.
Come on.
Have a seat.
We must be late.
- No, no.
- No.
Weiguo,
don't just smile there.
Introduce us.
Oh, right.
This is my older brother.
Thank you. Hello.
Hello, hello.
My sister-in-law.
- Hello.
My eldest sister.
Hello.
My little sister.
And our big treasure here.
- She's Niu.
- Niu.
Hello.
Aunt, you're really pretty.
Wow, so sweet.
Let me properly introduce her.
He Jiawen,
my girlfriend.
- Got it.
- Really pretty.
Let me say a few words.
Today, Jiawen is here
for the first time.
Let's give her a warm welcome, right?
- Right.
- Welcome.
Can you drink?
- Sure.
- Come on.
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
Alright.
I'm so happy today. I'll drink first.
Mom, drink slowly.
Now, let's drink. Cheers.
Come on, have some food.
Here.
Try the chicken soup my mom made.
OK.
Jiawen,
don't worry.
If you and Weiguo end up together,
I've already prepared
the house,
the furniture,
and the betrothal gifts.
Thank you, Mom.
Mrs. Chen,
the last time you gave us
such an expensive gift.
My mom's been worried
about how to return it.
It's just a little thing.
I'm glad you like it.
No need for any returns.
Don't stand on ceremony.
Come on, eat up. Have some soup.
Thank you.
Well,
the leather is quite good this year.
Weiguo is a fine young man.
He's strong,
sharp-eyed,
and hardworking.
Jiawen really knows how to pick a man.
Who are these leather items for?
You want them?
Well, they're for gifts.
I have to find someone
to take care of Jiayi's job.
It's been so many years.
We've seen a lot of good leather,
but all of it's been given away.
We should keep a little at home, right?
Any progress?
The Art Factory.
Sit.
This year, we'll start
with practicing lines.
Your hand must be steady.
Once you can trace the lines,
we'll start with coloring.
OK.
It's alright. Try again.
Jiayi.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I'm checking if there are cockroaches.
Are you taking me to buy shaobing?
Of course.
No problem.
You've suddenly become generous.
Well, I'm your sister after all.
Let's go.
The salary
Jiayi submitted for the first month
is wrong.
How do you know?
Mrs. Zhang's daughter
next door has the same job,
but she earns more than this number.
We'll talk about it next month.
If everyone were like you,
the national treasury
would've been empty.
Now, five of us are earning money.
Life is much better than before.
Shouldn't we loosen up for the kids?
But we can't start with Jiayi.
If the beam isn't straight,
the rest will be crooked.
Jiayi has always been strong-willed
but has never been able
to stand on her own.
Now,
she can finally earn money.
I bet the novelty hasn't worn off yet.
Let her enjoy it for a while.
We'll see how it goes in a while.
(Special Repair)
(Autumn 1982,
Hengdeli Watch and Eyewear Company)
Look, who's this big star?
So pretty.
It's better to come at the right time.
You bought your glasses
at the right moment.
What's this?
A camera.
I've loaded the film.
How many shots can we take?
You can take as many as you like.
Really?
The background is good.
Alright, go ahead.
Good.
Take another one.
Come on.
Good.
Take another one.
OK, one more.
Good.
Jiayi,
we've never taken a photo together.
No one can take one for us.
He can help us.
Alright.
Let's take one.
Sir,
can you do me a favor and take a photo?
I don't know how to do it.
- It's okay. I'll teach you.
- OK.
Look. After you finish the film,
just press this button.
Just frame us in the shot.
Got it.
Thanks.
Say "One, two, three".
One, two, three.
Alright, one more.
Come on. Let me hold you up to see.
- Take one more.
- OK.
The background is the lake.
This lake is beautiful.
- Come on.
Get ready.
Jiayi,
what are you doing?
Put your hands down.
This...
- Young man.
- It's Jiali, right?
Jiali.
We're taking a photo.
People take it step by step.
But you...
You ran.
Jiali, you misunderstood us.
We were at that eyewear store...
Misunderstood?
Why was his arm around your shoulders?
I...
Where did you get the money to buy this?
Jiayi.
Jiayi, what are you doing?
Why are you avoiding me?
Jiayi,
we're still friends, right?
Just ordinary friends.
Alright.
Ordinary friends are fine.
Jiayi.
(Ouyang)
What are you doing?
I'm not doing anything.
Jiayi, let's not go any further.
I know there's
a really good restaurant there.
Let's go eat.
Do you know him?
- No.
- Liar.
He's just a sunflower seed seller.
How could I know him?
Jiayi.
He's my dad.
I want sunflower seeds.
Why are you hiding from your dad?
I'm afraid you wouldn't like him.
You're such an outstanding beauty.
Ouyang Bao,
is this how you see me in your heart?
Your dad...
No matter how simple,
he's still your dad.
Without him, where would you be?
If you don't acknowledge your dad,
I won't acknowledge you.
Don't.
Dad,
why aren't you resting today?
Yeah.
There's a new movie today.
Hello, sir.
Hello.
Let me introduce you.
This is Jiayi,
the girl I've been telling you about.
The really good one.
Miss,
thank you.
What are you thanking me for?
You've saved my son.
Ever since he met you,
he's improved
and grown up.
You've saved him.
Sir,
I'm not that capable.
If he's offended you,
please forgive him.
As the saying goes,
even a toad has times when it's useful.
With the right guidance,
he'll be a great person.
Don't worry, sir.
Ouyang is a good man.
You raised a good son.
Well, I'll go to work now.
Dad, you go ahead.
Eat some sunflower seeds.
Take some, take some.
It's alright. Take some.
Alright, alright.
Take some.
Dad, I don't want any sunflower seeds.
Alright.
Take more, take more.
- OK.
- Thank you.
I'm going to work.
Goodbye.
Sunflower seeds!
My dad's roasted sunflower seeds
are delicious. Try them.
(Autumn Housing Allocation
for Employees)
Is there any first-floor left?
Who hasn't chosen yet?
Where's He?
I'm here.
- Here.
- Which unit do you want?
Is there still a first-floor one?
First floor?
There are only three first-floor units.
Now, Tang and Zhu have both
- chosen one.
- There's only one left.
I'll take this one.
- OK.
- He, let me have it.
I'm afraid of climbing stairs.
I don't mind
which floor I live on.
But my mom's coming
to live here soon.
She can't walk very well.
It'll be inconvenient for her
to climb the stairs.
Sorry about that.
He will live on the first floor.
First floor.
Third floor, third floor.
- I want the third floor.
Any third-floor units?
Just this one.
Look at how excited you are.
- How is it?
- A little excited.
When can we get the keys?
I want to go inside.
Why rush? The house is assigned to you.
It's not like it'll run away.
In a couple of days, you'll have it.
Look, that's a bedroom over there,
and this is the living room.
Right.
- I'll draw it for you.
- Where's the kitchen?
Here, look.
This is our house.
This is the entrance door.
When you come in, on the right side
is the bathroom.
Look, next to the bathroom
is a room facing the living room.
- I don't understand.
- This side is...
That is
a bedroom too.
It has three bedrooms
and one living room.
So many rooms.
How should we divide them
among the girls?
That's just
up to you.
You can arrange it however you want.
Finally, this day has come.
There's a yard at the front and back.
I'll plant roses
and jasmine flowers there.
Jasmine smells so good.
I'll also plant sunflowers.
Stop dreaming.
Mom said the yard should be
for raising chickens.
Will the outhouse be inside the house?
So we don't have to go out?
Look at you.
It's not a sitting toilet.
It's a squat toilet.
The main issue is...
How are we going to live there?
I'll say it first.
I'll share a room with Jiawen.
Why? I'll share a room with Jiawen.
You can live with her.
We're born with an order.
It's all settled.
I'm naturally close to Jiawen.
Why are you jumping ahead of me?
So what?
Jiawen, who do you want to live with?
I'm fine with anyone.
Anyone can live with me.
Don't say that.
You have to make a decision.
Jiawen.
I need to tell you
an important fact in advance.
Jiahuan's feet stink.
That's slander.
How about this?
You stop fighting.
I'll live with Jiawen.
- You're the 5th.
Anyway, Jiawen's bed
is already mine.
I'm closest to Jiawen.
Oh, really?
Everyone knows your little thoughts.
You just want to wait
until Jiawen gets married
and you'll have a big room
all to yourself.
What a dirty thought.
I've never thought that.
Then why are you explaining?
What am I explaining?
Why are you arguing?
Dad.
I can hear you all the way from here.
Dad, they're discussing
how to arrange the rooms.
That's right, Dad.
You have to make the decision.
Ask your mom about it.
Let her arrange it.
Mom doesn't care.
Then how do you want to live?
I'll live with Jiawen.
No, I'll live with Jiawen.
We both love reading, right, Jiawen?
I won't live with Jiahuan.
Who wants to live with you?
- Who wants to live with you?
Look, look.
This is why you can't discuss things.
It always gets messy.
What are you saying?
We're all family.
Are you enemies?
How about this?
Jiawen and Jiayi share a room;
Jiahuan and Xiaoling share a room.
Then we'll put the bunk beds
in Jiahuan and Xiaoling's room.
Who sleeps on the top bunk?
You sleep on the bottom.
Why? I want to sleep on the top.
I'm afraid she'll dirty my bed.
How about this?
We'll make you a big room on your own.
You'll sleep on one bed by yourself.
From now on, you'll be in charge.
Why are you laughing?
(Moving Celebration)
(Unit 2)
- Done.
- Great.
Alright.
Our new house.
Come down.
- Let's go inside.
- Lead the way.
Let's go.
(Unit 2, Moving Celebration)
(Harmony)
You've started.
- Weiguo.
- Try the Chen-style braised pork.
Good job, Weiguo.
- It's nothing.
- You surprised me.
I don't know if it suits your taste.
- Sit.
- Weiguo.
Jiawen is going to have a good life.
Mom.
Jiawen has always known
how to take advantage of situations.
Good job.
Hurry.
Eat your meal.
- It's okay.
- What do you mean?
Eat more.
Jiawen is the most sensible one.
She knows how to care for others.
Someone like her
will have a blessed future, right?
You all
should learn from Jiawen.
- Weiguo.
- I'll drink to you.
I think the girls
are all quite sensible.
Yes, yes.
Weiguo.
Welcome.
Thank you, Jiali.
Come on.
- Jianguo.
- Jiawen.
Jiali.
I wish you both the best.
You drink it yourself.
What do you think?
What do you mean?
How did I do today?
Honestly,
I was so nervous today.
I didn't notice you were nervous.
You look like an old hand.
An old hand?
My hand was sweating.
I was worried
I'd say something inappropriate.
You were acting.
It wasn't acting.
I just acted naturally.
You know me.
I'm absolutely true to myself.
Jiawen,
I've made up my mind.
If we're together,
your parents will be my parents,
and your sisters will be my sisters.
I'll treat them with all sincerity.
Go back now.
Jiawen,
do you think we can
take this relationship a step further?
I'll go back now.
Go back.
I don't know
the customs in your hometown,
so I went ahead and prepared some.
Consider it
as a proper betrothal gift for my son.
I hope you can grant their wish
and wish them a long
and happy marriage.
You...
You're too kind.
Also,
if you find
anything lacking,
just let me know.
I'll fix it right away.
Let's pick a date then.
Right.
You and Jiawen's dad can discuss it.
It would be best
to pick a lucky day.
It must be a lucky day.
How many times have you counted?
It's a thousand.
You can count a hundred more times,
and it's still a thousand.
A thousand.
I didn't expect
they'd give so much.
This isn't much.
I gave birth to her.
We've raised her for so many years.
What's more,
we have to prepare a dowry.
Are you marrying off a daughter
or selling one?
The amount they give
represents the respect
they have for Jiawen.
So what?
Our efforts aren't worth anything?
You...
I think you're only thinking
about the money.
You don't want it?
If you don't want it, I'll take it.
What about the dowry?
What about it? Isn't it ready?
They gave a thousand.
The dowry we prepared
isn't decent enough.
Then why did you just accept it?
When she gave it to me,
how did I know it was so much?
When you hold it,
you can feel the weight.
You feel it?
Oh, no.
Now what do we do?
I think
we have to give them a big item.
What big item?
How about buying a TV?
We don't even have one.
Let's buy it.
Let's buy two.
You decide, really.
Let's buy it.
Really?
Our family is getting a TV soon.
(In Service)
Mom, can I open a savings account?
What do you need that for?
I want to earn interest.
Do you have money for that?
Yes, I have my New Year's money.
Clever.
Alright, I'll have Jiawen teach you.
How can I work at the Savings Office?
Here?
You'll probably need
to be an accountant.
So, how do I become an accountant?
Learn arithmetic.
I can do arithmetic.
What's seven plus seven?
14. That's too easy.
OK, let's try something harder.
109 plus 283.
392.
Not bad, girl.
Let's do more.
56 times 63.
3528.
86 times 105.
9030.
You're good, He Jiahuan.
Didn't realize you're a genius.
You'll definitely be an accountant.
What are you doing?
Studying.
Did the teacher ask you to do this?
I'm studying myself.
I have to learn this in college.
You're going to college?
Aren't you?
Not sure, maybe I'll work first.
The Gaokao is the best way out
for people like us.
I won't. I want to be an accountant.
There's an accounting major in college.
Really?
Why would I lie to you?
This is for you.
This is the Qiulin brand radio,
the first one in the entire universe.
Jiawen, look.
These are all the gifts
from your in-laws.
You should keep them.
Mom, these are for you and Dad.
- I can't take it.
- We don't keep them.
All for you.
After you marry Weiguo,
the family expenses will only increase.
You should keep something for yourself.
Look at this.
Your in-laws said these bracelets
were from the Palace
of the Qing Dynasty.
They're worth something.
Mom.
Weiguo is a good child.
I'm at ease
with you marrying him.
Live well.
Let's talk about it.
How much is everyone
preparing for Weiguo's wedding?
Kesi, you go first.
Mom,
simple and frugal is a fine tradition.
When we got married...
Just tell me.
300.
Not enough.
500.
Well.
We'll give 500,
like Kesi.
You have kids,
so you'll need more money.
300.
Mom, how much should I give?
That's settled.
You may leave.
Be careful with family relations.
Mom has told me.
Your future brother-in-law and his wife
aren't easy to deal with.
Your future sister-in-law
and her husband
are also living at home
with two nephews.
It's all temporary.
Once Weiguo gets a house,
we'll move out and live alone.
How many years have
Weiguo's brother
and his wife been married?
They haven't had any kids?
Maybe it's just fate.
We can't force it.
When you marry him,
you'll have a son and a daughter,
and your mother-in-law will like you.
How will they feel?
What will they think of you then?
That's how important being fair is.
But I can't refuse
to have kids
just to cater to their feelings.
No need to do that.
So, just be careful, okay?
Alright.
Don't worry, Jiali.
I'll be careful.
Go to sleep.
Are you nervous?
No.
Another one is getting married.
It's better when you all leave.
Out of all the sisters,
you're the only one who can help me.
Jiali.
(Bride)
Help me put it on.
Don't rush.
This room will be yours soon.
I'm not in a hurry.
Why would I be in a hurry?
I know.
You've always disliked me.
Since we were little,
you always liked
to compare with me.
But no matter what,
you're still my sister.
So, if you face any difficulties,
you have to tell me.
Jiawen,
of course, I like you.
Now you have to leave.
I really feel
a bit reluctant.
Don't cry.
There's no banquet that never ends.
We all have to go through this.
Don't cry.
Now, can you help me put it on?
Come on.
No more crying.
(Happiness)
(Yunpian Cake)
(Two months later)
(Family Tradition: Kind)
Mom, look.
This is the Huangshan
Guest-Welcoming Pine.
Huangshan.
It's so beautiful.
What about this one?
This is the Bund.
Yes, the Bund.
Shanghai.
The Huangpu River.
What about this one?
This is the Lingyin Temple in Hangzhou.
Lingyin Temple.
Did you make a wish?
I did.
Good.
I knew it.
This trip was well arranged.
Not only did you have fun,
but you also brought back my grandson.
Mom,
we don't know
if it's a boy or a girl yet.
No matter if it's a boy or a girl,
I'll love it.
Rascal, it's your fault.
You didn't tell me the good news.
If Jiawen hadn't reacted,
I would still be in the dark.
You just don't know
what should be hidden from me.
I didn't hide it from you, Mom.
It's still not three months yet.
Once it's past three months and safe,
I'll definitely tell you.
Nonsense.
It's already safe now.
- Yes.
- Right?
Jiawen,
what do you want to eat?
I want some fried dough twist.
- OK.
- I'll buy it for you.
The ones outside aren't clean.
I'll fry it for you.
I was just waiting for you to say that.
Mom, fry some vegetable balls too.
Thanks, Mom.
Jiawen,
eat some fish.
Thanks, Mom.
Be careful of the bones.
OK.
I'll help you
pick the bones later.
Right, let him pick the bones.
That's not necessary.
- Just in case it gets stuck.
- Eat this.
Eat a piece of braised pork.
OK.
- Here.
- Have this.
Eat this.
Jiawen, eat as much as you want.
You're now
our priority protected person.
Priority protected person indeed.
Mom,
Jiawen is amazing.
Weiguo,
you guys try harder and have a few more.
We can also benefit a bit.
Kesi, the kids
will be ours. What benefit do you get?
I mean
you can have more.
If you can't raise them,
I'll raise them with Yimin.
Let's focus on eating.
No talking.
Eat quietly, sleep quietly.
- It's fine, Mom.
- You're an adult.
It's fine.
- Just eat.
- It's fine.
- What's wrong?
- Have some soup.
- OK.
It's Kesi and Yimin's fault.
This is different.
Kesi is anxious.
You know.
He even wanted Chunhua's first child.
That's Chunhua's first child.
Why should she give it to them?
Later, Chunhua wanted
to give them the younger one,
but they refused.
What does that show?
It shows they didn't want them.
After all, it's not their own child.
Hesitating is normal.
I'm telling you.
I'm not going to give them my kids.
Don't worry about that.
I'll stand by you on this.
As long as we don't give in,
Mom won't make it hard for us.
One, two, go.
You're heavier.
Of course.
I'm not alone now.
Go back, or my parents will see you.
I'm not afraid.
I'm afraid.
Jiayi,
when are you going
to make our relationship public?
We don't have a relationship.
You're really not in a hurry?
Your sisters are already married.
It's your turn now.
Ouyang, this is my business.
What does it have to do with you?
Also,
I didn't ask you to follow me.
You insisted on following me.
Right now, we're just friends,
nothing more.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'll wait for you.
That's your business.
For as long as time exists,
even until the sea dries,
I'll wait for you.
Then wait.
(Eight months later)
Jiawen,
I think it's kicking me.
It's moving a lot now.
So naughty.
What do you feel now?
I just feel like there's extra flesh
in my belly.
It's almost time.
Chunrong, can you give me the clothes
of your kids?
Sure, I've kept them.
OK.
Coming.
Mom.
It's hot.
Slow down.
Here, here.
Mom, I can't eat anymore.
I'm too full.
You're not alone now.
If you don't eat,
my grandson has to eat.
Come on.
How's it?
It's so delicious.
One more bite?
What's wrong?
Mom,
my stomach feels a bit...
Does your stomach hurt?
Do you need to go to the bathroom?
It's cold outside. Use the potty.
No, Mom.
I might...
- What's wrong?
- Maybe it's time.
Hurry! Hurry!
Find a handcart.
Hurry!
- It's time!
- Come on.
Don't panic, Mom.
Don't panic, don't panic.
- I'm here.
- Sure.
Take a deep breath.
Tell me.
Why hasn't anything
happened yet?
You know...
This...
This is a woman's life-or-death moment.
Mrs. Chen, come here.
(Labor Ward)
Sit down.
Do you want walnut cakes?
You keep pacing back and forth.
It's making me anxious too.
(Labor Ward)
(Operating)
- The power's out?
This...
♪Thoughts linger with snowflakes flying♪
♪Warm memories never fade away♪
♪Those past stories and moments♪
♪Find their peace in silent years♪
♪The memories buried deep inside♪
♪Gains or losses, hope you're fine♪
♪Time takes people away♪
♪Leaving their loved ones behind♪
♪What can I offer you♪
♪Mountains, rivers, and clouds♪
♪What can I give back to you♪
♪My heart is restless♪
♪What can I leave to you♪
♪There are no fireworks in the city♪
♪How can I tell you♪
♪Flowers bloom in distant corners♪
♪What can I leave to you♪
♪There are no fireworks in the city♪
♪How can I tell you♪
♪Flowers bloom in distant corners♪