[English subtitles are available]
Try and close your eyes again.
Take a deep breath.
Relax.
Try and synchronise
our heartbeats.
Is this the method you use
when you want to focus?
Who told you to open your eyes?
I won't close my eyes. You always tease me
and take advantage of me.
I'm not nervous now.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I believe that you can surely do it.
There's still some time
before the performance starts.
Make yourself feel relaxed.
I'll watch your performance outside.
P'Thanu.
Yes?
Can you keep me company until
my performance starts?
[I won't care no matter
who approaches me.]
[It's because this bow]
[is the only thing
I care about right now.]
[That's all.]
And, don't forget to thank your friend.
He reported the incident to the school.
If he didn't do so,
the wrongdoer wouldn't have been
punished in the first place.
Tong.
I need to tell you something.
Pok? What are you doing here?
Have you seen Tong?
I need to speak to him.
He went to take a break.
If he's back,
please tell him
to stay here after the performance.
I have something important to tell him.
Okay, I'll pass the message to him.
Thanks.
Did you hear what Pok just said?
Alright.
Our photography session will end soon.
That's right. You guys
can still make it in time.
You need to hurry if you haven't
taken pictures with our actors yet.
That's right. Please make haste.
You guys can still make it in time.
Those who haven't taken their pictures,
please hurry.
You guys can take pictures
with Jack first.
Okay.
Please take a picture with us.
Thank you.
Please hold on.
[Mark: You took a selfie with your fans.
Can you take one with your partner?]
[Kit: You mean this person?]
Oh, P'Jack.
Your performance just now was just like
a movie we can catch in an outdoor cinema
in the village.
Ko!
What's wrong with you?
Are you trying to be a Chinese ghost
with your get-up?
Have you ever seen a Chinese ghost
as handsome as me?
P'Jack,
it's rare for us
to look this dashing usually.
Don't you plan to take a picture
and keep it as a memento?
Hey!
You just want to
take a picture with me, right?
You must be out of your mind.
I was just passing by.
And I saw everyone taking pictures
with each other.
Just tell me if you want
to take a picture with me.
Stop hesitating. Take out your camera.
You wish to take a picture with me
that badly? Fine.
You're the one who wants
to take a picture with me.
Yeah, whatever you say.
Stop forcing me. Come on.
Hey!
Mark!
Hello.
P'Ko, P'Jack, what were you guys doing?
It's Jack-Ko.
Oh, okay.
I saw that you guys were
taking pictures together just now.
How about letting me be your photographer?
I'll make sure you guys
look great in the pictures.
It'll look sweet, okay?
Okay?
No one cares about that.
Precisely. Mark, are you out of your mind?
Who wants to take a picture with him?
If so,
suit yourself then. I'll make a move now.
Did you take the selfie just now?
I did.
Send it to me.
Okay.
Wayu, it's time to perform.
Are you ready?
For our next programme,
it's interesting,
and it's a huge production.
That's right. Let's not waste any time.
Please enjoy "The Land of Dreams".
This best scene comes from a fairy tale.
P'Thanu,
come here. We can enjoy the performance
best from this angle.
-P'Mark, let's take a picture together.
-Come.
One, two....
Like this.
Oh.
Yee.
One, two, three.
Another one.
Thumbs up.
Again. Like this.
One, two....
Smile.
Like this.
Okay.
Thank you.
P'Thanu, I did it.
Did you see that?
You were amazing.
Wayu, let's take a walk.
Okay.
Let's go.
Phai, we will be performing soon.
I'm so nervous.
Yeah, I'm nervous too.
Pok, are you okay? It'll be our turn soon.
Three of you, come here and wait.
Okay.
Good luck.
Pok, it's time to go.
These are jasmine.
Yeah.
Can we take a picture with you?
Sure.
One, two, three.
Thanu, come and help us out.
We have encountered a problem backstage.
Erm.
Okay?
Hurry up. We're in a hurry.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
What's going on?
The lights were still working
during our final rehearsal.
Now, some of them are faulty.
We don't know what's wrong
with them either.
We're trying to solve this situation too.
Please give us some time.
Yuki,
what are you doing?
I'm going to examine the circuits.
No need for that.
I asked a professional to help us out.
Just leave it to me.
You don't need to worry.
-Jew, I'll be counting on you.
-Okay.
I don't know where P'Thanu went.
You're amazing.
Both the spotlight and backlight
are working now.
This side should be fine now.
Thanu, what about your side?
This side should be fine as well.
Okay, this side is fine.
[Good, very good.]
[We still have one last side to check.]
[Thanu,]
[ask Kim to check the last side.]
[Ask him to check
if the circuits are working.]
Okay, my friend.
P'Thanu.
P'Thanu, are you here?
Yes, I'm here.
Be careful. Don't fall.
I was worried about you
when you went missing just now.
How did you manage to find me then?
P'Yuki told me about your location.
Are you done with this side?
This side is fine now.
I need to check the other sides as well.
The lights will be able to work
after I do so.
Let's head to another place.
This place is unsafe.
Okay.
Let's go. Follow me.
[One Night]
Thank you, P'Thanu.
Without you,
I wouldn't be able to
successfully fire the arrow.
I just boosted your confidence.
That's all I did.
Sorry for not keeping my words.
We promised each other before
that we won't let go of each other
no matter what happens.
Me too.
I also thought that I could
endure it and wait.
I thought I could wait until the day
when we could be together again.
But now, I know
that I was wrong.
I will never let go of you again.
Okay, P'Thanu.
I was an idiot.
I only cared for P'Pa's feelings,
even though I knew how I felt about you.
In the end, everyone was hurt
because of me.
I'm sorry.
Wayu,
don't blame yourself.
Just forget all of those, okay?
Just forget them.
You just need
to remember that we love each other.
Remember, you're the only one I love.
Very good.
Look over here.
I would like to thank you all
for helping us out.
-Thank you.
Thank you, Jew.
It's not my credit alone.
This is the fruit of everyone's labour.
Hmm.
Where's Thanu?
I heard that he came to help out too.
I haven't thanked him yet.
Oh, he went back because
he has something important to do.
Thank him for me.
Okay.
Wayu, P'Thanu.
What's with you two?
P'Kit.
I was wondering why P'Thanu
wasn't looking after the booth.
Sorry, Kit.
Please allow me to leave early tonight.
It's fine. I understand.
I'll return to the booth first.
Goodbye.
This is where they take pictures
with all the Inter.Groom participants.
I see.
Many people came here to take pictures
with the Thai groom.
But, I only wish to take pictures
with one person.
Haven't you thought of taking a picture
together with me?
I didn't bring any money with me.
If it's you, you can repay me
the money in another way.
I'll put this on your tab first.
I'll pay you next time.
Excuse me, Pee.
Can you take a picture for us?
Okay.
Show me a sweet pose.
How about hearts?
Arm in arm.
Let's take one with your arm
around his shoulder.
Can your face be closer to his?
Closer.
And then...
Pee, that's enough.
Thank you.
Let's take a walk.
Okay.
Tong,
can you listen to
what I have to say first?
I just wish to apologise to you.
I finally understand now.
Everything you did was for my sake.
I was a selfish idiot.
I'm really sorry.
Tong,
we've been through so much together.
If I beg you right now...
I'll make a move first.
Tong,
can you please give me another chance?
Tong.
How do you feel? Are you tired?
No. I just felt nervous.
My leg was shaking just now.
But, you did great.
I watched your performance.
Thank you, Sandee.
I wonder if Tong is willing
to speak with Pok?
I don't think this can be resolved
within a short period.
But, if they truly love each other,
they won't stay angry for long.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Let's try and persuade Tong, okay?
Only then, he can understand
where Pok is coming from.
Are you a wizard or Cupid himself?
Wayu, let's go back.
I'll send you back.
Okay.
Give me your bag.
Come.
[Mark: You were standing at the booth
all the time.]
[Mark: Many people
took pictures with you.]
[Kit: Are you worried or jealous?]
[Mark: Jealous.]
[Mark: And worried as well.]
[Kit: Where are you right now?]
[Mark: I'm resting backstage.
I'll get changed in a minute.]
[Kit: I'll head back first.]
[Mark: Okay.]
Thank you for everything today, P'Thanu.
So, see you tomorrow.
Do you wish to use the washroom
before you head back?
Okay.
I made you coffee, P'Thanu.
Thank you.
I'll go and remove my makeup first.
I can't even recognise myself
with such thick makeup.
I'll remove my makeup first.
Okay.
P'Thanu, can you bring me the white towel?
Thank you.
Is the music box broken?
That's right. It fell to the ground.
After that, there's no sound.
I'll send it for repair then.
By the way, P'Thanu,
don't forget to take back the
stained shirt you left here last time.
I washed it for you.
P'Thanu?
Seems like my shirt is dirty again.
I'm afraid you have to
wash it for me again.
It's getting late.
Do you need to head back?
Do you want me to head back?
I'll head back first.
Come to my house for a meal tomorrow.
I'll fetch you.
See you tomorrow.
You should head back now.
Drive safely, okay?
Goodbye.
[P'Kit]
Hello, P'Kit.
Just now, I...
Is that true, P'Kit?
Okay.
I'll head there tomorrow morning.
P'Pa.
P'Kit.
How's P'Pa?
He has lost consciousness
since last night.
His blood pressure has been
constantly decreasing.
Wayu,
do you know this?
He chose to give up on his treatment.
What? He gave up on his treatment?
[I write this letter of agreement]
[while I am still conscious.]
[This is my will.]
[According to Act 12 of the
2007 National Public Health Act,]
[please let me pass away in peace,
in a natural state,]
[and with dignity.]
[During the last moment of my life,]
[there's no need to use any machines
or unnecessary treatments]
[to prolong my lifespan.]
Is that true, Kit?
I'm going to speak to him.
I won't allow him to do so.
P'Thanu, P'Kit,
let's cheer for him.
He mustn't give up just like this.
We can visit him when he's awake.
Pa is gone!
He has decided
to leave in peace.
Pa, I'm here.
I'm here to keep you company.
You don't need to worry anymore.
P'Pa.
Wayu.
Wayu,
sing a song for me.
♫ Once, I met someone
who brought me happiness ♫
♫ Once, we were beside each other
all the time ♫
♫ But, our love didn't last forever ♫
♫ Once, life made us
took diverging paths ♫
P'Pa!
P'Kit!
♫ You and I were never apart ♫
♫ Still standing in my memories,
cheering for you with a smile ♫
♫ If life is but a dream ♫
♫ I'm happy that we once met each other ♫
[Now, I'm yours.]
[We will stay beside each other
and take care of each other,]
[just like how an arrow needs the wind.]
♫ I don't know what made me fall in love ♫
♫ I don't know why,
but my heart is shaking ♫
♫ Even though I saw your silhouette ♫
♫ I couldn't see clearly who was
walking towards me ♫
♫ The only thing I know ♫
♫ Is that I fell for you ♫
♫ Just like that ♫
♫ Because it's you ♫
♫ What do you want to do? ♫
♫ What do you want from me? ♫
♫ Why did I fall for you? ♫
♫ I fell for you without any reason ♫
♫ I'll be satisfied
as long as you're here ♫
♫ I feel happy ♫
♫ When I can see you ♫
♫ And listen to your voice ♫
♫ I miss you without any reason ♫
♫ Whenever I close my eyes ♫
♫ You appear in my heart clearly ♫
♫ I don't know why ♫
♫ And I don't know how to control it ♫
♫ Just let it be ♫
♫ Because I don't need
a reason to fall for you ♫
♫ No one ordered me to love you ♫
♫ I didn't fall for you on purpose ♫
♫ It was an accident ♫
♫ The closer I am to you ♫
♫ The closer I can see your eyes ♫
♫ The more satisfied I'll be ♫
♫ The only thing I know ♫
♫ Is that I fell for you ♫
♫ Just like that ♫
♫ Because it's you ♫
♫ What do you want to do? ♫
♫ What do you want from me? ♫
♫ Why did I fall for you? ♫
♫ I fell for you without any reason ♫