[The snowflakes on the seventh night bloom and wither. Like a short reunion and a permanent separation.]
[Snowy Night Timeless Love]
[Episode 4]
[Winter Hall, Apothecary Valley]
Chief Xue.
I've come here today
specifically to thank you.
Saving lives is what healers do.
Besides, you've already paid me.
There's no need to thank me again.
You only accepted payment for one.
But you saved not only Mo
but also my junior
and me.
In the past,
I indeed misunderstood you
and thought you were mercenary, heartless,
and indifferent.
But when I saw you put your life at risk
to save Mo in the ice cave,
I knew I was wrong.
All these things have made me realize
that although you appear cold,
you're actually
warm-hearted and caring.
If it weren't for you,
I would've been a pile of ashes by now.
Also,
earlier, you mentioned to me
an ancient prescription for treating Mo.
I suppose it must have been hard
for you to obtain it.
Anyway,
thank you very much.
I don't think you're here to thank me.
You just want the prescription.
I'm truly grateful,
but it's also true…
that I want the prescription.
You told me
that after I fully recovered,
you'd give me the ancient prescription.
I wonder if you can give it to me now.
Wait until tomorrow.
Thank you, Chief Xue.
These five things
are all rare medicines.
They're all so valuable
that everyone in the martial world wants to get them.
With just one of them,
a cultivator
can greatly increase their inner strength,
and a sick person
can recover like a miracle.
But I don't know if this prescription
can really work.
If it can save lives,
then it definitely works.
Moreover,
you didn't save just one person
but three.
Mr. Seven.
Ms. Qiushui.
Chief Xue.
This prescription
is recorded in ancient books.
Perhaps it was just
a whimsical scribble by the ancients.
No one has ever tried it before.
I don't know if it'll work.
Chief Xue,
just give me the prescription.
To save Mo's life,
I'll try my best.
This is the prescription for the Five Golden Pill.
It requires the Seven-Leaf Fungus
from the Holy Lake of the Moon Sect,
the Azure Phoenix Flower from the White Cloud Palace,
the Dragon's Tongue
from the cliffs of Mount Jun in Dongting,
the Snow Poppy from the Qingling Snow Mountain,
and the ten-thousand-year Dragon Blood Frost Pearl.
These things
are all rare and incredible medicines.
They definitely have reviving power.
Don't get too excited yet.
These five medicines
are scattered far across the world
and extremely difficult to obtain.
Moreover, these five medicines
are all treasured possessions
of different sects in the martial world.
Obtaining them is hard and dangerous.
Even if I needed to go to the ends of the earth
and brave all dangers,
I'd still get them.
Think twice.
If you take them by force,
you'll make enemies
with those sects.
You'll then be targeted
by a lot of people.
Your life will be in danger.
As long as I can save Mo,
I don't mind fighting against the world
or even losing my life.
Death is the easiest.
It ends everything.
But with each medicine you get,
you'll become more hopeful.
I fear you might successfully get
four of them
but fail to get the last one.
Then all your efforts would be in vain,
and you'd be in utter despair.
That would be more painful than death.
Now that I have a way to save Mo,
I can't worry about the future.
Since you've made up your mind,
you can leave the mountain today.
Thank you, Chief Xue.
Shuang Hong.
After obtaining those five medicines,
put them in this box
to preserve their potency.
Before you get them,
Ms. Qiushui can bring Mo here
for regular check-ups.
I'll do my best to stabilize his condition.
Thank you, Chief Xue.
Chief has other matters to attend to.
Please see yourselves out.
Thank you a lot.
Chief,
Mr. Seven still has
the Fate-Reversal Token in his possession.
He hasn't left the valley yet.
I'll go retrieve it now.
Wait.
We can wait to retrieve it
until he gathers all those five medicines.
How long will that take?
Three years? Five years?
Yeah.
How long will it take?
Huan.
It's cold outside.
Get in the carriage with Mo.
I need to have a word with my senior.
Yes, Madam.
Careful.
Senior.
Obtaining those medicines will be difficult.
You must be very careful.
I'll go to the Moon Sect
to get the Seven-Leaf Fungus first.
It shouldn't be too dangerous.
Junior,
after you return,
take good care of Mo.
I've told other juniors
to look after you and your son.
Senior.
I'm not returning to the Sword Sect.
Being back there would only bring back painful memories.
Then where are you planning to go?
Chonghua has a house in Guazhou.
The climate there is pleasant.
I've thought it through.
I'll take Mo there for recuperation.
Senior,
you made a promise to Chonghua,
but you can't take care of us
for a lifetime, can you?
You'll eventually marry and start a family.
You'll have your own children too.
Mo and I
need to have our own home as well…
Junior,
it's not just for Chonghua
that I'm looking after you and your son.
I also want to repay
Master's kindness in raising me.
You and I
grew up together in the Celestial Alp Sect.
Between us,
isn't there also
the bond of fellow disciples?
Before Mo fully recovers,
I won't be selfish
and think about anything else.
Really?
You have my word.
Yeah.
You've always been
a man of your word.
If it weren't for you these days,
Mo would probably have died already…
Don't worry.
I'll gather those medicines as soon as possible
to cure Mo.
Senior.
Since Chonghua passed away,
I…
I've resented
and hated you.
I was once so cold to you.
I…
I hope you don't blame me.
It's understandable that you resented me.
Besides, in my heart,
you've always been like my sister.
Why would I blame you?
Senior,
take good care of yourself.
You take care too.
[Longmen Village]
You're back.
Shall we drink tonight?
No problem.
Let's go.
Be careful not to burn yourself.
Okay.
Chief.
Mind the heat.
Don't rush things.
-Okay.
Chief.
Girls, be quick.
The villagers will be here soon.
Chief.
Go distribute the medicinal powder to the villagers.
Okay.
Ms. Li.
Guys,
today, our chief
has prepared
some medicinal powder for everyone.
After the consultation,
go over there to get a bag of it.
Drink it with water after going home.
-Thank you, Chief.
Come over here to get it.
Okay.
Chief is so nice.
Mr. Li.
Take this prescription
and go to the back to get your medicine.
Okay.
Thank you, Chief.
Sir.
What's the meaning of this?
Chief
knows that your eldest son
is going to the capital for the imperial examination this year,
and you've been worried about the travel expenses,
so she prepared this for you.
I can't accept this.
I really can't.
Chief,
for the past few years,
you've been treating us for free,
and you've even built an orphanage for us
so that
those homeless children
can have a roof over their heads.
We can never repay you…
I often see your son
helping the weak
in the village with farm work.
He'll make a good official.
If it weren't for that,
I wouldn't have thought of preparing this.
Besides,
I'm not giving you this money for free.
Consider it a loan.
After he becomes successful in the future,
you can pay me back.
Chief.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you, Chief.
Oh, right.
I almost forgot.
My wife and I
grew these
sweet potatoes ourselves.
They're not worth much.
Please accept them.
Yes.
They're too cheap as a gift.
You're so kind. I'll accept them.
Shuang Hong and the other girls love sweet potatoes.
But please don't do this again.
In the Apothecary Valley,
we have everything we need.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
Go get your medicine.
Let's go.
Okay.
Miss.
Don't worry.
Ms. Li just caught a cold.
Make a decoction according to this prescription
and take it three times a day.
Make sure to get enough rest
and try not to worry too much.
Here are the herbs.
I've already packed them for you.
Okay.
Thank you. Let's go.
Let's go. Thank you.
Mercenary and lustful.
Interesting.
It's in the dead of winter.
I told you not to fly a kite, but you still did.
[Ping'an Inn]
Let me see.
It hurts!
What's wrong?
Wasn't she fine just now?
She sprained her ankle flying a kite.
Flying a kite in this season?
Is this your kite?
Thank you.
Let me check on her.
It hurts.
Be gentle.
Hang in there.
You just sprained your ankle.
It may hurt a bit.
Hang in there.
How do you feel, Chu?
Try moving your foot now.
It's much better.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
Alright.
Thank you for your help, young hero.
It's nothing.
This small shop is mine.
Why don't you come in and rest for a while?
No need.
I'm in a hurry to continue my journey.
I won't stay long.
Why don't you wait here for a moment?
Let's go.
Get a pot of wine
and wrap up some
spring pancakes.
Please wait a moment.
I'll be right back.
Just a moment, just a moment.
Young...
Young hero!
Seriously...
What are you looking at?
The Doctrine Leader loves cleanliness and tolerates no speck of dust.
All of you,
clean him thoroughly
inside and out.
Yes.
Step back.
Move back!
Before, you didn't understand the rules.
That was fine.
But today,
since you've entered the palace,
you must follow the palace rules.
From now on, when you see the Doctrine Leader,
remember to kneel and bow.
Don't you understand?
Then think about your good friend,
Lie Xing.
Remember how he did it.
Come in.
[Yuan Yi Palace]
Long live the Doctrine Leader.
Doctrine Leader...
Long live.
Miao Shui.
You may rise.
You have indeed lived up to my expectations.
You are a born killer.
Just four years in the Asura Field,
and you've already fought your way out.
I am willing to serve the Doctrine Leader.
Come up.
Eye.
From today on,
you are the
Yuan Yi Palace's top assassin.
I want to give you something.
This sword is called Lixue.
I've treasured it for many years.
Its blade is thin and light,
cutting through iron like mud.
From now on,
it's yours.
Remember,
it's not for
trimming flowers or cutting grass.
You may go now.
Thank you, Doctrine Leader.
What are your orders, Doctrine Leader?
I need your help
to retrieve something.
The Seven-Leaf Fungus from the Moon Sect.
The Seven-Leaf Fungus from the Moon Sect?
Your Eye Magic
can control others' minds,
but the time is not ripe yet.
Do not use it.
Understood.
Go now.
If he can help me
retrieve that treasure,
I can more quickly
break through this level of cultivation
and enter a new realm.
Congratulations, Doctrine Leader, on gaining such a capable subordinate.
If your skills can further improve,
returning to the Central Plains
and regaining control of the martial world
will be within reach.
However, Eye
has a vicious nature.
I'm afraid...
What I need is precisely
someone truly cold-blooded and heartless.
Right now, he is
the sharpest sword in my hand.
Why did you abandon me?
Child,
don't be afraid.
[Doctrine Leader of Yuan Yi Palace, Chang Wujue]
Come to me.
Who are you?
[Young Eye]
Who are you really?
Come,
come here.
I will help you.
From now on, your name is Eye.
As long as the three golden needles in his body
continue to seal his memories,
he won't remember his past.
Don't forget to specially send
one of them to that place.
Make sure
that person can get the Fate-Reversal Token.
Yes.
[Apothecary Valley Back Mountain Cenotaph]
After all these years,
don't you understand the Chief yet?
She never
lets us interfere in these things.
[Young Xuehuai]
[Young Xue Ziye]
Hurry, go!
Mother!
Catch them!
After them!
After all these years,
I've been investigating
the truth of what happened back then.
The arsenopyrite on this dart
is the only clue.
I hope
that through this clue,
I can find the culprit from back then.
Village Chief,
uncles, and aunts,
I will do my best to investigate.
I hope that one day the truth will come to light
and comfort your spirits in heaven.
Master,
we've arrived at Apothecary Valley.
[Chief of Moon Sect, Jing]
Who might you be?
Isn't it said that Apothecary Valley treats patients
without asking for identity,
and only demands those two things?
Since you've come to the Apothecary Valley,
you must know the rules of Apothecary Valley.
Bring it here.
The Fate-Reversal Token and 100,000 in consultation fee
are both here.
For treatment at Apothecary Valley,
only the patient may enter the valley,
with at most one companion.
Others
must wait outside.
Wait for me at the foot of the mountain.
Chief.
This Apothecary Valley
is a place for treating illnesses.
They won't hurt me.
Yes.
This way, please.
Chief.
Please wait here for a moment.
This beauty before me
must be Chief Xue.
Black clothes with moon ornaments,
and the Nirvana tattoo of the Other Shore.
I presume you
must be the chief of the Moon Sect.
I called you a beauty.
Why didn't you return the compliment?
Not everyone
likes to be called a beauty.
Besides, you called me a beauty without permission.
I'm not pleased about it.
That's my mistake then.
I thought the Chief of Apothecary Valley,
greedy and lecherous,
is surely an old and
ugly person.
I didn't expect
to find such a sharp-tongued
and pretty young lady.
You attack before
we're done talking.
Is this your way
of treating guests?
You just used your skills to dodge,
now your Shenque and Qihai acupoints
should be burning and stinging.
At this moment, your Quchi and Tianjing acupoints
must feel like ice-cold snake bites.
Am I right or wrong?
In my opinion,
you're showing signs of poisoning.
Poisoning?
Since childhood, I've been dealing with
all kinds of poisons.
Disregarding whether anyone
could poison me
right under my nose,
I'm sure I can at least tell
if I'm poisoned or not.
Doctors can't treat themselves.
Although you're skilled in using poisons,
you're often the most likely to overlook poison.
The terrifying aspect of this poison
lies in the fact that
it lingers in
your vital areas,
persisting without an outbreak.
Unlike other poisons
that are fierce and violent,
it's not easily detected.
Look at your neck.
This is...
I've already applied acupuncture
to bring the toxins to the surface.
The faint
Manjushaka Nirvana marks on your neck
is evidence of your poisoning.
As expected of the Chief of Apothecary Valley.
You identified the cause at a glance.
It wasn't in vain that I
went through great trouble to obtain the Fate-Reversal Token
and traveled thousands of miles from Lingjiu Mountain
to this far northern land.
Then please, Chief, follow me inside.
I'll carefully check your pulse.
Alright.
The pulse is tight, rapid, and soft.
It's caused by gu poison.
Though it's rapid, it's soft.
Still treatable.
Who could have done it?
What medicine do you plan to use?
No need for medicine.
I will treat you with acupuncture.
I've traveled day and night to get here.
I'm really exhausted from the journey.
Could I rest for a few days
before receiving treatment?
I have my reason
for using acupuncture.
How about just one day of rest?
If you're not in a hurry to recover,
then you should leave the valley immediately.
How are you
more short-tempered
than me, the chief of a sect?
In this Apothecary Valley,
you are first and foremost a patient,
and secondly the Moon Sect Chief.
I've certainly learned my lesson.
No wonder you can single-handedly
manage Apothecary Valley
with ease at such a young age.
I'll follow your arrangements then.
It's better to recover soon anyway.
I can return to my sect earlier
to prevent any issues
that might arise in my absence.
Start preparing.
Yes.
You're here too.
Take a look at this.
This represents good fortune and wishes.
Is that true?
It is.
Vegetables, take a look.
The Seven-Leaf Fungus
is in the ancient tomb.
How many guards are there?
There are no guards.
You seem quite straightforward.
Let me give you a piece of advice.
It's not too late to turn back now.
Thanks for the warning,
but I must go.
The ancient tomb is located at the peak of Lingjiu Mountain.
It's surrounded by a forest.
Each tree has been watered
with the Moon Sect's unique arsenopyrite.
Thus, the trees are all highly poisonous,
[Lingjiu Mountain of Moon Sect]
forming a miasma.
You must get in and out quickly.
Don't linger.
As for what traps are in the ancient tomb,
I have no idea.
Because many people
have come for the Seven-Leaf Fungus,
but no one has ever
made it out alive.
[Miasma Forest of Moon Sect]
What a strong poisonous miasma.
Sect Chief.
Sect Chief?
[Ancient Tomb of Moon Sect]
Who are you?
I am the Moon Sect Chief,
Jing.
Is arsenopyrite
unique to the Moon Sect?
Yes.
Respected elders of the Moon Sect,
I, Huo Zhanbai of the Sword Sect,
have come today to save a friend's child.
I've come to your esteemed sect
to borrow the sacred Seven-Leaf Fungus.
I apologize for disturbing your rest
and hope you can forgive me.
In the future, if the Moon Sect
has any need,
I will not stop at anything
to help the Moon Sect.
Do you know about
the Mo Family Village in Wuling County?
Do you remember
Mo Family Village...
I remember.
What do you know?
Tell me quickly.
I once heard the former chief
and the priest planning
to attack Mo Family Village.
Over a hundred lives in Mo Family Village were exterminated.
So it was indeed the Moon Sect's doing.
I'm not...
I'm not sure.
How can you not be sure?
Think carefully.
In the fourth year of Huijia,
on New Year's Eve,
in the Mo Family Village of Wuling County,
what exactly did the Moon Sect do?