[The snowflakes on the seventh night bloom and wither. Like a short reunion and a permanent separation.]
[Snowy Night Timeless Love]
[Episode 18]
Xiao Cheng, Lan Lan,
hurry up.
Chief is coming back soon.
Warm up the bed
and close the windows.
-Okay.
-Let's go.
It's broken.
This is Chief's most treasured thing.
She's coming back any minute.
What should I do?
I didn't mean it.
I really didn't mean it.
Alright, alright. It's fine.
I'll tell Chief when she gets back,
okay?
What happened?
-Chief!
Chief.
Chief...
I didn't mean it.
I really didn't mean it.
Chief...
Chief, please punish me.
It's fine.
Chief.
Go after Chief.
What if she does something
out of sadness?
Okay.
Maybe
it's time for Chief
to move on.
Ziye.
Granny.
Shuang Hong
told me about the dead branches.
Watering a rootless plant with Rootless Water.
Master really
played a big joke on me.
Chief Liao had always hoped you
would awaken your inner voice on your own.
She wasn't trying to save Mr. Xuehuai,
but you, who were young
yet had a heart as barren as a dead tree.
The heart of a healer
is the heart of healing.
You were the one who gave that prescription to Mr. Huo.
You should understand
that you can't stop flowers from withering,
just like you can't stop people from facing their fate.
Instead of maintaining Xuehuai's
illusory life,
it's better to keep
the beautiful memories we once shared in mind.
That is the only eternal
and unchanging thing between us.
Master had a good intention.
It was my fault for being stubborn
and not realizing it until now.
Perhaps,
it's not just about Mr. Xuehuai.
This time, to uncover the truth,
Seven almost lost his life.
At that time, he lost too much blood.
I had no choice but to take the Heat Pill,
barely suppressing the coldness,
and that's how I pulled him back
from the brink of death.
I can't let anyone
risk their lives for me anymore.
Over these years,
I've been persuading you
to let go of the past.
Now,
it seems I can finally rest assured.
Ziye,
I'm happy for you.
At this moment,
if we could swap tea for wine,
it might be more enjoyable.
The cliffs are dangerous.
Don't die.
You haven't paid off your debt yet.
Here.
After finishing this last cup of wine,
I'll be leaving.
It's the last medicinal ingredient.
Yes.
It's already the last one.
I don't know if I can
successfully obtain the Dragon Blood Pearl this time.
It might take a long time before I return.
Take care of yourself.
In this valley,
I have the Snow Hail Formation protecting me,
so I'll be safe.
Then, after I return,
you can tell me
what you want most.
After all, I need to repay
the favors I owe you.
You should care more
about yourself.
The Dragon Blood Pearl
is a treasure
that many people will be fighting for.
Use the old soil to grow a new bud.
Plant it by the window.
Watering the new bud
will be like starting a new life.
He went to Mo Family Village.
Mr. Seven is very considerate.
♫As the wind blows and the snow falls, the scent of plum blossoms sighs♫
♫You nestle close, your whisper slow and tender♫
♫In the shadow, the stories of the heart remain untold♫
♫The bright moon in clouds reminds me of yesteryear♫
♫Drifting like smoke, I journey into the long night♫
♫In so deep, I'm trapped in the whirlpool of fate♫
♫In this world, light takes your form♫
♫Not to make my mark, just to make it all worth it♫
♫Traveling through hustle, you became my hope♫
♫Try to hide tears; how can I ever forget you?♫
♫In this world, light takes your form♫
♫Following your direction, together we tread this path♫
♫Joy and tears blurred the line between love and hate♫
♫Eyes reddened, love etched on the heart♫
Thank you, Snow Harrier.
[Ping'an Inn]
You came
at a bad time today.
My wife and the others
have already gone to bed.
With my cooking skills,
I could only heat up some
ready-made lamb for you to taste.
Brother Meng, you're too polite.
It's already quite rare to have a hot meal
when you're away from home.
Come. Sit down.
Let's have a drink.
Today, while my wife
and the others are asleep,
let's drink until we're totally drunk.
Here.
Good wine.
It has been so many years,
but today,
it feels just like
the first time
we drank together.
Yes.
Every time I came here,
I was in a hurry coming and leaving.
Now that I think about it,
time really flies.
You call me Brother.
And I'm
I'm a few years older than you.
There's something
I'm not sure if I should say.
Brother Meng, feel free to say it.
You've been
running around
and worn out.
Even though you never said it,
I could tell
that when you were looking at Tai and Chu,
this young couple, there was
a desire to settle down in your eyes.
So I want to advise you
to think about yourself
and consider settling down.
It's coming soon.
Really?
So this time, will all this running around
come to an end?
I hope for a good outcome.
Great.
I'm happy for you.
The assessment for the Five Sages this year
can begin now.
The Five Sages have assessments every year,
with the last place being eliminated.
The assessments are always in the summer.
Is it a bit early this year?
Ever since the assassination attempt on Nangong Yanqi failed,
everyone has been unsettled.
It's time to keep them on their toes.
Doctrine Leader,
did you notice anything unusual?
The fact that there's nothing unusual
is the most unusual.
Your martial arts are the best among the Five Sages.
During the assessments each year,
you're just playing along with them.
As for the other four,
Miao Shui seems gentle and soft,
but she's incredibly cruel;
Ming Li has mediocre martial arts,
yet he is cunning
and loves to attack when least expected.
As for Miao Huo and Miao Kong,
one is reckless and the other is rigid.
It seems that this year,
one of these two will be eliminated.
I've long grown tired of
these faces.
It's time
to see some new ones.
I got it.
The last one to return
will be replaced.
Go.
Are you crying?
What is your task?
To go to Yunxie Mountain
and take the head of Master White-Brows.
Master White-Brows?
He lives on the ice mountain all year long.
His Ice Palm
can easily
break your Kylin skills in an instant.
You have no chance of winning.
You might as well just die now.
Bah!
I don't believe
I can't defeat him.
Why don't we...
switch?
[Yuan Yi Palace]
Ming Li,
let's switch.
For the sake of
our history as colleagues,
I'll bury you by the Kunlun roses
that Doctrine Leader loves the most.
If you don't know how to talk,
just stop talking.
You brat!
Why are you everywhere?
Aren't you leaving?
I'm not leaving.
Fine.
After all, the last one to return
will be replaced.
[Jiuyao Villa]
Mo.
Uncle!
Let me take a good look at you.
Have you grown up a bit,
Mo?
Here.
What's this?
A pinwheel‌!
Do you like it?
Yes.
Mo,
come and take your medicine.
Senior?
Mo, good job.
Go play.
Be careful.
Senior,
I haven't seen Father for days.
Is Father...
Master is doing well
in the Sword Sect.
Well, is Chief Xue still...
It's all in the past.
Yes.
But Mo often asks about his grandpa.
I can only lie to him and say that
his grandpa will come to see him in a few days.
I really don't know
what I did wrong in my last life
that caused heaven to punish me like this.
My husband passed away,
my child is seriously ill,
and my father has committed a terrible mistake.
-I...
-What happened to Sixth Brother
is irreversible.
The matter regarding Master
has already reached the best outcome.
As for Mo,
he will
definitely recover soon.
As Mo's mother,
I'm the only one who knows
how much he has suffered these years.
Luckily, he has the fortune
to have met Chief Xue,
such a great doctor,
and you,
his caring uncle.
Now
we are just missing the last medicinal ingredient.
We're almost there.
I will find the Dragon Blood Pearl as soon as possible
to gather all five ingredients.
Senior,
once we gather all five ingredients
and Mo recovers,
why don't you move to Guazhou and stay here permanently?
Mo...
Junior,
all these years,
I've been out seeking medicinal ingredients
and have not been able to return to the Sword Sect
to carry out my responsibilities.
Chang Wujue from Yuan Yi Palace
is brutal and evil,
and has harmed many innocent people.
I want to return to the sect
as soon as Mo recovers
to apologize to the chief
and discuss plans
to eliminate Yuan Yi Palace with him.
Now that you're back this time,
why not rest for a few more days?
Mo rarely gets to see you.
He often talks about how much he misses you.
Uncle,
I want to go to the market.
Mo,
you've just recovered from your cold.
You can't go out to play.
But I want to go to the market!
I want to go to the market!
You want to go to the market?
How about this?
I'll take you to the market
and buy you some sugar figurines, okay?
To the market! To the market!
Okay.
Roast chicken!
Did you smell it?
Mo.
Does it smell good?
What are these?
They are buns.
Candied haws!
Fireworks.
Look.
Let's go over there and take a look, okay?
Okay.
What is that?
Great!
It's smoking!
Mo is rarely this happy.
Uncle, I want a grasshopper.
You want grasshoppers?
Alright.
I'll take you to buy one.
Okay.
Let's go.
Butterflies made of straw!
Grasshoppers made of straw!
Take a look.
Take a look at grasshoppers made of straw.
Which one do you like?
Well...
The parents are kind,
the husband and wife love each other,
and the child is adorable.
What a happy family.
I have plenty of little trinkets here,
so feel free to bring the child over anytime
to have a look.
You've misunderstood.
We're not a family.
I'm his uncle.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Senior, don't mind it.
I'm a single mom with a kid.
You've been taking care of us alone,
so it's inevitable that others may misunderstand.
It doesn't matter.
Mo,
which one do you like?
I'll buy it for you.
After that,
let's head back, alright?
Alright.
Okay. This one.
Senior,
I heard a traveling doctor has come to town recently.
Later, I want to take Mo
to see him.
Junior.
It is said that her medical skills are excellent.
We'll take this one.
The patterns of orchid and Lingzhi
on this jade pendant
are exactly the same as those on the Fate-Reversal Token.
Could she also be from the Apothecary Valley?
[Liao Qingran, the previous Chief of the Apothecary Valley]
This illness must have lasted
at least five years, hasn't it?
You can diagnose
Mo's condition?
It's been five years and three months.
The doctor who's been treating this child
has decent medical skills.
However...
He'll recover soon.
It'll be soon.
At the onset of Mo's illness,
he received a diagnosis from a skilled doctor,
who prescribed a remedy
claiming it could cure him.
Sir, could you please tell me
what ingredients
are in the prescription?
The Seven-Leaf Fungus from the Moon Sect,
the Azure Phoenix Flower from the White Cloud Palace,
the Dragon's Tongue from Mount Jun in Dongting,
the Snow Poppy from Qingling Snow Mountain,
and the Millennial Crimson Cold Dragon Blood Pearl.
Doctor,
what do you think of this prescription?
These ingredients
are all extremely rare
and exceptional medicines.
If you can gather them,
they will indeed be effective.
However, I must
give you some advice.
Spending quality time with him
and taking good care of him,
allowing him to feel happy and at ease,
will be enough.
Thank you, Doctor.
May I ask one more question?
Do you know a famous doctor
with the surname Liao?
No.
Sorry for bothering you.
Thank you, Doctor.
Go ahead.
Junior.
You should stop
looking for doctors everywhere.
Normally,
just make sure Mo takes the medicine
that Chief Xue prescribed on time.
There's only
one ingredient missing.
Mo's illness will definitely be cured.
Okay.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
Uncle, didn't you say
you would teach me swordsmanship?
I want to learn.
Senior, you have no idea.
When you weren't around,
Mo kept asking
when you would come.
He wants to learn swordsmanship from you.
Once you're stronger,
I'll teach you, okay?
No, I want to learn right now!
Mo.
Be good.
Stop it.
It's time to eat.
Senior,
I made your favorite dish,
stewed mutton.
I won't stay.
I need to rush back to Yangzhou
to look for the Dragon Blood Pearl.
Is the Dragon Blood Pearl in Yangzhou?
Its whereabouts are unknown for now.
I'll go to Yangzhou to gather some information.
There are many merchants
and martial artists there.
Perhaps there will be some clues.
The meal is ready.
Why not eat before you go?
It's fine.
Mo,
I promise you
that the next time I come,
I will teach you swordsmanship,
alright?
Then let's make a pact, Uncle.
Okay.
Cross my heart and hope to die,
stick a needle in my eye.
Here, a stamp.
These ingredients
are all extremely rare
and exceptional medicines.
If you can gather them,
they will indeed be effective.
I'm back.
Honey, you're back.
Did the free clinic go well today?
Today, there was a child.
He's only six years old,
but has an incurable disease.
However, the doctor who's been treating him
is quite skilled
and has managed to extend his life until now.
This doctor
is on par with my disciple.
Unfortunately, even so,
that child
only has about two years left.
Everyone has their fate.
Didn't we choose to retreat from the martial world
and live in seclusion here
because we couldn't bear to see
the unpredictability in the martial world?
Retreat from the martial world.
But who would have thought that you,
Wei Fengxing, the fifth disciple from the Sword Sect,
the esteemed Mr. Dashing
in the martial world,
would even be unable to farm?
After all these years,
[Wei Fengxing, the fifth disciple of the Sword Sect]
you still haven't reaped any harvest.
I...
I can't farm,
but I can fish.
My Dashing Sword Technique is agile and light,
making it perfect for fishing.
You're using the Dashing Sword Technique to fish?
Have all the fish been sold today?
Of course.
I kept one
for ourselves to eat tonight.
I'd like some crucian carp tofu soup.
No problem.
Go take a rest.
Alright.
[Yangzhou]
[Linglong Flower Realm]
Put it here.
Yes.
Be careful.
Work hard.
Hurry up.
Clean it up.
We'll have guests arriving soon.
Okay.
Mr. Huo, you're here.
We haven't opened
for business yet.
Would you like to go to the private room?
You guys talk.
I'll go handle something in the back.
Why are you here in Yangzhou?
I came to Yangzhou to find someone
and happened to pass through Linglong Flower Realm,
so I specifically came to thank you.
Previously, Qin Tiancheng from the White Cloud Palace
died in Yangzhou.
If it weren't for your keen observation
in discovering the human skin mask,
it probably
would have been difficult for me to shake off the suspicion.
It was just a small effort.
You have a reputation for being chivalrous.
I didn't want to see a hero wronged.
This is...
Yes.
This is Miss Cheng Ting'er,
whom you rescued
from Linglong Flower Realm back then.
But don't get it wrong.
Miss Cheng returned of her own accord.
Last year,
Miss Cheng's father passed away,
and the man who she thought
that she could entrust
let her down.
With no other options,
she returned to Linglong Flower Realm.
Most of the girls here
are like that.
Life is unpredictable.
This piece
is quite beautiful.
This piece is called "Yue People's Song,"
a song of longing for home.
Miss Liu,
are you feeling homesick?
I've wandered everywhere since I was little
and have no hometown.
Wherever the person I care about is
that's my hometown.
Where
is the person you care about?
I haven't had the chance to ask you.
Who is the person you came to Yangzhou
to look for this time?
I'm looking for a wealthy merchant
to ask him about
the whereabouts of a medicinal ingredient.
If you trust me,
perhaps I can assist you a little.
Indeed.
You are a friend of many literary figures
and celebrities in Yangzhou.
You must be well-informed.
Thank you in advance.
So, who are you looking for?
A wealthy merchant with the surname Li,
who seems to be in the business of trade
beyond the frontier
and occasionally comes to Yangzhou to make purchases.
Well, you don't need to worry then.
This Mr. Li is actually
one of my guests.
When he comes next time,
I can ask him for you.
Will this put you in a difficult position?
Thank you for your concern.
Since he is my guest,
how could I be put in a difficult position?
It's just a question.
What is it you are looking for?
Millennial Crimson Cold Dragon Blood Pearl.
Doctrine Leader!
I can't defeat him!
Miao Huo,
you're so useless.
I'm afraid I won't be able to keep you around.
I knew
you couldn't gain the upper hand
with Master White-Brows,
but I didn't expect you to be injured so badly.
The Doctrine Leader sent you here, didn't he?
Come on.
Come on!
I'd rather be killed by you
than go back and be fed to dogs!
What does that mean?
Are you giving me a head?
This is the head of Master White-Brows.
I've already held Miao Kong back.
He won't complete the task.
Take this back to report.
You're injured so badly.
I'm sure the Doctrine Leader will not suspect you.
Why did you help me?
If you don't believe me,
just throw it away.
Long live the Doctrine Leader.
Here is the head of White-Brows.
I've checked it many times.
It is indeed Master White-Brows.
Well done.
Thank you, Doctrine Leader.
It seems
you've been seriously injured.
Thank you for your concern.
Well...
That White-Brows
was indeed quite formidable,
but with just a few punches,
he vomited blood
and leaned against a tree,
like this.
Alright.
Then he died.
Go and tend to your injuries.
Yes.
Have the others returned?
Only Miao Kong has not come back yet.
After he returns,
have him come to see me.
Now that I think about it,
he has served me for some time.
I should see him
one last time.
Yes.
Envoy Miao Shui.
I came on the Doctrine Leader's order
to take someone away.
The Doctrine Leader has appointed Eye to manage the Asura Field.
Any changes within the field
must be reported to him.
This matter needs to wait until Eye returns to...
Are you done?
The Doctrine Leader gave the Asura Field to Eye,
and he can take it back at any time.
Think carefully
about whom you are truly being loyal to.
Well...
I'll say it again.
This is the Doctrine Leader's directive.
The Doctrine Leader wants to see you.
Follow me.
Miao Kong,
you have served me for many years
and rarely let me down.
Doctrine Leader, please spare me this time.
I just made a mistake.
You are my right-hand man.
How could I bear
to let you just die?
Thank you, Doctrine Leader!
But your current position
has been targeted.
Whether you can stay or not
depends on you.
Greetings, Doctrine Leader.
Come on.
The one who stays
will become my Envoy Miao Kong.
Doctrine Leader.
Well done.
You truly are the most outstanding one
who fought your way out in this year's Asura Field.
His position
is now yours.
Thank you, Doctrine Leader.
Aren't you going to change your mask
in the hall?
I'm ugly
and afraid it might disturb you.
Or is it that
you don't dare to show your real face?
Take off your mask.
[Xu Chonghua, the sixth disciple of the Sword Sect]