[The snowflakes on the seventh night bloom and wither. Like a short reunion and a permanent separation.]
[Snowy Night Timeless Love]
[Episode 24]
Remember to bury Laughing at the World wine
under the plum tree.
Let's drink together when I'm back.
I'll surely beat you.
♫Gaze at the stars, question the truth of Heaven and Earth♫
♫We reunite in the silent night, melting the coldness♫
♫With pure and earnest hearts, how many lovers remain?♫
♫Warm wine shared over forgotten dreams, to carry us through life♫
♫Across vast mountains and seas, I offer myself to you♫
♫Guarding every lonely night, holding a light for you♫
♫I give my remaining years, how could I ever break free?♫
♫Love falls like silent snow, sweeping away lost souls♫
♫Across vast mountains and seas, I offer myself to you♫
♫Guarding through partings and reunions, holding a light for you♫
♫I give my remaining years, how could I ever break free?♫
♫As long as you can recognize us every time♫
Doctrine Leader.
How's my condition?
Be honest!
This disruption to your cultivation
has hurt your internal organs
and even much of your meridians.
I have unclogged your blood flow.
But...
But even your Spring Breeze technique
can't do anything.
I'm incompetent.
Feng.
It's not your fault.
If even your Spring Breeze
can't do anything,
we can only get the extraordinary healer
from Apothecary Valley.
But you shouldn't be
traveling right now,
or you'll only get worse.
I can't go.
So bring her here.
Feng.
You're the kid I trust the most.
I believe you can
bring her here.
Right?
Yes.
Doctrine Leader.
Feng.
But remember,
you must be careful.
Come back within a month
to take the antidote
to the Ice Silkworm Poison.
Otherwise, my heart will ache.
Don’t worry.
I won't let you down.
Also,
this health disruption isn't a trivial matter.
No one apart from
you and Ming Li should
know about this.
Understand?
I've dealt with our disciples
guarding in the corridor.
But you haven’t shown up for a long time.
Some disciples
are itching to start things.
Perfect.
I can take this opportunity to lure the snake out of its hole
to see who wants me dead.
Go on.
Envoy Miao Shui.
What is this for?
Oh, it's Envoy Miao Feng.
It's dark and windy.
I thought there was a thief.
Fortunately, you're fine.
Otherwise, I'd feel
so guilty.
In that case,
please step aside.
What's the urgent matter?
You're leaving before dawn?
Do I need to
report to you?
Of course not.
But
I have to remind you again.
If you're lying
and our leader's harmed,
I really can't
let you go.
I don't care what your aim is.
If you dare to attack me again,
don't blame me for being rude.
Be rude?
You've always been kind.
I'd like to see
how you look
when you're being rude.
Envoy Miao Feng.
Why are you so serious?
Ease up.
It was just a joke.
But you're right.
You always have
a smile on your face.
I doubt I could tell
even if your smile's genuine.
That old geezer Chang Wujue
must really be in trouble.
[Yuan Yi Palace]
Mr. Eye.
Doctrine Leader is taking a nap.
Please wait.
Eye.
You're back.
Come in.
Long live the Doctrine Leader.
I went to Mount Changbai
to take the life of the Skypool Hermit
to avenge you
for the past sword feud.
You're indeed my trusted disciple.
You never let me down.
You came back from afar.
Just in time.
Check out
my newly recruited mastiffs.
Aren't they cute?
Do you recognize
this thing?
This is...
Sun Saintess,
Wuma.
What a foolish woman.
She even tried to kill me.
Who did she think she is?
Am I right?
Eye.
I only hate that
I couldn't kill her
for you.
The golden needle is still here.
Eye.
As long as you submit to me,
you can enjoy the luxuries
of the world.
Did he see through me?
Or was it just a test?
Chang Wu Jue is really unfathomable.
Thank goodness we didn't take action first,
or it'd be us two
who were dead.
That dead face
was even uglier than me.
His cultivation in seclusion failed
and he lost control.
He also barely calmed
the Sun Saintess' rebellion.
His vitality
is greatly weakened.
That sly old fox.
He actually summoned me
to avoid suspicion.
If I knew,
I'd have slain him
with my Lixue Sword.
Unfortunately,
I was squashed
by his bluff.
Couldn't that wretch Miao Shui
sent you a message or something?
We missed such a good opportunity!
It's fine.
Chang Wujue's cultivation is disrupted,
Miao Feng was sent out,
and even Ming Li's not in the palace.
Even if he summons
all the disciples,
it'd take some time for them to get back.
We have to act quickly.
Buddy.
It's all up to this one chance.
If we can't kill him this time,
there won't be another chance
to kill that damn doctrine leader.
Miao Feng should've
arrived at Apothecary Valley.
I wonder if
Xue Ziye will agree to his invite.
But
we have to do it
before he comes back.
I'm not sure
if he knows
about the Dragon Blood Pearl.
If he does,
we would fail.
I told you we should've
killed that woman.
Why did you let her live?
Do you really want to study medicine?
Or do you like girls with long hair?
I really don't get you.
Do you have a screw loose?
Seriously, you...
Miao Huo.
As long as you're happy.
I'll pick some confidants
from Asura Field
to deal with Miao Feng.
With how powerful Miao Feng is,
they won't be his match.
But if they manage to
stall Miao Feng,
we could rush to
kill the leader.
When will we do it?
To cover up his deteriorating condition,
he'll go to Yuan Yi Hall
as per his routine.
We'll do it then.
First, I'll return to Asura Field's dark realm
and meditate
to boost my Eye Magic.
It's not the time yet.
Don't be hasty.
Okay.
Keep your eyes closed
for the next few days.
I'll inform Miao Shui.
We must seize this opportunity.
I'm here.
Don't worry.
Here.
Your song
seems like an invitation.
The tune
moves in the same trajectory
as the chess player who moves the black pieces,
warm and cozy
like the spring breeze.
If I'm not mistaken,
you're the chess player
I play with
whom I've never met.
I’ve been waiting here
for you for a long time.
You and I always come as we please.
Why are you waiting for me?
Farewell.
Today might be
the last game of chess
I play with you,
Chief Xue.
As a martial artist, I guess
there are many things out of your control.
Then let's
finish this game today.
Aren’t you curious
why it’s the last time?
We got acquainted playing chess
and talk about chess.
I know not to cross the line.
If it's personal,
there's no need to pursue it.
Besides,
the game has to end one day.
And there will always
come a time to bid farewell.
Chief Xue, you won.
Is something bothering you?
In the past,
your moves were always smooth,
meticulous,
gentle, patient,
and never hasty,
but never giving up.
You always found a way to turn things around.
But today...
What's wrong?
It was like you were supposed to win
but you sabotaged yourself.
Your first moves
were a bit too hasty.
As for your last moves,
you had a chance to rectify things,
but it was like you didn't realize it
and gave up.
Because it's our last game,
did you let me win?
Indeed...
I lost to you, Chief Xue.
This match
could have been better.
Now that the game is over,
let’s say goodbye.
Chief Xue.
I hope there will come a day
when we can play like this again.
♫Longing etched in my heart, but all it brings is parting♫
♫Plum blossoms are about to fall; I'll see you here♫
♫Why are you late and why is it about to snow again?♫
♫Warm stovetops and green film in wine, like an eternal farewell♫
♫Don't stop drinking; keep lingering and enjoy the long night♫
♫After all these years, my yearning for you is still as clear as the bright moon♫
♫Looking into the distance, speechless and sleepless♫
[Caohai Inn]
♫Warm stovetops and green film in wine, like an eternal farewell♫
♫Don't stop drinking; keep lingering and enjoy the long night♫
♫After all these years, my yearning for you is still as clear as the bright moon♫
♫Looking into the distance, speechless and sleepless♫
Chief.
♫Longing etched in my heart, but I don't wish for your acknowledgement of my love♫
Mr. Seven went south to Yangzhou.
♫Asking the stars about our fate, as fireworks appear in my dream♫
It'll take at least a month to return.
The snowstorm outside the valley
is too huge.
You should go back and rest.
♫I've fulfilled my wish, having traveled this far with you♫
I'm stuffed.
I came out for a walk.
It's too cold.
♫I've fulfilled my wish, having traveled this far with you♫
Let's go back.
Okay.
Hong.
Coming.
Here.
Okay.
Who are you looking for?
I'm Huo Zhanbai, the seventh disciple of Sword Sect.
Greetings, Senior Liao.
Seven?
What brings you here?
You may not remember,
but I met you once.
Two years ago, at the Guazhou market,
you checked a kid's pulse.
I'm that kid's uncle.
I remember now.
That seriously ill child?
Yes.
I'm here today
to convey a message on your disciple's behalf.
After all these years,
it's still finally came.
Come in.
Did you come from Apothecary Valley?
Yes.
How has Ziye's health been?
Not very well.
Her cold disease
is getting worse.
So it came to this after all.
Have a seat.
It's my fault as her master.
When Ziye was only 18 years old,
I left her in charge of Apothecary Valley.
All these years,
she must've had a tough time.
This hairpin
was a token I left to Ziye
when I left the valley.
That girl
is always smart and strong.
I thought her current
medical skills
were invincible.
To think
she can't avoid using this token.
Is she still adamant about
me helping her revive Xuehuai?
I told her long ago
that it's impossible.
I don't think it's Xuehuai...
but the child
I just mentioned.
I see.
This prescription
can’t cure Mo's illness,
but it can be said
to have saved three lives.
It seems this prescription
doesn't work on Mo.
Not only that.
Her initial
five-herb prescription
was actually useless.
Useless?
How could this be?
Why weren't
these herbs used?
Where's the Dragon Blood Pearl?
These herbs
are all extraordinary,
but they're all extremely potent
and incompatible.
It's impossible to combine them
into a medicinal drug.
What did you say?
So she's been lying to me all along?
She didn't lie to you.
But I...
But I spent eight years.
I spent eight years!
I went through fire and water
and gave my all
for eight years just for this.
How is this prescription useless?
How could it be?
Ziye said in the letter that
although this prescription is recorded in the ancient books,
she tested it and learned that
it doesn't help with Mo's illness.
Ziye must've gave her all
to help Mo survive till today.
Even now,
she’s still planning for Mo's survival.
I'll use these herbs separately
to create medicinal drugs
to extend Mo’s life.
I think
that's why she asked you
to find me with this.
But I spent a whole eight years.
Eight years!
She should've long told you
that Mo will eventually die.
But if she said that,
how will
you and Mo's mother
face that fact?
Ziye must know you very well.
So she couldn't tell you
the truth.
You've known her for eight years.
Do you know what she is obsessed with?
To find out the truth
of Mo Family Village's massacre
and awaken the person in the ice.
You two are very similar.
You both have obsessions,
desperately seeking
a glimmer of hope.
You know what?
This is the only token
I left to her.
I once told her
if she encountered difficulties,
she could bring this to me
and I'd do my best to help her.
I thought
she'd use this hairpin
to revive Xuehuai in the ice.
But I never imagined
that she'd use this
to save
a kid she has no ties with.
From now on,
I’ll be responsible
of Xu Mo's treatment.
Ziye did everything
to save Mo for you.
I think this is the only thing
she could do for you.
I know you can't accept it
for the time being.
Think about it.
Mo’s illness
can't be cured.
I've found an ancient prescription
to cure Mo's illness.
Only if you wake up can you save him.
Huo Zhanbai.
♫A cup of wine, a toast to the world, as wind and snow knock on the door♫
♫Sigh for love and hate, leaving no trace upon the palm♫
♫Life drifts like dust, when will we meet again?♫
I'm serious.
If you're severely injured again, don't come back.
I can't afford to waste my energy.
♫From vibrant warmth to icy cold, it's just a single turn away♫
♫Gaze at the stars, question the truth of Heaven and Earth♫
♫We reunite in the silent night, melting the coldness♫
♫With pure and earnest hearts, how many lovers remain?♫
♫Warm wine shared over forgotten dreams, to carry us through life♫
♫Across vast mountains and seas, I offer myself to you♫
Huo Zhanbai.
Wake up.
♫Guarding every lonely night, holding a light for you♫
♫I give my remaining years, how could I ever break free?♫
This is Mo's medicine.
What?
You still can't bear to leave?
♫Love falls like silent snow, sweeping away lost souls♫
Actually...
Actually,
all these years,
you've been trying your best
to extend Mo’s life.
It's enough.
Huo Zhanbai.
You huge fool.
I'm sorry.
♫Gaze at the stars, question the truth of Heaven and Earth♫
Senior.
Actually,
♫We reunite in the silent night, melting the coldness♫
when I saw you at the Guazhou market
and saw the jade pendant on your waist,
I already guessed
♫With pure and earnest hearts, how many lovers remain?♫
you were the former chief
of Apothecary Valley.
You said
Mo's illness is unmanageable.
♫Warm wine shared over forgotten dreams, to carry us through life♫
Since then,
every time I think about
Chief Xue's hesitance when talking about Mo...
♫Across vast mountains and seas, I offer myself to you♫
I've actually
long had my doubts.
♫Guarding every lonely night, holding a light for you♫
Do you blame her?
♫I give my remaining years, how could I ever break free?♫
Like you said,
♫As long as you can recognize us every time♫
she prescribed
this impossible prescription.
She saved me,
Mo, and Mo's mother.
All these years,
she did everything
to save me
and Mo.
She kept hiding the truth
so I wouldn't lose hope.
I once told her that
obsession is like a crutch.
Without crutches,
one can't survive the snowstorm.
She knows that
as long as there's a glimmer of hope,
I'll do my best
for this hope.
Why would I blame her?
She just
gave you a chance to do your best
so you wouldn't feel guilty.
From what you said,
you'd already guessed that
the prescription might be ineffective.
Why didn't you verify it with her?
Regardless of the medicine's efficacy,
I'd have kept looking for the herbs.
In that case,
why should I ask?
No matter what,
I'll try my best to save Mo.
Don't worry.
I will do my best
to save Xu Mo.
I'll discuss it with my husband
when he gets back,
and we'll set out immediately.
I'll go pack up.
I kept persuading her to let go of her obsession,
but I couldn't
let mine go.
Ziye.
You could have
told me sooner.
Why did you have to
bear so much blame and torture yourself?
Honey.
Do we have a guest?
Seven?
Seven!
Fifth Brother?
-Why are you here?
I was about to tell you
my husband is your fifth brother.
I thought
you came to summon him back
to Sword Sect,
so I didn't reveal his identity.
It's fine.
Seven doesn't care about these.
Seven!
Why are you here?
It's a long story.
Seven came to me
with Ziye's handwritten letter.
She needs me to save someone in Guazhou.
He is in critical condition.
We've to leave tomorrow morning.
Who managed to get my wife's attention?
Sixth Brother's child,
Mo.
Six's child?
Where is he now?
Catch up later.
Bao peed again.
Okay.
Honey, hurry.
Change his diapers.
I'm here. I'm here.
Seven, take a seat.
Why are you back so late today?
Did you go drinking again?
I didn't!
Alright, my dear baby.
It’s okay.
Chief.
Someone's here to see you.
See me?
Do they have the Fate-Reversal Token?
Yes.
They even
have many of them.
What do you mean?
They have nine tokens.
You need medical treatment?
Isn’t this
your chess mate?
I'm Envoy Miao Feng from Yuan Yi Palace of Mount Kunlun.
I was ordered to come here
to seek treatment from Chief Xue.
You're actually from Yuan Yi Palace?
I heard
you like seclusion
and only provide treatment in this premise.
So I first followed
the person releasing the Fate-Reversal Tokens,
Ms. Shuang Hong,
and collected
all the tokens.
No wonder he said it was his last time
as my chess mate.
May I ask if
there are nine patients to treat?
There's only one patient.
But I was afraid
you wouldn't agree to the treatment
or how my treatment
would be hindered if you're also treating others,
so I just got multiple tokens.
It wasn't tough anyway.
Who is it that needs treatment?
Yuan Yi Palace's doctrine leader.
While
cultivating in seclusion,
he suddenly felt unwell.
He hasn't fully recovered
despite days of rest.
He heard that Apothecary Valley
has top-notch medical expertise,
so he ordered me
to come all the way here to seek treatment.
Chief Xue,
please visit Yuan Yi Palace to treat him.
I'm sorry.
We never treat patients outside the valley.
Even this
won't cut it?
I heard that you ask for hefty medical fees.
100,000 to save one person.
My leader ordered me
to bring some meager things here.
He's willing to pay ten times the usual fees.
I'm not feeling well.
I can't leave the valley.
I'm unable to
accede to your request.
I'll have to ask you to leave.
Before I came here,
I also heard that
you can’t leave the valley
because you can't withstand the cold
with your cold disease.
Is it true?
If so,
I can help you
get rid of the cold disease.
In that case,
your medical skills
are even better than mine.
You're the world's top healer.
Have you heard of the Spring Breeze?
You should worry about yourself first.
Your hair's turning blue
because of the Ice Silkworm Poison.
I was poisoned
with the Ice Silkworm Poison.
To resist the cold poison,
after 20 years,
I finally mastered the secret technique
of the Holy Fire Order.
The snow actually melted.
You’re an excellent doctor.
But compared to internal power,
there are areas where acupuncture falls short.
May I have the honor
to get rid of your cold disease?
Life and death are predestined.
Doctors never treat themselves
since ancient times.
I, Xue Ziye,
am not a coward who can be threatened
by death or threats.
Chief Xue.
If you refuse...
What?
Has the evil side been exposed?
Looks like Yuan Yi Palace
aren't that capable.
Envoy Miao Feng,
you should know
that if a doctor's not willing,
the patient will never recover.
I'm not afraid of death.
You can't threaten me.
Even if I go with you for treatment,
you don't know medicine.
How can you tell
if my prescription is correct?
With just
mere adjustments
in the proportions,
I could make an unorthodox prescription
that
might cause your leader
to die sooner.
Of course,
I understand the risks.
So I've never
thought of offending you.
If you have to refuse...
Since I've failed my duty
and can't return to Kunlun,
I can only kill myself here.
Stop!
Chief Xue...
Since...
you saved me,
does it mean... you agree to treat my leader?
What a lunatic.
It seems your leader's orders
cannot be disobeyed.
Carry him into the valley.