You're awake.
I fell asleep just now.
Yes.
It's okay. Why don't
we head back now?
Let's go.
Let's go home.
The sunshine was
so comfortable just now.
Yes.
Let's go.
Okay, I'm coming.
Oh my goodness!
Wait for me!
I've told you everything I needed to.
That's what's been happening with us recently.
Oh my God,
that's so romantic!
This is definitely Aunt Pearl
playing matchmaker for you.
Mu Yilin,
I'm warning you,
don't mess this up again, you hear me?
Why do you always bring up the sore spots?
Aunt Pearl went through all that trouble,
coming from so far away,
to set you up with
such a handsome guy,
you need to seize this opportunity!
Seize what?
Don't worry,
this time your sister will help you check him out thoroughly.
Don't talk nonsense,
I don't have those kinds of thoughts.
Xu Sansan.
Sansan.
What's up, Ali?
Delivery. Try this.
You made this?
Get lost!
Why are you here?
I want you to taste my cooking.
You made this?
Young Master Ali,
just stick to managing your restaurant,
cooking skills can't be forced.
I really tried this time,
it's definitely different.
Smells delicious.
Lu Hui.
I didn't know you had such cooking skills.
If they won't eat it but you will, what does that prove?
What else?
We can't let you cook alone.
Let's go make a couple dishes too.
Come on.
You can cook too?
Food's ready. Let's eat.
Coming.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Yilin.
That's impressive.
If we couldn't cook,
Yilin and I have been on our own for so many years,
we would've starved to death long ago.
I'm the only restaurant owner who can't cook.
Try it and see how it tastes.
Let's dig in then.
Delicious.
This dish is good too.
Yilin,
when are you planning to go back to Beijing?
I need to stay for a couple more days,
because I'm planning to check out
the tourist routes around here,
since I promised Director Jin
I'd give her five travel routes each month.
Five?
So if you're free tomorrow,
I'm planning to check out the attractions nearby.
Where to?
Let's start with the lavender garden.
If you're not busy tomorrow,
you can come with me.
I'm free tomorrow. I'll go with you.
That works.
You're familiar with this area anyway,
and since you're available tomorrow,
you can show me around.
No problem,
it's settled then.
Five paths.
Five routes.
I'll just call you Wutiao then.
From now on,
you're a little lamb with a name too.
Good morning.
Morning.
Why are you smiling so happily?
Going out is exciting.
Coffee.
I brought some too.
Let's have both then.
This is really comfortable.
Look.
This place looks good from any angle,
doesn't it?
Beautiful.
Little girl,
could you help me with something?
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
Let's take another one.
One more.
Good. You can choose which ones you like.
Okay.
You two should join in too,
let me take a photo of you together.
Come on, get up there.
We don't need to.
Come on,
let's do it.
Come here.
Come closer.
A bit closer.
Boys will be boys.
Raise your left arm.
Your left arm.
Higher. Higher. More. More.
Lift it more.
Down. This way. This way.
Again. Lift it again.
Good. That's it.
Perfect.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Here.
Ma'am.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
You young lovebirds
should travel more while you're young.
Unlike us,
who only have time to travel when we're older,
right?
Sir, ma'am,
where are you visiting Xinjiang from?
We came from Khorgos.
We also came from Khorgos.
Are you locals from Khorgos?
No, no, no.
I'm from Lianyungang,
and I've been
doing business here for decades.
Sir,
do you happen to know someone
who also came here about 30 years ago
to run a luggage business?
Her name is Zhenzhu.
Zhenzhu?
Is that Zhenzhu from Lianyungang?
Yes.
How do you know her?
She's my mother.
Back then
I was your mother's driver.
I had never seen a woman
hauling a cartload of goods by herself
to such a distant place.
What's wrong?
Hey!
Help us!
Let me help.
Give me the rope.
Where are you heading?
I'm going to Khorgos.
Khorgos
is still quite far from here.
Yes.
It's getting dark soon,
and even if you fix your cart before leaving,
it would still be dangerous.
My home is just over there,
why not stay for the night and leave tomorrow?
Don't worry, we're good people.
Our yurt is clean,
come have some hot tea
and continue your journey tomorrow.
Alright.
Good,
leave the cart here and follow me.
Wait a moment,
let's take a photo.
Such an amazing experience
would be a shame not to capture.
Three, two, one.
If I hadn't
followed your mother all the way here back then,
this logistics company wouldn't exist today.
What happened next?
Have some hot water.
Thank you.
The
rain cover,
I've already set it up,
so we don't have to worry about rain tonight.
Thank you,
thanks.
This place is so unique.
This is how we Kazakh people build our homes,
just like this.
That,
what is that?
Dombra.
Dombra,
can you play it?
Yes.
Do you know how to sing
Wang Luobin's songs?
Wang Luobin,
I don't know him.
I really love his songs,
all of his songs,
I love them all.
I also really love San Mao's books,
and I really admire
their love story.
San Mao,
what kind of books are those?
In her books,
there are deserts,
grasslands,
love stories,
and herself.
I haven't read them.
I'll read some to you.
Okay.
Thank you for giving me this false hope,
our beautiful memories
have been blurred by my tears.
When I occasionally remember,
the memories are still fresh,
just like back then,
I loved you
without any purpose.
I
only love you.
Um,
have some water.
I'll, I'll
sleep outside today,
you can stay inside the yurt,
alright, good.
Oras Baisbek
Biliko Dulaitibai
Zhou Hong Li Jinwei
Yu Xuan Li Jingyu
Gao Danbai Feng Xueying
Liu Yifu Hong Kejia
Lin Anuan Huang Yizhe
Liu Mingxuan Liu Junwei
Zhang Yuehan Zhang Shuiqiang
Zhang Jinlei Feng Wentao
Ji Weijia Li Shuai
Xue Jinmei Chen Wenwen
Li Helong Sun Baihe
Song Yanlong Zhao Weixu
Fan Hao Li Siyuan
Zhu Pengxiang Sun Chuanyue
Zhang Xinran Wang Qiaoyun
Sun Jianqiao Zhang Xinran
Wang Zhengxing Guo Xing Ju Hao
Ju Hao Wang Zhengxing
Wang Zhengxing Ju Hao
Mao Pengyuan   Shi Weicong
Aixi Culture Media   Wu Chunhua
Beijing Sruimu Film and Television Media