What are you two doing here?
What?
Come here right now.
What's going on?
What's the matter?
Hurry up,
come here.
What are you doing?
Hurry.
Tell me the truth.
You.
Are you dating someone?
No, I'm not.
Then where were you last night?
I just slept in the car last night.
Just slept?
Did you take off your clothes?
Yes, I did.
The temperature difference between day and night is huge there,
I was afraid she'd get cold.
Did you kiss?
No.
You definitely did.
No,
why are you being so nosy?
Let's go, get out of here.
Xu Sansan, stop your fantasizing.
Berlin
Okay.
Stand here.
Good.
A little forward. Careful.
What are you doing here?
I'm waiting for someone.
Are you a teacher too?
Are you also visiting the museum?
No way.
He must be waiting for his girlfriend.
A date.
Who goes to a museum for a date?
Who says you can't date at a museum?
I think museums are great.
It really is a date!
Go away.
What do you elementary kids know about dating?
Look! There's a pretty lady over there!
Where?
Stop messing around.
Listen.
Do me a favor.
Sansan.
Come take me to the museum.
Brother, you're so handsome.
Sister, you're so beautiful.
You even brought your own cheerleaders.
Great.
Let's go.
Coming.
Here.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Who takes a girl to a museum on their first date?
Don't you like it?
No,
I enjoy visiting museums too.
I knew it.
That's not what I meant.
Why do you keep staring at me?
Well, because you're beautiful.
The brother is so handsome,
and looks perfect with the sister.
Did you teach her to say that too?
No, no,
kids just see things clearly.
Fine.
Look,
these are our border defense soldiers.
My grandfather told me
that he once cooked Big Plate Chicken
for the border soldiers back then.
Really?
Ali,
tell me,
did those border soldiers back then
also find their Big Plate Chicken
too salty and bitter?
Sansan,
you're always picking on me.
Where are you going all dressed up so beautifully?
Guess what?
I think
you're going on a date with Ali.
How did you know?
You and Ali are together.
You two.
Stop, stop!
No, no.
Don't make things up.
I just have
a little interest in him now.
I really need to thank Auntie Zhenzhu
for not only matchmaking for you
but also setting me up with someone.
Xu Sansan
I have to remind you
that someone once told me
not to fall in love so easily.
You and Ali are
moving way too fast
Don't be ridiculous.
don't you think?
Have you properly checked him out?
Here you go, sir
the usual.
Cold is fine.
Sure thing.
Thank you, young man
Cold.
you're a good person.
I'm still evaluating him
but I judge men on three things:
good values
good character
and how he treats me.
Let me tell you
good men on the market these days
are really hard to find.
It's not that I'm moving too fast
you need to step up your game.
Your judgment when it comes to men
needs some improvement
you know?
I'm off
get back to work.
Actually, there's one more thing
which is whether he's handsome or not.
Bye!
I bet that last point is what you really care about.
As long as he's good to me.
What about his character?
Thank you.
Come on.
Everyone gets one.
Thanks.
Is it good, sis?
It smells wonderful.
Jia Dan.
For this video traffic,
I know who can help us.
Still working on the plan?
I've already got
a premium three-day tour,
a three-day tour for seniors,
a three-day tour for young people,
and a five-day tour.
I just have one last route
to figure out.
What are you doing?
You'll definitely come up with a plan,
but right now the most important thing
is to take a break.
What's this?
A proposal that the boss rejected earlier.
Smile Travel.
Plus.
What does that mean?
The 'plus' means
that during this trip,
you can add anything you want to it.
When I first created this proposal, I thought about
collaborating with social media influencers
and partnering with e-commerce platforms.
Along our entire travel route,
there are many ethnic specialties
and local products.
So we can
use these specialties and products
to create a dedicated travel route.
This way,
it maintains its tourism aspect
while also achieving some
commercial value.
So everyone makes money
and finds their smile again.
Smile Travel.
Plus E-commerce.
What about the specific plan?
Xiaolisibai Adanbieke
Ehelasi Bayisibieke
Tusunai Tasibolati
Bilike Dulaitibayi
Zhou Hong Li Jinwei
Yu Xuan Li Jingyu
Gao Danbai Feng Xueying
Liu Yifu Hong Kejia
Lin Anuan Huang Yizhe
Zhang Yuehan Zhang Shuiqiang
Ji Weijia Li Shuai
Xue Jinmei Chen Wenwen
Li Hongjian Jing Pengliang
Li Helong Sun Baihe
Song Yanlong Zhao Weixu
Fan Hao Li Siyuan
Zhu Pengxiang Sun Chuanyue
Zhang Xinran Wang Qiaoyun
Sun Jianqiao Zhang Xinran
Wang Zhengxing Guo Xing Ju Hao
Ju Hao Wang Zhengxing
Mao Pengyuan Shi Weicong