With so much information,
I don't know how much of it is true
and how much is false.
Do you think the address she left is real?
We can figure out from her ID number
that she is seventeen.
But she filled in twenty-seven for her age.
It shows she never intended to give her real information
to the doctor.
Then most of the content here
is not credible.
But sometimes when people lie,
it's just a subconscious act.
A lie is not necessarily a complete lie;
it's just a packaged and modified truth.
Dongcheng Jiayuan really exists.
I see what you mean.
The Dongcheng Jiayuan she wrote down must be fake.
The reason she wrote Dongcheng Jiayuan
shows she often passes by or is familiar with it.
Jiela Internet Cafe,
Feiyue Gym,
they are all places she has been to.
She also wrote Dongcheng Jiayuan,
which means this area
should be within her frequent activity range.
If we exclude Dongcheng Jiayuan,
there are three left.
Two.
This Lihua Yihaoyuan
is a newly built high-end neighborhood.
They are all large flat apartments,
with an average price of over 40,000.
Do you remember what that person was wearing?
I remember she seemed to be wearing Arc'teryx.
It's quite expensive.
I don't think so.
The spelling of Arc'teryx is like this.
The apostrophe is in the top right corner of ARC.
If I remember correctly,
the one on hers was in the bottom right corner of ARC,
which means she was wearing a knockoff.
If she was really wearing a knockoff,
then her financial situation shouldn't be that good.
She couldn't afford that kind of house.
Sir,
Liyuan Neighborhood.
One out of two.
That's a fifty percent chance.
No need to go to the next neighborhood.
This is it.
Okay.
Everyone's here.
So,
each of you will take charge of one trash can
and help me find something.
No way, we can't do this.
Listen to me.
My mom accidentally
threw away something very important to me,
but she forgot which trash can she threw it in.
The surveillance cameras in our neighborhood are broken,
but this item is really important to me.
I'm begging you all.
I'll pay you extra.
I see.
No problem.
Okay.
As for what I lost,
it's not convenient for me to say.
But the garbage bag I lost has bloody gauze in it.
So if anyone finds bloody gauze, call me,
okay?
Okay.
Come on, get moving, hurry.
Found it!
Wait a minute.
It's full of glass.
There's quite a lot of blood on this,
and iodophor was clearly used.
She probably didn't use this.
Go keep looking.
Keep looking, everyone look.
I'll give an extra thousand to whoever finds it.
Here, found it!
Where did you find it?
In this takeout bag.
Liyuan Neighborhood, Building 6, Unit 2, 204.
Open the door!
Open the door! Open the door!
What happened to your face?
My plastic surgery failed.
Are you the one who told Huangmao to take the video?
Is it you?
Found it.
Not bad.
Once you get the video and confirm there are no backups,
you can leave.
Don't meddle in other affairs.
Wait for my next mission.
Didn't you two have a pretty good relationship?
Why did it end up like this?
Because her grades are better than mine.
She's prettier than me.
She's better than me at everything.
Why?
I mean, you...
Never mind.
Anyway, you've received the punishment you deserve.
Take care of yourself.
Eat up quickly.
If you go hungry,
your dad will be heartbroken.
After I finish everything
and my daughter returns,
you must hide well.
Empty threats are meaningless,
but they let you vent your emotions.
Do you need to say a few more?
No need.
I just want to give you some instructions.
My daughter doesn't eat cilantro,
or chili.
Her favorite is tomato and egg stir-fry,
but remember to add some vinegar.
That's all for now.
Tell me.
What do you want me to do next?
You cooperated well today.
If you keep this up,
your daughter will definitely be comfortable.
But this is just the beginning.
Let's call it a day.
Get a good night's rest
and wait for my call tomorrow.
The person in the video is your daughter.
What exactly is the countdown on your bracelet?
Also, do you really not know
what is inside your body?
What exactly happened?
Nothing happened.
Your condition doesn't allow you to run around.
I know you might have things you can't say.
But if you need help,
let me know anytime.
Okay, got it.
Thank you.
It's getting late.
You should go home early too.
What's wrong?
Do you want me to walk you home?
No.
I think you might need some help right now.
How can you help me?
I...
How about this?
Can you buy me a bottle of water?
I'm a little thirsty.
What does this mean?
This is my phone number.
I think
you want me to buy water for you
and then take the opportunity to leave.
Don't worry, I won't.
Help me look into someone.
Did you sleep okay last night?
Thanks to you,
it was fine.
Then you should cherish it.
You'll have less and less time to rest from now on.
A new mission is here.
Production Team
Action Team