Two chocolates.
Call.
Let's show.
Continue.
Only 5,000?
Raise you 20,000.
I'll bet 50,000.
That's more like it.
Call, call.
His hole card is a four.
Then I'll show.
King.
Thanks, Officer Shao.
That must be another ten years of your salary.
Your luck has been pretty good before.
It's about time I got on a winning streak.
Go ahead.
You should've toughened up earlier.
Okay.
All in.
I'll call.
Three of a kind.
That's indeed a big hand.
But I also have three of a kind.
Three plus two.
A full house.
You used to be a cop,
and you suppressed me.
I couldn't beat you.
But now this cop
is useless.
See the guest out.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong, Officer Shao?
I haven't lost everything yet.
How can this game be over?
You're out of chips.
Gambling is risky.
Yes, you have a point.
How about I keep 3,000 for gas first?
Sorry.
I was being presumptuous.
Come on, 3,000.
Come on.
Shao Yu's hole card is an A.
Three of a kind.
Let's see.
Officer Shao, we can wrap this up.
From the cards on the table,
you don't have much of a chance.
What if my hole card is a 5 or a Q?
You are out of money.
How about this?
Let's
seal the cards first.
You go back and mortgage your house too.
I'll wait for you.
No need.
That's too much trouble.
I have something to bet.
What else do you have to bet?
Are you really betting her?
Didn't you say before
that you'd pay 100,000 for a night with her?
I'll let her accompany you for a year.
10 million.
I bet on this round.
Is she gold-plated?
10 million.
But if you put it that way,
I really do like this girl more and more.
All right, it's a bet.
Officer Shao.
Even if your hole card is a Queen,
you still can't beat me.
Just give up.
But if your hole card is a 5...
It's possible.
But...
But what?
But my hole card can't possibly be a 5, right?
Why are you so confident?
Because you know my hole card is an Ace.
Sorry.
My hole card
is 5.
Four of a kind.
When I was a police officer,
I worked undercover in an underground casino.
I know all
your tricks.
When we started playing mahjong,
you could actually see our tiles through the monitors.
Everything is in your control.
The dealer's hand is a flush, winning on a 6-character.
The next player's hand is all triplets, winning on a 4-dot.
The opposite player's hand is a straight,
waiting solely for an 8-character.
Then you used various cheating tricks
to let us win a little.
You gave us a taste of winning first
to lure us into the big game.
Mahjong.
I won too.
Me too.
And when playing blackjack,
you rigged the dealing shoe.
The cards will follow your pre-set program
when dealt to the others.
No matter who the dealer is,
you will always get good cards.
Sorry, blackjack again.
Because of the rules of blackjack,
you can't completely control the others' minds,
so you can't guarantee that the cards you set up
will definitely end up in your hands.
Your hand is good enough.
The dealer probably can't beat you.
Lao Zhang, enough.
18 is close enough.
If anything unexpected happens,
your people will analyze the remaining cards
and provide the best solution.
Li Si, keep hitting
until you bust.
Hit.
Wang Wu,
whether Brother Hui hits or not,
you both stop hitting.
Stand.
What the hell?
Standing on 12?
Play it safe.
They relay instructions to your two shills through earpieces,
sacrificing them.
To ensure that in this round
you can get the cards designed earlier.
It's 20.
No wonder you didn't lose any money when playing just now.
When I was the dealer, you bet less.
When someone else was the dealer,
you followed my bet.
But I have a question.
How did you do that?
Simple.
I have this thing too.
And your card shuffler at the critical moment
is no longer under your control.
Hello, Brother Shao.
Do me a favor.
I had someone hack into your system
and control the shuffler.
Brother Hui, his hole card is an Ace.
You thought you dealt me an Ace.
Unfortunately, that's only what you saw on the computer.
How dare you cheat!
All right.
I'll be taking this money.
If I remember correctly,
I won 10,003,000.
Keep the 3,000.
Buy your little brother something good to eat.
I've been running this casino for a long time,
and I always accept my losses.
But you just admitted
that you cheated too.
The money you won by cheating,
how can I give it to you?
I did cheat.
But you cheated too.
So we're even, okay?
According to our rules.
Take this one million principal
back.
Did I just say
I hacked into your system?
The footage captured by all these cameras
is on my friend's computer.
If I give it to the police...
If you give it to the police, you're in it too.
So what do you want to do?
Give me a chance to turn the tables.
Okay.
But
how we play
is up to me.
I'll take 4 million out of this 10 million.
I'll play the remaining 6 million with you.
If you win,
this 6 million
is yours.
If you lose,
this 6 million is also yours.
But
you must answer a question for me.
What question?
You definitely know the answer to this question.
And I won't make it too difficult for you.
Thinking about it, I seem
to be at a slight disadvantage.
I have to take this four million.
Didn't I just say
that I've hacked into your system?
With footage from so many cameras,
imagine if I gave it to the police.
Fine.
How do we bet?
We don't trust each other right now.
How about this.
We just leave it to luck.
We'll still play Blackjack.
But
we can't play it ourselves.
We'll let someone else play for us.
And they have to be blindfolded.
They can't look at the cards.
Winning or losing
is entirely up to heaven.
I can even make another concession
and let you be the dealer.
A tie means I lose, too.
Sister Hai, do you want more?
What about you?
Want more?
Do you want more?
I admit defeat.
I accept it.
Officer Shao.
Ask away.
When I was a cop,
I had an informant named Mr. Bai.
You should know him.
Sang Rong killed him.
What I want to ask is,
who leaked his identity as an informant?
Fine.
It's been so long.
It doesn't matter if I tell you.
Actually, we had no idea he was your informant.
The reason Lao Bai was killed
was because he...
was because he broke a major taboo in the underworld.
He seduced the boss's wife.
He slept with Brother Rong's wife.
Impossible. Then Mr. Bai...
Officer Shao.
I only entered the answer to one question.
Lighting crew.