Your mission is complete.
Then I can take off my bracelet, right?
From what you're saying,
you want to terminate your cooperation with us.
The flash drive plus the three of them
in exchange for my daughter.
Is that enough?
Okay.
In four hours,
I will send your daughter home safely.
You agreed so readily.
Let me finish.
We are only one step away from our ultimate goal.
What comes next is not a demand,
but a request.
I hope you can help us.
Help you?
Why should I?
Because you cut off my daughter's finger.
No need to decide so soon.
We still have time.
Catch up with some old friends first.
Jessica.
Help him take off the bracelet.
Screw you.
Don't you want to know
what our ultimate goal is?
I know,
Ding Tian.
While completing the missions,
I was also secretly investigating the target's information.
Help me look into someone.
Emergency contact
number: 1355233041.
You made such a big scene.
What is it,
Wang Yu?
Help me look into someone else.
I will send you the information later.
I found they all have one thing in common.
They were all assaulted by Ding Tian.
That little girl Li Bing, whose bullying video was filmed by the blond guy,
six months ago,
was raped by Ding Tian.
To cover up the truth, Ding Tian
approached her best friend.
She is your best friend.
Talk to her.
Tell her to forget what happened today.
Here is 100,000 yuan.
Consider it my compensation for her.
Okay.
What did I tell you yesterday?
Why didn't you bring the money as told?
No.
Mind your own business.
Get out of here.
Get out.
90s Cool
All by yourself, little girl?
Wearing so much.
Why not take some off?
No.
If you don't take them off,
we'll help you take them off.
No.
And you want me to use Zhang Qian
to get Wang Yu's address.
Later, I did send someone to find that psychiatric hospital
and verified it with Zhang Qian.
Two years ago, Wang Yu
was also raped by Ding Tian.
At the time, she even found Ding Tian through a reporter
to expose him.
Ding Tian then asked Zhang Qian
to help him settle the matter.
Mr. Ding,
you don't deny the crimes you committed against Wang Yu, do you?
I didn't commit any crime.
Xiaoyu,
weren't we in a consensual relationship?
You're an adult, too.
You can't just say
that because we broke up,
you can accuse me of rape.
When did I ever date you?
We have evidence.
Then go call the police.
I know you have your ways.
We'll see you in the papers first.
I've read all the files.
Find a way to shut her up.
Let me go.
I'm not crazy.
Let me leave.
Even if I let you out,
you're dead anyway.
(Hello. The number you have dialed does not exist.)
(Please check the number and try again.)
If you wanted my help against Ding Tian,
there were countless ways.
But you chose the one I absolutely cannot accept.
You shouldn't have touched my daughter.
Actually,
they weren't the only two
he assaulted.
That day
was my graduation from medical school.
To celebrate,
my brother booked a fancy restaurant.
Happy graduation.
Thank you, brother.
Brother,
I will work hard to make money to repay you.
Silly girl.
We are family.
Don't be silly.
Sir, ma'am,
here is your wine.
We didn't order any wine.
It's a gift from the gentleman over there.
Please say thank you for us,
but we don't need it.
Brother.
Why did you forget your keys again?
Smells good.
You even cooked.
I didn't expect you to be so domestic.
What exactly do you want?
Very pretty.
If you don't leave, I'll call the police.
Call the police?
Didn't you ask what I want?
You'll know soon enough.
You almost made me waste my effort.
This is a gift from my mom.
Do you know how precious it is?
Touch my camera again and I'll kill you.
So.
Since then,
I stopped cooking
and only order takeout.
I owed some money back then.
If you can't pay back the money,
I'll leak those photos of you.
What if I still can't pay it back in two days?
How about this?
Let me give you an idea.
You have dinner with my boss,
and the debt will be written off.
What a pity.
You can't speak.
When you do that,
you don't make a sound.
It's fine. Eat first.
You know martial arts.
Does your whole family know?
Don't be afraid.
I'll be gentle.
Did you forget what I just said?
Not making a sound at all?
I hate it the most
when doing the deed,
and the woman makes no sound,
like a dead fish.
Make a sound!
Scream!
Make
a sound!
Make a sound!
Scream!
I will make him pay back double.
At that time, I received an invitation.
Let me help them design an
encryption program.
This is Jessica, whom I mentioned to you.
She's a very skilled computer expert
who won international awards when she was young.
Hello, Mr. Ding.
Boss Ding.
It's so late, you...
I heard you like red wine,
so I brought a bottle.
What?
Am I not welcome?
No.
Come in.
What's this?
It's nothing.
I have a little quirk.
You'll see in a minute.
Have a seat first.
Okay.
Nothing much.
It's just that...
I can't sleep at night.
I came to see you.
I also have something to tell you.
You probably don't make much money programming, right?
Why don't you be with me?
Mr. Ding, are you kidding me?
Do you look down on me,
or the money?
Mr. Ding.
Programming is my job.
It's getting late.
Please leave. I need to rest.
Come here.
Ah!
My men are all outside.
Mr. Ding,
please don't do this.
The more you scream, the more excited I get.
Mr. Ding.
How about this?
Let's go to the bedroom.
It'll be more comfortable there.
Okay.
Let me out.
Help!
The three of us have finished telling our experiences.
Actually, there are many more victims like us.
It was wrong of us to threaten you with your daughter.
But we really need your help.
Action Team