If I had known you were waiting at home,
I would have brought your little brother back too.
I thought the guy who got the passports, rescued Jessica,
and took down Zhang Defa
would either be as strong as Lu Bu
or as cunning as Sima Yi.
I didn't expect that after seeing you,
I'd think you're more like Li Wenming,
and you're even sick.
It's quite surprising.
Who is Li Wenming?
The security guard downstairs.
Thank you for the compliment.
You guys go out first.
Now that they've both left,
why don't you invite me to sit down
and we can talk slowly?
You've been here for over half an hour, right?
You've probably rummaged through my bed.
Do you still need me to invite you to sit?
Let's talk.
Then I'll get straight to the point.
Shao Yu,
from Tangzhou.
Admitted to Tangzhou Police Academy 18 years ago,
graduated with the best grades in the last ten years,
and directly joined the criminal investigation team.
Badge number 016933.
And you became the youngest captain
of the criminal investigation team in Tangzhou's history.
Four years ago, during a hostage rescue operation,
you recklessly shot and killed a suspect.
So you were disciplined
and dismissed from the police force.
After that, you started a small business.
But because of your wife's early death,
you had to raise your daughter alone.
However, you never stepped out of the shadow of taking off your uniform.
So, neither your subsequent career nor your life
has been particularly satisfactory.
And you haven't given enough care to your daughter's growth,
resulting in a not very harmonious father-daughter relationship.
Actually, you've always felt guilty towards your daughter.
She became your weakness.
When others use her to threaten you,
you will do whatever it takes
and are willing to do anything.
You investigated thoroughly.
But since you investigated so much,
you should also know
that I am just a pawn.
So you shouldn't look for me.
You should look for the chess player.
Right.
Although you are just a pawn,
you did do some things after all.
You have to take some responsibility.
I can give you a chance.
Help me find that person,
and I'll let bygones be bygones.
Moreover...
We can also help you save your daughter.
My daughter is in their hands now.
I can't take that risk.
Don't be in such a hurry to refuse.
You don't know much about me and the people behind me yet.
We are absolutely capable of helping you save your daughter.
Of course, from another perspective,
we can also make you and your daughter
disappear forever.
Contact me when you've made up your mind.
That's fine.
We still have plenty of time.
If you change your mind,
you can find me.
Why are you here?
Let's find a place to talk.
I'm working right now.
Wait until I get off work.
What's wrong with you?
Where is my daughter?
Why did you hurt her?
I...
I don't know what you're talking about.
I know everything.
Stop pretending, okay?
Wait a minute.
I'll go change my clothes.
How did you know?
You said you never cook,
and only order takeout.
But you have a habit.
You tear off the personal information section on the receipt
very neatly.
Aunt Liu,
could you please clear the takeout from the table?
Earlier at Zi's house,
I saw that on her leftover takeout bags,
the personal info section was also neatly torn off.
Exactly the same as your habit.
I didn't pay much attention to it then,
but now I understand.
You must have been to Zi's house.
You guys are together.
And my CT report, you prepared it in advance, didn't you?
Before, I had abdominal discomfort,
so I went for a checkup.
But the day the report came out,
something happened to my daughter,
so I didn't get a chance to read it.
Today, I accidentally saw the report
that suspected a tumor in my abdomen.
But the strange thing is,
after you told me there was a foreign object in my abdomen,
all my discomfort
completely disappeared.
Today I got a CT scan,
and I found out
there is no foreign object in my abdomen.
To set up this bomb mechanism,
you conveniently removed my tumor.
You did it, didn't you?
You and Zi kidnapped my daughter
and used her to threaten me into doing your tasks.
You just cut open my belly
and used the wound to make me believe there was a bomb.
I guess you put anti-inflammatory drugs in my abdomen,
wrapped in a dissolvable coating.
After a certain time,
the coating dissolved,
and I would feel pain
and believe there was a bomb.
Of course,
you probably thought it wasn't foolproof enough,
afraid I might get a CT scan myself.
So you figured out a way
to make that bullied boy
appear near your clinic.
I took him to you for treatment,
and coincidentally got a CT scan there.
Then you could use the prepared report
to completely solidify this story.
You kept following me on the pretext
of needing further checks for the foreign object.
Actually, it was just to spy on me, right?
If it was just to spy on you,
it wouldn't be this troublesome.
I was genuinely worried about you,
afraid you'd be in danger.
Put away your fake face, okay?
My purpose for finding you today is simple.
Tell me where my daughter is.
Otherwise,
I don't know what I might do.
I really don't know where she is.
I was forced to do all this.
What did they use to force you?
I can't say.
But I will try my best to help you
rescue your daughter.
How will you help me?
My daughter's pinky
was cut off.
What?
I didn't expect things to go this far.
I thought they just wanted to scare you.
I don't believe what you say.
I only believe what I see.
Give me your phone.
I'm really not lying.
They all contacted me directly using this phone.
Whether you're lying or not,
and whether you were forced or not,
what I want to tell you now is this:
If my daughter gets hurt again,
even just a little bit,
all of you
will pay the price.
Come in.
Good memory.
You memorized my number with just one glance.
Contact me when you've decided.
My home is not safe right now.
They probably installed cameras.
They have my daughter right now.
I can't take that risk.
So you had to reject me back then.
I have no hostility towards you.
They are my real enemies.
I'll cooperate with you.
Help me save my daughter.
No problem.
After all, you proved your loyalty
by exposing the female doctor to us.
I knew you would follow me.
But she's just a minor character.
You'd better not touch her yet,
because
she might be useful to me later.
I finally understand why they chose you.
Let's get down to business.
You said you guys are powerful.
So what can you offer me?
We can provide any resources you want.
And,
if I'm not mistaken,
your next mission
is to get a USB drive.
A new mission is here.
Get a USB drive for me.