Fuck.
Hello, my love.
How are you?
I need to be with y--
That makes no fucking sense.
Emilia reported her brother,
and they both got arrested.
It had to be them.
Well, obviously not.
But why Luis?
Why would he want to kill Joel?
Because he's a son of a bitch. That's why.
Sure, he's not the kind of guy
to use the most orthodox methods
to make sure justice is served,
but being a murderer…
You don't know him like I do.
He's been extorting me for months.
He's a real bastard.
Tell him everything.
-He found out--
-Is it true he was turning tricks?
Tricks? What tricks?
Well, not magic tricks.
We'll tell you later.
-Did you know?
-Emilia blurted it out.
I thought she was trying
to convince me Dalmar killed him.
No, it's true.
They set up a prostitution ring here
behind my back.
Luis found out,
and he's been using it to blackmail me.
I was pissed with Joel,
as you can imagine.
I went to talk to him, and I lost it.
I yelled. I pushed him.
I basically asked him
to stop and leave me out of it.
I guess Joel confronted Luis
and threatened him with Alumni.
-That's how he settled everything.
-Exactly.
So we think
Luis took out the root of the problem.
-So it's your fault, then.
-What?
You got Joel to confront Luis.
What? Am I the one to blame
for his blind ambition, Omar?
Is it my fault that he was
with Héctor and those pricks?
And that he became a sex worker?
Am I really to blame?
What?
The tricks.
Joel was blinded by money,
and he wanted to be like them.
He dug his own grave.
I'm sorry, but it is what it is.
Give me the video.
No, we're taking it to the police.
It's settled.
And what do you think they'll do with it?
They'll stop at nothing
to cover for their own.
This can't be covered up, Omar.
-This is solid evidence.
-We need to be smart, guys.
We have a smoking gun.
The timing needs to be right.
Luis has to pay, of course.
But the siblings can't get away scot-free.
But they didn't kill Joel.
They wasted no time
in accusing you and Dalmar.
Not to mention, they beat me up.
Give me the video.
I promise you, they'll pay.
I want to see Luis behind bars.
You will. I swear.
But let me do it my way.
You owe it to Joel, Isa.
We all do.
I just sent it to you.
You have two days. That's it.
The handsome cop?
They really are the worst.
Cops and handsome guys.
How long do we have
before they let Dalmar out?
He might already be out.
-Héctor and Emilia were arrested.
-Them too?
You know, I would have put money
on those rotten siblings.
-We need to do something, Chloe.
-I know.
I'm sure the Black kid
still has that video of me.
-Mom.
-What?
You scare me when I see you thinking,
whiskey in your hand.
Let's make him an offer he can't refuse.
Sure. Since the last one
was so successful.
Well, we're going to need a plan…
S.
-S?
-S.
"Skedaddle." I just came up with it.
The school year is about to end.
If this fails, it's S.
Plan S.
Getting out of here.
-What about Eric?
-What about him?
Baby, you can find
a cute boy who's crazy anywhere.
Think of Eric as your first go.
By the way,
since you have a thing for nutcases,
make sure the next one is loaded.
Think about your future.
I don't get why you're with Héctor.
He's using you.
You're his plaything.
He only gets a hard-on
when he humiliates you.
It's gonna tear you apart down the line.
Is that what you want?
You sure do love to exaggerate, huh?
He's not like that, Omar.
And even if he were,
I can keep him in check.
Yeah, that's exactly what Samu said.
And look how he ended up.
I couldn't cope
if the same happened to you.
Thanks for your concern. Really.
But there's no need.
Can I tell you something?
Never mind.
No. Say it.
Sometimes I think that
if you and I had met
at a different point in time…
If… I don't know.
If we had met
at a different point in our lives,
maybe things would have worked out.
You wouldn't have even noticed me.
I would have always noticed you. For real.
And… who knows?
Maybe life has a second chance
in store for us.
The future is only two weeks away.
We'll leave all this behind.
I don't feel sad at all.
I only want to heal my wounds.
This week, I'll be asking you
what you'll be doing after Las Encinas.
Is there a life after this?
Is there a future?
Don't be shy. Send me your ideas.
You think?
I don't buy it. It seems so fake to me.
I'm not in the right mindset for this.
Why not?
We need to get our lives back.
You can go back to social media,
pass all these fucking exams,
and leave this behind.
How can I leave this behind,
knowing that Dalmar will be let out
and that he might have
the evidence to put Carmen away?
Not this again. Seriously?
You want justice for Joel's death, right?
I want the same for Raúl.
What more justice do you need?
The guy who abused you is dead.
Didn't you dream of him disappearing
when he bullied you and abused you?
-He's not here anymore.
-But I didn't want that for Raúl.
Can't you see he's got you trapped
even after his death?
He won't let you move on, Sara.
Free yourself from him.
Forget about him.
I'm not sure I can.
You can.
Come on, record me.
Ask me about what I'll do after all this.
You. What do you want?
I'm here to see you.
To see you there,
on that side.
Screwed. Without your power
and your arrogance.
It feels good.
I have evidence that would free you.
It's a video.
Someone left a phone
filming your orgy, and…
Oh, surprise!
It recorded Joel's murder too.
-If I hand it in, you'll walk.
-What are you waiting for?
The thing is, I'm in no hurry.
You corrupted Joel,
and he's dead because of it.
I don't care who the perpetrator was.
What do you want? Money?
I want you to beg me.
To humiliate yourself.
To feel how Joel felt
every time he was with you.
Joel loved fucking me.
He loved everything I stood for.
That's why he was willing to do
whatever it took to succeed.
And he was hungry too.
I bet he never fucked like that with you.
Oh, is that it?
Didn't you want to see me beg?
Aren't you going to fight?
Oh, you impoverished folk are so weak.
You get what you deserve.
You want the video? The solution is easy.
You and your sister sign a confession,
declaring that
you were the ones who beat me up.
One confession for the cops,
one for the public,
saying you wanted to beat me to death.
Oh, Omar. You're bluffing.
You have nothing. Get lost.
Maybe Emilia won't think the same.
Are you really willing to go to jail
for a crime you didn't commit?
You're sentencing your brother
to 20 years.
And you'll get a few years too.
If the evidence exists,
it'll come to light.
With or without your help.
I'm the only one who has it.
And if you don't sign the statement
within 24 hours, I'll destroy it.
No lawyer will be able to get you out.
Not a chance, Aladdin.
POLICE
It must have been really tough, huh?
Why the hell are you here? And you?
We're here to support you.
So that you see you're not alone.
It must be tough to get out
and have no one waiting for you.
So here we are. Carmen and Chloe.
You convinced me to incriminate myself.
Dalmar, don't cling to the past, please.
Only resentful people do that,
and they never amount to anything.
And you know what?
Their skin wrinkles much sooner.
Although with that ebony skin of yours,
you don't need to worry.
Look… get lost.
A hundred thousand.
What?
A hundred thousand for the video.
I'll be deported soon.
If I cooperate with the cops
and share the video,
I might get my residence permit.
Or they might tell you to fuck off
for giving them such irrelevant evidence.
You're offering me 100,000.
It can't be that irrelevant.
Fine.
I admit it.
It could make things
a bit trickier for me.
But I assure you,
it won't solve your problems.
They'll send you back,
and you won't get a cent.
I'm offering you money
and a lawyer to fight for you.
What if I got you a better video?
One where you can see
who actually murdered Joel?
They already arrested those fascists.
They didn't do it.
I'll get you the video,
you give it to the cops,
and I guarantee you
they'll give you your residence papers.
You'll be granted citizenship,
but you won't get a single euro.
Mom.
Why offer him that kind of money
if you have that information?
Mom, give him the money.
Of course. A deal's a deal.
100,000 for your video.
Now, don't tell me
we're not your guardian angels, Dalmar.
Get me that video, and we'll talk.
So, Héctor, tell me.
Are you ready to confess?
Mmm, no. Because I didn't do it.
We'll soon find out who did.
You don't say.
Omar has a recording of what happened.
Have a judge issue an order for it.
What recording?
A perv snuck a phone in to film
our party but filmed something else.
If I were you, I'd tell the judge.
How do I imagine my life
after Las Encinas? Well…
I want to go into medicine
and study psychiatry.
Everything that goes on in here
is super important.
Okay, cut. I sound like a dickhead.
Just a bit.
Let's do it one more time.
Nico, I don't know
if anyone will be interested in this.
Ask me something, then.
Before we talk about your future,
do you have any unfinished business?
I guess I would have done things
differently with my cousin.
That way, we wouldn't be
so distant and screwed up.
To think that the year is coming to an end
and that he might leave like this
isn't cool at all.
Eric, let's fix this, okay?
I swear I'm sorry for all
the crappy things I've done.
Honestly.
I love you, man.
That's better.
What happened?
-We've been robbed!
-You don't have anything to steal.
Omar, we've been robbed.
What?
-Is there something I should know?
-Shit, they took my laptop.
Hey, do you mind if I spend some time
with Omar now?
I have a bad feeling about this,
and… I'll call you later, okay?
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
Okay.
-Is this about Joel's video?
-What?
The video of Joel's murderer.
-You know about it?
-Chloe mentioned it.
And since our apartment is trashed,
I put two and two together.
Maybe you have it and someone wants it.
No. That's not it.
If you had it, we could use it
to get my residence papers.
Right.
Does that mean you have it?
One second, Dalmar.
Hello?
Yes, that's me.
Omar, this is my family's lawyer.
He helped me write my statement.
I admit responsibility for the beating
and for wanting to beat you to death.
All we need is your signature and mine,
and then you'll accept my confession.
That's great.
Come on, sign it.
I have something better.
Whatever you want.
All you have to do is ask.
I'm your Santa Claus,
your fairy godmother, your genie.
Whatever. Tell me what you want,
and you'll get it.
And think big.
I just want your signature.
Would you really turn down
the chance to have it all?
What kind of future do you want?
I'll make it happen. Be ambitious.
Or are you the kind of sucker
who won't dare to have real dreams?
That's how you won Joel over, right?
And where is he now?
You're smarter than him.
And you have the advantage now. Use it.
Your families make you believe that.
In your world, everything is for sale.
But it's not.
I'd set fire to you, your little sister,
the fucking Alumni club, and the school.
-Done.
-What?
You want to finish us off?
And Las Encinas? It's done.
I'll offer you that.
Shut down Alumni, shut down the school.
What are you talking about?
Tell me you don't want it.
Tell me you wouldn't love it
if it all closed for good.
Think about it.
What will happen if I sign this?
We'll be sentenced to a few months,
and we won't even go to prison.
And that public scorn you dream of? Zilch.
Not gonna happen.
Do you prefer that to the grand prize?
So, what should we do?
Should I sign?
Or you give me the evidence,
and we end Las Encinas?
Omar, are you home?
What's going on?
Nothing. Someone broke in,
and I'm a little paranoid.
Nadia, I might make a deal with Héctor
to shut down Las Encinas.
I give him the video
proving his innocence,
and he'll shut the school down.
Omar, are you okay?
Sure.
Stop worrying about me, damn it.
I'm going to end that cancer of a school.
It's in my hands.
That's all that matters.
Not if I'm okay or not, Nadia.
This is much bigger.
Do you hear yourself?
Forget about revenge.
About shutting down the school.
About making deals I don't understand.
Can't you see you're becoming like them?
If you make deals and get swept away
by their way of doing things,
you'll think you're winning.
But in reality,
you'll be their next victim.
-I'll die if anything happens to you.
-I'll be fine.
Isn't that what Samuel said?
And Joel?
Whenever we think we've outsmarted them,
they go in for the kill.
Omar, forget about all of this.
Go to the police.
I can't lose you.
Not you.
Hello.
-Omar.
-I'm here to report a crime.
-Okay.
-I have a video of the night--
-I'll deal with this.
-Don't worry. I'll do it.
Yeah, she can do it.
Don't waste your time.
Don't worry. Come.
No, I'd rather come back some other time.
Relax, Omar. You're in good hands.
If you're reporting a crime,
the sooner, the better, right?
REPORT
GO TO YOUR NEAREST STATION
Tell me, what's this about?
Come on. I'll help you.
You wanted to report something,
and you had a video of the night…
What night?
Do you have it?
Luis, I'd rather come back later.
And I'd rather we be direct about this.
That's if you can. You need to be brave,
and I don't know if you are.
I don't know what you mean,
and I don't get your tone either.
You know perfectly well, Omar. Hey!
Listen. You give me the video,
and your suffering is over.
I wouldn't like you to leave here
and have some sort of accident.
Give it to me, damn it!
No! Help!
Help! Help me!
What's going on here?
Just a misunderstanding.
What the fuck happened, Luis?
You heard him. A misunderstanding.
So he knows you have the video?
We're screwed, guys. I'll call him.
-Call him? What for?
-He's been hitting on me for months.
Will you stop this, Isa?
We'll just go to the police and--
No, Iván. Don't you realize
it's no use going to the police?
Omar was just there.
There's only one way to end this.
Hey, babe. How are you? All good?
Listen, I'm free tonight.
How about we meet up around ten o'clock?
Isa, he's not stupid.
I know he's not stupid,
but he wants me badly. He'll be there.
Trust me.
-Omar, can you stop her?
-We can't go to the police.
-Trust Isa.
-I said no, damn it! Isa!
I won't leave you alone with him.
You'll have to find another solution.
So help me, then.
Okay, but how?
We hang out for a while.
You turn up. We grab him.
Oops! He has a little overdose. He dies.
Isa, are you nuts?
I mean, you've totally lost it.
You want to ruin your life?
Listen, this club is more yours than mine.
My share of it is nothing but debt.
My mother won't speak to me.
My father…
My life is pretty screwed up as it is.
Don't say that--
I'm going to get some champagne,
and we can chill for a while, okay?
-They'll bring it up.
-I want to walk.
I'll do squats on the stairs.
Thank you.
I love you.
I love you so much.
Hey, you're going a bit too fast,
aren't you?
Sorry.
-Sorry.
-You don't have to go.
Are you okay, Iván?
I just kissed Joel.
But it wasn't Joel.
Because I won't kiss Joel ever again.
Guys, love each other as much as you can.
Life is like that. Before you know it…
It's too late.
Let's do a video.
Now?
Sure. Didn't you do
live videos about school and stuff?
This is the very essence of the school.
This is about the future, right?
I don't know what future awaits me.
But what I do know is
that it's much better than a year ago.
Thanks to my cousin and his family,
who took me in and took care of me
despite all of my quirks and my flaws.
I know many people hate Las Encinas now
because of what it represents,
but it has meant everything to me.
All because you were here, Nico.
And you brought me with you.
I love you, man.
And thank you.
Are you forgiving me?
You apologized. What's left for me to do?
I made your life impossible.
But despite that,
you've always been there for me.
Okay, Sara. Cut.
No, let the whole world know, man.
I love you.
I don't know what will happen to me,
especially now that I'm moving out.
But you'll always be with me. Always.
I know many people hate Las Encinas now
because of what it represents,
but it has meant everything to me.
Luis won't pay for Joel,
and the siblings won't pay for beating me.
Las Encinas and Alumni will live on.
It'll be business as usual.
But at least us decent people
can still be honest and dignified.
More like tamed.
So that nothing changes.
Nadia, if we do nothing to change things,
nothing changes.
In order to change
something so systematic,
you can't just punish
every action individually.
You need to get rid of the root cause.
And that's really hard.
It takes a long time,
and it's a long struggle.
Let's have dinner.
Omar, where are you going?
To you.
Because you deserve it.
So you're leaving Nico's house.
Yeah, I've already relied on them enough.
But I won't go far.
Okay.
Because you and I have plans, right?
Yeah, sure.
But we don't need to talk about that.
No.
This is good too.
This is good too,
but you're not avoiding talking
to me, right?
Look, Isa gave me this.
She says doing it on 2C is… Whoa!
You down?
I mean, I don't need anything.
All I need is you. Don't you agree?
This whole thing of taking drugs
at school, at the club, during sex…
-While having a snack, I don't--
-Okay, we won't do it. Look.
What if we record it
and send it to Sara?
Doing live videos of Las Encinas
with no sex involved?
Now, that's not very realistic.
I'm kidding, you dork!
Fuck me as it if were the last time.
What are you talking about?
I'm kidding.
I just got carried away, okay?
But since we're not taking drugs
or making a video, well…
I was joking, silly.
God, I could eat that silly face of yours.
I love you.
Shit.
Hello.
Want a drink?
Or two.
Are you arresting me?
Do you want me to?
My house, my rules.
Put them away.
You won't need them
to have a good time with me.
Trust me.
If I trusted people like you,
I'd be dead already.
Okay, let's play my game for a while,
and then we'll play yours.
Get naked.
I need you to do me a favor.
-Start a live video with me.
-Okay.
Okay, but let's go somewhere quieter.
You're graduating, and I don't know
what you learned at Las Encinas.
I can tell you what I learned, though.
Rich sons of bitches
cover up for each other.
They know how to do it.
Otherwise, how can you explain
that this shitty school
has seen cases of overdoses,
rapes, murders,
and none of them made the news?
I don't get it.
Why do your parents
keep enrolling you here?
My friend Samu was killed.
So was his girlfriend, Marina.
Iván and I almost lost our lives.
And those fascist siblings
and Alumni drove Joel into ruin.
Okay, they didn't kill him.
But that doesn't matter.
This school's poison reaches everywhere
and corrupts everything.
Seriously, isn't anyone
going to do anything to stop this?
Are your children's lives worth so little?
How many more have to die?
How many more have to suffer
to put an end to Las Encinas?
I also need to add a video.
Can we upload it?
Do you think I'm an idiot?
You want to seduce me so that I confess
to a crime you think I committed.
No, baby.
It's more like… the last meal…
for the condemned.
I am that meal.
What are you doing with that?
Killing me with an overdose?
That's how you're going to die,
you fucking bitch!
And you know what? No one will care.
That poor rich girl, gone broke,
addicted to all sorts of shit,
couldn't handle her debts,
the hustlers at her club,
her daddy's death…
Everyone will understand
why you'd want to die.
But I won't stick a needle in you.
You're more into this pink shit, right?
Oh, dear. It was laced
with fentanyl and GHB.
Poor thing. It's too bad.
Open your mouth.
Open up, bitch!
Hey, wake up.
Wake up. We need to have some fun
before I finish you off.
Hello.
Let's cut the crap and fuck already.
Look, I'll give you a little bit of this
to help you relax. Open your mouth.
Open up, Isa. Open your mouth.
Don't move. Open your mouth.
There.
That's it. There you go.
Where the fuck is Luis?
You.
Wake up.
Wake up, hey.
Hey, wake up.
Are you okay?
Isa, open the door, damn it!
What the fuck?
Luis, get away!
Isadora is unconscious.
I don't know what she took.
Call an ambulance.
Shut up!
You're making a mistake!
I had nothing to do with this!
We need to help her.
You're under arrest
for the murder of Joel.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say may be used against you.
Isa, wake up.
Get dressed.
Fuck.
Do you know what your problem is?
You're a fucking mediocre piece of shit
who came into our lives
and thought he could have it all.
Of course.
If a fickle, pampered
little brat like me had it all,
you could too.
And you know what? You can't.
Because even if you were up to your balls
in coke, in 2C,
and every fucking drug in the world,
you would never in your life
reach our standards.
Enjoy your last meal.
-Fuck!
-Come on, let's go.
-What did you do to me, bitch?
-Shut up and walk.
-You're making a mistake!
-Move!
Hey, are you okay?
Yes.
Luis?
Call an ambulance.
Sara?
I think you wanted this.
Do whatever you want with it.
What?
I was planning to use it
to help me with my situation, but…
I don't care anymore.
And I think it's about time
that we all started doing things right.
If I have to leave the country,
I will.
Are you looking for Chloe?
Yes. Have you seen her?
She must have run off.
I sent her a video,
and she probably doesn't like it.
Tell them I'm coming after them.
Her and her mother. Both of them.
Be careful. That's fragile.
And it has to arrive in Milan intact.
They can't wait for us to get there.
Damn it, Emi.
MOVING COMPANY
INTERNATIONAL TRANSPORT
Leaving without saying goodbye?
No. We're only going for a couple of days.
I know Sara has the video of your mom.
I know, Eric, but…
it was a question of time.
We were bound to leave sooner or later.
It is what it is.
You know I'd stay with you all my life.
Do you?
Then take me along.
I'm going with you.
Mom?
That's the last thing you want, trust me.
Besides, don't think of it as a goodbye.
If it's meant to be, you'll meet again.
Say goodbye. We're leaving.
How are you?
Why can't he come with us, Mom?
This pain will go away, my dear.
It will. Believe me.
We all need to put down roots
once and for all somewhere.
Let him do the same
with his aunt and uncle and Nico.
I'll make sure that you meet again.
Sooner than you think.
Okay, honey?
Right now I need you to give me
this trip, just the two of us, right?
Yes.
Put your seat belt on.
Let's go.
I wanted you to see this firsthand.
This is thanks to you, Omar.
And I'm not going to detract from myself,
because I intend
to contribute to the cause
all the files full of scathing information
about this school that I have in storage.
I'm fucking sick of being their puppet.
Dear students, after an urgent meeting
held yesterday
with the members of the School Board
and the Parents' Association,
I hereby inform you that Las Encinas
will close immediately and indefinitely.
What about our exams?
Do we get an automatic pass?
To ensure that you have access
to your final exams,
we have reached an agreement
with a public high school.
Did she say "public"?
The principal's office
will remain at your disposal
to answer any questions
or queries that you may have.
It's over.
SAN ESTEBAN HIGH SCHOOL
Is this a school or a kindergarten?
They're all, like, super young, right?
No, girl. They're our age.
Guys, it's this way, I think.
Hey, how's it going? I have a question.
I need to take a little something
because this is all quite fucked up.
Where's the restroom?
Over there.
Want some?
No.
Subtitle translation by: Toni Navarro
and Meredith Cannella