Maybe im not safer for you
Denial
records
Please like andshare
I still won't repeat it
Stay lover
govern
I still have no hope
It's been a long time
I still can't stop my head
The universe is dark
I still have no hope
Or how to give up
A piece of lies, I don't see the universe
Time is silent
The universe is dark
Who can write your tenderness
Who can always say
Finally, I can't stop
But I can't stop
I'm waiting for you
To become a star
I still have no hope
I'm willing to be with you
I'm waiting for you to become a star
I still have no hope
Episode 1
Uncle, I heard that Brother Tang has disappeared
Can this news be true?
Yes, brother
We are not ordinary people, we are the family's elders
He is not here
Who is the owner of this shop?
Yes, yes
Everyone, it's true that Feifan is missing
Feifan is missing?
Yes, Feifan is missing
What should we do?
Okay, everyone
But it doesn't mean that Feifan is in a bad situation
Everyone, please rest assured
I have sent someone to look for him
I believe that there will be news soon
It's time to settle accounts
The family's elders are not here
How can this be good?
Everyone, everyone
In my opinion
Why don't we choose a temporary manager first
To take advantage of the business
What do you think?
Second brother
You just heard the news of Feifan missing
Don't care about your son's safety
But hurry up and find someone to replace him
Brother, you are mistaken
Our family can't only have this benefit
You have to be responsible for all the East families
Moreover
I am afraid that our military family
Will be destroyed in a few decades
My dad is right
Uncle
You see
You know that brother Tang is missing
Why are you hiding it from us?
What are you talking about?
Everyone, the elders
Not long-term
There is a reason to cover up the price
But now
There is no news of Feifan missing
The Prime Minister sent people to help him find him
I believe that Feifan will return safely
Good
Tang Hu
Come back to our house
Okay, all back
Thank you for your hard work
Go back to your house
Thank you
I thought I could get the power
But your uncle
Is here to help us
I am so ashamed
It seems that Feifan is missing
Uncle can't stay in the capital
He was in charge of the war
Feifan went to the capital to check the accounts
Now he is not here
Uncle will help him personally
He is leaving
The whole army
Isn't it a bit of a fight?
Son, in this situation
How can your uncle leave the capital without worry?
I think he will send a tent
To check the accounts in the capital
Dad, don't worry
I have a way to let him go personally
General
Did you take the medicine?
I took the medicine
But I can't guarantee that he won't stay
My wound
Is to save General
To make him go back to the capital
General
Should you give me some compensation?
What do you want?
I want General to escort me to the west
My young master is not in the west
But I am going to go to the west for him
Who knows what will happen in the capital
If so
Why don't you go directly to Yannan?
My young master has been looking for the incense in Yannan
I am going to the west this time
Except for the business
I want to buy it for you
Beixuan is more expensive than the west
Why don't you go to Beixuan?
I have heard from my mother
Beixuan also has a gold box and a mine
But the military family is not in the same business with Beixuan
I am not familiar with the terrain of Beixuan
I am sorry
What if I go there?
What's the point of going there?
My young master will be so ashamed
So the new incense you have
Is from this incense
What's good about the military family?
You are so concerned about it
Let me see
Where are you going?
How did you promise me?
You went to the west
You went to the dragon pond to study
You were so careless
How could you go there?
But you are so shameless
How can I do that?
My master has sent people to the temple
I have already sent the message
You should be at home and get the news
Father
There is not much time left
You saw the morning stars
I heard that you were not available from the sky
If you really can't come back
It's not cheap
Besides
You are a man
Why can't I go there?
You have been here for a long time
He has a rich experience
You have never been out
How can you compare with him?
General
I have saved your life
Can't you agree to this small request?
Since you already know
The gold and silver are sold in Beixuan
Why don't I take you to Beixuan?
The military and the west are close
So you can buy the lowest price in the gold and silver market
Beixuan
I heard from my mother
The gold and silver are sold in Beixuan
But it is still a big deal
I am afraid that the price of the purchase
Is not as good as the price of the gold and silver market
Young master is the master
You are not worth it
I promise you
Let you and the west go to the fire
The same price is added to the price
Then I will thank general's beauty
But you enter Beixuan
Not difficult
But
I have no family around me
OK
Say it
What's the condition?
Isn't this the owner of the house?
The military family is famous
You have been with the military and the women for so long
The imitation technology should not be too bad
I learned it from young master
Of course
This imitation technology is also the second of the leader
If general does not mind
I will eat the imitation technology of the second of the leader
How about the imitation technology of the second of the leader
How about it
What are you doing
So it's a blind date
Give it to me
Miss is not going to Beixuan
The execution order cannot be in his hands
This is the全部 treasure my father left for me
The whole of Xiangzheng's group
Give it back to me
You said you wanted to make a contract
It's a contract with the rule
The execution order is also the final letter left by young master
Give it back to me
Are you going to give it back
Good
Don't throw it away
You and my brother have been friends for years
Only you
Never lost because of my identity
Even remember his days
I thought I was the first son of Zhengfang
Maybe my father
To make me the leader of his group
Give me a chance to be the emperor
And my mother
As a woman in the west
Can't enter the capital forever
Every year I can only pretend to be a famous woman
Come here to see her
Yao Chengchu, the chairman of the west
And Beixuan
The chairman of the west
I buried your mother here
It's also her wish to return to the old home
This time
My mother can meet you to come to the prime
It's her fortune
It should be my fortune
Your mother is in heaven
If not for you to come to the prime every year
I'm afraid I'm going to die
You and I are too close
It's too close
Mrs. Zhang
General, you're here
Have a taste of this west-flavored dessert
Just help me persuade my little master
To talk about our woman's wish
The girl who brought you to wear a man's dress
I think it's good
It's good to be with my master at a young age
Don't be too young
My little master
This aspect is always not good
Please help me persuade
Aunt
You should prepare dinner
Today we will eat some horse milk and garlic
Look, you're so anxious when you say this
The old man is not a small person
It should have been a marriage long ago
You say yes, General
What Mrs. Zhang said
You have already passed the age of the meat can
In a sense, it should have been a marriage long ago
Yes
Look at what the general said
Okay, you talk about it
I'll go cook dinner
It seems that you still can't let go of that woman
You said
That woman has already married someone else
You should let go
The person who can make you forget
I believe it must be the woman of the seven
그
Li Fenyin
Datsang
You must be the one from the Shame League
He...
is different from others.
After five days,
it's Mrs. Sunba's birthday.
This time,
I only saw the leader of the Western desert,
I think Xicheng Kun
is on the way to the Western desert.
The Sun tribe has been keeping the balance.
The Sun tribe's army of Danyang is not strong enough.
If Xichang Kun is destroyed,
it must be a big trouble.
The Western desert has always been
the enemy of the whole tribe.
Sunba
will know what to do.
Have you forgotten that
Mrs. Sunba's son-in-law, Yuli,
is Xicheng Kun's cousin?
But if we can get close to the Sun tribe,
we should be more than half of the family.
We should be more than that cousin.
Young Master,
I heard that
Princess Liangzhou's son-in-law,
Sun Zhao Min,
is not married yet.
Young Master is in a state of shock.
He's not married yet.
What matters is
that he dares to live in the half of the world.
I'll take you to the mountain of the desert to dig the mine.
All right.
Get ready.
Get up and go to Liangzhou tomorrow.
My Lord,
the Prince of the city sent a secret letter.
What's wrong?
The Princess of Qingkou is leaving the letter.
His Majesty and Empress Dowager
are looking for the Princess as soon as possible.
Time is running out.
We must go to
the Sun tribe tomorrow.
How can we find the Princess?
Go to the Qingkou first.
But the security of the Qingkou is more important than anything.
How about this?
He Jiao,
lead the troops to the Sun tribe to find the Princess.
I'll go to Liangzhou with A'Li.
All right.
I'm here to save you.
This medicine is for treatment.
Take him.
Brother Lie fought the upload photos.
I should choose leave it to him.
Your imperial Rs make it good.
What a pity.
It's not good.
I should use the Kesi to make one.
You know Kesi too?
The Kesi's army never treat me as a sister.
I just know everything.
You're theć forty.
What's so funny?
I just know that
Wu Yubai was
Missishuo.
What?
Nothing.
I just heard about it.
You look like a person
who doesn't care about the world.
Why are you here?
I didn't expect
you're a smart slave.
But I heard
that if you're too smart,
you'll kill the master.
What about you?
Will you kill me?
Sir,
here's the hot water you want.
I'll do it.
I don't know why
Brother Lie and a man from the Yan State
disappeared.
I don't know when
I'll find him.
You said your brother
and a man from the Yan State
disappeared.
Are you here to
ask your brother?
My brother
is a hero from the North.
In the past,
the three-legged thief
and the murder case
were all about Brother Lie.
He's the master.
Of course.
He's the God of War in the North.
It seems that you're in danger.
So you're the daughter of the North.
I'm the enemy princess of the North.
Brother and sister of the King
are the most precious daughters.
If he's not a man from the Yan State,
I might
treat him as a man
and exchange him for a young man.
Do you have a way
to find your brother?
I don't even know where he is.
I'm not with him.
He won't take care of himself.
He lost himself.
I don't know where to start.
Maybe your brother
has returned to the camp.
Why don't we go to the camp and have a look?
Yes, you're right.
I've been out for so long.
Maybe Luo Qi and He Ji Yao
have already found him.
I've been with He Ji Yao since morning.
It's all his fault.
He won't let me follow him.
Even if I didn't find Brother Lie,
it would be good
if I found them.
Are you sure you want to get her?
I don't know when she'll get back to normal.
She will have to struggle lures.
If she can work with
all theterminal bullies and shopkeepers
in one occasion,
the Uhhard Army Project
will raise the case.
Did Lady off- Iím worried about she?
General,
when did you come here?
Why are you so surprised?
You're too obsessed with it.
What are you thinking about?
Zizi's rumors are already very dangerous.
I'm afraid it won't be easy
to go to Liangzhou.
You're worried about my safety.
I thought you were thinking about Jun Feifan.
Young Master is a wise man.
Why do I have to agree with him?
General,
there are many enemies
who want to kill you.
They're like the enemy.
I'd better think about
how to protect my life.
What?
You regret to be with me?
The situation is more serious.
I believe you have a solution.
It's a matter of time.
The evil spirits in the West
don't need to be in the heart.
They can be in the way.
Don't think about it, General.
It's not what you think.
You're just trying to make a move.
When I went to find Lord Luo Zhizhou,
he was already seriously ill.
He would save me or Wu Wu.
He would save me.
But you're suspicious of me.
You're just trying to be my father.
You're late for a short time.
You must be thinking too much.
Miss Qiluo can't be as sincere as you are.
But I'm still there.
I know you're kind.
When will we get out of the city?
Why are you in such a hurry?
You can't miss the chance.
If we can find the golden incense jade stone,
you'll be very happy.
Of course I'm in a hurry.
If that's the case,
we'll get out of the city tomorrow morning.
You've been thinking about getting out of the city long ago.
Why do you say it's because of me?
We don't need to know each other so well.
We should figure it out.
Only then can we get out of the city.
It's late.
You should rest early.
I'm not going to see you off.
The blood is still in the heart.
The fairy was stolen by the horse.
The maid said she couldn't hide it for too long.
She has to prepare the target in advance.
OK.
Let's go.
Thanks.
Slowly.
OK.
Go.
Enjoy!
They are Investing all.
Stay as many as you can.
Let's clink our ه
Everyone has one!
We've just introduced to you.
Keep playing.
Come on.
That's right. Everyone has it.
Everyone has it.
Please.
Then you're done.
Why are you trying to save me?
What?
Don't fight.
Stop fighting.
Don't talk.
Stop.
Stop fighting.
Let's go.
Thank you for helping me.
You look so handsome.
How do you call me?
Call me Qi Luo Bianke.
Mr. Qi.
Miss, can you wake up?
Sorry.
Zhang Min, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
Mr. Sun.
General.
Thank you for saving my daughter.
I don't know why you're here.
Please forgive me.
You're welcome.
We came here
to congratulate Mrs. Sun.
I'm afraid you don't know
that the birthday banquet
of my cousin this year has been canceled.
The Liang State is in a big mess.
Now there's a plan.
The people are helpless.
Now the whole Liang State is in a mess.
Mrs. Wu and I
really don't have the heart
to hold a birthday banquet.
Mr. Sun, you're so kind.
I'd like to share the wedding with you.
Mr. Sun is my cousin.
The Liang State is my business.
I'm not old enough to care about you.
How about this?
The birthday banquet is canceled.
Please forgive me.
I'll be here for a few days.
I'll be grateful
for your help.
Thank you, Mr. Sun.
I've been a murderer for many years.
I've been missing water for many years.
General Lie sent me this token.
It's the blessing of the people of Liang State.
Come on.
I'll toast to you.
It's my honor to share the burden with you.
I don't need to prove myself.
But now, Wang Shengruo
is working with us.
Since Mr. Wu and Lie are here,
I'll help Mr. Sun
to solve the problem of Liang State.
I'm glad to hear that.
It's not a matter of solving the problem.
What's the matter, Mr. Xi?
This is the state affairs of the North.
It's not convenient to talk about it in front of outsiders.
This gentleman is not like the noble of the North.
I wonder what's the relationship
with the general.
Mr. Qi is my benefactor.
You don't need to be angry.
I see you're lucky.
I'm glad to see you're here.
Let me toast to you.
Thank you for your help.
You're welcome.
It's the first time I've come to Liang State.
They're so boring.
Why don't I take you out for a walk?
Mr. Qi, what do you think of my competition?
I'm not good at it.
This gun is good.
It's heavy.
Of course.
I specially made it for the general.
Liang State is heavier than the second one.
What's the point, Your Highness?
My parents gave birth to me.
There was a saying in my childhood.
Women can't even get a gun.
They can't protect the people of Liang State.
I'm so worried.
I always think of choosing a husband for me in the army.
So I've been getting the most guns since I was a kid.
I want to prove that I'm not a man.
I don't need to be a doctor.
I can protect the people of Liang State.
Brother, you only have three daughters.
You still need to have the military property of the army.
How about this?
You can learn from me now.
It's good to help you to share the burden in the future.
Brother.
Father, I can also share the burden for you.
Good.
Don't make trouble.
A girl should learn from her husband.
She should be a woman.
People always have prejudice against women.
Both of you are good women.
Don't talk about others.
Just give up.
Go out and act like a man.
Don't mind the princess.
Actually, I know you're a woman in the city.
You're a woman.
Protecting the people of Liang State is not a matter of consciousness.
Are you ready?
Of course.
As long as I can protect the people of Liang State,
I'll do anything.
Being a tribe leader,
not only can you fight against the enemy,
but also lead the people to live a rich life.
If you have the ability to see this,
I can make a promise to you.
Let the princess be the leader of the Sun tribe
as the young master.
Really?
General, don't you think I'm a woman?
I can't be the leader.
It's hard to be a good leader.
As long as you can be a good leader,
you don't have to think about others.
Thank you for your words.
What are you doing?
You're in the army of the Sun tribe,
and you're still here to fight against the enemy.
Father,
it's all because of the woman by the side of the enemy.
It's a big deal.
It's a good thing for us.
Woman?
The man by the enemy
is the woman who saved me in the city.
I wanted to wear her in front of me.
You fool.
If you wear her in front of you,
won't you be exposed to the enemy?
You're not capable enough to
push the responsibility to a weak woman?
Forget it.
Since the enemy is here,
we'll try our best to get the support of the Sun tribe.
Luckily, we got the line.
You still have to be more careful about Sun Zhao Min.
She's Sun Ba's favorite daughter.
If she comes to you,
we'll take the advantage of her.
I understand.
At the banquet,
Sun Ba didn't want to talk about Liang Zhou's affairs with us.
I'm afraid he's determined to support Xi Chang Kun.
Maybe.
Sun Ba is always loyal.
He doesn't want to participate in the wolf master's battle.
Now he's in a hurry.
He's in the decision between me and Xi Chang Kun.
Otherwise,
he won't leave us.
You used to walk with Sun Ba.
And Xi Chang Kun is his cousin.
He's afraid he won't survive.
But you have my support.
I can fight with them.
I have to get Sun Ba's support
in Liang Zhou's case.
My parents helped the late emperor to get the power.
They sent a weapon to the people.
If it has nothing to do with the north and the north,
I'm sure I won't believe it.
A'Li,
it's been 12 years.
Even the late emperor didn't find any evidence.
The late emperor and the empress dowager
didn't cooperate to protect Wu Hu.
It's an accident.
Don't investigate it.
Now the brotherhood is over.
If Yan Ming can take the position of the wolf master,
I'll take the risk.
So I can only succeed in the wolf master's battle.
I can't fail.
Xi Chang Kun has brought Liang's family to solve the problem.
He's taken the advantage of it.
And Sun Ba is against us.
He's afraid he won't believe it
because he's afraid it's not easy.
The only way to solve the problem is to solve the problem.
You have a way.
You said that
you took a banana from Yan Nan
to the princess.
Yes.
I forgot to give it to the princess.
I'll take it to her.
No hurry. I have a way.
Let's go together tomorrow.
Go.
Sister Zhao Min.
I've been looking for you for a long time.
So you're practicing martial arts here.
I know you like to eat weapons.
I especially found a good weapon for you.
Look.
No need.
I've been looking for you for a long time.
Sister Zhao Min.
We're family.
Take it.
Who said you're family?
Lord Sun and Madam Sun
want to be your son-in-law.
Sister Zhao Min is a good girl.
Fang Yan, Beixuan, Wubu.
Except me,
who else can be your match?
I choose Fu Xu.
You must be on my side.
If you win,
I'll think about it.
Choose the weapon you like.
Gu Yan.
Duke Jiu, are you still here?
I heard Father-in-law say
Jun Fei was
The rest of the people have been sent to the Sanbukuan to know the situation.
My lord has sent some high-ranking men to find Feifan.
Any news?
Not yet.
It's strange to say that
we didn't find Jun Feifan and the guard's corpse at the scene.
Do you know why?
Your majesty,
the Sanbukuan was a criminal.
It's common to kill people.
Feifan was lucky to meet a thief.
He must be in a dilemma.
He wanted to know the truth.
He escaped to find the body of Xuan Iron.
His majesty...
His majesty was so smart.
Then did he go the wrong way when he was looking for the body?
Your majesty,
Feifan is a common person.
What path should he take?
He knows the most.
Er 냉 !
Yu'er, i...
You always go for the lead.
I was right about the last thing we did.
Your majesty,
you can feel at ease.
I've already made some decisions
They alone reject you and only give us the funds.
400 lire.
Upon those talks,
Father, don't look at me.
If you have the support of the Prime Minister,
will we be able to get the military power?
What do you mean?
Didn't we bring all the great masters to find the great uncle last time?
He took the Prime Minister to suppress us.
Now they're not here.
Why don't we focus on the relationship between the Prime Minister and him?
But the Prime Minister and them have been closer these years.
If we go to find the Prime Minister,
do you think it's good?
Father, you're wrong.
The Prime Minister can see that
it's our military power's signature.
It's not his military power's fault.
Moreover, the military power's fault is not over yet.
The uncle is already old.
The Prime Minister knows better than me.
Choosing the new chief of the military power is a disaster.
In my heart, I became a shadow
Embracing the song of my hurt and tears
Full of the past, the red sunset
Just a little bit, a little bit of love
Falling into my heart, becoming a heart
Embracing the song of my hurt and tears
Full of the past, the red sunset
Just a little bit, a little bit of love
Falling into my heart, becoming a heart
Embracing the song of my hurt and tears
Full of the past, the red sunset
Just a little bit, a little bit of love
Falling into my heart, becoming a heart
Embracing the song of my hurt and tears
Let you fall in love with me again