I'm fine.
Come.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Come.
Are you hurt?
I'm not.
I'm dead.
We can only find the others.
Come.
What's wrong?
Did you hurt yourself?
I'm fine. I can't leave.
Come on. I'll carry you.
You're injured.
I can leave by myself.
Go to the military base.
You should change your military uniform.
Don't let me say it again.
Come on.
Chief.
Take away the stone.
First, take the bomb out of the room
and report it to Brother Wang.
Then lock it here.
And report it to the police.
Remember.
You don't need to be involved.
Chief.
But on the west side...
Brother Wang is in charge.
And I won't say anything
about the Xichengkun.
Yes.
Chief.
I heard the bomb exploded.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
What's this?
Look.
Chief.
This is the report from the Ye Nantan.
This is the portrait of the military.
When I opened it,
I felt like a girl.
But it wasn't.
Chief.
The portrait is a horrible quality.
And the detective said
the military was in Ye Nantan's family.
After the Xichengkun,
they went straight to the capital.
But the military looks good.
They are brothers.
General, are you here to ask me
if it's the military's rebellion?
Are you?
I also hope so.
This way, I can get freedom.
And I'm not a child.
I'm a child.
I'm not a child.
I can only take the patient to a good place
to take the rebellion
to the capital.
General,
I've been out for so long.
I haven't been to the capital.
If the rebellion is gone,
it won't be like this.
I've been to the capital with Feifan.
How can the military suspect me
to be Feifan?
Just ask.
Let's go back.
Here.
Thank you, General.
The Empress Dowager is here.
Your Majesty.
What's going on?
Mother.
Yu'er, how is Yu'er?
Yu'er.
Mother,
the doctor said that Yu'er was too frightened.
She needs to rest.
Your Majesty,
what's the reason for you to find out?
Luo Zhizhou went to check it out.
It was because there were many people in the horse market
that the horse was frightened.
So he went to the market and frightened Yu'er.
Now I've already
handled the rider of the horse.
After a few days,
I thought of letting the Empress and Yu'er
go with me.
Now it seems that
Yu'er is afraid that
she has a plan against me.
I'm afraid.
Your Majesty,
Yu'er is always brave.
She won't be afraid
because of the surprise.
She's afraid to be angry.
These days,
she has been arguing
and wants to go to the amusement park.
There are chances for her to go to the amusement park.
Now the Empress
should accompany Yu'er to take care of her body.
That's the most important thing.
When the body is well-being,
she can ride the horse.
It's time for her to go.
Mother.
Just listen to Your Majesty.
Stay in the palace
and take care of Yu'er.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I respect your words.
I'll get you some medicine.
Thank you.
You should take good care of your wound.
From the south to the north.
The road is dangerous.
It's dangerous to die several times.
It seems that I still have to
complete the appointment with General
and go back to the military base.
Brother Liu.
I'm sorry.
Third Sister.
Brother Liu.
Qingming.
Qingming, you're still alive.
I thought you...
How did you get into this?
I'm still alive.
I'll be with you in the future.
Stop it.
I've told you several times.
Didn't I say I wanted to see you?
It's her.
Who are you?
Stay away from my slave.
Slave?
Qingkong, I have no choice.
Brother Liu.
I didn't find you in her.
But I got a slave
from a foreign slave.
Look at her.
How is this slave?
She's right.
You hurt her.
She's too good.
She almost got killed
and sold her to be a flower shop.
I'm not hurting her
to save her, right?
Brother Liu.
Look at my side.
How about you show me now?
Qingkong.
Don't fool around.
I'm not fooling around.
Qingming.
Why did I talk to you?
Don't make me cold because of Brother Liu.
Qingkong.
Miss Jun is not a slave.
She's my guest.
Your Highness.
I'm from the businessmen in Ye Nan.
I'm Jun Qiluo.
Brother Liu.
Are you with her?
Otherwise,
how can a businesswoman
be your guest?
Miss Jun saved my life.
Of course, she's my guest.
So you saved Brother Liu's life.
Okay.
Then you're my guest.
Your Highness.
I have a favor to ask you.
Please take it.
Take a look.
I'll thank you for saving my life.
You're right.
She's our guard,
Shao Qiming.
She's not a slave
but a slave.
Please let her go.
I just said that
Qingming is my slave.
Even if you're Brother Liu's guest,
you can't be a slave.
Are you going to
challenge me?
How can you be a slave?
Li Shanlie is the most slave.
How about Li Lianlang?
If you win,
she's yours.
Okay.
Qingkong, don't make a fool of yourself.
Brother Liu.
This is a game
that Miss Jun didn't make.
Don't interfere.
Miss Jun is injured.
I think you don't want to be promoted.
You'd better rest.
You can play tomorrow.
Okay.
I'll never admit that I'm a slave.
If that's the case,
we'll go to Li Shanlie's place tomorrow.
We'll be there at the top of the list.
Okay.
Don't go back to rest
when you're tired.
Don't worry about the king.
Let's go.
I'll take you to the old house.
Why did you stop me?
The competition will be more painful
if you push and push.
You're a female,
but you're smarter than her.
Qingkong is on the horseback.
You can beat her.
How can you know
that I can't beat her?
Anyway,
I must win
no matter what.
I'll do my best
to win.
no matter what.
I'll do my best
I must save Qi Ming as soon as possible.
Miss,
you're so nice to your servant.
Qi Ming is not a servant.
He grew up in my house
since he was young.
He's my family.
I brought him out
but he didn't protect him.
He was so naive.
I was so naive.
Miss,
if you win the competition tomorrow,
he can come back to you.
The situation is that
even if I win,
he might not
protect her.
Why do you still have a general?
He will definitely help you.
General,
he only helps the princess.
How can he help me?
Miss, you're too much.
Look,
the general knows
you can't eat
the food in Beijing.
So Luo Qi asked a few
Yanan chefs to cook for you.
He also asked the He's team
to go to the Sanbuguan
to buy some
Yanan seasoning for you.
The general was born in the business.
He never cared about the ceremony.
But he didn't dare to
take Miss Man's ceremony.
He's already
aware of the general's concern.
The general also knows
Yanan's food
is all small and delicate.
And Beijing
uses a large plate of heavy-duty food.
So he specially
chose many delicate dishes.
He made
a big dish of Su Lao.
These days,
the general's concern for Miss
is all in his eyes.
These concerns
are probably not for the general.
Miss
knows his feelings for you.
The princess is the only one
in the world.
No one
dares to offend her in the whole of Beijing.
But the general
will listen to you.
If you're worried,
tell the general about it.
No matter how the princess
makes a move,
she won't leave.
Now I know
why she's
going back to the capital with the princess
and wants to take her back.
Miss Qiluo.
No one can take
my permission.
Young Master,
in order to let Miss Jun
play the role of a military pilot,
we have to
work hard.
What do you think
is their relationship?
What relationship?
Of course it's Miss
and the guards.
They just called her Miss.
Do you hear that?
Yes.
Young Master,
are you new to the army?
I mean
she's in the 3rd division
and called her Qiluo Young Master.
Young Master is still thinking about it.
Miss Jun
pretended to be a military pilot
and was injured.
She would help me.
Besides, she's a personal guard.
And look,
the military pilots
are all in the same boat.
What's the point of suspecting her?
Miss Jun
is the eldest lady of the military.
Send a message to the military pilots.
If she sees the security of the eldest sister
and comes to the 3rd division
and breaks the bones,
the military pilots
will be in danger.
I'm afraid
she won't risk her life
for Qiluo.
Make sure
the military pilots
are not afraid of her.
I didn't come to ask you.
When did
you become
a Qiluo Young Master?
But you don't know
that Miss Jun
is a man.
She's actually
the eldest lady of the military.
She's a soldier.
What?
Slow down.
Gu Fei,
the horse is running too slow.
There's no time to ride.
It's so fast.
Your Majesty,
the young master is so arrogant.
I'll go talk to him.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Young Master.
Calm down.
Yier.
Your Highness,
the young master is scared
and scared of the horse.
He's still scared.
The young master is so arrogant.
He's afraid of hitting the horse.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
Yier doesn't
hit the horse on purpose.
He just
was so happy
a few days ago.
I thought about
this every day.
Don't blame me, Your Majesty.
Yier asked me
to play with you.
Since that's the case,
I'll let Yier
meet you
at the amusement park.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Yier.
What's the meaning of this?
I taught you
the kungfu of the Qing State.
At least you got
a good lesson from me.
You can't even hide
the most outstanding moves.
How can you win it tomorrow?
You should try it.
I'll help you
with this.
You're asking for me for the first time?
You're doing this
for a man?
He's always
by my side.
He never
made me feel wronged.
Now,
because I'm so affectionate,
I have to
throw him out
no matter what.
He's a man of the imperial family.
You're sick in the capital.
Why do you
live like this?
He's a completely different person.
But my father
wants to marry him.
General,
as long as you can
save the Qing Army,
I can agree to
whatever the conditions are.
What about you?
What do you think?
Your father
wants to marry him.
So you agree?
General,
what do you mean?
I don't know.
I just want to
marry him.
If you're willing,
I'll do it.
I'll let you know
how to get married.
But I don't know
what you're thinking.
You said
to save Shao Qiming,
you can agree to whatever the conditions are.
I heard that
the Ma Zui will be
a team in the third division.
I wanted to
save the Ma Zui
but I'm too late.
I have to save the team
and get the gold and silver.
I know you have
a father.
But I never mention it.
Now,
Shao Qiming is fighting with you again.
I'll let you go again.
If you're not happy,
you can kill me.
I won't be embarrassed.
Are you serious?
Qin Hu.
Are you okay?
Big Wan you...
Group.
I don't want you and me to be together.
Even if I kill you now,
the dead won't come back.
If you really want to make up for it,
let the three departments stop the incident of the armed assault and the murder.
Okay.
The incident of the armed assault and the murder
will never happen again.
I will guard the side of the department
and protect the safety of the wound.
Why is Miss so close to Xuan Lian?
So you're here to fight with me for that Ye Nan's girl.
But Brother Lie is the warrior of the north.
The future wolf master.
No one can fight with her.
You're poisoned.
You're a martial arts master, but you don't escape.
I knew you had a purpose.
So I added a little bit of softness in that incense.
What are you doing?
I want you to listen to me.
Jing Ming,
you used me to make her a criminal.
You're my person.
If you want to come, you can come and go.
If you dare to let that young girl
protect me,
I will make sure she won't die in the north.
What's wrong?
You're in a bad mood.
I heard you're in a bad mood.
So I came to drink with you.
It's not good.
I heard from Qing Kuo
that she will compete with Miss Jun tomorrow.
Are you helping Qing Kuo to make a plan?
Or helping Miss Jun?
If you can't search the road,
you must go to the phone number.
Then search the stop.
Watch out for this sentence.
Be careful not to make a mistake.
Otherwise you can't search.
Then turn around and click on the complete list.
You can get in after searching every time.
After getting in,
it's the hot house and the movie theater.
If you can't find it,
you can search the right corner.
The first time I asked for it,
I was just gonna win.
She wanted that guard to come back to her side.
You can make a deal
with the other team.
Isn't it nice?
Why are you unhappy?
I'm afraid that guard will take her away.
I still need to rely on her
to find Jun Feifan.
Is this your real idea?
Or is it the trap you found yourself?
A'Li,
your concubine
can't be a woman of the same kind.
Don't believe in too much.
How about this?
I'll go to the theater with you tomorrow.
I'll keep an eye on you.
Qin Mi.
Xiaoxian.
What happened to you lately?
How could you be...
No, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
We should leave now.
I'll escort you back to your home.
No.
I haven't got the key yet.
I found the Prince of the King's name.
If we leave now,
all the deaths of our journey will be wasted.
No.
I won't let you and me separate.
Let's leave here first.
We'll figure it out.
I've found the key.
I'll go to the theater with you.
I'll figure it out.
I've found the Prince of the King's name.
But in the Beixuan Palace,
only Xuanli can help me get the key.
Xiaoxian, don't you forget what happened to Qian Shan?
Xuanli is a real man.
She's not a real man.
You can't be with her.
The Shang team is not his intention.
The man of the Xins is a man.
Besides, he promised to save you for me.
The Shang team is a deal.
A deal?
He's already said something
in the middle of the night.
What happened in the real world?
What happened?
You find a place to hide.
If the princess finds out you're not here,
she'll come to find you.
Think of something.
Please come to me.
Be safe.
Xingkou, Miss Xu Yan is a guest.
You found her on the horseback.
Don't lose your gift.
Brother Lie,
the competition is the competition.
Even if she's a guest,
I won't let her down.
You can't go in.
As long as you're safe,
I'll win.
I know.
Brother Lie is so weak.
The princess is a master of chess.
I'll teach her a lesson today.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
Do you think they're good at chess?
After all, Miss Qi Luo is a hard-working girl.
The princess has grown up on the horseback.
She must have a better reputation.
It's not certain.
Miss Qi Luo,
no matter it's a strategy or a plan,
she's always thinking about her men.
If Miss Xu Yan really wins,
will she leave with Shao Qi?
You watch them.
If you get in,
you'll be punished immediately.
Yes.
Why did you come to Bi Xuan?
To kill you.
I told Miss Qi and Shang Du.
I didn't come back in person.
You should leave now.
Leave Bi Xuan.
Let go of Miss Qi Luo.
We'll leave immediately.
She's staying by my side.
You can't take her away.
Don't make a fool of me.
You're a traitor.
How can you keep her away?
Don't worry about her.
Go.
It's boring to fight in this place.
Why don't you go and kill the tiger?
You can't kill the tiger.
If you succeed,
I'll leave you alone.
She's been staying by my side for so long.
I haven't raised you up.
Are you too arrogant?
Yes.
Since you're so confident,
let's hide in the desert.
Let's hide.
Miss Qi Luo is your important person.
I'm more important.
Chief,
the princess is leaving with Miss Luo.
Let's go.
This is the entrance.
We can take the tiger back later.
Your Highness,
the painting is good.
Let's go.
Go.
Brother Liu,
let's go.
I won.
I'm happy to leave.
Your Highness, I won the game.
Please promise me.
Who said you won?
What's the meaning of this?
I'm the princess of Beixuan.
I can do anything.
It's none of your business.
I'm the one who's been watching.
I don't want to hide anything.
Please.
Let's share it.
Brother Liu,
you're doing this for her.
You're ruining our game.
I won't.
We're from Beixuan.
Your beauty is so sweet.
It's good to let it go.
You're not the one who's done this.
Why did you only say me?
You're right.
It's the princess I promised.
Don't blame her.
Come here.
What are you doing?
The evil spirit and the evil spirit.
Send the Shaoqingmen back.
Yes.
Qin Kou.
A'Li.
I'll send her back.
Please.
I'm not leaving.
She's my slave.
I must take her away.
For a Shaoqingmen,
do you want to fight with your brother?
I...
What?
He's the only one who's with me.
I won't let her go.
Don't make things worse.
Otherwise, Your Majesty...
What will you do to me?
What about the Empress Dowager?
If she knows about this,
she'll kill Shaoqingmen.
Go back with me.
Lian.
Our chance has come.
What?
Someone wrote a letter to Jun Feifan.
They said that
the military chief's sister Jun Qiluo
was in their hands.
Yes.
But she was tortured.
She also asked Jun Feifan
to go to the Ministry of the Third Ministry
in a limited time.
Or else,
Jun Qiluo would be killed.
But Jun Qiluo is in the capital.
Why would he show up in the Ministry of the Third Ministry?
That's a good idea.
I'll send him back.
Why would he show up in the Ministry of the Third Ministry?
Jun Qiluo is cunning.
He'll leave.
The important thing is,
you change the letter
and send it to Uncle.
You're a bad boy.
You can't be so anxious.
No, he still loves the woman.
Jun Qiluo is Jun Feifan's sister.
By then,
aren't you afraid of him?
I don't know
where Jun Feifan is at the most.
Don't make things worse.
I'm going to be a good cook this time.
I asked him to escape once.
I can't let him escape for the second time.
Xiaoh Chiang,
is she Yang resting?
She IKEA assigned me
on thewentater meeting with Sixth Prince.
Awesome.
Boneless.
Miss.
Have you seen Qin Ming?
He is still here
when I arrived early in the morning?
I can't translation
the Lord to tell me
hisdling to the north conspiratorily.
Miss.
the Fifth Ministry of escorted Unknown Order
will be in time.
His Majesty has called for me.
Xi Changkun will not let us in easily.
There's always a way.
Young Master.
We have a secret team with a man with a stomachache.
A secret team?
The location is full of information and information.
There are two departments in the house.
The location is very complicated.
Almost no place to enter.
If the evidence is really in the secret team,
we have to think of a safe plan.
Young Master, the palace is open.
Your Highness, you are in the palace right now.
What's the matter?
We just know that the West Department is fighting against the security forces.
I heard that it's a very serious matter.
It seems that someone can't do it.
General Lie.
Miss is eating the East.
What?
With the Shao Qi people.
What happened is not true.
Young Master,
it's not the time for Xi Changkun to be in the palace.
He Qun, you go to the palace to serve the order.
He Ji wants to follow me.
Yes.
Your Excellency, according to your arrangement,
Shao Qi people have already gone to the secret team according to the information.
After the news of the girl in Yan Nan's business,
she immediately followed.
Where is Li?
As you expected,
after General Lie and Miss De Zhi's leaving,
she also followed.
Lian.
As long as you don't show up now,
I don't need to face you.
My Lord.
Do you dare to ask if this plan
is to attack Princess Qinghou?
Why are you asking like this?
When I just returned to the palace,
I saw Princess also going to the secret team.
Princess Qinghou left the palace without any reason.
She will definitely attract the attention of the Queen Mother.
If the Queen Mother orders to follow her,
it will be troublesome for her.
Don't waste your time.
Before the black sky,
you must make the choice and avoid the forest.
Yes.
My Lord, the secret team is ahead.
If we go in,
we will be caught in the trap.
We will also break your plan.
Sister, the oil will be in the oil.
The sky can only find people.
Brother Li.
What are you doing here?
Someone saw my slave going to the forest.
He Ji Yao, take Princess back to the palace.
Yes.
Find her. No one wants to take me away.
Princess, Qinghou.
My Lord, I will go after her.
Wait a minute.
Don't go back to the secret team.
Take her to the mountain range.
I will go there.
Yes.
Qingming.
My Lady.
What are you doing here?
I saw the letter in your room.
I said I wanted to find some gold and stone to come to the secret team.
It seems that the slave knows that you want to go to the secret team.
It's not a trap.
It's just a dream.
It's good that he wants to kill me.
I also have a plan to report.
It's not him.
He doesn't have to do that.
Besides, he doesn't know
that I want to find the key to the secret team.
My Lady.
You are in the dark now.
It's him.
But I know something about the days we spent together.
I don't have to do that.
But I have never seen anyone else
who went to the secret team.
Except him.
Who can send my letter to the secret team?
There is a miracle at this time.
Let's leave here first.