Pi Han Wool needs to be
sent to the disciplinary committee.
So will we, then.
You might get expelled, too.
I'm okay.
We're okay, too, then.
Right.
By the way,
the teacher who tried to
punish Pi Han Wool a year ago
was murdered the night before the meeting.
Pardon?
The police said it was a random killing,
but Yuseong kids secretly believe it was Pi Han Wool.
What? Just to prevent the meeting?
That makes no sense.
Would Pi Han Wool really go that far?
Because it would've gotten him expelled.
Yuseong isn't just a school to him.
It's a kingdom he created.
But he gets kicked out of it?
Not only would it hurt his ego,
the succession plan at Yeonbaek
would be affected, too.
No one would fear him anymore, then.
He'd risk his life for it.
Anyway, he'll do anything to cancel the meeting.
What are we considering?
We just need to attack him first.
- I agree.
- No.
- Why not?
- What if we fail?
Why are you thinking about failing first?
Ms. Lee's safety is on the line.
We have to be absolutely careful.
No, but—
Se Hyeon is right.
We can't let her get hurt even a bit.
What do we do, then?
Until the meeting happens,
we'll have to protect Ms. Lee.
♫  Yeah, we the backpacker  ♫
♫  Inside my backpack is firm determination, we are the backpackers  ♫
♫  We are the backpackers, yeah the backpackers  ♫
♫  Even if my shoes get stained, backpackers  ♫
♫  We are the backpackers, we start out fearlessly  ♫
♫  Bad bish in this game, there are no rules in this game  ♫
♫  Bad vision on my mind, we'll find a way to win  ♫
♫  It's all your fault, all I need is my backpack, the boss of this block, right  ♫
♫   Yeah we the backpackers  ♫
♫  Even if my shoes get stained, backpackers  ♫
♫  We are the backpackers, yeah we the backpacker  ♫
The investigation regarding the children...
has there been any progress?
Yeonbaek Gang must've silenced everyone.
It's not easy to find the witness.
By the way, Ms. Lee,
how about you stay away from the school for a while?
We don't know what Pi Han Wool will do.
I'll try to protect you as much as possible,
but there's a limit to that, too.
Are you telling me to run away?
Come back after the meeting.
If a teacher runs away in fear,
it'd set a bad example for the students.
They even spread fake news.
We don't know what they'd do.
I should protect them with the disciplinary meeting.
It's me, Ms. Lee.
What made you call at this hour?
Are you sure you won't give up on the meeting?
I'll pretend I didn't hear it and hang up.
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
If that's what you really want,
I need to tell you something.
Regarding Yuseong Tech High
and Yeonbaek Foundation's corruption.
Why are you... telling me this tonight?
From the way it's going,
the meeting might actually happen tomorrow.
Ms. Lee, will you really go to school now?
Will you be okay?
The vice principal wants to make a confession.
I should hear him out.
It's the night before the meeting.
If...
they're up to something...
Even so, this would be a chance.
As you already know,
Yuseong isn't normal.
Chairman Pi laundered money using the
Yeonbaek Foundation to fund his political career.
It's a known secret.
His father is the king of Yuseong.
Of course, no one could touch Pi Han Wool.
In the end,
the school has been raising a monster.
You prepared well for the meeting. Right?
Yes, don't worry.
I have written testimonies from the victims
and testimonies from the teachers, too.
How impressive you are, Ms. Lee.
I'm truly touched.
I appreciate you working up your courage, too.
Vice Principal!
Vice Principal.
Where did he go?
Surprise.
This is giving me major deja vu.
I think something similar happened before.
What did I say then?
"To steal someone's time, you don't threaten them.
You ask for understanding."
Wow, seriously.
I was so moved then.
That's why...
I'll ask you to understand first.
Ms. Lee Han Kyeong,
give it to me while I'm asking nicely.
Ask nicely? F*** it.
Give it to us, you f***ing bitch.
Geez, this is so much work.
Please give it to me.
You were recording?
I'm taking this.
Here.
Will you really hurt me?
Why?
You thought what happened to the teacher was just a rumor?
Even if I disappear and the meeting gets canceled,
your wrongdoings won't disappear.
So, please stop now, Pi Han Wool.
I'll give you a last chance.
I think you're mistaken about something.
I'm the one who's been...
giving you a chance,
Ms. Lee Han Kyeong.
Soon, the police will come.
It records well. Right?
Yes.
By the way, do you really have to do this?
I want to be the evidence myself.
Just 30 minutes.
I'll go in if I don't hear from you after that.
Oh, Detective Na Tae Man?
Mic check. One, two.
Can you hear me, you idiots?
You're all dead,
you f***ing sons of bitches!
♫  A'right. This is my world  ♫
♫  I have a question. What about this hood?  ♫
♫  Guess who's back? Tell 'em I'm back. Bring a lot  ♫
♫  Bring anyone. Do your best  ♫
♫  My name on top  ♫
♫  Parking lot, backyard, rooftop  ♫
♫  I turn them into my stages by standing there I'm yawning  ♫
♫  I'll let you sleep soundly as if you're on vacation  ♫
♫  I go after my goal with a pure look  ♫
♫  I don't want to see a loser in the mirror  ♫
♫  Make more plans  ♫
♫  I have no doubts  ♫
♫  It's pretty funny...  ♫
The meeting will happen at 10:00 a.m. in four days.
In four days?
We need to watch Ms. Lee closely until then. Right?
- Yes.
- Three days is 72 hours.
- 72 hours.
- We can totally do it full-time.
Guys,
you need to be careful.
If a teacher runs away in fear,
it'd set a bad example to the students.
Done, right?
Ms. Lee, I don't get this question, either.
Oh, that one?
I'm confused by this one, too.
I think this would take some time.
This one, too.
Will you really go to school now?
It's the night before the meeting.
If they're up to something...
Even so...
this would be a chance.
Guys.
How did you know I was here?
F***. Damn it.
You're the cheeky 10th graders.
Could you move?
Ms. Lee needs to sleep well tonight.
There's a f***ing important event tomorrow.
- A disciplinary meeting.
- Wow.
The babies came to save the teacher?
How scary.
That f***ing...
You chose the wrong side, Soon Cheol.
Give me a f***ing break.
Come at us, assholes—
Joon, leave with Ms. Lee.
What? Why should I leave?
Because I trust you the most.
You mean that, right?
He loves it.
Go, Ms. Lee.
- Hurry up, Ms. Lee.
- Guys.
Hurry! Hurry!
You came faster than I thought.
Joon, you go first.
- What?
- Se Hyeon.
Hurry, Ms. Lee.
Lee Joon!
Long time no see, Joon.
Anti.
I'm in the Yeonbaek Family now.
So, don't look for me anymore.
Ms. Lee, leave now.
Joon.
They'll cuss me out if I don't get you out.
Hurry up and leave now.
Hurry.
Ms. Lee Han Kyeong...
I could've followed her and finished her off.
But I've been wanting to fight you.
- What are you doing here?
- Well...
Han Wool said the scouter position for
Yuseong was available.
By joining the family, you meant...
becoming Pi Han Wool's underling?
Pi Han Wool?
You used to get beat up and bleed like a loser.
How dare you utter his name?
Thankfully, Han Wool... let me have a revenge match.
Move, move!
What was the motive for murder?
Move!
You screwed my dad.
Should I start by removing an arm?
What happened to your spirit, loser?
This f***er is high maintenance.
♫  Come out, come out  ♫
♫  Wherever you are  ♫
Bingo.
How fun.
I haven't had such a tight fight before.
Why are you taking things so far?
They've been tortured,
bullied,
and forced to take the wrong path.
They wanted to, but they couldn't study.
School shouldn't be a place like that.
Why are you taking it so far?
- What?
- If you canceled the meeting quietly,
Lee Han Kyeong or your friends wouldn't get hurt.
Shut up!
Gosh, what do I do?
What's with those eyes?
What's the point of staring like that?
Should I remove them for you?
Anti, why?
Color it red to look tough, so no one picks on you.
Haven't you seen "Slam Dunk"?
What ruined you like this?
If I became strong,
I thought I could stay with you.
Give me a break.
F***!
Idiot.
It's easier to fight you one on one.
Bang. I'm done here.
Shit.
Who says it's one on one?
You little bitch.
You fight two at a time in 2:2.
The bullies versus the study group.
Let's see which team works better together.
You're out of luck.
You're out of ammunition.
I'll teach you... a real lesson now.
F***. You f***er!
Let go!
- Joon.
- Let go!
Wake up, Lee Ji Woo!
Focus on the basics!
Why try to cover everything?
Just focus on the basics.
What, you bastard?
Look at the ones who get the perfect score.
They say they only study the textbook.
Stop being greedy and...
just focus on the basics.
You want to learn martial arts?
I want to support Ga Min, too.
I'll do anything.
Violence isn't allowed.
But...
to protect what's precious,
you sometimes need to fight.
So, what did you learn from Ga Min's mother?
I've never hit anyone and...
I was afraid to get hit, too.
She said there are only three things I can do.
What's the first one?
Endurance.
To be exact,
the courage to keep my eyes open while being hit.
Hey. Wow, what a strong punching bag.
You must've trained at Yuseong.
Right?
What's the second one, then?
Memorizing the vital spots.
The last is the hand skills.
It's the knuckle punch for a fight.
A loser like him...
Why don't you study, too, then?
This isn't your 100%, right?
By chance,
did you think buying time with me
would get Lee Han Kyeong out of here?
What?
You underestimated me.
I'm disappointed.
What did you do with Ms. Lee?
So?
You want to use your full power now?
I'll crush you properly.
So, bastards like you don't get false hopes.
I said working hard doesn't do anything.
You think Yuseong would change if I'm not there?
Even if I disappeared,
Yuseong wouldn't change.
Never.
Everything changes.
I'll...
I mean...
we'll show you.
Ms. Lee.
- Come here.
- She's alone.
- What will you do?
- Come here.
Give me a break.
What will you do?
You want to fight?
What are you doing?
Come here.
Ms. Lee!
What?
What are you?
Come here!
You should return the favor to Ms. Lee.
It's none of your business.
Look. Getting pinched hurts.
But Ms. Lee...
got stabbed for you.
I can't stand owing someone. F***.
We're doing this because of that psycho?
Why am I on the frontline?
♫  We the backpackers  ♫
♫  Inside my backpack is firm determination  ♫
♫  We are the backpackers  ♫
Grow up, you sons of bitches.
♫  Even if my shoes get stained, backpackers  ♫
♫  I always start barefoot without fear  ♫
♫  You're all basic to me, but I always step high  ♫
♫  My black top got dirty, I loosen my necktie  ♫
♫  You don't get the basics, stupid  ♫
♫  I'm ready to fight right  ♫
Come at us!
You F***ERS!
♫  We're the backpackers  ♫
♫  Even if our shoes wear out, backpackers  ♫
♫  Yeah, we're the backpackers  ♫
♫  Our promises are in the backpacks, backpackers  ♫
♫  We're the backpackers  ♫
Here's the disciplinary committee's verdict.
More than half of the committee members agreed
to have Pi Han Wool, the 11th grader...
expelled.
If Pi Han Wool doesn't agree with the decision,
he can request the provincial office of education
disciplinary committee to review—
You had good teachers and friends, too.
You weren't grateful for them and
you decided to hit rock bottom like this.
Take responsibility for that and reflect on it.
Then, you'll get another chance to
change your life.
Pi Han Wool, would you like to come with me?
What's this about?
Will you really hurt me?
Why?
You thought what happened to the teacher was a lie?
It won't be easy for you this time.
Why are the cops here?
ðŸ“ Channel Managers ðŸ“š:
queen_sung_kyung &amp; miss_rochester.
ðŸ“ Editors ðŸ“š:
hannalee123 &amp; keiratc (TEs) | vicky_daebak (GE) | kakashiandme (CE).
ðŸ“ Segmenters ðŸ“š:
pilar_velasquez (CS) | nazsaria | juli_ann__ | queen_sung_kyung &amp; miss_rochester.
ðŸ“ Cover Designer ðŸ“š:
juli_ann__.
Try changing the school, then.
Fine!
I said I'll go. Hold on, hold on.
Let me smoke a cigarette first.
Please?
There's no smoking at school.
Ex-Vice Principal.
- Take care!
- Bye-bye.
People change every day.
You little!
- I caught you!
- You didn't!
Even so, they say you can't fix a person.
This is a case that went viral recently.
The group fight at a high school in Ancheon
turned out to be fabricated.
The students who fought the security guards
weren't troubled teens who tried to steal.
Because rather than change positively,
more tend to go the opposite direction.
Yes.
Attorney Hwang is here regarding Han Wool.
Tell him to just take care of it.
For that reason,
we try even harder.
To become a better person than yesterday.
- Come here.
- What? What? What?
When did you get out?
What are you doing?
To create opportunities...
even in hellish situations.
Fiery firefighter?
Isn't that amazing?
Someone who saves people in danger.
Shit, it's so f***ing cool.
- Totally.
- You really suck.
What did you say, Hee Won?
Developer.
It suits you.
It sounds perfect.
How about you, Ji Woo?
Ji Woo wants to be a teacher, of course.
Will you beat up your students?
Hey. Why would I beat up students?
How about you?
Me?
I haven't decided yet.
Ga Min, how about you?
- Huh?
- What's your dream?
Oh, my dream?
Mine is to go to college.
Why?
Well, because...
becoming a college student isn't anyone's dream.
Is that so?
By the way,
is it always decided?
- Huh?
- It might sound difficult now,
but you can achieve it if you try until the end.
Isn't that what dreams are about?
So, studying hard and
going to college is my dream now.
Okay, the study group members,
finally,
we have the finals schedule.
Geez...
Seriously...
Gosh.
Until when?
I'll beat Lee Joon this time.
- I don't think so.
- I think so.
- I'll poke your eyes out.
- I don't think so.
- Quiet.
I don't think so.
This is Yuseong Technical High School in Ancheon.
Our college entrance journey continues.
♫  My name on top  ♫
♫  Wherever you go, parking lot, back yard, rooftop  ♫
♫  I make them all my stage
Let you meet the line  ♫
♫  My two feet, yawn, I’ll put you to sleep  ♫
♫  Like you're on vacation
Chasing after my goals with a pure expression  ♫
♫  When I look in the mirror, I don't want to see a failure
I make more plans  ♫
♫  I believe this, no doubt  ♫
♫  Why is such a funny question  ♫
♫  You're throwing an egg at a rock, like you don't understand  ♫
♫  Look at my grades, I've bet myself  ♫
♫  Steep growth  ♫
♫  Throw a fast curveball, slider  ♫
♫  Yeah, I'm a rider  ♫
♫  When I go low, drop your eyes  ♫
♫  Or keep quiet  ♫
♫  Shoot a goal like it's football, I like the pain, addicted  ♫
♫  I just take it and keep going forward like a bulldog  ♫
♫  Cut it off, please, (Please) set me, oh, free (Yeah)  ♫
♫  Just bring me closer and closer  ♫
♫  Run it off, I got my hoodie on me  ♫
♫  Let me go, let me go, let me go  ♫
♫  Cut it off, please, (Come ride with me) set me, oh, free  ♫
♫  Just bring me closer and closer  ♫
♫  Run it off, I got my hoodie on me  ♫
♫  And I'ma make it up from this hood, from this hood  ♫
♫  Uh, yeah
I'm on my whole lifе, I got my hoodie on  ♫
♫  Just don't take it serious though  ♫
♫  Uh, take a stab, mess with me, it's your losing move  ♫
♫  Let it out, inhale, nothing to exhale, just pass out  ♫
♫  I'm not interested in your childish gang fight  ♫
Your grades went up a lot.
You must've studied hard.