[English subtitles available].
Phun!
Pham!
It’s nothing, man.
Phun's just helping her study, that's all.
It's nothing.
Seriously, I’m fine.
[EP14 Phun-Earn]
Handsome as you are,
don’t stay single too long!
Let me introduce someone...
The other day, I met a girl,
and she's super cute.
Anyway, please look after Phun.
Take care of him.
Let Phun find good love...
to be worthy of him being a good boy.
I think I don't have to teach you anymore.
You're even better than me now.
Mick, what the hell are you doing?
I want you to keep teaching me.
Do you like it when I yell at you or what?
No, I want you to be nice.
How about this...
Pack your stuff.
I'll take you for snacks.
Okay.
[Noh] What’s up?
Can you come over?
[Ohm] What’s wrong?
Let's go P'Ohm.
Just pack your stuff and go home today.
I have something urgent to do.
I'll buy you snacks some other time.
Hey!
Yo, why’d you call me?
Who did this to you?
I don’t even know what I’m supposed to feel.
Then break up?
If you don't want to break up...
Just talk to him.
When people are together...
If they don't talk...
It won't work out, right?
But if he really cheated on you...
He'll have to deal with me.
[Phun] I'm done now. Should I go find you?
Are you at the club?
Where did you go?
I'll wait at the school gate, okay?
He still hasn't replied to your Line?
Did you call him?
He's not answering.
And at the club?
He's not there.
Or did he already go home?
Been watching all day, didn’t see anything.
Seriously, what's going on with you two?
I don't know.
I think it's been normal.
Normal for you, but is it normal for him?
Or is it about Pham?
Why does she get involved?
You’re with her all the time, that’s why.
Well,
as she came alone,
I had to welcome her, right?
Aren't you worried that Noh will overthink it?
You said there's nothing,
But if your boyfriend overthinks it...
are you cool with that?
What should I do if he overthinks it?
Apologize him!
If apologizing doesn't work,
then kneel down and beg.
Shit, Oi!
You don't have to come.
I don't want to see you, asshole!
Phun, I'm going home first, alright?
See ya.
I'm in school!
Want to eat something?
I'll get fat.
Damn, look at you!
Skinny as hell.
If you can't handle it...
Call me, okay?
Didn't you go to the club today?
I looked for you, but you weren’t there.
And...
why you're going home so late?
Did you know? Our school won!
So your friend lost?
Yeah.
I'm surprised.
Actually, she's really good.
I'm going home.
Noh!
Huh?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you mad at me?
You're good at school.
But why are you so stupid?
Don't think I don't know about Pham.
Know about what?
Pham and I are friends.
Friends?
Friends can hug each other like that?
I told you, Pham's just a friend.
I really love you.
Oh, Phun!  You haven't left yet?
Not yet. How about you?
I just finished eating.
Are you feeling better?
I'm okay now.
Mike, this is Phun!
Thank you for taking care of Pham for me.
No problem.
Better luck next year!
Just one more score. I'll definitely be back next year.
We'll get going then. Bye Phun!
Good-bye Noh too!
Eh, good luck!
See?
She has a girlfriend.
Why are you still jealous of me?
She was upset that she lost at the time.
So I comforted her.
That's all.
Then why did you hug her?
Noh!
There's really nothing going on.
When she hugged me...
It didn't feel the same as when I hug you.
Can you trust me?
Are you alright?
You seem stressed these days.
I...
I was thinking...
Maybe we shouldn't be together.
Why?
Phun!
Think about it.
If I weren't your boyfriend...
you would have already told your family.
But if you...
had a girlfriend...
who was good at school...
you would have told your family by now, right?
But it's me.
Then let's go together.
Go where?
Go to make you feel better.
How about this?
Do you like?
This one's good too.
[Phun] Come on!
[Noh]  I can't see behind.
[Phun] Come on in!
Why'd you bring me here, dude?
You can come home too?
Good evening!
You're back late.
Go take a shower and sleep.
Dad!
I have a partner.
You're finally saying it?
Go on.
I want everyone to accept my choices.
Both about the student council...
and my partner.
You chose for yourself...
Did you think it well?
I've thought about it carefully.
This person's stubborn...
Hard-headed, silly, and quick to anger...
, but I'm happy when I'm with that person.
In this world...
I can obey you in everything.
But I want to ask for just one thing: to choose for myself.
I'll only choose this person.
At your age...
You don't know what it's like to regret...
making the wrong choice.
Can you handle it?
I don't know what the future holds.
But if I don't choose this person now, I'll definitely regret it.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Aren't you going to tell me who is that?
I'll tell you when that person's ready.
Suit yourself.
You're grown up now. Think for yourself.
Don’t come crying later that you don’t want to stay here anymore.
I love you the most!
Love Mom too!
Love Pang too!
I promise I'll be even better!
That's enough, Phun!
You're already good enough.
Next time, if you have anything...
Just tell dad and me...
Don't keep it to yourself, okay?
You don’t have to be the perfect kid all the time.
Just be happy. That’s enough.
Alright then, I’ll be less “perfect.”
There might be nothing left!
Noh!
Yes.
Staying here tonight?
Noh is sleeping with me tonight.
What I said about choosing a good person...
It doesn't have to be a girl.
Go on, it's late.
Go take a shower, do your homework, and go to bed.
I'll definitely do my homework...
Let's go!
Why didn't you tell me first before doing this?
Is it okay?
Do you know how much I love you?
Stop overthinking.
And when you're ready, you can tell Dad with me.
Oh, I can't...
But you've thought this through, right?
You still don't trust me?
Can I get a reward?
What reward?
Can I?
Damn!
Do whatever you want. Don't ask.
I totally forgot...
I promised Keng to do my physics homework.
I'm late now.
Noh!
Really.
Your dad told you to do your homework,
so I thought about it.
Don't do homework with others.
Only with me.
Give me here.
Stop it! Stop!
[3 days to the final. Fighting for 70%!]
[Club use suspended during exams.]
A man finds that...
It's faster to hear a shark in water than in air by 1.8 seconds.
The question is, how many meters away is the shark from him?
Why calculate? Just flee!
Right!
Do sharks even roar?
What does it sound like?
Blub Blub!
Shut up!
Hey, I saw it on TikTok!
The answer to this one is 800.
How can you hear it from 800?
Maybe 400?
[Everyone] 800! 800! 800!
What are you guys doing?
How was it?
Can everyone do it?
Everyone, thanks to the teacher!
Thank you, ma'am.
[Today is the Pharmacy Camp!]
Whoa!
Look at him.
Coming early and still being dramatic.
It's still summer break...
And I have to wake up at 5 a.m. for this camp.
Who the hell signed me up for this?
Don't let me find out huh?
Sign here!
Hey, but I think...
Since we already signed up...
We have to put in some effort, right?
That's true
This is the pharmacy camp, man!
Come on, guys!
Here, eat this.
There is still a long way to go.
Thank you.
Why didn't you tell me...
that you were coming too?
The teacher told me to come.
I forgot to tell you.
But don't worry.
I'll be on my own.
You can do whatever you want.
What's with him?
Looks like the kid is sulking with someone.
Yeah, and I don't think he even realizes it.
This is gonna be fun.
By the way...
why does each tag have a different color?
Different team.
But Phun is on the yellow team, and you're on red.
So you're not together.
Marwin also joins?
♫How close is love is supposed to be?♫
♫Which theory book should I see?♫
♫Missing you—does that mean love?♫
♫Dreaming of you—does that mean love? ♫
♫Every song I hear is all for you.♫
♫Everywhere I look, I see you too.♫
♫Can’t hold your gaze for more than a while,♫
♫Are these the signs of love?♫
♫Where can I find the answer?♫
♫Which love theory holds the key?♫
♫The more I search, the less I see. ♫
♫The way I feel… for you.♫
♫Everything I do… for you.♫
♫Missing you when you’re away. ♫
♫All I want is you, just having you here.♫
Hello everyone!
Today...
We're going to have you...
select the leader.
And once you select them...
have them sit at the front of the line.
Okay?
You are the first, so you are the leader.
First one! First one!
You can be!
As you're already sitting there...
Yeah, you're at the front.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I'm late.
No problem, please have a seat.
Since you all come from different schools...
we're going to have you...
play an icebreaker game.
Alright everyone...
Our camp activity...
is called...
"The Hungry Ghost"!
While we're at this camp...
we can't walk around alone.
Especially the villagers.
Because the hungry ghost will kill you.
[Villager]
The Hungry Ghost kills the villagers by ripping off their name tags.
But the hungry ghosts can't walk around alone either.
Because we have the Shaman to kill the hungry ghosts.
Shaman King!
And on the way back, we'll tally the scores...
to see which hungry ghost killed the most villagers.
And which Shaman killed the most hungry ghosts.
Enjoy, everyone! Good luck!
Okay everyone, don't forget the rules.
You can disperse now.
[Everyone] Copy that!
Eh, win!
How did you get here?
Does your dad know?
Yeah, he does.
My dad took me.
Oh!
Did he do anything to you?
No.
He didn't.
And I don't think he will anymore.
Why?
My dad'll send me to study in England.
So I asked him to see you here for the last time.
He said I could come, but when I go back...
he’ll send me to London right away.
It's okay.
About that...
Forget it.
We're together now.
I want to spend this time with you.
Damn, Earn, did you really pee there?
The bathroom was full, man!
What if someone sees your worm?
-Is that true?
-Yeah...
There you go!
-P'Ton, can I have a lot of pork?
-Yes, sure.
-Noh, do you want pork?
-Thank  you.
Look tasty here.
Give me back my pork!
What? Are you stingy?
This one's pumpkin!
It is also edible.
It tickles! Move!
Give me your arm.
I'll put on mosquito repellent for you.
Bleh, love makes me sick!
The couple next to me is just as sickening also!
-Which couple?
-It's you!
Can you carry our bags for us?
We're going to set up the room.
-See you!
-Eh, wait!
Damn!
Mick, want some snacks?
Do you even like me a bit?
Why are you asking?
Do you like me even half as much as you like Noh?
Jeez!
Whoa, are you guys laying now?
I think I'll sleep here.
I'll be here then.
Phun, yours is here.
Why are we sleeping there?
The feng shui's good—I checked.
Come on, stay away from my friend a bit.
So you can miss each other more.
Then where do I sleep?
Next to Noh where you're sitting now.
Why do I have to sleep with him?
Duh, it’s all part of the plan.
This is your chance to regain that closeness away from Phun.
I know.
Know what?
I know I can’t compete with Noh.
But I won't give up. I'll keep fighting until you really like me.
-But...
-No need to say anything.
I think you should fight too.
Because you once told me...
If we like something, we should fight for it.
So why don't you fight?
And you want me to break them up?
You can't do that.
But if you can...
I'll give up.
Are you challenging me?
Shit!
-What?
-What are you doing?
Got a partner and now you’re protective, huh?
Asshole!
Alright, if you’re all ready,
let’s meet at the field, alright?
Hurry up, guys!
Yes, sir!
I think that senior’s face is red, right?
♪ Love is like the morning sun. Even though it’s dark now,♪
♪I know that tomorrow, I’ll find it right there.♪
♪Or is love like the wind, passing by, making the heart feel warm and tender...♪
♪only briefly, before moving on?♪
♪If love is real, don’t keep yourself hidden anymore.♪
♪If love is real, don’t let me keep searching for you.♪
♪If love is real, do you know I’ve always been here waiting for you here?♪
♪I want to know if we're waiting to meet.♪
♪I want to know if you’re waiting to meet me?♪
♪Do you count every second like I do?♪
♪I’ve been saving my love, waiting to meet you for so long.♪
♪ Don’t let me wait any longer if love is real.♪
♪If love is real...♪
Noh!
I'm sorry about what happened earlier.
I didn't mean it.
It's okay.
It was just a game.
Come on, let's pick teams.
Even if you don't think anything...
But I do.
You know how I feel about you.
Earn!
Listen to me.
From the first day until now...
I haven't changed.
I still think of you as a friend.
What's wrong with being friends?
If it was someone else...
I'd have punched them.
But I saw it was you, so I was chill.
No matter how many times you kiss me.
I still think of you the same.
Okay?
Okay.
Okay, fine then.
Where are you going?
To shower?
Come on, guys, take a shower. It’s not cold!
-Take off your shirt!
-Nope, I won't!
-Hurry up and shower, guys! We're freezing here.
-Hurry up!
1...2...
Go!!!
Hey!
What are you guys doing? No invite?
Eh, I still want more.
Noh, you're done. Let's go.
You go shower!
Ohm, can I shower too?
Go somewhere else.
No, I'll do it here.
No, we’re all men!
I'm a man too.
Win, go somewhere else!
Nope, showering right here.
Here's for elders.
You'd better say seniors.
So tired!
Aim, your twerking was top-notch!
Even my Ohm can’t compete!
Of course I do! Wanna see it again?
Oh, Jeez!
Switching from beauty queen to comedian, huh?
Yeah.
Oh, Jeed's gang isn't coming tomorrow.
Last I heard, they said they’d skip camp.
Too bad!
Do you feel bad?
Then look at this.
No, you should do it like this!
Like this?
You have to do this. Look at me.
That's so cute.
-Let’s go shower, shall we?
-Yeah!
-Earn!
-Hmm?
if I steal your blanket tonight,
don’t get mad, okay?
I get cold easily.
I think I don't want to die yet.
Pete!
Let's swap places!
Why?
Afraid someone won’t sleep tonight.
Who?
Whatever. Switch! Switch!
Are you a Hungry Ghost?
I am not.
You're a Hungry Ghost?
No, I'm not either.
I'm turning off the lights!
[Noh] Good night, you drama queen!
So...
Did Earn kiss you?
That wasn't really a kiss.
It was just a game.
I want to apologize to you about Noh.
Oh, thanks.
I'm not mad at you.
Noh!
[Watch the uncut version of Love Sick 2024 online exclusively on the iQIYI app and IQ.com.]
[Translated by Jackree Bunyamethi]