♪Waiting for the wilted flower
to finally fall silent♪
♪Waiting for the time
divides the sunset glow♪
Stay still.
Lose the glasses.
♪Struggling in this perpetual cycle♪
♪Promises are answering his lies♪
Your perfume gives you away.
♪Tick, tock, tick, tock♪
♪Tears are speaking♪
♪Mist blinds his eyes
from seeing rose graffiti♪
You want a surprise, don't you?
♪The dialogue sounds hoarse,
I can only hide my words within♪
♪Love me, will you? Quiet, silly♪
♪Or just let it go?♪
♪My youth is like burning snowflakes♪
♪Your castle is fended♪
Happy anniversary, Dear.
♪So happiness may bloom flawlessly♪
Happy anniversary.
Dear.
What about mine?
(I'll head off to the boat
to get ready.)
(Pick you up for diving at 10 PM.)
(See you later.)
[Love you forever]
[Gu Cheng]
I'll be right there.
[President of Anshi Furniture]
(The Yan couple from Anshi Group)
(are discovered embezzling)
[Financial Personnel]
(a significant amount of funds.)
[of Suspected Corruption Commits Suicide]
(The situation is still under review.)
(Recently, there was a suicide
in a neighborhood)
(witnessed by the 14-year-old daughter
of the deceased,)
(Yan.)
(Based on our information,)
(the deceased was connected
to the embezzlement case)
(of Anshi Group.)
(However, due to the lack
of crucial evidence...)
(Mom.)
(I will find the truth.)
[All of Her]
[Episode 1]
[Four years later]
Thank you for attending
the press conference.
Four years ago,
Zejia met an accident.
So, I took on
the role of acting general manager.
Initially, many people looked down on me
and Anshi Group.
Fortunately,
I didn't let down
your trust and support.
Anshi managed
to sail through the hardships.
[Yan Zhen]
This miracle
[General Director of Anshi Group]
was achieved by all of us.
I believe
we will create more miracles.
You're not the largest shareholder here.
I don't think
it's appropriate to say that.
Ms. Yan.
Everyone here
recognized your capability.
But, as you said,
you're an acting general manager.
It's been four years.
It's time to step down, is it not?
By any chance, do you want
to sit on it until retirement?
In this agreement,
Mr. Wang signed his shares over to me.
Kindly have a look.
Mr. Wang.
About the shares
you're transferring to me,
I'll give you an extra percentage
[Shares Transfer Agreement]
based on the market price.
Besides,
I've prepared a gift for your wife.
Please open it.
You don't have much time left.
Your wife will be reaching here
in a minute.
Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven,
six,
five...
Fine.
Are you Mrs. Wang?
Ms. Yan prepared this for you.
This seems pretty nice.
Quite expensive, right?
Yes, quite.
Several hundred million.
Dear guests,
any objections?
[In loving memory]
[Chu Xin]
If no...
[youngest daughter of the Chu family]
Yes.
Who's she? What is she doing here?
What's going on?
What happens?
[Anshi Group]
I didn't know
you had become the largest shareholder.
Xin.
Thank you for bringing Zejia here.
After this press conference...
Drop your act.
You won't get a single dime
from the Chu family.
Anshi Furniture contributed
30 percent of the group's cash flow.
Madam Chu wouldn't take your side
even if she were here today.
I don't care.
Your achievements so far
should be all thanks to the shares
my brother gave you.
Yes.
I toiled to run the company
because I didn't want
to ruin his effort.
I hope to give him a better Anshi
when he returns.
[Gu Cheng, marketing director,
Yan Zhen's childhood friend]
But it's been four years.
I have to accept the truth
even though I hate it so much.
So,
I'd like to make an announcement here.
Today,
I officially declare the death
of my husband,
Chu Zejia.
Xin, let's go home. Stop it already.
Who are you to decide his death?
You know better
whether it was an accident or not.
Xin, come down. Don't make a scene here.
If I had known
that something was amiss
behind Mr. Chu Jr.'s disappearance,
I wouldn't have transferred my shares
to Yan Zhen.
You declared the death of Chu Zejia...
Please give your comments.
Please excuse us.
The accident happened
on the day of your wedding anniversary.
Why were you not on the boat?
We won't make any comments today.
Excuse me.
Make way, please.
♪Waiting for the wilted flower
to finally fall silent♪
♪Waiting for the time
divides the sunset glow♪
♪He stalks my mind and memories♪
♪Struggling in this perpetual cycle♪
♪Promises are answering his lies♪
♪I'm just a walker-on
in this tear-jerker♪
♪Tick, tock, tick, tock♪
♪Tears are speaking♪
♪Mist blinds his eyes
from seeing rose graffiti♪
♪The dialogue sounds hoarse,
I can only hide my words within♪
♪Love me, will you? Quiet, silly♪
♪Or just let it go?♪
♪My youth is like burning snowflakes♪
♪Your castle is fended♪
♪Let the heavy downpour
awaken the summer♪
♪I turn away from glamor♪
♪Your garden is sown with fairy tales♪
♪I stay under the limp spring blossom♪
♪Trimming off all the mess♪
♪So happiness may bloom flawlessly♪
[No incurable pain,
no not the end of the destruction,]
[all lost, will be back in another way.
John Shors]