[Chae Jong Hyeop]
[Seo Eun Soo]
[Park Sung Woong]
[Unlock My Boss]
[Locales, organizations, characters, agencies, and incidents in this drama are not real. This is a work of fiction.]
With the advent of the year 2000, computers will fail to recognize the year and operate strangely.
This is called the Millennium Bug or Y2K.
While the entire world is fretting over this problem,
some people are hoping to make a profit using this opportunity.
Mr. Nam, who has completed five years at his company this year,
receives a long service allowance of 90,000 won per month.
However, as the internal clock of the computer changed to the year 2000,
his years of work suddenly became -95 years
and his allowance changed to -1.72 million won.
As the last two digits of the four-digit year changed to 00 from 99,
You actually shouldn't clip your nails at night.
the computer recognized it as the year 1900.
[Video Chatting Fever]
Oh? Why not?
If a field rat eats your nail clippings,
it takes your form and appearance.
Really?
Scary, isn't it?
So don't discard your nails just anywhere.
Make sure to throw them in the trash can.
In Seong? My gosh.
In Seong!
In Seong.
Oh?
In Seong, what are you doing?
I'm spreading them so the rats can come and eat them.
Say what?
One can go to school instead of me,
and another one can do my homework.
I'll also ask them to help with the dishes and the laundry
since your back hurts, Mom.
Stay right there. I'll come up.
Look over there.
That star resembles you. It's pretty.
Really?
Wow!
Where's In Seong's star?
Right over there!
The one that's twinkling brightly?
So that's yours?
Yours should twinkle too.
[1: Unlocked]
[2022]
Would you like to try a delicious apple?
Thank you.
Baro, turn it off.
You've been watching a Silver Lining VR Lens simulation.
Good job, Baro!
[Lining VR]
[Main Character of the Story, Talk, Feel, Experience a new world]
The era of reading fairy tales
and watching animations is over.
Now, I can personally become the main character of the story and talk,
feel, and experience a new world.
Even if you're in your room,
IU will sing in front of your eyes
and Son Heung Min will pass you the ball.
A world where the wall between virtual and reality has collapsed,
this is Silver Lining's technology.
[Lining VR]
Why did you turn down Silicon Valley's love calls and join hands with Beomyeong?
Is the merger with Beomyeong a strategic move for the launch of self-driving cars?
Please comment on your scandal with Beomyeong's executive director, Oh Mi Ran.
This stage is to present VR, which will enable children to dream.
Please focus on that.
Princess?
Shall we meet the dwarves this time?
Yes.
Wow, it's Snow White!
Mom, I want to take a picture with Snow White.
Sure, sure, let's go.
Mom, Snow White smells like dad.
Smells like dad?
Gosh, did you drink?
Were you drunk on the job?
I had a blind wine-tasting gig.
One glass led to another... I'm sorry.
I told you not to drink before your shift.
Do you take me for a fool?
Do I look like a fool to you dressed in this costume?
No.
I... wasn't going to say this, but...
this is why you're still doing part-time jobs at your age!
What's wrong with my age?
I'm at an age where I can do anything except be a child actor!
Oh, is that so?
Then you should go to Hollywood. What are you doing here?
- I mean... that's–
- Whatever!
Why isn't your friend here yet?
I can't reach him.
There are officially seven dwarves. We can't have just six!
Don't you know Snow White has seven dwarfs?
How do you...
You have no professionalism.
Don't come to work anymore.
Punk!
Don't come.
Professionalism!
Ribbit...
Ribbit, ribbit.
What a loud frog.
He's coming through!
Call Son Heung Min's people
and set a date for an additional motion photography session during the national team convention.
And send a flower bouquet to IU's management congratulating her on winning first place.
On the card, write that her high notes in the new song were fantastic
and pretend to be interested.
- Hello.
- Hello...
It's okay. You can stay.
Okay.
A video meeting has been scheduled with the R&D team,
so push back the 4 p.m. meeting with the investment bank branch manager by fifteen minutes.
You are connected to the main system.
Baro, repeat the schedule I set up.
Set a date for Son Heung Min's additional motion photography session.
Gift IU a flower bouquet. A congratulatory card is a must.
A video meeting with the R&D team at 4:00 p.m.
A meeting with the branch manager of the investment bank at 4:15 p.m.
What should we do?
At this rate, the job of a secretary might become redundant.
Secretary Jeong, you should look for a new job before it's too late.
I'll look into the HR policy regarding department transfer and retirement.
Gosh, I was just joking.
It wasn't funny?
No.
You are more AI than an AI.
"The era of reading fairy tales"
"and watching animations is over."
[Directing and Acting]
Now, I can personally become the main character of the story and talk,
feel, and experience a new world.
Even if you're in your room,
IU will sing in front of your eyes,
and Son Heung Min will pass the ball to you.
A world where the wall between the virtual and the real world has collapsed,
Did it start?
this is Silver Lining's technology.
Not yet.
Wow, bean sprout soup.
Hey, but...
who knew Lee Geon Wook would be the male lead?
He...
learned how to act by following us around in the theatre troupe.
He must've worked hard.
What about the motorcycle?
It broke down again.
Buy a new one. A motorcycle is a rider's life.
Hey,
if I had the money to buy a motorcycle, I'd buy shares in a motorcycle company.
That's how you earn money.
You should learn how to invest from me.
Learn?
You even resorted to private loans when you got into bitcoin.
Wow, no!
I don't even go to coin karaoke after that.
And I...
have a final interview at Silver Lining tomorrow.
Watch what you say to a person who's about to
board the job express.
Was this... kimchi soup*, not bean sprout soup?
(Building castles in the air)
You little...
Wow, hey.
He has such an intense face. What the hell is this?
Silver Lining's President, Kim Seon Ju.
- Don't you know?
- Not at all.
I am super sincere. I even try to think and act like him while eating.
- This small preparation–
- Putting his photo this way
makes it look like a memorial table.
Hey, it's time. Lee Geon Wuk will appear!
Hey, set it up. Set it up!
It's too bright. Movie theater mode.
Baro, turn on the lights.
Yes, you've done a great job today.
Current indoor temperature is 24°C.
Humidity is at 43%. Fine dust levels...
I'm well aware.
President Kim is here. Hang up.
After analyzing your eating habits this month,
I recommend consuming more protein.
I ordered thirty extra eggs.
Good job.
When did you come home? Have you eaten—
What about Min Ah?
Dad!
Gosh, my princess!
Did you wake up because of me?
I didn't go to sleep because of you.
Read me Snow White.
What should I do? I have some work to do.
Ji Hye, please find the VR headset in the living room.
Okay.
I like it better when Dad reads to me.
[Confidential]
Young Master,
I loaded it in the trunk.
All right.
Should I tell them to bring you some snacks?
It's all right. Carry on.
[2-0]
[Confidential]
[Dad]
[Snow White]
You can't do that here.
Please don't kill me.
You can't die before you pay back my money.
You can't die without my permission.
Here.
Tomorrow morning at nine.
I received the money, so you must get on.
Sir!
[Seamen Wanted*]
No!
(*Not professional seamen, but usually sold for slave labor)
[Silver Lining Networks]
[Interview Hall]
Yes, Mom.
Son, did you eat breakfast?
I had a hearty meal.
You didn't eat seaweed soup, did you*?
(*Eating slippery seaweed before exams is considered a jinx)
You'll slip on an important day.
Do you still believe those superstitions? Don't worry.
I have a really good feeling this time.
I see a flower road ahead—
Why? What's going on? In Seong!
I'll call you later.
Yes.
Hey—
What are you going to do about this?
I was on my way. You're the one who suddenly bumped into me.
The interview is in less than half an hour.
What are you going to do about this?
Follow me to the restroom.
Who is she commanding? Unbelievable.
Back in the day, I did taekwondo—
Why? What? Why... Why are you doing this?
- Take it off?
- Sorry?
I said, take off the shirt.
Well...
I mean... What are you...
Go inside and give me your shirt.
I mean, what?
I'm not at fault.
It is just compassion for a job seeker.
E-Excuse me?
Are you just going to leave?
How am I supposed to return this to you?
Excuse me!
Your strength is...
diligence?
Yes.
I got the perfect attendance award for twelve years straight and have never once been late.
Twelve years...
Diligence is for the age of agriculture.
This is the age of information.
Gosh.
Your father runs an orchard.
Yes, my father runs an orchard...
[Park In Seong]
He said this apple is our family's hope.
However, to me, hope...
He's not going to take a bite, is he?
this.
Then you should've gone to the States
and applied to that company.
If the States has Apple,
I believe Korea has Silver Lining.
But why are you sweating so much?
As expected of the top company in the industry,
the interview is quite straining.
I think there's something more straining than this interview.
I am talking about your shirt.
- Yes.
- I understand your motive for applying.
I can explain this...
I gave your resume a scan.
You're like Pyeongyang noodles,*
(Cold noodles in beef broth in North Korean style)
which are very hard to find these days.
Pyeongyang noodles?
Academic background, credentials, and experience,
not a single thing is remarkable.
Gosh.
It is simply bland.
That's why I'm sitting here.
I'm sure Silver Lining will be
the secret ingredient
that will bring taste to my otherwise bland resume.
Even so,
don't you think you lack too much experience?
But I must be given a chance to work, to gain experience.
Then work.
That is my intention.
I am sitting here for this interview for that very purpose.
You don't have any internship experience either.
How can I give you a job
when you don't have any experience?
How am I supposed to have experience if you don't allow me to work?
That's why I'm telling you to work, okay?
That's why I'm asking you to give me work!
- What?
- I'm sorry...
- Are you all right?
You have the attention of the whole world,
and you want to meet this old geezer?
Vice Chairman,
I am looking for proactive cooperation with Beomyeong Electronics.
My subordinates are the ones who handle this,
so I couldn't pay much attention.
You see, I have many things to take care of.
The first thing Beomyeong Electronics needs to take care of
is this.
Do you...
know how Beomyeong Group began?
We came all this way by selling ramen.
I'm well aware.
It started as Beomyeong Foods in an impoverished country.
It grew to Beomyeong Construction with the development of the country
and fostered a construction boom.
And finally, it grew to Beomyeong Electronics once we became a developed country.
Beomyeong has never
missed the trend of its contemporary generation.
The choice made in a moment
always dictated the next ten years.
But now,
do you want to go against the flow of the era
by not actively introducing AI to the electronics field?
Do you wish for electronics with Beomyeong's logo
to end up like walkmans, pagers,
and videos, which we no longer see around?
Are you patronizing me?
Beomyeong Electronics is lucky,
since you have Silver Lining with the world's best technology as your partner.
On the contrary,
Silver Lining is unlucky
since its partner, Beomyeong Electronics,
is bullheaded.
How old is President Kim this year?
He's forty-three years old.
A bastard younger than my child dares to...
That bastard with no class is trying to shake up my whole company.
Employment express, my foot.
More like a southbound train to my hometown.
I endured for ten years as a job seeker.
How could I not endure those ten minutes?
Wow, you folded quite a few.
Hold on.
Yes, Master—
I mean...
- Landlady, hello.
- Yes, hello.
You're aware your contract is about to expire, right?
Yes, I was going to call you about that anyway.
I'd like to renew it for another two years.
That's a shame.
I'd like for you to move out.
What are you saying?
The laws have changed,
so the tenant may stay for two more years if they wish to.
The law has indeed changed.
So if my immediate family says they want to move in,
you must move out.
Your immediate family?
Yes.
Keep that in mind.
Mom, I'm back from school!
Yes, my son, you're back.
Him?
He's going to live here alone?
That's right! My son.
He's at an age where he wants to move out of his parent's home and be independent.
- Independence? Am I Ahn Jung Geun, the freedom fighter?
Hurry and get in. You have to go to cram school!
Hold on!
It must be great for you
since your parents live in Seoul.
Ji Won, hurry and get inside!
Coming!
My gosh.
♫ I guess ♫
♫ I am still young ♫
♫ I must be ♫
♫ Mom! ♫
♫ Why do I keep waiting? ♫
♫ Why do I suddenly miss you? ♫
♫ I guess I'm still young ♫
♫ I must be ♫
♫ Mom! ♫
♫ Why do I keep getting sad? ♫
♫ Why do I suddenly want to cry? ♫
♫ I came to pick flowers ♫
♫ On a hill dyed in autumn ♫
♫ And fell asleep ♫
♫ I fell asleep ♫
♫ Mom! ♫
♫ Where am I going? ♫
♫ When I'm lonely, I look at the sky ♫
Why are you so late today?
You should at least give me some time to stop by home.
I know you frequently go back and forth
while I'm at work.
Wh-When did I?
I pay you for those hours too.
I'm going to the convenience store.
What's the point of life-sustaining treatment?
She's just burdening her daughter.
Be quiet. She can hear you.
I want her to hear me.
I feel sorry for her.
She's got a life ahead of her.
She'll just waste it, nursing her mom.
If I wanted to get a job,
they said I needed experience.
But
you know what?
I need to get a job to gain that experience in the first place.
M-Me, too. Me, too.
I need to invest in stocks to earn money.
But hey!
I need money to invest in stocks.
They're just asking all poor job seekers to die.
Hey,
is Silver Lining the only company in South Korea?
It's okay, it's okay. You'll get another chance next time.
Of course, I will.
Of course, I will. But
the thing is...
I know I will be a mess until that next opportunity.
Why are you like this today?
It's not the first time you failed an interview.
Hyeon Ho, would the sting of a punch be any less if you get punched more often.
It still stings.
What happened with your house?
What did the realtor say?
Fifty million won?
That's right.
You need another 50 million won.
Not five but fifty—?
If you want a house like that, that's the market price.
- Where will I get a large sum like--
- I understand your situation,
but I recommend you hurry.
You're also aware, right?
That housing in Seoul is the cheapest today?
Call me later!
I lived my life giving it my all,
but I'll have an additional debt of 50 million won in just two years.
What have I done wrong?
Why must I be in debt?
Do you think it's that easy to get into debt?
What bank would lend money to a job seeker?
Forget it and just live with me.
You barely have enough room for you to sleep comfortably.
I appreciate your offer, though.
Then what will you do?
Will you pack up and go back to your hometown?
I really do want to go back to my hometown.
But
most of the companies are in Seoul.
What can I do?
Hey, if people like us
want to live in Seoul,
Seoul Detention Center is all that's left.
Excuse me,
Seoul Detention Center
is actually in Uiwang, Gyeonggi-do.
Gosh.
She's going to work.
No, coming back from work.
What a filial daughter.
Your interest is piling as we speak.
I'm paying you back.
When will you finish at that rate?
Your debt is fifty million.
If I were you,
I'd at least sell an organ of that living corpse.
Or if you don't like that,
you could sell something else.
Could you even sell me for an expensive price?
So what I'm saying is...
love your job and consider it
as something you were born to do.
Hyeongnim Ma Pi, hello.
Why am I your hyeongnim?
Where's Madam Jeong?
Yes, this way, please.
Baby, hello!
Hello, Oppa!
Hello.
You have a nice vibe, like a college student.
If you have fifty million won in debt, the house can pay that off.
With some touch-ups,
she might even bring in thirty million won per month.
Breast surgery is eight million won,
skin care will cost about one million won per month as well.
Also, I have to wrap myself in luxury bags and shoes,
in addition to the dress, hair, and makeup.
How much profit are you left with?
She won't do.
You said she had a good vibe.
She doesn't have a server mindset.
What do you mean? She works as a secretary.
She'll cause a huge accident if I sit her down at a table.
Sorry.
Do I work here, or do I keep my job?
Go to your job.
I'll see you again.
I won't run.
So stop coming to my work.
I don't trust people.
I trust money.
I'll see you.
Isn't there a closer camping site?
Min Ah said that wouldn't work.
We have a hotel suite room sitting around.
Who does she take after to have such an analog sentiment?
Gosh, what do I tell them?
[Friday, June 10]
[Sunny]
[Shopping]
Gosh.
I haven't gone home in a long time.
I can't go empty-handed.
What?
It's a good price.
Ta-da!
[Ham]
What's this?
[Chuseok* two years earlier] (*Korean Thanksgiving)
It's a ham set that is made up of
92.44% pork.
My goodness, you didn't have to.
I heard the village head's eldest son took him to Hoengsung to buy him Korean beef.
Honey!
Ta-da!
[100% Wild Tuna, Lean Meat Tuna]
What's this?
[Chuseok one year earlier]
It's a 100% wild-caught tuna set made up of
79% skipjack tuna.
My, my. You didn't have to.
I heard the village son's younger son
took him to Japan on an airplane to buy him tuna.
- My goodness!
- Gosh.
No.
I can't win with food.
Why did he come?
My goodness, Son!
You must be busy, why did you come?
If he stands and stares about,
that makes him a totem and not a person.
Here.
[Baro AI Speaker]
What is it this time?
Is it a cooking oil set?
It's artificial intelligence. An AI speaker.
Hey, artificial intelligence means...
it's that...
Alpha-something that beat Lee Se Dol, right?
Well, it's something similar.
Wow.
Wow...
You really didn't have to buy this!
Gosh, it must be really expensive.
He must have money rotting away.
You don't even know what it is.
If you have this,
you can turn off the light
and turn on the TV while sitting still.
Is a young man whose all four limbs work fine,
really that lazy to move around?
It's my fault for raising you to be this.
Really!
He was thoughtful to buy a present for us!
He doesn't even know the value of sweat.
Get the refund right away*!
(*Same sound/spelling as Baro in Korean)
Did you call for me?
This thing..
I couldn't find the song you mentioned.
Gosh.
Such a good for nothing.
I see, Mona Lisa*.
(The word for "good for nothing" sounds like Mona Lisa in Korean)
I'll play Jo Yong Pil's song.
It's Jo Yong Pil's song.
Wow.
What is this?
Mr. Jo.
I'm Park Jae Chun, the Chungcheongbuk-do Fan Club Branch Manager.
[King of Pop, Jo Yong Pil 50th Anniversary Concert, Fan Club]
♫ Even if I give you my all ♫
♫ Can't I win that heart? ♫
♫ You without a smile ♫
♫ You are the Mona Lisa ♫
♫ With a sad look ♫
♫ Should I look and turn around? ♫
♫ You without tears ♫
♫ You are the Mona Lisa ♫
It's there!
Please put it in the cart.
Oh, my.
Wow...
It's this one, right?
That's correct.
With roasted sweet potatoes,
a campfire,
and even the shooting stars!
Gosh, it's so romantic!
You must be so happy.
Yes, I'm so happy.
Out of everything, I'm happiest about going with Dad.
I want to be there already.
- Yes!
- Director, nice shot!
Shouldn't you be joining the pro league?
Even most men would tuck in
their tails in front of you.
No matter how good she is, she's still a woman.
Do you...
know who Sorenstam is?
Of course, I know her.
Isn't she the legend of women's golf?
Even that legend
ranked 96th at a men's competition
and got cut off, to her embarrassment.
Vice Chairman, nice shot!
Score!
I also like Sorenstam. I'm a fan.
Sorenstam shocked everyone by retiring while she was near the top.
She knew when to step down.
She did not let things get ugly by prolonging her time as a player.
And people call that "the course of nature."
What do you think, President Kim?
Well, I think it's only natural to have a meeting
in a meeting room instead of a golf course.
Okay, sounds great.
Let's hurry. Min Ah is waiting.
Could I go to Seoul instead?
All of a sudden?
Sure. You do that.
The business trip is over anyway.
Instead, there's no overtime pay.
Yes, Do Yun. Come here.
Sheesh, I said I would do it.
No, I'm going to tell Dad later that I did it.
So, Ma'am, you can just rest.
Can I do that?
[Sky, Star, Wind, and Poem]
Oh, it's the president.
Why aren't you here yet?
I'm sorry for being late. I'm almost there.
[Chungcheongbuk-do Camping Site]
You're not late, Dad.
It's just that we were early.
You can eat first if you're hungry.
I don't want to. I'm going to eat the meat you grilled and—
I'm going to raise it.
- Who drives like that?
- After cram school,
I went to the mart–
and I bought–
Hello?
This time I–
- It won't do–
- Min Ah!
Your voice keeps dying.
Why am I getting no signal?
What?
Is something wrong?
Suddenly, I couldn't hear him anymore.
I couldn't even tell him I bought sweet potatoes.
What's this suddenly?
There's absolutely no signal.
It's delicious.
Of course.
Eat a lot.
Hey, hold it properly.
It's just that our son doesn't have any tricks up his sleeve,
but he's still good and kind.
That's why we named him In Seong*.
(*Inseong: a person's character)
A person's character comes first.
That's right.
Father, I have something to tell you.
My security deposit suddenly went up...
Couldn't you withdraw that deposit and come live down here?
Don't say pointless things.
Why?
Did something happen?
Well, the thing is...
You know what havoc the last typhoon wrecked.
I am thinking about doing the repairs and
plant that... what's it called... shine muscat?
You know, the green grapes. I'm thinking of getting into that,
but it costs quite a bit.
Are you going to use my deposit for that?
You did more than enough, and I think we waited long enough.
Even so—
If it did not work out until now, it would never work out.
Aren't you going to be thirty soon?
You don't even have a proper job, gosh.
Are you telling me to give up again?
In Seong.
I even gave up on acting because you told me to give up on pipe dreams
and live like other people.
Hey, you punk.
That was because you were wasting your time as a young guy!
What is he saying right now?
Gosh, In Seong's dad!
Why is the door not opening?
What did I get to do, really?
Two years in the army and four years in college.
I even took a leave for two years to pay for the tuition.
I'm doing my best to make something out of myself,
but why do you only keep saying that it won't work? Why?
In Seong... In Seong!
Gosh, In Seong!
You should've at least finished eating before storming out.
What about Father?
He's having some soju.
Shall we have some expensive drinks?
Expensive drinks?
Ta-da!
I'm sure you're frustrated, but wouldn't he also be just as frustrated?
Your father was not like that before.
That's not true.
He was always like that.
No, he wasn't.
That's because you saw him after he aged.
Hey.
Do you think you're the only one who had a dream?
Your father also had a dream and passion.
But now,
time has weathered him down. He's only left with ill will.
Challenge?
A challenge is good.
But what if you fail?
Your father is just scared.
He's afraid you'd fall and never get back up again.
He wants to help you get back up.
But as parents,
he's afraid we might not have enough money to do that.
- Hey.
- Correct!
What's that on your face?
On my face?
It's a cloud!
What?
The call cannot be connected. Your call will be forwarded
- to messaging and
- What's the answer? The ceiling!
will be charged after the beep.
I guess so.
Now, then.
What shall we do?
There must be an emergency at the company.
Are you really not going to eat?
You could be in big trouble.
Do Yun, do you want a cookie?
Open wide.
There you go, sweetheart.
Let's eat this!
Dad will come for sure.
[Draw the unlock pattern.]
[Slow motion video, image panorama timelaspe 1x]
[Post]
[Help me.]
I seem to have become a smartphone.
There's only 15 percent battery remaining.
I'm currently located somewhere deep in the mountains of Chungcheongbuk-do.
I'm leaving the detailed coordinates below.
[Register]
If you see this post, please come here and charge the battery for me.
[Good concept, haha]
[It's too extreme of a concept, haha]
I will reward you. I will reward you.
You're awake.
Did you have a nightmare?
I didn't.
Did you have a sad dream?
No.
I had a sweet dream.
Then why do you cry so sadly?
Because
it's a dream that can't come true.
What was the dream about?
I was the president of a company.
The president?
Hey, that's a good dream—
Were you sleeping until now to have a dogsh*t dream like that?
Goodness, Honey!
You should be grateful if you can become a minor employee.
But what now? The president?
That brat has not
come to his senses.
You little—
Where the heck is that brat running off to?
That place is infested with snakes.
Go and catch some snakes while you're there!
So I can make some liquor.
They're announcing the results today.
Why are they not contacting me?
What were you expecting when you made that mess out of the interview?
What?
It's the outback again.
I want to go to an amusement park.
Let's go to an amusement park on your birthday.
You mean it, right?
Okay, let's go.
I guess the ox will do the harvesting itself.
I'll make it so that Mom and Dad won't have to work.
How do you plan to do that?
I'm going to grow up and become an actor.
Then I'll make a lot of money.
Just wait and see.
I don't need money.
I just need an autograph from Cho Yong Pil*.
(*One of the most popular Korean pop singers)
Just an autograph?
I'll get you to take a picture with him too.
Then that's a promise!
Gosh, not you too, Honey.
Why do you keep getting his hopes up?
What's wrong with you, Honey? You're discouraging him.
I'll give you all the support you need.
Shall I send you to an acting school in Seoul?
Are you serious?
Of course, I'm serious!
The mood is ripe. In Seong, do you want to dance it off?
Now, there!
♫ Even if I give you my all ♫
♫ Can't I captivate your heart? ♫
♫ You without a smile ♫
S-Snake, it's a snake.
I'm only twenty-nine years old.
Academic background, credentials, and experience,
not a single thing is remarkable.
I'd like for you to move out.
This is why you're still doing part-time jobs at that age!
Yes.
Perhaps this is for the better.
Mom,
Dad,
this bad son is going off ahead of you.
Properly!*
(*The Korean for "properly" sounds like "Talk Baro")
Baro! Baro!
Baro!
Did you call for me?
I'm sorry for not having lived properly.
- Here, right here!
- What?
I'm right here!
That's not mine.
My phone's over there.
You were bitten by a snake.
We're dying together.
Baro, please save me.
Save me first.
I only have three percent left. Hurry!
Hurry!
I have heard this voice somewhere before.
Now only two percent left. It's come down to one as I speak.
What nonsense is this? 112*.
(*Emergency number for police in Korea)
You can't call the police.
They might be colluding with them.
- On this contract right now—
- Call right now!
Charge me right now!
D-Doctor?
Yes?
How am I alive?
You had a drop in heart rate and blood pressure.
Wow, was it a venomous snake?
No, it had no toxicity at all.
You were too shocked by the fact that you were bitten,
so you fainted.
Luckily, the paramedics arrived promptly and wrapped up the scene.
You can be discharged after your IV injection is complete.
Okay.
That's what happened.
Why would I have a dream like that?
It's going in properly.
Okay.
This is your phone, right?
The paramedic asked me to give it to you, saying it was found where you fainted.
- Sorry?
- Please lie back down.
Oh, okay.
This isn't mine.
D-Doctor.
Doctor!
This guy talks.
L-Like me.
Re-examine...
t-this.
Doctor, shouldn't you examine me again?
It's almost dinnertime. Where could he have gone?
[Rent Listing]
Gosh, it's locked.
You charged me.
Hello.
I'm President Kim Seon Ju of Silver Lining.
Oh, hello, President Kim Seon Ju.
As if I would say that.
Hey, if you're President Kim Seon Ju, then I'm Steve Jobs.
I know it's hard for you to believe.
I also feel the same.
Gosh, is someone controlling it remotely or something?
Or is it voice modulation of some kind?
There's something I need to show you.
O-One billion won?
I'll reward you with 100 million won first.
Please tell me your bank account number.
Is it a new voice phishing scam?
Voice phishing tells you to send money.
They don't say they'll deposit money.
Oh, that's true.
I only have 20,000 won anyway.
What could possibly happen?
One, ten, hundred, ten thousand...
Wh-What are you?
I'm Silver Lining's President, Kim Seon Ju.
Are you really Kim Seon Ju?
Wait, you're President Kim Seon Ju, Sir?
If you fulfill my request,
I can give you the whole one billion.
If you're...
really President Kim Seon Ju, on top of the billion won,
please hire me at Silver Lining.
Sure.
Go to the office.
My spit came out.
Please become the president of Silver Lining
in my place.
President?
The president?
[A false dream is toxic]
[Hello, this is Silver Lining's Recruiter.]`
[This is to let you know about our decision to not hire you.]
[Unlock My Boss]
Fine. I was just cast to act as the president.
Let's go with this acting of a lifetime!
What are you scheming now,
appointing a young brat as the president?
On that day, why I had to hike the mountain in the middle of driving up in my car.
This is why you need my cooperation.
- Who do you think I am?
- Do you want to get fired?
Secretary Jeong could be the most trustworthy ally or the most lethal foe at the same time.
That's how I can blow away Silver Lining and my f***ing niece.
Let's set it so they'd waste some time.