[Chae Jong Hyeop]
[Seo Eun Soo]
[Park Sung Woong]
[Unlock My Boss]
[Locales, organizations, characters, agencies, and incidents in this drama are not real. This is a work of fiction.]
When the AI AlphaGo appeared for the first time,
[Supreme Court, Reviewing Trial Use of "AI Judge"]
the possibility of AIs replacing some careers was largely discussed.
It seems the age of AI judges isn't too far away.
The Supreme Court decided to review the proposal to
[Day of Silver Lining Final Interview]
use AI exclusively to settle compensations in a civil court case.
Here is your beef bone soup.
- Okay.
- Here.
Hello.
Aigoo, welcome!
- How many people are you?
- Three people.
Please sit anywhere you'd like over there.
There are many people.
Let's sit there.
A system where it creates...
drafts for the verdict automatically.
Young man,
aren't all the news broadcasts live?
That's right.
But over there...
he's...
The AI will take over...
Oh, you don't know about AI anchors.
It uses the computer to replicate the announcer's face and voice.
Replicate?
Aigoo...
What a strange world.
Aigoo, seriously.
- Enjoy your food.
- Yes, thank you.
Aigoo, what should I get?
Are you here to eat alone?
I came
to get an update today.
Okay.
Thanks to you, I get to eat during the noon news broadcast.
While doing that, you might
- end up starving.
- Sorry?
If you can't prove to have a more competitive edge than him,
wouldn't you end up that way?
You're really confident.
If you're that confident,
please come to the evening news and say it in person.
The plan for Silver Lining.
Why would I?
I'm giving you a special invitation.
I'm capable of that much, at least.
Do you know how many subscribers Silver Lining's SNS (social networking sites) has?
It's way more influential than the evening news.
Why would I bother making an appearance?
You choose to respond to good intentions with evil.
President Kim, do you tend to make many enemies?
I tend to state the facts.
[2: Unlocked]
[Baro]
So you're saying...
President Kim Seon Ju's soul was trapped in a phone
on top of being ambushed?
And you picked up that phone.
How are you seeing and talking right now?
It's a process where I see through
the camera lens and talk through the speaker.
Wow...
They make them nicely these days.
Then try explaining this as well.
Do you see it? Someone like Kim Seon Ju got ambushed,
but there's not a single news article about it.
If they're able to ambush someone like Kim Seon Ju,
they can cover it up as well.
Gosh...
- It sounds like a scam.
- Don't do it if it sounds like a scam.
There are more than enough people who need one billion won.
Oh, wait!
The 100 million won! Is that
real money?
You can go ahead and confirm it yourself.
Do you think I won't be able to?
Spending money is the easiest thing to do.
All right.
I'm going to buy wireless earphones.
It better not be fake money, or else.
[Order Complete]
This really works?
Really?
Wow...
What do I do?
It's so hot.
How...
How could this happen to me?
Is this...
perhaps...
like The Truman Show? (T/N: An American movie in which the main character discovers that his whole life has actually been the subject of a 24/7 reality TV series)
Do you believe that a person's trapped in a phone?
Does he lack common sense or something?
- Wouldn't you be fooled if you got a billion won?
- Seriously!
It's so funny.
[Park In Seong]
Aigoo!
- President Park!
- Hyeong!
There, there.
It's weird.
Isn't it weird
that I became a president?
What's so weird, man?
Is there a law that says you can't be the President of a subsidiary of Beomyeong Group,
the company with the highest market cap in the country, Silver Lining?
What the heck?
What's all this?
A bib?
Are you Superman or something?
It's a congratulatory gift.
[Light of Miracle! L.E.D.]
It's a LED mask that passed the safety standards
set by the Ministries of Industry and Food and Drugs Safety.
220 LED chips will permeate deeply into your skin and
create elastic and translucent skin.
[Light of Miracle! L.E.D.]
What's this? Why are you doing this?
H-Hyeong, why are you doing this?
Hyeong!
Gosh!
Let me look at the facts objectively.
Park In Seong!
You're going to decide logically.
This is a dream.
This is reality.
It's a dream.
It's reality.
In Seong, come and eat!
Fine. Well...
I just got cast as President.
Park In Seong,
let's go with this acting role of my lifetime!
I think I gave you more than enough time.
I decided.
You just need to register your fingerprint on this contract.
I'll send the signed contract to your email.
In Seong, let's eat!
Okay.
There's just...
one last question I have.
It'll be your last question.
From now on, you just have to do as I say, In Seong.
I thought about this over and over, but...
there's something I don't understand.
If you're really Kim Seon Ju...
President Kim Seon Ju of Silver Lining,
why did you have to–
Choose me out of so many other people? ♪
♫ I never once wanted a relationship... ♫
- ♫ That was to be just a pass-by. ♫
- Are you into showbiz stuff again?
I thought I'd get some help with the farm since my son came to visit us.
It's my fault for expecting and jumping to conclusions.
That's not it.
- I'm preparing for a talent show.
- What?
What did you say?
I got hired...
- by Silver Lining.
- What?
What?
Silver...
I've never heard of that company.
Do they sell jade pads?
Silver Lining is an IT company leading future technologies.
Chosen as number one for four years in a row in job seeker preference surveys,
it's a global company that
even a countryside old man should be aware of.
Countryside?
Doesn't it seem like the machine is riled up?
Wait...
then...
our son got hired by a corporation?
Oh, my son!
You did so well! Aigoo...
Aigoo, I'm so proud of you.
Thank you so much.
[I couldn't find it.]
[Retreat.]
[Beomyeong Group]
The magpie cried early in the morning.
It looks like something good will happen on your way to Seoul.
Yes.
Will your phone wear out if you keep rubbing it like that?
Aigoo, I'm so proud of my son.
Here.
[Deposit: 50 million won]
Fifty million won?
I was sending you money.
Where did you suddenly get this much money?
I decided to withdraw my security deposit.
Did she already give you your money?
I guess the landlord was in a rush.
Where are you going to live then?
The company is providing a residence.
It's a big corporation, you know.
Aigoo...
Can we really just take this money?
I'm sorry for being unable to be a good son thus far.
For now, use it for your urgent needs and
also... build a big greenhouse for the shine muscat.
(T/N: A popular breed of large green grapes)
I'll be back.
Is he okay? Don't we need to go after him?
Let him be. He's going to brag to the foreman.
Aigoo...
you're making me so proud. My baby.
That's right. There's nothing you can't do with a phone.
So why can't a person be trapped in a phone?
Are you sleeping?
There's no such a thing as a nap in Kim Seon Ju's life.
I don't live my life that half-heartedly, you see.
Okay. But...
even if you...
sent an email beforehand, will the employees believe me to be the boss?
They won't trust you, In Seong.
Instead, they'll obey if it's my decision
because I have authority and credibility.
You just stay still, In Seong. I'll make you the boss.
There's a place you need to go before.
[Seoul]
How does a pair of pants cost 530,000 won?
Sir, this is the price of the belt.
This item costs 5.3 million won in total with the top and bottom.
Sorry?
Oh, my gosh.
Wait, where are you going?
It's too expensive.
- I'll just order it online–
- Buy them.
What?
I'm telling you to pay with this.
It looks good on you.
It looks really good on you.
It's very nice.
Buy that one as well.
Sunglasses need to be oversized, with an edge.
In Seong?
In Seong, that's enough. That's enough!
SNS is prohibited.
Check the contract.
[SNS is prohibited.]
What is this one for?
Wow...
It's so nice.
Do the bubbles always
disappear so quickly?
It's different from dramas and movies.
Gosh, had I known, I would've brought a scrub.
Nice. So happy.
♫ You only live once ♫
I'll pay with this.
Well, room service will be paid when you check out.
Oh, that's right.
That's right! They also did it... like that in Las Vegas.
Wow...
I ate all this delicious food by myself.
Aren't you hungry? Will you be full if I charge you?
I haven't felt hunger in here.
Oh, then...
what about sleep? Can you sleep?
I don't have time to sleep. I have a lot of work to do.
What?
I need to know what happened on the mountain that day.
But unbelievably, I don't remember exactly up to one week before the accident.
It's something like post-traumatic
stress disorder or memory loss?
That's why I checked my schedule with Baro.
I had a golf meeting with the Beomyeong family that day.
Then I was on the way to the campsite to meet my daughter.
I'm sorry for being late, Princess.
My phone's GPS location also matches the itinerary from that day.
- Then how did you...
- But the strange thing... started here.
Isn't this the local road by the mountain?
To get to the point where you picked up this phone,
I need to have started hiking from here, but it's not even a hiking trail.
What about the car you drove that day?
I'm searching for the same model with the same color, but I can't find it.
They probably scrapped the car.
I'm looking for more clues, but there's a limit to doing it inside a phone.
This is why you need my cooperation.
Did I really even go to the golf course that day?
Why did I get out of the car all of a sudden,
and why I had to hike over the mountain...
I must find out the truth
to know why I ended up in this state.
That's how I can return to being a president and
being a father.
I understand.
It's okay. It's okay.
Is this the head here?
Butler Shim!
What about the boss?
Can you still not reach him?
You said you've known the boss since he learned how to walk.
Is there anyone you can contact?
He does big things.
He could've gone on a business trip overseas.
Better yet,
he didn't get to rest these days.
But he doesn't just take days off without a plan.
That's why we can't take off, either.
What are you doing right now?
What do you mean?
Why would you leave the phone here?
Isn't it common to leave it by your head when you sleep?
So are you saying two men will sleep on one bed?
What do you mean by sleep? Why would you put it like that?
Gosh.
Geez.
Aigoo...
Wait.
Should I turn off the phone? So you can rest?
Just leave it.
There's no guarantee I'll still be here after a restart.
I wanted to make this certain before going to work.
Why me?
You said you failed the final interview for Silver Lining, right?
That proves that you have no affiliation or connections at our company.
I'm riding the parachute*
(*Preferential hire by higher-ups)
because I have no connections.
As the boss, on top of that?
Sleep comfortably because it'll get exhausting starting tomorrow.
Wait.
Yes?
Take off the case!
If you have my phone, they'll be suspicious of you.
[We Make Future]
Before your first day, you need to remember some things.
Hello.
Beomyeoung's Executive Director, Oh Mi Ran.
As Chairman Oh Beom Geun, founder and her father, suddenly lost consciousness last year,
she's taken the role of Chairman, more or less.
Regarding the progress on the development of self-driven cars...
As Beomyeong Car's biggest shareholder, she plans to succeed with self-driven cars
and officially become Chairwoman, stepping over her uncle.
This is the end of my presentation. Thank you.
So she'd need Silver Lining's help to make the brains of those cars, right?
And Vice Chairman Oh Yeong Geun can't stand to see that.
As he served a prison sentence in his brother's place, he's not a man who holds back.
He also has an exceptional loyalty toward Beomyeong.
He'll never be satisfied with being the Vice Chairman.
We're just a shrimp getting crushed by those two whales, then?
Silver Lining is not a shrimp.
We're the kingmaker who can hop on any of the whales' backs.
Director Kwak will be outside.
He's a typical "strong to the weak" and "weak to the strong" type.
He's from Beomyeong Electronics, who worked under Oh Yeong Geun.
He was planted to hold me in check.
Today is the new president's first day of work.
Let us greet him with a devout and genuine heart. Understood?
- Yes, Sir.
- Okay, line up.
Button these up.
Is it always like this?
It wasn't like this when I was here.
They became old-fashioned because their boss changed.
President!
How do you do?
Act as naturally as you can.
What are you doing? Hurry and go!
Right. Don't be afraid, Park In Seong.
You were the golden 27th Class of Evergreen Troupe.
What is there that I haven't done?
I've done my best with any role.
This is my stage and...
from this moment on, I'm the president.
Sound!
Speed!
- Camera!
- Roll.
One to one to one.
Ready...
action!
What are you doing right now?
Shouldn't you all be working?
This kind of protocol...
I absolutely hate it.
Don't do it ever again.
Okay.
Okay, dismissed.
Did you have any discomfort on your ride over, Sir?
The Pyeongyang noodles from back then?
Hello.
I'm Secretary Jeong Se Yeon.
I see a road of flowers in front of my–
The shirt, right?
Come this way, President.
Yes.
Do you and Secretary Jeong know each other?
We met once by coincidence.
Excuse me. That day...
You don't need to explain how a job seeker became
the president overnight.
- It's this way.
- Okay.
[Office of President (CEO), Park In Seong]
I prepared as much as possible in a hurry, but is there anything else you need?
This is sufficient.
It feels new to be seeing you like this again.
That's true.
It wasn't that I interviewed you, but the new boss, you, had interviewed us.
I just knew you were different from the interview.
Is that so?
Your preparedness to inspect in advance like a secret royal inspector...
If I was rude in any way, I apologize.
I heard from President Kim Seon Ju via email.
Yes. Well...
By the way,
what's your relationship with President Kim?
Age, schooling, hometown,
and even your looks.
You have nothing in common.
Let's say we have a particular relationship.
Exactly how are you particularly related?
That's...
It's okay.
I touch him like this.
Sorry?
Meddling...
with each other and advising a type of touch and no touch.
You understood, right?
By the way,
I've never been a president before.
Aigoo...
Who ever gets to be born as president?
You learn as you go.
Even if that's true, I just have no experience.
More so, you need to be given opportunities to realize...
your capabilities.
You're very different from when I first met you.
You see... I might lack some hair* here,
(*He says the word for "thoughtless" here, but it sounds like "hair")
but I'm a warm person once you get to know me.
What would you
like to do about your secretary?
- Sorry?
- I'm talking about Secretary Jeong.
Usually, when a new president comes,
it's very common to bring the secretary they already work with.
What do I do? Should I get a new secretary?
Secretary Jeong worked with me for a long time.
She doesn't talk lightly or show her emotions easily.
Then I won't replace her.
On the other hand, it means knowing her true feelings is that much more difficult.
As much as she knows me well, there's a high chance of her finding out about us.
Then I'll replace her right away.
She's fully aware of my official itinerary and private schedules as well.
She probably also accompanied me at the last golf course meeting.
I might be able to find a clue from Se Yeon, then.
Secretary Jeong could be the most trustworthy ally or
the most lethal foe at the same time.
Now, what should I do?
Go to the President's Office and connect my phone to the computer.
For what purpose–
Sh*t...
Ahjumma!
- I'm sorry.
- Are you crazy?
I told you not to put cleaning tools in front of the restroom, didn't I?
- Look!
- I was mopping the floor, so...
Look, a person fell over there!
- I'm sorry.
- How many times do I need to tell you? So annoying!
- Do you want to get fired?
- I'm sorry
Excuse me. It was my mistake. I was looking at my phone, so–
- Hurry and wipe it.
- Just leave.
Wipe it up right now!
I wasn't going to say this, but
this is why you're cleaning the restroom at that age!
this is why you're still doing part-time jobs at that age!
This is my stage and
I've got influence.
Ready...
action!
Don't do anything that makes you stand out.
- Wipe it up!
- Are you the only one working here, Ahjussi?
You're so annoying.
Do you want to get fired?
Who the heck are you?
I really wasn't going to say this, but
this is why you're abusing your position at that age!
It's upsetting
to be on the receiving end, right?
This young bastard. Who do you think I am?
Hey!
I'm Team Manager Nam of the Sales Department.
Which department are you from?
He's the newly appointed President, Park In Seong.
President, please come this way.
Thank you so much.
Your action just now is a clear violation of the contract.
I'll apply the three-strikes policy. You have one strike.
I'm sorry.
I really wanted to try it once.
Abusing my power.
[Abusing my power ♡]
My first day of work is already so hectic.
"Connect your phone to the computer"?
Yes.
I need to check if there were attempts to hack Baro 4.0 in the past few days.
If it's the beta version, does that mean it's still being developed?
There are more tests to do.
Wow, it even has Son Heung Min.
Because he's Silver Lining's model.
We can even create your voice with just one hour of recording.
Basically the same principle as listening to recent songs in deceased Kim Kwang Seok's voice.
I took a step further from there.
Baro, what should I wear today?
Current temperature is 18°C.
I suggest a dress that goes well with the spring breeze.
Okay! A dress!
Baro, what should I wear today?
Current temperature is 18°C.
I suggest a dress that goes well with the spring breeze.
Gosh, you idiot.
So far, AIs were designed to give the same answers to the same questions.
However, we're developing a customized AI which does deep learning on certain individuals at Silver Lining.
It's not your generic AI masked under the name of versatility.
It's an AI that thinks, decides, and talks like Son Heung Min, my mom, or me.
Baro 4.0 will be just that.
I see. Is that why
you became the test model as well?
Don't try to know more.
I'm still a president, so I need to know–
I can trust you because you don't know anything.
The more you know, the less I'll be able to trust you.
This is President Kim Seon Ju of Silver Lining.
Due to a decline in health, the previous president will take a sabbatical.
I'm contacting you to approve the appointment of the next president.
- Move aside!
- You can't do this, Sir.
- You won't move?
- I can't let you pass.
Move aside!
- Move out of the way!
- Vice Chairman!
- What the heck is going on?
One moment, please.
Hey, move out of my way!
What are you scheming now?
Please calm down, Vice Chairman.
This is the Beomyeong Group Chairwoman's Office.
Yes.
When Hyeong-nim was in this place, there were fundamental principles. However,
during this critical period, take a sabbatical?
During this critical period, could he be facing an unavoidable circumstance?
On top of that, appointing a young brat as the president!
The board of directors won't just sit back!
As the largest shareholder of Beomyeong, I approved.
Who exactly won't sit back?
Why don't you just wait and see?
If it's gold, it'll shine.
If it's iron, it'll rust.
Beomyeong...
Electronics is...
Yeong Geun's.
And then...
Car belongs to...
Mi Ran.
So you're saying as Silver Lining's stock price rises, Beomyeong Electronics' value falls, right?
You catch on faster than I expected.
Inherently, Silver Lining and Vice Chairman Oh can't get along.
Who's there?
It's the list of new secretaries from Director Kwak.
All four of them can start working tomorrow.
There must be a misunderstanding. I haven't decided to replace my secretary...
[Office of President (CEO), Park In Seong]
Are you acting out of line again?
Park In Seong, I clearly warned you.
Clearly, our deal was to make me president, not to be an avatar.
In Seong?
Park In Seong–
There you go. Nicely done.
Straight from here...
Aigoo, what brings you to this lowly place?
I'd have come right over had you called.
This.
Wow, did you already finish reviewing it?
Do you also want to check out your replacement?
Pardon?
Why would you give the list of Secretary Jeong's replacements to her?
Because that's her job.
Did you have to make her deliver the list of people who will replace her?
That's how it was done–
If that's the case, change it now.
At least,
while I'm the president,
no low-level employee nor executive will get backstabbed or be cornered in broad daylight.
Something's happening in the lobby.
Gosh, what the hell?
Who the heck are you?
Let me go!
Geez...
You're here.
I know her.
I told you not to come to my work.
I told you I only trust money.
I won't have a reason to see you again after this, right?
How did you get this money?
I just need to pay back the money.
Why?
You won't take it if it's dirty money?
Write a receipt
saying I paid off my debt.
Write a receipt before you go.
What do you mean?
There's 50 million won remaining.
Do you think money grows on trees for me?
Of course, you have to pay the interest.
You should've paid me sooner if you were going to end up paying me anyway.
I'll see you again.
Se Yeon is a good person,
so I've decided to work with her.
You've known her for a total of six hours and 48 minutes since getting to work,
and you've deemed her a good person?
I think Se Yeon will become a reliable ally.
And your reason?
Do you have a basis for that conclusion?
Her shirt.
This is a woman's size.
I wish my stocks would jump, but instead
the tame cat is the first to jump on the table.*
(*A Korean saying that means watch out for the quiet ones)
It's not what you're thinking.
What do you think I'm thinking?
What exactly am I thinking?
Is she pretty?
Her heart is pretty.
It had nothing to do with her, but she stepped up to help.
Oh, the one who lent you her shirt for the interview?
Yes.
- Wow.
- She's a good person.
A good person?
Then why are you blushing? Huh?
Hey, listen carefully.
We're going to include Miss Shirt's friend for a double date.
I can act as the WD-40 in the middle, so you can just relax.
My instincts tell me Miss Shirt is pretty.
What do you mean, shirt?
Stop saying nonsense
and convince me with precise data and probability or irrefutable logic.
It's a matter of life or death for me.
But can you really explain a person with data or probability?
A person isn't an AI.
You're wrong.
The probability of trusting someone recommended by Director Kwak is 0%.
In contrast, Secretary Jeong is half-half.
Secretary Jeong is the better choice.
This is how you should convince me from now on.
[Office of President (CEO), Park In Seong]
You just agreed as well.
At the same time, you rammed into Director Kwak as you pleased
and only have one strike left.
He's a rookie.
He's just a naïve child whose emotions escape him,
so you can rest assured.
Yes.
That's what I thought.
How dare such a baseless bastard...
I'll have the board of directors propose a dismissal.
What can we gain from chasing out a rookie?
Just wait.
Let's set the stage so they'll waste some time.
That's how I can blow away Silver Lining and my f*cking niece*.
(*He pronounces the word "niece" in Korean to sound like the f-word)
Understood.
How did that thing go?
I'm looking into it.
Okay, keep at it.
I can't believe I get to live in a place like this.
I never knew I'd live somewhere like this, either.
I guess...
You should be living in a 67 pyeong* house in Pyeongchang-dong,
(1 pyeong = 35.5832 sq. ft.)
but you're living in a 6.7 inch space.
- Oh?
- What?
Is something wrong?
It's already 6:00 p.m.
Since I'm the boss,
I can just leave on the dot without walking on eggshells, right?
You didn't really seem like the type to walk on eggshells to begin with.
Wow, goosebumps!
I get that a lot.
I guess we've become really close in this short time.
Se Yeon, Are you not getting...
off work?*
(*Made a pun with her name)
It's already five minutes past 6:00 p.m.
These are handover materials.
Well...
Throw them out,
Secretary Jeong.
See you tomorrow!
Is it here?
That two-story house is my house.
- Could I buy this kind of house with 1 billion–
- You cannot.
What?
With 1 billion won, you could maybe buy a bedroom.
Wow, my sorry one-room life...
Anyway, is she even coming?
Min Ah likes to buy chocolate cookies from the mart.
After buying groceries with the nanny, she should be home about now.
It's SDMLH.
Sorry?
"Spending Definitely Makes Life Happier."
That kid knows the taste of capitalism.
She's coming.
Oh, she doesn't know me.
Is that her?
She's so cute.
Are you okay?
We waited all this time.
You only saw her for a minute.
Let's just go.
He's coming back out.
Is he going home?
No, they're both live-in caretakers.
He drives pretty recklessly.
Follow him!
- Sorry?
- I said, follow him!
Why? I went through the trouble to get here.
Hurry and follow him!
Seeing how I'm in this state, there definitely must be a disruption in their plan.
They'll be approaching to get a grip on the situation.
In that case, there's no other suitable target than Butler Shim.
[I have arrived.]
Or...
He might already be an accomplice.
Go and find out who he's meeting.
Welcome.
Who is that?
What?
Why is Se Yeon coming out from there?
President, take a look.
Go back home right now!
- What?
- Now!
Hurry!
Bring out the manilla envelope from my study.
I'll release the door lock.
You can go in now.
Around this time, the nanny will have put Min Ah to sleep and
should be cross-stitching in her room.
You have about one hour.
What do I do now?
I-I don't think I can enter through the front door.
Go to the right side.
To the left now.
No, no. Further ahead.
To the left from here.
It's huge.
Go in through the poolside door.
Don't worry about the CCTV.
I'll erase the footage.
You said you'll make me a president, but you're making me a thief instead?
Did you think it'd be easy to earn one billion won?
Take your shoes off.
I can't erase your footsteps from inside a phone.
The study is the last room on the second floor.
There's someone in there.
It's armor.
An armor!
It's empty inside.
There's no time. Hurry and go!
Ji Hye went down to the first floor.
Wow...
Wow, there's a car in here!
It's an expensive car. Be careful.
Where is the envelope again?
The safe next to the desk on the second floor.
Go up the staircase over there.
I can't see because it's dark.
Let's just come back when no one is home.
You saw at the café.
They've started to make their move.
We need to find it immediately.
This isn't a study.
It's larger than my house.
There should be a safe next to the desk.
There's a passcode here.
Zero, six, three, zero.
There's nothing!
Did you look properly?
The manilla envelope isn't there?
There's nothing inside!
L-Let me take a look!
There's no way it could be missing!
Are you sure you left it in here?
You could be mistaken.
No, no. I always leave it there.
By the way what exactly is it?
I need to know what it is to find it.
Wait a minute. The hallway lights turned on!
Calmly hide yourself.
- What do I do now?
- Calmly!
We never know, so let's look a little–
Han Ji Hye is coming to the study.
Hurry! Hurry!
What do I do, President?
If I get caught now–
Oh, my gosh!
What's wrong?
I thought I heard something from the study.
There's no way.
President isn't even here.
[Restricted Caller ID]
Didn't you hear it just now?
I heard it.
It sounded like a phone.
Oh, my. It was mine.
It's the president!
What?
What did he say?
He said he'll give me a raise.
How silly. It was mine.
My heart almost stopped.
You don't come from Silicon Valley for no reason, right?
How did you think to send a text in that split moment?
You just need to trust me now.
Wow...
What's this?
Restricted caller ID?
[Why are you not picking up? I'm the owner of that phone.]
What's this nonsense? This is Kim Seon Ju's phone.
[Give me my phone back!]
Kim Seon Ju...
What is your identity?
[Unlock My Boss]
Are you really Kim Seon Ju?
Do you know what the really unfair thing is?
Daring to sit in that seat for once...
Are you telling me to live at your house, President?
Se Yeon must also be quite confused.
Looking back, they were days of agony.
Are you able to communicate with the president?
President of the renowned Silver Lining should at least take responsibility for what he said.
Dodge!
Move!