[Meet You at the Blossom]
Mr. Jin.
Huai'en.
You lied to me.
I didn't.
Huai'en, listen to me.
Mr. Jin is hiding
such a pretty girl in his mansion.
No wonder he left the girl in Yicui House
to themselves.
No, I didn't.
Why didn't Mr. Jin go out often?
It turned out
that he had a pretty girl in his house.
Look at her pretty face.
She must be a woman dressing like a man.
She's a woman dressing like a man.
No wonder Mr. Jin hasn't been here lately.
No.
She's really gorgeous.
Gorgeous.
Mr. Jin, good for you.
You're so lucky.
No.
Where did you get such a beautiful girl?
My hand.
Run.
Huai'en, listen to me.
I didn't.
I'm not here to have fun.
I am here to…
Have you forgotten your promise to me?
No. I haven't.
Is that what you call liking?
Why did you lie to me?
Huai'en.
Huai'en, I didn't.
I didn't serve you well, did I?
Why did you come to a place like this?
Huai'en.
Huai'en, you have to trust me.
I didn't.
Huai'en.
Young master.
He's fine.
Rather than getting back at me,
you'd better think
about how to keep their mouths shut.
Stop crying.
It's all right.
Go.
Jin Xiaobao,
You tantalized me first.
Since you tantalized me,
you can't go back.
It's okay if you can't control yourself.
I'll control you.
You can hang out with girls
without fear.
That's because your Jin family is rich.
Then, I'll take everything from you
so that you can't tantalize anyone else.
From now on,
no matter where you are,
you can only rely on me.
He woke up.
Young master.
Young master, don't cry.
Young master, cry if you want to.
Young master,
Yicui House has been taken care of.
I've given them enough money.
They wouldn't say anything about it.
We didn't tell the master
and the madam either. Right?
It's all right, young master.
As for Huai'en,
we won't let him go.
No.
If he dies,
what should I do?
What was wrong with me?
How did I fall in love with him?
Young master,
you might be obsessed.
I heard about a religion in Miao district.
They have Gu poison
to confuse men.
I…
I think Gu poison
is used by women.
You're right.
Says who? Men can use it, too.
Young master, I think you were poisoned by him.
Right, young master.
You must have been poisoned.
Otherwise,
how can you be so infatuated with a man?
He's right.
Young master, don't worry.
We'll offer a large reward
to find the poisoner.
When your poison is lifted,
we'll deal with him.
Does…
Does that really work?
Of course.
You go get people from that religion.
I'll give him
all the money he wants.
Ask him to poison Huai'en.
Okay.
And make Huai'en fall in love with me.
Young master,
are you out of mind?
He almost killed you yesterday.
Yeah.
You can't blame him for yesterday.
But he shouldn't have been so cruel to me.
How did I fall in love with such a bad man?
All right, young master.
Zhuang.
Master.
What did His Highness say?
Huai'en
is the son of the second prince
and Princess Xue.
What?
What should we do now?
Kill him now.
Kill him?
Zhuang,
go arrange it.
We'll take action tonight.
Mr. Jin, please don't kill him.
We need to use him
to draw the second prince out.
Master, are you really going to kill him?
You can't disobey His Highness.
Dear,
what should we do?
His Highness is from the Imperial Court.
Zheng Huai'en is Xue Wei's grandson.
Although we didn't mean
to kill Xue's whole family.
We are responsible.
If they look into it in the future,
will we get away with it?
What do we tell His Highness if we kill him?
What do we tell him?
We'll see.
Anyway, the secret path
will be completed in three days.
By then, we will go away.
Xiaobao is in love with Huai'en.
Don't mention Xiaobao to me.
Shame on Xiaobao.
I don't know
what Zheng Huai'en did to him.
All right.
When Xiaobao knows the truth,
he will leave him.
I hope so.
Lord,
Master Jin knows who you are.
He's gathering his men.
Ask all the warriors to take action tonight.
Yes.
Wait.
Don't hurt the Jin family.
I came to you to explain.
I know
I used to have a bad reputation.
But…
But I only love you now.
I had to hang out with them
to get the prescription for my dad yesterday.
I didn't expect me to get drunk.
But I didn't do anything.
What if I'd been a little late yesterday?
Sorry, I was wrong.
Don't be mad, okay?
I promise I will never drink again.
If you're still mad,
you can hit me.
Do you think I won't hit you?
Hit me.
As long as you are not mad,
you can hit me to death.
You're good at pleasing me.
Jin Xiaobao, listen.
I'll let bygones be bygones.
But
now that you're engaged to me,
if you go to that kind of place again,
I'll break your legs.
Got it?
I'll never go there again.
It's all right.
It's a night watchman.
Huai'en,
you're holding me so tight.
I can't breathe.
Xiaobao.
You did something wrong today.
And I forgave you.
If I do something wrong,
you have to forgive me, too.
Of course.
I will forgive you for whatever you do.
A man should love his wife.
Do you mean it?
You swear.
You swear you'll forgive me
whatever I do wrong.
I, Jin Xiaobao, swear to the Lord
that I will forgive you
no matter what you do wrong.
Otherwise…
You don't want to go to a brothel, do you?
I can't agree with that.
Other than that,
I forgive you for whatever you do.
Huai'en.
What's wrong with you?
Xiaobao.
I haven't told you what my last name is, right?
Isn't your last name Zheng?
It's not.
My name is
Zongzheng Huai'en.
Surround him.
Get him.
Protect our lord.
Who's there?
Zhuang.
Stop chasing.
Let's bury Zhuang.
It's all right.
We still have the roster.
We still have a chance.
Master, something happened.
Master.
Xiaoyu is missing.
The roster is missing.
Master.
It's over.
It's all over.
Lord.
What does the Imperial Court
intend to do with the Jin family
when I get the roster?
Kill them all.
What does my dad want to do with them?
He wants the same.
Li Gongxiang,
the Jin family is extremely wealthy.
They have countless treasures.
I don't care if you hand them over
to the Imperial Court or to my dad.
But you must not kill the Jin family.
As you command, Lord.
Prince Shen has got the information.
Now the city is on lockdown.
You can't leave through the main gate.
This is a confidant
who has been with me for 20 years.
He will take you out of the city
by the secret path.
Your Royal Highness's.
Sit down.
We got there late.
Huai'en got the roster.
I set up traps in Huaizhou.
But they seemed to be on guard.
My men waited all night
and got nothing.
By now,
he should have taken the roster
out of the city.
Mr. Wang,
why don't we go straight to Jinqishan Mountain
and destroy their base?
We have countless fine soldiers.
Are we afraid of those rustics?
Your Royal Highness,
Jinqi Mountain is miasmatic,
and its terrain is complex.
Zongzheng Yuzhan has been staying there
for nearly 20 years.
If we attack rashly,
we are like handing ourselves over.
The chief military officer
has been a spy for years.
Didn't he get a clear picture of their base?
Shaoyu.
Calm down.
Your Royal Highness, please calm down.
Zongzheng Yuzhan is eccentric
and suspicious.
No one but Gao and Huai'en
could approach him.
Gao is loyal to him.
As for Huai'en,
I kind of watched him grow up.
He killed
and robbed
for Zongzheng Yuzhan.
He never disobeyed him.
But this time, he secretly deployed in advance
to save the lives of the Jin family.
I think it had something to do
with the young master of the Jin family.
We might as well make good use
of the young master of the Jin family.
It must be so.
He made out with Jin
in the cave the other day.
It was disgusting.
So,
Mr. Li, what are you going to do?
Your Highness,
do you remember the Lingxi Gu poison
you mentioned last time?
Lingxi Gu poison?
Is that the Gu poison
that can manipulate people?
Do you want to use that on Huai'en?
It's dawn, Mr. Li.
It's time for you to meet your old friend.
Excuse me.
Go.
Hurry up.
I'll kill you.
Master.
Dad.
I'll kill you.
You'll kill him.
Why did you hit me?
Xiaobao.
Mom.
Kill me if you want.
What does Xiaobao know?
What happened?
Where is Huai'en?
Don't mention him, Xiaobao.
He took Xiaoyu
and the account book away.
Our Jin family is finished.
What?
There's no time to explain.
Xiaobao,
I've set Zhaocai and Jinbao free.
They have nothing to do
with the Jin family anymore.
Follow them
to Su Yin's in Annan.
Don't come back.
What are you talking about, mom?
Zhaocai, Jinbao, take him with you.
My son, be good.
I'm not leaving.
I'm not leaving, mom.
Take him away.
Dad, mom, let's leave together.
Young master.
I don't want to be separated from you.
Dad.
Just go, Xiaobao.
Master.
Mr. Jin,
how are you doing?
Get out of the way.
Back off.
Back off. Move.
Get out of the way.
Move.
Did you hear the news?
The richest man in Jiangnan was confiscated
of his property and sentenced to death.
Great.
Those dishonest merchants
should be sentenced.
I can't afford two drinks a day.
But they use nice Huadiao wine
to wash their feet.
It is said that they will be sent
to Linjing in three days
and be decapitated in the autumn.
What do we do?
They won't be decapitated, will they?
I don't think so.
Let's eat.
Only when you are full can you have strength.
We'll go to the Su family after the meal.
His Highness said
we could go to him if we have difficulty.
He will save our young master.
Let's eat.
I don't want to eat.
Come on.
Eat.
Get in there. Hurry.
Get in there.
Dad.
What happened?
What are we guilty of?
Why are we confiscated of our property
and sentenced to death?
What is in that account book?
What's the use of knowing that?
Even if I die, I want to know it.
Dear,
it's time to let him know.
Twenty years ago,
the new emperor ascended the throne.
He made Xue Tongen, the daughter of Xue Wei,
the Imperial Concubine.
Xue Tongen was Lianyu's aunt?
The most beautiful woman in the world?
That's right.
Princess Xue was favored by His Majesty.
Xue Wei took advantage of that
and got promoted.
He held an important position
in the Jiangnan Imperial Silk Weaving Workshop.
Soon after,
Princess Xue was pregnant.
As a result, the Xue family gained more power.
All officials flattered them.
They were very successful.
Later,
the Empress found out that Princess Xue
had an affair with the second prince,
and that child was not His Majesty's.
To cover up the scandal,
Princess Xue was killed by the Empress.
The second prince escaped with the child.
And Xue Wei was condemned.
Overnight,
the Xue family
was finished.
But…
what does that have to do with our family?
Because after that,
the second prince united with Xue Wei.
He used the name of prince
to lure Xue Wei into rebellion.
The two of them hit it off.
They colluded,
accumulated wealth,
and recruited soldiers.
Then, Xue Wei chose some merchants
who did not have much money
but had momentum
and lured them with huge profits
to establish the Furun Chamber of Commerce.
Our family
was one of them.
The Furun Chamber of Commerce
became bigger and bigger.
Soon, it accumulated a large amount of w-w-
wealth.
I thought
our Jin family was destined to succeed.
However,
five years ago,
I found that our Jin family
was just a puppet used
by the second prince to accumulate wealth.
Dad.
His Majesty is young and promising.
Not only did he quell the civil strife,
but he was about
to defeat the uncivilized tribes.
After his triumphant return,
he will rule the country.
The wealth amassed by our Jin family
will fill the empty treasury.
At that time,
our Jin family
will be the first to be dealt with
by the Imperial Court.
Dad.
We are hanging on by a thread.
So, I recorded all my possessions
in an account book.
Now, the account book is missing.
The Imperial Court
can hold us accountable fairly and squarely.
I had…
already thought of a way out.
Our family
could have left safely in three days.
I didn't expect
Huai'en
to be the son of the second prince.
He took the account book.
My work went down the drain.
The account book was sewn
by me in Xiaoyu's clothes.
Even Xiaoyu didn't know it.
But he found it out.
Master.
Did you see Huai'en take the account book
and Xiaoyu in person?
Is there
a misunderstanding?
Xiaobao.
Look at the situation.
Why are you still making excuses for him?
What did Huai'en do to you, Xiaobao?
No, dad.
I just want to know the truth.
Master.
Zhang Chun has been
doing background checks for years.
He never made a mistake.
You looked into him, too.
He's just a young master of a normal express.
He's not the second prince's son.
There must be a misunderstanding.
No.
Xiaobao.
Huai'en
is the son of the second prince.
No.
He wouldn't do this to me.
Why would he do that?
Dad.
Dad, mom.
He wouldn't do this to me.
You don't know.
He risked his life to save me.
How could he do this to me?
I know.
He must have been forced by his father.
His father is inhumane.
He had a lot of injuries.
His father treated him badly.
He must have been forced by his father.
Xiaobao.
Even if he did it,
he had his reasons.
You have to trust me.
He wouldn't do this to me.
I didn't expect Mr. Jin to be infatuated.
Let's sit down and talk.
I didn't expect Mr. Jin
to have such deep feelings for my nephew.
Nephew?
Yeah.
He's the son of my second brother
and Princess Xue.
No, he's not.
He's just a young master of a normal express.
How is this possible?
Xiaobao.
I see.
It's you.
It's you, right?
You tried to kill him many times.
Now, you're slandering him.
What do you want?
Xiaobao.
Sit down.
Zhang Chun.
All the information he gave you was fake.
Mr. Jin, I was forced.
Zongzheng Huai'en poisoned me.
I could only follow his orders.
Xiaobao.
Over the years,
Huai'en has changed his identity many times
to help my second brother with his rebellion.
He's ruthless and inhuman.
But he does everything
my second brother tells him.
He lied to you from the beginning.
Xiaobao.
His purpose…
was to get the account book
of the Furun Chamber of Commerce.
I've been deceived by him, too.
Because of our blood relationship,
I wanted to persuade him to change his ways.
But he took advantage of my sympathy
and stole my vital roster.
Didn't he already give you the roster?
He gave you the roster to save me.
Xiaobao.
Are you talking about this?
It's fake.
Huai'en used two of his confidants
to make a distraction.
He used you
and the fake roster
to bait me.
The real roster has been taken by his man
to his dad.
You
and I
were both tricked by him.
Xiaobao.
Jin Xiaobao.
You tantalized me first.
From now on,
no matter where you are,
you can only rely on me.
How is this possible?
Stop.
How can it be so real?
Your Highness,
please leave him alone.
My second brother
has been lying low and gathering strength.
He studied crooked ways
and established the Tong Sect.
His followers are all over the country.
There are his men in the Imperial Court.
There are names
of traitors that the Imperial Court
painstakingly collected over the years.
Now,
my second brother
has got your family's property.
He can recruit soldiers
and rebel now.
The country will be in chaos soon.
You helped with that.
Mr. Jin.
Stop.
Your Highness.
We're going to die.
Why do you have to be so aggressive?
You can…
redeem yourselves.
The Furun Chamber of Commerce
still has some property.
I think only you know where they are, Mr. Jin.
Huai'en worked secretly
to save the three of you.
I think that's because
he wanted to get the property.
So, he will meet you again.
When he comes to you,
all you have to do
is put this on him when he's off guard.
So you can redeem yourselves.
It's Gu poison.
Open it when you need it.
All you have to do is put it
on Huai'en's bare skin.
When you get it done,
I'll let the three of you go.
Mr. Jin,
even if you don't think about yourself,
think about your elderly parents.
It's all Huai'en's fault
that you're where you are today.
He has no sincerity for you.
Are you going to risk your parents' lives
for him?
Think about it, Mr. Jin.
It's not true.
Why?
Why did he do this to me?