=Camellias=
=Episode 3=
(Ancestral Tablet)
(Father Ruan Xiuyuan's Ancestral Tablet)
Father.
Rest assured,
I will use the blood of the Rong clan
to honor your spirits in heaven.
Lord Nine-Thousand is resting.
(Nanfeng Pavilion)
I came specifically to serve you.
(Strange.)
(He's not of royal blood,)
(yet I can't control him.)
Had enough?
My Lord,
are you satisfied?
You've got skills.
Found me so quickly.
Oh no. He was waiting for me.
Still trying to control me?
How could that be?
I
only wish to serve you.
What are you doing, My Lord?
Didn't you say you wanted me?
I'm giving you the chance.
Of course I want this.
I just worry your body
might not handle it.
You've lived in a dungeon.
You must know nothing
of intimacy between men and women.
Let me teach you.
(What's wrong with him?
Why is he acting so strange?)
(So this was all for show.)
My Lord,
I have my ways too.
He's gone.
You touched me for so long.
Did you find the pendant?
My Lord, you're no ordinary man.
I can't read your mind at all.
Then you lose.
But after the past few days,
you must believe
that I possess the Divine Power.
Besides,
whatever you command,
I will give my all.
You mentioned before
that the Divine Power
can control people's minds.
Can it control anyone?
Not everyone.
Servants and young noble ladies,
they're ordinary-minded.
I can easily manipulate them.
But someone like you,
with a will as strong
as iron walls,
I can't.
Stop it.
Go back.
I'll take you to the palace tomorrow.
(Taiji Hall)
Dress as a servant and stay close to me.
Remember.
Do not draw attention.
Yes.
I'll follow your lead, My Lord.
I heard you spent last night
in the Dragon's Embrace.
With such a fine body,
you may have all the skills,
but I fear you lack the strength.
General Rong Xiu, you must have
eyes in the back of your head.
You know my every move.
Indeed.
When hunting the other day,
I spotted this jade bi
at first glance.
His Majesty
will be delighted.
I fear it's just a crafted illusion.
A skilled artisan's work.
Don't you understand, My Lord?
In this world,
sometimes,
right and wrong
don't matter.
Such a massive jade bi.
Presenting this will surely
delight His Majesty.
I was hunting a few days ago
when a nine-colored deer led the way
(Diligence in Governance)
and revealed this jade bi.
It must be a divine blessing,
a sign of Your Majesty's glory
lasting ten thousand generations.
What?
It's cracked! How did it break?
How dare you!
General.
How could he?
A broken jade presented
to His Majesty?
Yeah.
That's supreme disrespect!
(Right and wrong don't matter.)
(Those are your own words.)
(Break the jade bi.)
(Now's my chance to leave.)
Isn't this openly defying the Emperor?
How can a flawed piece
symbolize His Majesty's authority,
even the nation's fate?
Before entering the palace,
I inspected it thoroughly.
The jade was flawless.
This is suspicious.
I beg Your Majesty
to grant me a few days.
I will get to the bottom of this.
You must be
exhausted from these past few days.
Take a good rest.
This matter,
let it go.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
(I should have known)
(she wouldn't behave.)
Consort Yu!
Mercy, Consort Yu!
Why are you still alive?
Holy Maiden,
I had nothing to do
with your sister's death!
You were my sister's personal maid.
She died,
yet you still live.
Do you expect me to believe
you had nothing to do with it?
Even if you don't speak,
I can uncover the truth.
I'll talk!
Consort Rong forced me
to plant the Zhao Gu worm!
I had no choice!
You sacrificed my sister
to save yourself!
Then you will join her in death!
Join her.
Join her. Join her.
(Sang, even if I die today,)
(I will make sure all who harmed you)
(join you in the underworld.)
Who goes there?
My Lord!
She offended me.
Offending Lord Nine-Thousand,
she deserves death.
Take her.
Yes.
How dare she offend the Lord?
She deserves death!
Take her!
Reporting, Your Highness,
the inner palace guards report
that the maid who served Jiang Yusang
somehow offended
Lord Nine-Thousand today
and was executed.
She's here.
Spring has come.
Send some peach blossom cakes
to my brother's manor.
Yes.
General,
peach blossom cakes from Consort Rong.
Zhaohua is so thoughtful.
She knows my favorite
is peach blossom cakes.
If not for Zhaohua
insisting on marrying that darn emperor,
I would never have given everything
to help him take the throne.
And yet,
not only does he mistreat her,
but he's also unfaithful.
Zhaohua, rest assured,
I won't let anyone
dim your glory.
♪The moon sinks in the west♪
♪The cold lamp burns low♪
♪No one knocks upon the mountain gate♪
♪Snow-white winds and moonlight
touch me first♪
♪Pear blossoms fill the courtyard♪
♪Yet love and hate entwine♪
♪Bound by precepts,
yet craving worldly desires♪
♪Gathering red beans
for half a lifetime♪
♪The Buddha speaks of countless paths♪
♪How can one glance spanning ages
save a wandering soul♪
♪Trapped within
the space between your brows♪
♪Falling deeper and deeper♪
♪The green lamp sheds no light♪
♪Upon one who entered the path♪
♪The six senses cannot cleanse
the dust of the past♪
♪In dreams, it's you♪
♪Beyond dreams, no one♪
♪Clinging to one obsession,
adrift in a sea of suffering♪
♪I can't forget the stars in your eyes♪
♪Our fate had already taken root♪
♪In this mortal world, there is only us♪
♪Hopelessly bound by love♪