=Camellias=
=Episode 13=
Feng Liu.
My Lord!
What happened?
He suddenly attacked me.
How could that be?
My Lord.
Rong Zhaohua.
Holy Maiden,
please don't act rashly.
To the outside world,
you're already dead.
If Rong Zhaohua
killed you now,
no one would ever know.
Besides,
My Lord risked everything to save you.
Don't let his efforts go to waste.
My Lord.
You're awake.
My Lord,
you're finally awake.
The Holy Maiden
has already bandaged your wounds.
But what happened just now?
You actually attacked her?
My Lord.
You...
What's wrong with you, My Lord?
My Lord.
You hit me too, My Lord?
My Lord,
are you alright?
My Lord!
My Lord.
Yukui.
Look at you.
You went full force on me,
but treated the Holy Maiden gently.
You'd rather hurt yourself
than hurt her,
choosing beauty over loyalty.
My Lord,
you haven't eaten all day.
Perhaps
you should have something.
Too sweet and cloying.
Who likes this?
My Lord,
you usually
love these peach blossom cakes.
This one's acceptable.
My Lord,
stay away from greasy food.
Holy Maiden.
From what I can see,
My Lord isn't poisoned.
He's been struck
by a secret art called Soul Swap.
Once this art takes hold,
it changes you.
What you once liked,
you'll dislike,
and what you disliked,
you'll suddenly like.
From what I see,
Holy Maiden,
My Lord
went full force on me,
but toward you, he still seems to have
some shred of awareness.
So,
I'll leave My Lord
in your care.
You want some?
Get out!
Zhaohua?
Zhaohua,
I didn't know it was you.
Are you hurt?
Your Majesty,
there's no need
to explain.
These wounds are nothing.
The wounds in your heart,
those are what break my heart.
May I ask
what's troubling you?
Just
some trivial matters of state.
Is that true?
I think
it's someone's disappearance
that's been troubling you.
I can't hide anything from you.
The reason I'm still thinking of her
is that
she has her uses.
Zhaohua,
don't take it to heart.
I don't mind.
I know
that in Your Majesty's heart,
I come first.
Other women,
they're just playthings.
If you want her back,
I'll bring her to you.
You'd really do that?
But rest assured,
in my heart,
you'll always be first.
I know.
Let me go!
Let go!
You witch,
let me go!
Witch!
Call me that again,
and I'll have to punish you.
Do you think
I can't kill you?
Can't look at me?
Afraid you might remember something
and fall for me again?
What are you doing?
Hey.
Don't think that just because
you treated my wounds,
I'll trust you.
(Don't think that just because)
(you took my injuries onto yourself,)
(I'll go easy on you.)
(If My Lord wakes up)
(and sees you here,)
(he'll be overjoyed.)
Come on.
Drink the medicine.
Not drinking?
Then don't blame me for being forceful.
Hey.
Holy Maiden.
How is My Lord?
He took the medicine?
That's amazing, Holy Maiden!
Let me tell you.
All of us
tried one after another,
but none of us could get him
to drink it.
What did you do?
Never mind the method.
They're just superficial wounds.
Now that he's taken the medicine,
he'll recover soon.
But the Soul Swap...
Right.
Holy Maiden,
do you know of any way
to break the Soul Swap?
Perhaps
we should find the answer within him.
Use his childhood memories
to awaken who he is now.
Do you know
what he loved as a child?
I don't know.
Wait.
I remember now.
Once,
when I was traveling with My Lord,
he saw a mother
flying a kite with her child,
and he looked so pleased.
Right?
Yes, yes.
If he had a choice,
My Lord
would probably just want
to be a free and unbound young master.
That's easy enough.
♪The moon sinks in the west.
The cold lamp burns low♪
♪No one knocks upon
the mountain gate♪
♪Snow-white winds and moonlight
touch me first♪
So?
Do you like it?
You're the one playing, not me.
Why would I like it?
♪Gathering red beans
for half a lifetime♪
Now you're playing.
♪The Buddha speaks of countless paths♪
♪How can one glance spanning ages
save a wandering soul♪
♪Trapped within
the space between your brows♪
Hey.
I trust you.
♪The six senses cannot cleanse
the dust of the past♪
♪In dreams, it's you.
Beyond dreams, no one♪
♪Clinging to one obsession,
adrift in a sea of suffering♪
♪I can't forget
the stars in your eyes♪
♪Our fate had already taken root♪
♪In this mortal world, there is only us♪
♪Hopelessly bound by love♪
(I trust you.)
Yukui.
♪The moon sinks in the west♪
♪The cold lamp burns low♪
♪No one knocks upon
the mountain gate♪
♪Snow-white winds and moonlight
touch me first♪
♪Pear blossoms fill the courtyard♪
♪Yet love and hate entwine♪
♪Bound by precepts,
yet craving worldly desires♪
♪Gathering red beans
for half a lifetime♪
♪The Buddha speaks of countless paths♪
♪How can one glance spanning ages
save a wandering soul♪
♪Trapped within
the space between your brows♪
♪Falling deeper and deeper♪
♪The green lamp sheds no light♪
♪Upon one who entered the path♪
♪The six senses cannot cleanse
the dust of the past♪
♪In dreams, it's you♪
♪Beyond dreams, no one♪
♪Clinging to one obsession,
adrift in a sea of suffering♪
♪I can't forget the stars in your eyes♪
♪Our fate had already taken root♪
♪In this mortal world, there is only us♪
♪Hopelessly bound by love♪