=Fights Break Sphere=
=Episode 1=
Down there! It's below!
It's down below! Hurry!
My mother said fear is like the dew.
It arrives in the dark
and is bone-chilling cold everywhere in the wilderness.
In that situation, don't worry.
Just endure till dawn.
When the sun rises, everything will be gone.
The Fight God is the sun on this continent.
A millennium ago, he led five big clans
in fighting the Soul Hall
in the coldest place in the North
and sealed them in the dark underground.
That brought peace to the Fight Qi continent.
He knows that as the day and night alternate,
the light will soon dim
while the dark will soon rise.
The children of the five clans
are the ones guarding the light.
Hurry! Run!
Run! Hurry!
[Wu Tan City]
I'm Xiao Yan, son of the Xiao family in Wu Tan City.
When I was nine years old...
Announcing... The champion of the Fight Qi
Martial Arts Youth Competition is Xiao Yan!
- Good!
- Good! Xiao Yan!
I mastered the nine stages
of Fight Qi martial arts skills,
which made me the strongest
and youngest genius on the mainland.
The news of the revival of the darkness
also came from the North in the same year.
My mother joined the five big clans
and marched toward the Soul Hall.
I can't stay.
It's my duty.
Every person has their own responsibility.
Mother!
No one knows what happened on that journey
to the North back then.
My mother returned but was badly injured.
The Venerable Medicine Supreme, he...
From now on, no matter what happens,
you must properly protect this Spatial Ring.
Mother, in that case,
don't leave me again.
I won't. Not for a day, not ever.
I want to see you grow up.
I won't leave you again, not even for a day.
Where are the treasures?
Tell me. I want you to get rid of it yourself.
Since you said that
I betrayed the alliance of the five clans,
and became a slave to Hun Miesheng;
then, why would I have the treasures?
Mother! Mother! Mother!
- Xiao Yan!
- Mother!
I escaped and returned to the house of Xiao
only because I wanted to see my son.
If you want the treasures,
go and get them from Hun Miesheng.
Sect Leader Yun, Hun Miesheng asked me
to convey a message to the five clans.
"Darkness is coming."
You're afraid, too?
People from the other clans rushed here.
They said she was a traitor,
that she killed the Venerable Medicine Supreme,
and kept the treasures for herself.
They forced her to kill herself.
Mother! Mother!
Even though Madam did that,
she still can't cleanse the tainted reputation of the Xiao Clan.
Are all of you joining together to coerce me?
Making the assumption
that the treasures are definitely in my hands.
You have already dragged
the House of Xiao into hell,
and you are still going to
keep the treasures for yourself?
Then I will give all of you a statement.
Xiao Clan Leader!
Father personally destroyed
his Fight Qi martial arts skills.
The House of Xiao has been on a decline since then.
Sometimes I feel what Mother said was right.
The fear has lived inside me for seven years.
I want to work hard
to become strong and powerful.
I want to find out the truth
behind my mother's death.
But the truth seems to be that over the past seven years,
no matter how hard I try,
my Fight Qi skills have been deteriorating.
Fantastic!
Xiao Yan, come on stage!
What is he doing?
Is he able to do it?
- Why is he even here to compete?
- That's right.
I'm Xiao Yan
and I'm the last piece of trash
on this mainland.
Let's go back.
Xiao Xun'er, come on stage!
Fantastic!
Senior Brother Xiao Yan.
Am I in a position for you to still call me your senior?
Senior Brother Xiao Yan, you told me once,
"One has to be able to put something down
in order to pick it up again.
Those who can let go
are the ones who can be free."
Let's go back.
Brother Xiao Yan, have some water.
Take a look! This piece of trash
is quite hardworking.
Don't listen to them, Brother Xiao Yan.
You've been practicing very hard these days.
I believe one day you will become the top Fight Practitioner.
It's a pity that no matter how hard he tries,
he's still a piece of trash.
Hey.
I'm talking about you, a piece of trash.
Not satisfied? Are you not satisfied?
What are you doing?
I'm asking you if you are still not satisfied.
You good-for-nothing! You dare to make a move?
Your Fight Qi skills are as weak as a child's
and you still need a girl to protect you.
- Why did you hit him?
- What was the meaning of that?
What's wrong? You're fine, right?
Go after him!
- After him!
- Stop running!
- Stop right there! Stop running!
- Stop right there!
Hurry! That way!
Stop running!
Lord, 5 qians of white musk slices.
[*Each qian is 5 grams]
All right.
You fought again?
I did.
Father, teach me the Mad Lion Crazy Stars
martial arts technique. I want to defeat them.
You are not suitable for that.
I can practice day and night.
I will work harder than them.
Even if I regress, I won't be like you.
You destroyed your own Fight Qi skills
and hide in here managing ledgers!
Bring me the ruler.
Watch your mouth.
Hit yourself.
- Young Master.
- Come with me!
Let's go. Let's go.
Brother Xiao Yan.
Thank you.
Young Master.
Young Master, Master wants you to come back.
All right.
Father.
You've come.
This is the Xiao Family Medicine Shop's Mister Wan.
Father, why did you want to see me?
You don't have to practice
Fight Qi martial arts skills anymore.
Follow Mister Wan and be an apprentice
in the medicine shop.
You're to be his apprentice
and take care of the medicine shop business.
Father, I want to be a Fight Practitioner.
We are taking the exam
for getting into Jia Nan Academy soon.
If I can't get in,
I can't be a good Fight Practitioner in the future.
You don't have that kind of talent.
I do!
I-I do.
In this year's Fight Qi martial arts main competition,
how did you place?
What's your Fight Qi ranking?
Father, I will definitely succeed in learning it.
Don't make me a shop apprentice.
I-I will work harder than anyone else.
I practice fighting even in my dreams.
Mister Wan, please take a seat first.
I...
Please take a seat.
Come, please sit.
Come, come. Please take a seat.
And you come over here now.
Kneel down with a cup of tea
and pay your respects to Mister Wan.
After acknowledging him as your teacher,
learn to manage the business at the medicine shop.
Father, I don't want to be a shop apprentice.
I want to be a Fight Practitioner.
If I can't learn it today,
I will use ten years to learn it.
If I can't learn it in ten years,
I'll learn it in twenty.
If I can't make it in twenty years... Even if I need to
practice until I am dead, I still want to be a Fight Practitioner!
Father, I beg you, please don't make me a shop apprentice.
Don't make me a shop apprentice!
My child, with your talent,
you will die sooner
if you become a Fight Practitioner.
If something were to happen to you,
I won't be able to face your mother.
Just accept your destiny.
Come... Pay your respects to your teacher.
No, I will not!
Fine. You are the most precious.
Then I will do it for you.
Father!
- Clan Master, you—
- Sit down!
According to the rules, my son lacks discipline.
I apologize for letting you witness it.
Please, accept this cup of tea.
Master.
Take him back.
Forbid him from entering
the Fight Qi martial arts training place.
The back courtyard is where
we keep the medicinal herbs.
What's stored over there
are jars of herbal wine.
Remember this.
Those over there are very expensive.
Don't break them.
Let's chop these herbs first.
Don't grab so many!
Press them down before you chop them.
Cut it into smaller pieces!
I heard you've learned martial arts skills before?
I like to throw a couple of punches myself.
I learned some moves from the front
of a martial arts skills training studio
when I peeked over from the fence.
Let me show you.
You show no promise of a good future.
Coming to a medicine shop to be a nobody.
For you, it will be of no use
even if you practiced until you are eighty years old.
Slow down! If you break the chopper,
the Master will yell at us!
You will be sending those finished herbs
to the martial arts skills training studio.
- Which martial arts skills training studio?
- House of Xiao, of course!
Clan Leader has given his instructions.
He said they are taking the exam
for entry into the Jia Nan Academy soon.
Hence, they need extra supplements daily.
Who are you?
Little Scoundrel, you look just like your mother.
Who are you? Where is this place?
I'm your Grand Old Master!
Grand Old Master has been dead
for seven years already.
You are a ghost, right?
Who did you say was a ghost just a while ago?
You're not a ghost! You're not a ghost!
What am I?
Grand Old Master! Grand Old Master!
Grand Old Master.
Are you really my Grand Old Master?
But didn't you die seven years ago?
How could you show up here?
Seven years ago, I locked myself in here.
So to those on the outside,
I am indeed dead.
Outside?
Then where is this place?
The Spatial Ring on your finger.
We're inside my Spatial Ring?
Come with me.
People on the outside would never have thought
that the Star Fall Pavilion treasures
that they've all wanted for so many years
were in the palm of a young fool all along.
If I'm still not impressed by my ingenuity,
then I'd feel embarrassed by it.
Are the Star Fall Pavilion treasures in here?
Yes.
That year, your mother risked her life to save me.
I was afraid that these treasures that had been passed on
for generations would fall into the hands of bad people.
So I told your mother to move everything here
to be locked inside with me.
But all these years, my two disciples,
one seeked refuge at the Soul Hall,
one committed suicide and died.
As for me, I reside inside this ring all alone.
But it's good that I have you.
If I hadn't relied on absorbing your Fight Qi skills,
my soul might have long disintegrated and disappeared.
So, you were absorbing my Fight Qi skills?
Yes.
So, as I practice every day,
my Fight Qi skills that are deteriorating every day,
- are absorbed by you?
- Yes.
You absorbed it daily?
Did you just...?
Do you realize that over the years
because I've lost all my Fight Qi skills,
that I've suffered so much humiliation?!
And it's all because of you!
And... And my mother, in order to save you
and those so-called Star Fall Pavilion treasures,
she was forced to kill herself by those people.
Forced to kill herself!
Did you know that?!
Instead, you hid yourself in this Spatial Ring
and didn't come out!
That's because I can't get out.
And since I haven't recovered,
I wouldn't be able to win even if I went out.
You harmed me... You harmed my mother...
I'll kill you, you old man!
Scolding child, why are you being disrespectful
with your Grand Old Master, hitting and kicking me like that?
Since you're so incredible, come out with me.
Go out? Where to?
To get revenge.
Yun Shan, Yan Luotian, all those people
who hounded my mother to death.
I'm not going. I just recovered.
Grand Old Master!
Didn't you just call me an "old man" just now?
Don't kneel. I get anxious
when I see people kneel.
Why don't we do this?
There's no need for you to be anxious either.
Let me rest for a bit and regain my vital energy.
Since you've come, do your job well.
If you're unable to become a Fight Practitioner,
selling medicine is not so bad.
Even if it's not as an alchemist,
but just a...
medicine merchant or the manager of a pharmacy,
you'll also be superior to a lot of people.
A person above others.
What's wrong with being respected by others?
Do you understand my reasoning?
Think about it.
Young fellow, you really are not sensible.
You just sneaked out on your own,
causing me to get scolded.
Fine, take care of this job.
Where's the wine? Where did it go?
Who drank it? Where's the wine?
Get up!
What's going on here? Where are the wines?
Say something!
You scoundrel. You've got some guts.
Tell me! Where's the wine?
I don't know!
You're still being tough-mouthed? Hit him!
Where's the wine?
I've got nothing to say!
Let me tell you that your father wished to
entrust you to me not just once or twice.
Since you've become my disciple,
you're now a shop attendant here.
I then must discipline you.
Today, I must remove
that "young master" attitude of yours.
Hold him down well!
Lad, if you have the guts,
don't dare shout that it's painful.
I'll beat you!
Grand Old Master, your alcohol tolerance is quite good.
Grand Old Master, give me some pointers.
If your pants fall, lift them up yourself.
This matter has nothing to do with me.
That fist technique was taught by my mother.
And my mother was taught by you.
Hence, if my technique is wrong,
it's directly your fault.
And moreover, who are you?
You won't dare to drink my wine for free, right?
That fist technique of yours is not bad.
To drive away flies when you're using the latrine,
it will be very suitable. Too bad,
if the foundation of your Fight Qi skills were a bit better,
the effect of those fist attacks
would have been different.
Yes. My mother also said that
here on the Fight Qi continent,
one must control one's fist using qi.
It's just that all the Fight Qi skills
I've cultivated these past seven years
were all consumed by you.
I wasn't left with anything.
How could my foundation get better?
Moreover, you Old Man, have been recuperating for so
many years and absorbing so many of my Fight Qi skills,
yet you still are not ready.
It's all mere talk.
That, I can understand.
Look well, Little Lad.
This Long Fist technique was left
by the Fight God to be used by the five great clans.
It looks simple, but every stance
must be full of Fight Qi.
Will you be able to learn it?
I don't understand.
If you're this good, why did you die there?
If you have such strong Fight Qi skills,
why did you need my mother to save you?
Is Hun Miesheng really that strong?
Do you know what the strongest kind of fight technique is?
It's the human heart.
It's people who are close to you that scheme
for so many years to harm you.
That year, if not for your mother saving me,
I really would have died
by the hands of the person I was closest with.
The world's number one.
The world's number one needed to be protected
by a woman and a child.
It wasn't easy for me to steal some wine to drink,
but it caused you to get beaten up instead.
That is the world's number one
you're talking about?
Vengeance! Everyone wants to get revenge.
But now, even my desire to take revenge is gone.
As for you, why don't you just be an attendant
at the medicine shop? It's good that way, too.
I'm unable to just hide and be a coward.
- Who are you calling a coward?
- You tell me.
That year, just because of you, many people died.
My mother was innocently forced to commit suicide.
My Fight Qi skills were absorbed by you for seven years!
Seven years...
You want me to just be an attendant
in a medicine shop?
Let me tell you. There's no way.
It's your choice if you want to teach me or not.
Just a minute.
Star Fall Pavilion's Thirty-Six Medicine Formula.
Earning the blessings of Heaven and Earth,
the Xiao Clan were originally
the descendants of the Farm God.
Be a good alchemist, and in the Jia Ma Empire,
everyone will respect and fear you.
They won't dare to offend you.
If you cultivate following the instructions in here,
you might even have a long life.
What do you think? Not bad, right?
I will definitely learn to be an alchemist.
But... I still am going to be a Fight Practitioner, too.
This is a gold medal that the Jia Ma Empire
gives out only every three hundred years.
Take this gold medal and, in the Jia Ma Empire,
you can have the money or power that you want.
A million man army will roar for you.
Take it to womanize every day
and have a few drinks. How about it?
Dirty Old Man.
Don't talk to me that way. Don't forget.
I'm your Grand Old Master.
You're the one who forced me to call you that.
If you just leave me behind in this way,
do you think you're doing right by your mother?
Give me the Spatial Ring.
What is this?
This is my present for you.
No matter what happens in the future,
you must keep this Spatial Ring safely.
My mother instructed me before she left
that I must protect this ring well.
I will always wear it.
You can drink as much wine as you want.
Anyway, I'm good at enduring a paddling.
Just treat it as doing my filial duty toward you.
I don't owe anyone, you little brat! How dare you say
that my temper is bad?! I'll kill you with one slap!
You owe me a lot!
Father, did you call for me?
It's been years since we've seen Yanran.
Yanran's here?
The Nalan Clan are currently recruiting talents
to go to Wu Tan City
and attend the Jia Nan Academy examination.
I'll give you leave.
Buy some gifts and go visit Yanran.
Don't bother. In my current state...
The engagement was set
by your grandfather and the Nalan family.
Now that both you and Yanran are grown,
it's time for you to see each other.
This is...
the visit letter I wrote
for the Clan Chief of the Nalan Clan. Take it with you.
- Miss.
Good day, Miss.
The matter concerning the Xiao Clan
is quite hard to handle.
Xiao Zhan is a stubborn man.
I still have things to do,
so I'll take my leave now.
Grandfather.
Who made you angry?
This is a letter from your master.
He sent four disciples
on an eight hundred li journey
to bring this over quickly.
It's about your marriage.
What Sect Leader Yun Shan said is right.
One seeks his way up, just as water seeks its way down.
[T/N: One should always strive to make progress.]
Faster or we'll be late.
- Faster.
- Wait for me.
Young Master.
Let me do this kind of work instead, Young Master.
What is it? I'm delivering water
to the martial arts skills training studio.
No, you will be delivering water
for just a few more days, Young Master.
Just let me attend to you on this one more time.
- Young Master.
The tailor is here.
He's waiting for you in the hall.
What?
Before classes at Jia Nan Academy begin, Master wants
to have your marriage with Miss Nalan be done with.
He'll be choosing an auspicious day
next month for your wedding.
Let's hurry... We don't have enough time.
Five days from now,
it will be your engagement banquet.
Good. Turn around.
Let me measure it. Good.
Good.
How about this?
It'll do.
You're getting married soon.
Why aren't you happy?
There's nothing to be unhappy about.
It's just that it feels like
I'm still in a dream.
Look for someone to copy this.
Based on the prepared name list,
deliver it to our friends and relatives.
Yes, sir.
Master!
Master, the distinguished guests are here.
Cloud Mist Sect's Head Alchemy Elder Gu He,
also known as the Pellet King, asks for an audience.
Pellet King Gu He?
Pellet King Gu He is here.
It's my great fortune to have you visit us.
Xiao Clan Leader lowering yourself to welcome me
is making me feel so overwhelmed.
- Please come in.
- Thank you, Clan Leader.
Xiao Clan Leader indeed has an air of a martial arts warrior.
This study of yours is quite uniquely decorated.
Brother Gu, please tell me the purpose of your visit.
Brother Xiao, this is a small token gift.
I hope you can accept it.
That is a sixth level mythical medicine.
It can revive a dead person and can also
transform the bones of the dead into flesh again.
In the past, Xiao Clan Leader was forced
to completely destroy your Fight Qi.
Let's not talk anymore about
whether that was right or wrong.
Once you take this drug, although your Fight Qi
won't be able to return to its previous state,
I'm still confident that it can reach 60
to 70% of your previous strength.
What is the reason
that you're giving me such a precious gift?
Brother Gu, please express it clearly.
♫ If you want change, battle it out with no fear of chaos ♫
♫ The sky is dark, there’s misery on earth,
the people are living in a terrible state ♫
♫ Constant hatred and bitter attachment become evident ♫
♫ In this lifetime, you will see your feat
such as has been tempered with fire ♫
♫ Confide in me your aspiration, that constant dream
in your heart that’s difficult to fulfill ♫
♫ To fulfill my promise,
I conceal an arrow inside my gold-threaded sleeve ♫
♫ Being mesmerized for a moment
by the purgatory and the lava ♫
♫ Jumping in with a leap with
neither grace nor resentment ♫
♫ Young but bothered by undiminishing worries ♫
♫ Worries adding on to worries,
the mountain calls and the sea roars ♫
♫ Rushing headlong even if
heaven is narrow and earth is small ♫
♫ Chaos in fighting the evil and foreign forces ♫
♫ Disturbances that no one can escape from ♫
♫ Disadvantaged but don’t belittle or take advantage ♫
♫ of the young ♫
♫ Heroes never ask for names ♫
♫ or titles ♫
♫ On the board of notables ♫
♫ I’ll showcase my martial arts skills ♫
♫ It’s opportune to take advantage of youth ♫
♫ and become famous sooner ♫
♫ Proud and aloof, holding a heavy sword in one hand ♫
♫ Young but bothered by undiminishing worries ♫
♫ Worries adding on to worries, ♫
♫ the mountain calls and the sea roars ♫
♫ Rushing headlong even if
heaven is narrow and earth is small ♫
♫ Chaos in fighting the evil and foreign forces ♫
♫ Disturbances that no one can escape from ♫
♫ Disadvantaged but don’t belittle or take advantage ♫
♫ of the young ♫
♫ Heroes never ask for names ♫
♫ or titles ♫
♫ On the board of notables ♫
♫ I’ll showcase my martial arts skills ♫
♫ It’s opportune to take advantage of youth ♫
♫ and become famous sooner ♫