=Fights Break Sphere=
=Episode 5=
Medicine Elder! Medicine Elder!
Medicine Elder!
What's the matter?
There's someone outside that I can't defeat.
Do you have any other way?
Be a bit more mature, all right?
That person is one rank higher than me.
There's no way I can fight him.
Your skills are lousy.
There are many that you can't defeat.
Leave me alone. Let me sleep for a while more.
If I don't defeat him,
then I can't even get into the academy.
Can you please stop bothering me? Just because
you can't defeat him, you come inside to ask me?
If one could learn from someone instantly,
that person would be a god!
It won't do, Medicine Elder!
If we don't defeat him, we're done!
His Fight Qi is higher than yours by many ranks and stages.
Have you seen an adult beat a child?
How can you win?
You being the world's number one alchemist is
of no use either. At critical times, you are helpless, too!
No use relying on the prodding method!
I can't help you with this.
Can you please let me go?
If you don't teach me, I won't let go.
Fine. I'll teach you. That should do, right?
Use your Fight Qi to block your six channels
and cut off your three vital vessels.
When your opponent looks at you, he'll go, "Oh, no, he's dead!"
Think about it. Who can win against a dead person?
If he can't still defeat you,
you will be unrivaled in the world.
Three Thousand Thunder Movement!
Bang...! Bang...! Boom...!
Senior, I only know one move in this Fight Technique.
I still haven't learned the others.
Little rascal.
Brother Xiao Yan!
Xiao Yan!
- Brother Xiao Yan.
- Xiao Yan.
Xiao Yan!
- Brother Xiao Yan.
- Xiao Yan.
Did my martial arts energy increase again?
Xiao Yan. Xiao Yan!
Brother Xiao Yan.
Xiao Yan.
You beat Xiao Yan to death.
Just you wait! The Xiao family
and the Gu Clan will all come to find you.
If one is willing to fight, he must be able
to accept defeat. Whether he's dead or not,
you can't blame me.
Brother Xiao Yan.
Brother Xiao Yan...
Xiao Yan.
Fine. Let me take a look at him.
Move aside.
Despicable. Shameless!
You stole our stuff
and you still dare to say we are shameless.
If you have the ability, get me out.
Let's fight using real abilities!
I can't beat you with my ability now.
Why don't you just stay here for two years.
I'll come back to find you when I have mastered the skills.
You.
But if he waits two or three years,
won't he starve to death?
Then I'll never be able to win.
Why is that?
Because no matter how powerful a person is
he still can't beat a dead person.
Senior Bai Shan is legendary in the academy
for being unbeatable.
Get me out of here!
Senior Bai Shan, for your delivery
of so many energy talismans today,
we won't torment you anymore.
Once we get to the academy, we will tell
your friends to come and dig you out.
Great, since we are full now, let's get going.
We should be able to reach the academy before it gets dark.
This is wrong. What's the point of burying me here?
You all have taken away the energy talismans.
Let me out already!
Just you wait. Once we're back at the academy,
I'll kill you all!
The fire hasn't been extinguished yet!
This is the forest! Be careful of the tinder!
Before entering the academy, I thought
that I was the strongest among all the first years.
Never thought that there existed a scenario of
"In the world, everyone is better than oneself.."
How did you train? Your Fight Qi is so strong.
That's right. Quick, tell us.
My Fight Qi is increasing very slowly.
Can you teach me how to train my qi?
I know. Brother Xiao Yan's skills
are certainly products of god-given talent and hard work.
His god-given talent is that he had already attained Stage 9
Fight Qi Skills when he was just nine years old.
For hard work, he diligently trains from morning to night.
If all of you want to catch up with him,
you would have to put in a lot of hard work.
Enough, Xun'er. It's not that exaggerated.
I also have had a long period of low Fight Qi.
Fortunately, I didn't give up
and was able to get past it.
Stage 9 Fight Qi Skills at nine years old?
Then, doesn't that mean I'll never become a Fight
Practitioner in this lifetime?
How is that possible? Jia Nan Academy
has trained countless Fight Practitioners.
As long as you enter the academy,
you'll surely walk the path of a Fight Practitioner in the future.
During our Smelting Trial, we wouldn't have been
able to survive if any one of us was missing.
From now on, we can be considered as sworn brothers
who will live and die for each other.
- From now on, if you have questions on training, just ask me.
- Sure!
- I can teach you, too.
- And me.
Thank you to all of you!
You better teach us properly then.
No problem.
♫ From sprouting one leaf ♫
♫ To covering the whole blue sky ♫
After the cruel training in Black Point Region,
our group finally arrived at the Jia Nan Academy.
Thousands of years ago, the Fight God
preserved his lifetime of attainments there.
He also left behind seeds of righteous spirit
that would guide the youth of the Fight Qi Continent
to resist the darkness and triumph over evil.
We'll soon learn Fight Qi at the Jia Nan Academy,
along with alchemy
and other martial arts fight techniques.
So from now on, we bear the duty to fight the Soul Hall
and accept the mission to protect the light of life.
[Jia Nan]
How about it? What can you say about my clothes?
- Your clothes are quite nice. - Really?
- I feel that they are better than ours.
- That's right. A white robe looks better than this.
- I think that your clothes look good, too.
Old friends and new students, hello.
I'm Mi Tengshan.
Today, the Association of Elders chose me
to address the first years.
I'm not good at giving speeches at all.
Especially when I'm seeing first years
who have traveled through the Black Point Region Forest
for three days and three nights
and are very hungry and tired.
The canteen of the academy is now filled with food,
yet all you still have to stand here to hear me talk.
I really feel sorry for that.
But... I do have to talk about the important matters.
Regarding the importance and meaning of this academy,
there will be teachers who will tell you in detail.
I will only talk about
two important rules and regulations.
First:
There is only one principal at Jia Nan Academy,
and that is the Fight God.
Even though he is no longer with us now,
the academy is jointly managed by the elders.
In other words, it means that upon entering this academy,
all of you are the Fight God's students.
You then must forever be prepared to fight against
the Blood Sect, Soul Hall,
and the evil sects in the extremely cold North.
If you are against doing this,
you can now leave
so that we don't harm others or ourselves.
Second:
The academy is strictly against private fights.
Any students that participate in any private fights
will be severely punished.
Suspension. Confinement.
Even up to expulsion.
If any of you want to fight,
you can post a public announcement in the
Fight Techniques Public Arena, and compete in public.
Everyone, remember these two rules.
I'm also done with my speech.
I wish all students
improvement in your learning and a happy life.
Now, you can all enter the academy as quickly as you can.
- Let's go.
- I'm very hungry.
- Wait a while. - Wait for me.
- Hurry.
Hurry.
Are you all right? You seemed to
be distracted ever since it started.
I keep feeling that
there are a lot of malicious gazes staring at me.
Didn't you hear it earlier?
Private fights will be punished.
I don't think they have the guts to do that.
Let's go eat.
Let's go.
This is your room.
When you leave the dormitory area,
there are several good shops on its eastern side.
Buy your martial arts techniques (manuals)
and lesson books there.
Whatever you want to buy, just go there to buy it.
If you want something that's rare and strange,
go to the students' flea market during public holidays.
- Thank you, Senior.
- There's no need for formality.
No... You... Aren't you here
to look for trouble with us?
I'm not the same as that Black White Evil Duo.
Once you are their seniors next year, you will also go to
the Black Point Region to steal from the first years, too.
This is jungle education. Everyone
entering the academy must pass this stage.
Do you think I really need
your small quantity of energy talismans?
- Senior, may I ask you something?
- Ask away.
Why was there no attention paid to us
when we were on our way here a while ago?
All of you created quite a sensation when you robbed
the seniors in the Black Point Region.
First years are usually all afraid
of being avenged by the seniors.
Who would dare to get close to any of you?
So the four of us living together
is to wait for the seniors to cook us in one pot.
When will they come?
Junior, don't be so hot-headed.
This isn't the Black Point Region.
Who would dare to engage in private fights?
Just guard against the Black White Evil Duo
and you'll be just fine.
Those two are very petty.
They won't let anyone pursue the female juniors that they like.
They also won't share the energy talismans that they stole.
A lot of people don't like them.
After you defeated them,
there were a lot of people celebrating.
Let's go. I'll take you all on a tour.
Sure.
You can all go ahead first.
I'll clean the room.
Let's go.
Greetings, Sect Leader Bai.
- You are even a sect leader?
- Yes.
The academy allows students to form sects.
Everyone helps each other.
Not the type of sects for fighting though.
- Greetings, Sect Leader Bai.
My younger brother Bai Shan and I created a Bai Sect.
We mainly train in martial arts and fight techniques.
After several years, when all of you know more people,
create your own sect.
You can earn energy talismans from it.
Right?
I didn't hear wrongly, did I?
Bai Shan is your younger brother?
Indeed. We are biological brothers.
- Why? Do we not look alike? - Alike.
- His Fight Qi is higher than yours.
And he's older than you. How are you two alike?
This is called growing up before one's time.
What do you know?
I'll take you to the Fen Tian Qi Training Pagoda now.
All high ranked martial arts must be trained in there.
Under that place is a big snake that spits fire.
If your Fight Qi stage is low, stay far away from it.
Let's go. Come with me.
Greetings, Sect Leader Bai.
Sect Leader?
Sect Leader Bai, wait for me!
Every rest day per week and during holidays,
the academy will open up for a flea market.
People exchange their treasures here.
You mainly have to depend on this to earn energy talismans.
Those who come here are not poor kids.
As long as your item is interesting enough,
you will surely earn some profit.
Come and look, classmates. A low-level little beast.
This pair of Flying Dragon Wings isn't quite stable.
You need to use it for some time first
for it to gain stability.
Let me give you a special offer.
I'll maintain it for you for free every year.
- Are you all right?
- Let's take a look.
You are really too heavy.
This pair of wings is unable to carry you.
Let's go. I'll help you
look for a pair of Griffin Wings.
It's all my fault for having low Fight Qi.
My dream, when I was a child, was to be able to
create a pair of wings and fly up into the sky.
Never thought that humans could really put on wings.
Senior, how much is that pair of wings?
- Having wings like that can make things convenient, right?
- Of course.
Senior, help me find me a pair of wings
that won't need Fight Qi.
I've been a Sect Leader for two years
and still can't afford to buy a pair.
You all should stop thinking about it.
- The pair of wings that fell to the ground cost over 10 million.
- What?
In the future, you three can rent a stall, too.
Just sell whatever you can.
When you earn some money, you'll be able to improve
your equipment and rent a training place. Right?
- That's logical.
- This area is the household area.
The items in these shops are all exquisite ones. You can
go in and buy. There is a post office to the side.
If you're going to write letters to your family
or send some packages, you go there.
And there are some small restaurants.
If you're unwilling to eat the food from the canteen,
you can come here to eat.
If you go straight from here, it's the classroom area already.
Fine. Thank you, Senior.
- It's nothing.
- We'll just wander around by ourselves from here on.
- Good. I'll get going then.
- Senior, take care.
Senior, take care.
You two just stroll around first.
I'll just go check on Xun'er.
Let's go take a look over there.
Vote for who you like.
- I bet on Bai Shan! - Those betting on Bai Shan, put
your bets here. The chances of Bai Shan winning is very high.
Those betting on Gu Ka, put your bets here.
Gu Ka is a dark horse.
Student, do you want to bet?
You can cheer on the player that you like.
Those students who haven't voted yet,
quickly vote now! Vote now.
Who will win this round?
Let's all wait and see!
Begin.
Good! Good! Good!
Good! Good!
We were really lucky to be able to pass through that
Smelting Trial with this Bai Shan guarding us.
Yes, those two are not on the same level.
This won't last to the second round.
Good!
Bai Shan, you're really great! Good!
Bai Shan wins!
Brother Xiao Yan!
You're all here?
- How is it? Are you getting used to living in the dormitory?
- It's quite good.
If you need anything, just write a letter home
and let Father send it here.
I'm already attending school.
How can I still ask Father for stuff?
That's true.
How about this. If you want anything,
I'll buy it for you.
Little Sister Xun'er, just say what you want.
I'll also buy it for you.
Xun'er, in your dormitory,
did you make any female junior friends in there?
Introduce one to Hao Tian.
What a coincidence? I just made a new friend.
She's really nice and she also likes Hao Tian.
That's what I said. There are many female juniors
who have good taste.
Quick, tell us. In what way is she good?
She... is eight feet tall, waist size is eight feet, too.
She's even from a family of generals.
Before her, there are even six
Fight Grand Master older brothers.
That doesn't suit me, right?
She already said that she fell in love with you
at first sight during the opening ceremony.
She just loves people from your Department of Alchemy.
A handsome man can indeed invite trouble.
There she is now!
♫ From sprouting one leaf ♫
♫ To covering the whole blue sky ♫
♫ One region of the world is in my heart ♫
♫ Even as things change with the passage of time ♫
♫ From dreaming of growing wings ♫
♫ To flying high and having difficulty in hiding my talent ♫
Mother!
Move aside!
♫ I want, I want to experience trials and tribulations ♫
♫ I want, I want to forge ahead courageously ♫
♫ I want, I want the mountain in my sight ♫
♫ I want, I want never to have any higher plains to climb ♫
Everyone, you've all seen it.
In Fight Technique, there are "three don'ts."
And Student Hu Jia committed all of them.
The "first don't" is speed.
Throwing a punch when you haven't firmly congealed
your Fight Qi Whirl will make you float and become powerless.
This is like a drummer.
Although he is able to keep up the rhythm,
the drum beats are inconsistent.
The "second don't" is stiffness.
When it's time to fight, the other party
will surely have the ability to attack.
If you're unable to make the appropriate adjustment
during the change in attacks
and continue just like you train alone at home,
you all will surely suffer a great disadvantage
when you are outside.
Understood.
One more time.
I'm not fighting anymore.
The "third don't" of Fight Technique
is to fight timidly. You must know the power of
all kinds of Fight Techniques and the fighter's drive
are closely connected. And Student Hu Jia's Fight Qi,
compared to when we started,
has decreased to more than a half.
Hu Jia, you can go back down now.
Who's next?
You go...
Xiao Yan, come on up.
Teacher Ruo Lin,
I can only do the Five Movement Fist.
Then show me the best movement you've got.
Yes.
Eight Extreme Collapse!
Weird.
Why is it weird?
It felt like the power was hitting
but absorbed in cotton.
This Eight Extreme Collapse technique you've shown
can be considered to be passed on from an authentic source.
Every form of the Five Movement Fist reportedly
has this kind of power.
It's just that you were too ferocious, like someone
who has excessive Yang but deficient Yin.
You tend to only use ferocious force against
your opponent, so your flexibility is too weak.
I used a gentle Fight Qi to surround you.
Hence, your power could not be fully exerted.
During the next training session, you must remember
to adjust and turn to achieve a realm of perfection.
You mustn't keep attacking fiercely.
If you see someone stronger than you
and you counter force with force,
you'll then be horribly defeated.
Thank you for your guidance, Teacher.
Next!
Student Hu Jia, don't sleep during class.
Everyone, today we'll study
the Basic Techniques of Alchemy.
On your tables, there are herbs like this one.
This is the legendary Gather Spirit Herb.
This herb is very delicate.
Remember. Alchemy is refining with fire.
If you can control the fire
to any intensity you want,
then you're already halfway done
with refining your medicine.
When refining with fire,
the fire is in your heart.
The movement of the fire must
merge with your heartbeat.
At the most suitable time,
extract the essence of the medicine.
This, by the way, is the essence
of the Gather Spirit Herb.
This thing placed on your table
is called Dragon Tree Tassel.
A tree like this must be at least thirty years old
before it can be used for medicine-making.
At this time, you need to fiercely
attack it with a strong fire.
Pay attention to the fire's angle and temperature.
Bull's Eye Stone, Elderberry, and Fire Lotus Fruit.
The Gather Spirit Herb is the king.
The Dragon Tree Tassel is the subject.
The other medicines are the assistants.
The fire is the mother. The medicine is the son.
This is the medicine pellet we've produced
by refining with fire.
This is a medicine for injuries.
You can use it for both internal and external injuries.
In the future, students from the Department of Alchemy
will learn more things.
As for those from the Department of Fight Techniques,
it's enough for you to learn some medicines
to treat fighting injuries.
Next, you all try doing it by yourself.
♫ From sprouting one leaf ♫
♫ To covering the whole blue sky ♫
♫ One region of the world is in my heart ♫
♫ Even as things change with the passage of time ♫
♫ From dreaming of growing wings ♫
♫ To flying high and having difficulty
in hiding my talent ♫
♫ In the long and arduous journey, no matter what
was in my way, I resisted the winds ♫
♫ The youth I once had was not in vain ♫
During the refining, the amount
of Gather Spirit Herb Essence must be high
or else when you put in the Dragon Tree Tassel,
it will explode easily.
♫ I want, I want the mountain in my sight ♫
♫ I want, I want never to have any higher plains to climb ♫
♫ From sprouting one leaf ♫
♫ To covering the whole blue sky ♫
♫ One region of the world is in my heart ♫
♫ Even as things change with the passage of time ♫
♫ From dreaming of growing wings ♫
♫ To flying high and having difficulty
in hiding my talent ♫
♫ In the long and arduous journey, no matter what
was in my way, I resisted the winds ♫
♫ The youth I once had was not in vain ♫
Why didn't Brother Xiao Yan come to learn alchemy?
Xiao Yan found himself another teacher.
He looks down on Teacher Gu He.
You... Why didn't your face get blackened?
Your face is so dark.
♫ I want, I want never to have
any higher plains to climb ♫
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Seven!
Stop! Stop!
It's Five Movement Fist.
It's a fist method that you all have been
training in since you were little.
Why does it look like you haven't eaten?
Do you all feel that upon arriving here
at Jia Nan Academy,
you will be learning some outstanding
fight technique or martial arts?
If you all can't even master the Five Movement Fist,
what else can I teach you?
Teach you what!
Listen well! Next, Elder Han will give you a lecture.
Here, gather!
What Elder Ge said earlier is very accurate.
In your first semester here at Jia Nan Academy,
you must master the Five Movement Fist.
I know none of you want to learn this
because it's too easy.
But I need to remind you
to never forget this fist technique.
In terms of fight techniques,
all forms of any fight technique in this world
originated from this fist technique.
This was especially devised by the Fight God
to begin the training of the youths
from the Five Great Clans.
Even though there are only five punches in it,
it includes all
the essence of all the fight techniques in this world.
If you're able to do it well,
it can provide endless power.
I remember that during the recruitment in Wu Tan City,
our student Xiao Yan
used a Fight Technique created from the Collapse Fist
and fought a Cloud Mist Sect disciple
till he flew into the air.
You all probably don't believe me, right?
It's fine.
Let's call him out. We'll demonstrate it here
to show it to you all right now.
How about it?
Classmate Xiao Yan, come.
Come, everyone. Move aside...
Don't be shy. Come.
If my guess is right,
it should be...
Eight Extreme Collapse!
Are you all right, child?
Why does the Fight Technique you have learned
originate from our Star Fall Pavilion?
Where did you learn it?
I think...
we should add one more crime
of "privately passing down a Fight Technique"
to your mother's crime of treason.
This is called the crime of stealing a technique.
My mother isn't a traitor.
Your mother isn't a traitor?
Why then did she have to take her own life
for fear of persecution?
Also, if she didn't steal it,
where did you learn
this Star Fall Pavilion Fight Technique?
Nonsense!
How dare you talk to an elder like that?
My mother isn't a traitor.
She's not a thief!
I believe Brother Xiao Yan's words.
It surely wasn't like all what you said.
Enough... Let him go.
He was still a child back then.
But I... I forgot about proper decorum.
Everyone, intensify your training.
After training today, I'm punishing you
with cleaning up the whole training studio!
Let me tell you that
if you dare talk to an elder like that again,
I'll beat you to the point
that you will regret it!
What are you looking at?!
Listen to my command. Continue the training!
One!
Two!
What is this?
This is my gift to you.
Keep it with you and no matter what happens,
you must properly protect this Spatial Ring.
Mother, then don't leave me.
I won't leave you. Not even for one day.
I want to see you grow up.
Not even missing one day.
Hey!
- Hey, what are you doing?!
- Move...!
Gu Wenxin colluded with Soul Hall to kill Master.
Quickly bring her out for me!
Gu Wenxin is a monster!
She charged into our Star Fall Pavilion and
robbed us of our Fight Techniques and Martial Arts.
She took the relic of Spiritual Cauldron
from our Venerable Medicine Supreme.
Everyone, look.
This was caused by that Gu Wenxin monster.
Also, the brothers behind me,
the wounds on their bodies were caused by her!
I want to ask
who has personally seen my wife
murder Venerable Medicine Supreme?
Clan Leader Xiao, the student of Venerable Medicine Supreme
who saw with his own eyes was your wife's junior, Han Feng.
Quickly hand over Gu Wenxin.
Otherwise, you all will not see tomorrow's daylight.
What? The Xiao family also wants the treasures?
You...
Elder Nalan, Sect Leader Yun.
You all returned alive.
Why don't you tell everyone
what you saw?
You murdered the Supreme,
robbed Star Fall Pavilion,
betrayed the alliance of the five clans.
Since you say
I betrayed the alliance of the five clans,
and became a slave to Hun Miesheng,
why would I have the treasures?
Where are the treasures then?
Tell me. I want you to resolve it yourself.
- Xiao Yan.
- Mother!
I escaped and returned to the House of Xiao
only because I wanted to see my son.
If you all want the treasures,
go and get them from Hun Miesheng.
Sect Leader Yun, Hun Miesheng asked me
to convey a message to the five clans.
"Darkness is coming."
You're afraid, too?
Mother! Mother!
Xun'er, go kowtow to your aunt.
This house wine, I originally
wanted to drink it with you.
[The memorial tablet of Gu Wenxin]
I'm leaving it all for you.
I'm leaving Xun'er here.
In the future, let her surname be Xiao.
Why is that?
Leaving a member of the Gu tribe here will make it
easier for us to keep in touch in the future.
Xun'er, at Aunt's house, you must be obedient.
Father! Take me home.
I don't want to stay here, Father.
Father.
♫ The outcome is nothing more than an added bonus ♫
Xun'er, I will visit you every year.
Father! Let me go. I must find my father.
Father!
♫ Pain is perhaps a godsend for your growth ♫
♫ The dejection before the bloom is just transitory ♫
Why did you come here?
I ate a lot. I am taking a stroll to digest.
♫ I promise you that for a period of time ♫
♫ I will be next to you by your side ♫
♫ Your bold and uninhibited dance in flight ♫
A girl cannot do heavy manual labor.
♫ My rainbow phoenix sings an opera aria ♫
Then I will stay by your side.
♫ I yearn to love you wholeheartedly ♫
♫ You fight to break the night's desolation ♫
♫ I sever... ♫
♫ The moon's befuddlement ♫
♫ You know that dreams are your wings. ♫
♫ Pain is perhaps a godsend for your growth ♫
♫ The dejection before the bloom is just transitory ♫
♫ The hopelessness before the groundbreaking,
I will resist it with you ♫
♫ I promise you that for a period of time ♫
♫ I will be next to you by your side ♫
What?
I just realized today
that you are Gu Wenxin's son.
If it wasn't for your mother's betrayal that year,
how would it have been possible for my parents
to die in the Extreme North area?
How can you still have the face to live?
♫ If you want change, battle it out with no fear of chaos ♫
♫ The sky is dark, there’s misery on earth,
the people are living in a terrible state ♫
♫ Constant hatred and bitter attachment become evident ♫
♫ In this lifetime, you will see your feat
such as has been tempered with fire ♫
♫ Confide in me your aspiration, that constant dream
in your heart that’s difficult to fulfill ♫
♫ To fulfill my promise,
I conceal an arrow inside my gold-threaded sleeve ♫
♫ Being mesmerized for a moment
by the purgatory and the lava ♫
♫ Jumping in with a leap with
neither grace nor resentment ♫
♫ Young but bothered by undiminishing worries ♫
♫ Worries adding on to worries,
the mountain calls and the sea roars ♫
♫ Rushing headlong even if
heaven is narrow and earth is small ♫
♫ Chaos in fighting the evil and foreign forces ♫
♫ Disturbances that no one can escape from ♫
♫ Disadvantaged but don’t belittle or take advantage ♫
♫ of the young ♫
♫ Heroes never ask for names ♫
♫ or titles ♫
♫ On the board of notables ♫
♫ I’ll showcase my martial arts skills ♫
♫ It’s opportune to take advantage of youth ♫
♫ and become famous sooner ♫
♫ Proud and aloof, holding a heavy sword in one hand ♫
♫ Young but bothered by undiminishing worries ♫
♫ Worries adding on to worries, ♫
♫ the mountain calls and the sea roars ♫
♫ Rushing headlong even if
heaven is narrow and earth is small ♫
♫ Chaos in fighting the evil and foreign forces ♫
♫ Disturbances that no one can escape from ♫
♫ Disadvantaged but don’t belittle or take advantage ♫
♫ of the young ♫
♫ Heroes never ask for names ♫
♫ or titles ♫
♫ On the board of notables ♫
♫ I’ll showcase my martial arts skills ♫
♫ It’s opportune to take advantage of youth ♫
♫ and become famous sooner ♫