=Fights Break Sphere=
=Episode 21=
Xiao Yan! Xiao Yan!
I think we should divide and conquer.
There are only two hours available.
It won't be easy to gather all these medicinal herbs.
Right... Hao Tian is also from the Department of Alchemy.
I'll follow him. You two aren't very interested
in this. Just look around.
- Let's just meet at the starting point in two hours.
Let's go. - Goodbye.
Be careful.
Wait for me! I'll go with them, too.
There are still some over there!
Let's go there.
There are fewer people over there. Go...
All of these are mine.
Brother Xiao Yan, we're the only ones left.
There's a few over there.
Those will be yours. These will be mine.
Don't fight with me.
Come with me over there. Let's go.
What's wrong with you?
Just now, I saw Fan Ling came in here, too.
Where is he?
Let's go over there. Go.
Both of us should go find some things, too.
State Teacher, the Alchemist Guild received the decree
for a full-scale search for Elder Mi Tengshan.
This the first decree of the new emperor.
You must do it seriously.
Yes.
Return my Clear Spiritual Stone to me!
I'd already loaded it in the bag.
You all are bullying people too much!
Don't you know that here on the Fight Qi Continent,
the strongest become the most respected ones?
If you want to place blame, just blame your parents
for not teaching you any good skills.
You’re simply an intolerable bully!
Just blame this Clear Spiritual Stone
to be on my list.
Bro, go home and practice for a few more years.
Return my Clear Spiritual Stone to me!
- Come.
- Give it back to me!
- Bullying me too much! You all...!
- Give it to me!
- What?
Do you still want to fight?
With just those tricks of yours?
Don’t show yourself off.
You...
- What are you doing?
- What?
- Who asked you to bully people?
- You're taking advantage of the few.
Do you still have any dignity?
Jia Nan Academy, how is it your concern?
I just hate all you bullying people.
How’s that?!
Mind your own business!
Come up here if you have the ability
and take it from me!
What are you doing?! If you throw it again…!
What do you want to do?
I just tossed it. I'll just toss it once again.
You! If you have the guts to face me, come down here!
What are you doing?
Can you let me fight?
Fine. Fine. Don’t fight anymore.
Time is running out.
Let’s all leave together.
Just a lousy piece of rock.
I’m giving it to you as a present.
All right. See if there’s any ahead.
- That plant! That big plant!
- That one.
Let me.
Be careful.
This is good. We've harvested a lot today.
Everyone, I think we should separate at this point.
Why?
It’s a little too inconvenient.
Where is it inconvenient?
Everyone is looking for the same thing.
Just in case we find it together. Whose is it?
- What this senior said is reasonable.
- Right.
Time is urgent. Let’s separate here.
By the way, I’m Yao Jie of the Star Fall Pavilion.
After we leave here, I’ll properly thank everyone.
I'm taking my leave. I'm taking my leave.
Yao Jie, if you meet them again, come quick and find me.
All right.
Goodbye.
Showing off like you’re a hero. Let's go.
Pick the medicine!
Over there! Go...
Do you see it? That plant.
Be careful.
I have one here. You?
I have one over here, too.
That’s right. This Yellow Ground Dragon
is even more powerful than the Qi Spirit Grass.
It can make a broken limb be reborn.
It will still be a baby plant
until it's lived for 500 years.
But the plant over there has absolutely aged 500 years.
It’s already fully grown up, and it can still run.
If you agitate it, it’ll just run away.
But by all means, you must not hurt it.
If its medicine bleeds out,
its efficacy will decrease tenfold.
Gently! You need some water.
I’m your senior! Don’t I understand?
- How can it be done without water?
- Right.
How can there be no water
in the Mystical Mountain Painting?
The Mystical Mountain water comes from Heaven.
Get ready.
It’s coming out! It’s coming out!
No more water. No more water.
- What to do? What to do?
- Hurry to catch it.
Oh, all right.
Don’t go!
You...
Give it back to me!
Brother, what did you say?
It’s ours. We waited on it for a very long time.
Yours?
This is my painstaking catch from the ground.
I’m very busy. I won’t keep you company.
Hand it over!
What? Do you want to grab it?
Hel--
It's running away!
Xun'er.
Don’t run! Where is it?
It's there!
Where is it? It ran away!
Here. It ran that way.
Don’t run! Don’t go!
- What are they doing?
- Stop!
They’re chasing after the Yellow Ground Dragon.
- Yellow Ground Dragon?
- Grab it!
Let’s go take a look.
- Don’t run! Is that it?!
- No. They going toward the dark back side.
The Emperor said we can’t go there.
Then, shouldn't we call them back?
Let's go. Come on.
Yellow Ground Dragon!
Don’t go! Hurry...
Stop! Stop! Grab it!
Xun'er!
Youngsters nowadays.
Let’s see where you can run to now.
What’s all the fuss about?
Xun'er.
Qilin Blood!
Such huge Qilin Blood.
This is the first time I’ve ever seen it.
Oh heavens.
Hurry. Look! Sixth-Rank Magical Crystals.
Have you seen such a huge pellet medicine?
I'm fine with being the last one.
I have to take this back with me.
Brother Xiao Yan, we don’t want to
take the first place anyway.
Just take however many you can.
All right. But why does this place
have so many treasures?
You all, look over here!
Medicine Elder!
Medicine Elder.
These are the Magical Crystals over eighth rank.
As long as you use these,
your strength will come back as the greatest
on the Fight Qi Continent. It’s imminent.
Good. You're considerate.
You're considerate. That's rare.
That... We're like locusts tied to one rope.
In it together for better or worse.
You don’t need to exert so much effort going back
and forth. Wait until Mystical Mountain Painting closes.
Everything on that side will be yours.
All right. All right. Don’t scare me.
We'll go out in a moment.
All right.
Then, do you know the history of this mountain?
Isn’t it a place where the Fight God cultivated?
Yes. But the dark side of this mountain is a cauldron.
Now you are covered by the cauldron.
And you still have time to come flatter me?
Hurry and leave.
Go back and save your brothers.
My heavens!
Hao Tian. Hao Tian.
Han Xian.
Hu Jia.
Xun... Xun'er.
Xun'er!
Brother Xiao Yan! Hurry.
Come over here and see.
What happened?
This is bad.
Hu Jia.
Let go of me! Don’t steal from me.
Who’s stealing from you? Wake up a bit.
See what is over on that side.
Hurry. Go... Han Xian.
- Han Xian. Han Xian...
- Mine.
All these are mine.
Hao Tian, come...
- What are you doing?
- Let's go. Come...
My... My pellet medicine! My pellet medicine!
- You all, look at this.
- My pellet medici-
Wake up. We should leave.
Let's go.
Let's go. Go...
Why are we here again?
Let's go. Hurry. Let's go.
Xun'er, let's go.
This side.
Didn’t we already walk by here?
Yes. We did walk by here.
Let's go. Hurry up.
Hurry up.
Brother. Brother. How was it? How was the harvest?
What things are inside?
Let's go. Let me tell you.
How come only a few people came out?
Once entering the treasure mountain, what reason
is there for returning empty-handed?
People die because of money.
Birds die because of food.
I only hope these disciples aren’t too greedy.
That wouldn't be good.
Does State Teacher think we need to
send people to find them or not?
When an Alchemist sees good medicinal ingredients.
One is even willing to lose one’s life.
If you advise them at this moment.
Why would they be willing to listen?
Your Majesty Ye Lan, don't worry. The proverb says, "If you want
something wonderful, go to a perilous peak." There's still time.
We're trapped by ghosts.
We're definitely trapped by ghosts.
We're trapped by ghosts?
The time for going out is quickly ending.
If we’re trapped in here,
that would be a huge trouble.
An evil place. Why can’t we go out?
This place must be the mouth of a big cauldron.
If my guess isn’t wrong,
we’re currently right in the middle,
inside the cauldron.
Both Seniors, I know you must have died unjustly,
but it wasn’t us who harmed you.
Please show us your spirits
and tell us how we can get out.
I promise to burn incense every year to you.
No... I promise there will be wine and meat.
I’m still not married.
How can there be ghosts?
Wake up. Think of a way.
All right. All right.
We have to pray.
Don't care about the competition.
Return all their items back to them.
Let’s see if that will work.
Pour them out.
- Hurry. Pour them out.
- I can't give it up. I can't give it up.
Let's go.
Why are we still here again?
We probably really won't be in here
for sixty years, right?
It's all your fault for bringing us here!
What did you say? You...
What are you two arguing about?
Hao Tian, if it wasn't for you insisting on
chasing that thing, would we be here?
At that time, we also yelled for you not to come in!
You insisted on coming in here yourself.
Who are you blaming?
Brother Xiao Yan.
Do all of you remember
how many corpses there were a moment ago?
Two corpses.
Xiao-Xiao Yan, don't scare me.
There's only one corpse left now.
One less corpse.
Who are you? Why do you want to deceive people?
What must we do to leave this place?
Brother Xiao Yan, if you continue to
grab his neck like that, he'll die.
What are you laughing at?
Funny. Oh, so funny.
You guys have run around eighteen times.
I was counting.
You're the one who caused all this trouble!
Young lad, don't be so fierce.
You should be more polite toward an old man.
Stop beating around the bush.
Say it. Who are you?
I'm an alchemist.
Sixty years ago, I snuck into the Imperial Palace
and found this painting.
I then went into it.
So that's how it was.
Elder, sorry for offending you earlier.
Please tell us how to leave this place.
We'll take you out with us.
Why go out? It's so good in here.
On Fight Qi Continent,
is there any place better than here?
Those medicinal herbs, pellets, magical crystals,
you can have as many as you want.
Elder, we are still students.
We still have to go back to study.
- That's right.
- Please help us. Tell us the way out.
There is no way out.
This is the mystical mountain of the Fight God,
the dream place of so many people
on the Fight Qi Continent.
Are you all stupid?
Elder, we're begging you.
Please tell us the way out.
Elder, you like this place,
but we don't.
If you don't help us today,
even if I have to destroy this mystical mountain,
we must go out.
Essence Flame? What are you doing?
You said earlier that there was no way out.
- Then I'll blast a way out then.
- Wait!
You really don't know how to appreciate good things.
Fine. Come with me.
Hurry! There's no more time!
Hurry! You're always the fastest
when escaping for dear life.
Hurry!
This... What is happening here?
How come it's like this?
Someone is setting fire to the entrance.
You all don't move!
Step back...
If this doorway fails,
the people inside can't get out for sixty years.
If you are so confident, then enter.
The designated time will be up soon.
I won't hinder you if you want to go in.
But... no one can save you afterward.
Hurry! Hurry!
Who's out there? How do we get out? Right...
- The doorway will be closing soon. Oh, no. I don't want
to get locked in here for sixty years. - Me either...
What should we do?
- We can't get out?
- Yes.
What's going on?
Someone set up a poisonous fog.
A lot of our brothers have already fallen.
If you get poisoned again,
we don't have an antidote this time.
I have the Beast Flame and the Essence Flame.
I surely can control this poison.
Don't worry. We can't really stay on
this rotten mountain for sixty years, right?
I don't know. Hurry. Look.
- He actually went in there.
- That's right.
Is he that strong?
Brother Xiao, you still came.
You are burning up your Fight Qi.
Fine then. Let me see how long you can burn.
You joined in the Alchemist Competition
just to wait for this day, right?
You said it correctly.
This place will be sealed with the essence
of the youth from all Five Clans inside.
With just me, in exchange for so many of you,
it's well worth it.
How about it? Do you admit defeat?
- Do you want to die? Don't go in there.
- Right, don't go in there!
Oh, right. I forgot to tell you.
The poison you took in during the competition
actually can't be cured.
I used my own blood as the main ingredient.
What you don't know is, the person who takes it in
will be forever loyal and serve Soul Hall.
This is called a blood alliance.
Brother Xiao, should I turn you into
my slave or just a lackey?
But that's not enough to vent my anger.
You hurt my father.
I'm going to seek revenge for him and behead you.
Who is your father?
The person who possessed the old emperor.
We almost succeeded,
but you just had to interfere.
Now, you can't interfere anymore. Right?
Say farewell to me.
Xun'er, go!
How will they get out? What's going on?
Who is causing this trouble?
You... quickly go in!
Why are you not moving? Hurry up!
Your Majesty, please spare me.
If I go in, I won't be able to get back out.
- Stop your nonsense. Quickly go in! Go in!
- Your Majesty!
If I go in, I won't be able to get back out again.
Your Majesty, calm down...
With only him going in, it won't solve the problem.
Those students have already been trained
in their respective schools.
Each one has exceptional abilities.
They surely can turn this misfortune into a good one.
Your Majesty, calm down.
Stop making things difficult for him.
Brother Xiao Yan, do you still remember the items
given to you by those three weird merchants?
Xun'er, step back.
You're terrific, Brother Xiao.
Let me tell you all.
So what if your poison has been cured?
This doorway will be collapsing soon.
None of you can get out.
I also forgot to tell you
that during the competition,
the poison you took in, not only has the Beast Flame,
it also has the Bone Spirit Cold Flame.
I... carelessly left a seed of them inside.
Now, it's time for you to bid us farewell.
- We can go out now!
- Yes, there's now hope!
This is great!
- Brother Xiao Yan, let me help you!
- Xun'er!
Xun'er, quickly tell them to leave!
Hurry! Make them leave!
Go! Go!
Hurry!
Quickly go! Hurry! Run!
Hurry! Hurry!
Xiao Yan, let me help you!
You leave, too! Hurry!
I'm not leaving!
Hurry! Be obedient!
Once you get out, I will immediately follow.
All right?! Quickly go!
- I told you already that I'm not going!
- There's no more time!
- It's collapsing.
- Go!
Hu Jia and Hao Tian, take her away!
Let's go!
- Go!
- Xun'er!
Let's go!
- Take her away!
- Brother Xiao Yan!
Let's go!
Brother Xiao Yan!
Brother Xiao Yan is still inside!
Xun'er! Xun'er!
- It's dangerous!
- Brother Xiao Yan is still inside!
Xun'er!
- Brother Xiao Yan!
- There's no use even if you go in!
Such a good treasure just got destroyed like that.
Too bad.
- Xiao Yan is out!
- Xiao Yan!
- Brother Xiao Yan! - He's out!
- Turn him over.
- Are you all right?
- Brother Xiao Yan...
- Quickly save him.
- What to do? Medicines...
Here.
Here. Give him some water.
He just exhausted his Fight Qi.
I had him take a Qi Returning Pellet.
Now, it's all up to him.
- Xiao Yan.
- Brother Xiao Yan.
Mother!
Mother, don't go!
Mother! Where are you?
Mother!
Mother...
Mother.
Mother, how come I can't find you again?
Is it that hard to find your mother?
So noisy.
Say it. Where can I find my mother?
I can tell you, but I'm afraid that you won't dare.
What is there that I can't dare to do?
Okay then.
Use a dagger to slit your throat
or hang yourself with a rope on a house beam
and you'll see her already.
Medicine Elder,
please stop mocking me.
So what if I'm mocking you?
Let's see if you dare to be greedy again next time.
It's so easy if you want to die.
If not for my Fight Qi protecting you,
you would have died so many times.
But this time, it's a bit more troublesome.
What's wrong?
You drank the blood of a Blood Sect clan member.
Fan Ling wasn't lying to you about that blood alliance.
It indeed can't be cured.
Technically speaking,
you're already a member of Soul Hall.
It's fine. The Bone Spirit Cold Flame can suppress it.
Bone Spirit Cold Flame can indeed suppress it,
but it can't completely cure it.
Bring that Mystical Heavy Ruler of yours over here.
The Mystical Heavy Ruler is indeed a magical weapon,
but it is also an evil weapon.
On this, all the martial arts
techniques of Soul Hall are written.
You must be very careful.
What am I being cautious about?
Entering into a blood alliance is equivalent
to opening up the gates of Soul Hall.
On here are the top ranked martial arts techniques
that Soul Hall never teaches to outsiders.
If you don't have any other weapons on hand,
you can temporarily use this Mystical Heavy Ruler.
You must remember
that you're a member of the Xiao Clan.
Your mother died fighting Soul Hall.
You must not read any of
the martial arts techniques written here.
♫ If you want change, battle it out with no fear of chaos ♫
♫ The sky is dark, there’s misery on earth,
the people are living in a terrible state ♫
♫ Constant hatred and bitter attachment become evident ♫
♫ In this lifetime, you will see your feat
such as has been tempered with fire ♫
♫ Confide in me your aspiration, that constant dream
in your heart that’s difficult to fulfill ♫
♫ To fulfill my promise,
I conceal an arrow inside my gold-threaded sleeve ♫
♫ Being mesmerized for a moment
by the purgatory and the lava ♫
♫ Jumping in with a leap with
neither grace nor resentment ♫
♫ Young but bothered by undiminishing worries ♫
♫ Worries adding on to worries,
the mountain calls and the sea roars ♫
♫ Rushing headlong even if
heaven is narrow and earth is small ♫
♫ Chaos in fighting the evil and foreign forces ♫
♫ Disturbances that no one can escape from ♫
♫ Disadvantaged but don’t belittle or take advantage ♫
♫ of the young ♫
♫ Heroes never ask for names ♫
♫ or titles ♫
♫ On the board of notables ♫
♫ I’ll showcase my martial arts skills ♫
♫ It’s opportune to take advantage of youth ♫
♫ and become famous sooner ♫
♫ Proud and aloof, holding a heavy sword in one hand ♫
♫ Young but bothered by undiminishing worries ♫
♫ Worries adding on to worries, ♫
♫ the mountain calls and the sea roars ♫
♫ Rushing headlong even if
heaven is narrow and earth is small ♫
♫ Chaos in fighting the evil and foreign forces ♫
♫ Disturbances that no one can escape from ♫
♫ Disadvantaged but don’t belittle or take advantage ♫
♫ of the young ♫
♫ Heroes never ask for names ♫
♫ or titles ♫
♫ On the board of notables ♫
♫ I’ll showcase my martial arts skills ♫
♫ It’s opportune to take advantage of youth ♫
♫ and become famous sooner ♫