=Fights Break Sphere=
=Episode 22=
Xiao Yan...
- Say, can't you two move aside first? I'll
transfer some Fight Qi to him. - I will, too.
No, no... you two can't.
Your Fight Qi isn't that strong.
Say, will it be faster if we pass it
through his mouth? Like eating medicine?
His mouth?
What? How?
Using your mouth to transfer the Fight Qi to him.
Can that work?
Give it a try.
That is such an eyesore!
Aren't I doing it to save him?!
Why don't you do it then?!
Come!
You all are overthinking this.
It's me who will still do it.
I can't do it. I can't kiss him.
Your Xiao Yan is already awake.
Awake?
Brother Xiao Yan.
Xiao Yan.
- Brother Xiao Yan.
- Xiao Yan.
- Han Xian...
- He's awake!
What rotten idea was that?
You want to kiss me?
Isn't it all thanks to my rotten idea?
If not, would you wake up this fast?
- Alright already.
- This is so great.
- Did everyone safely come out?
- Come.
- Are you all right?
- Give me a hug.
Come.
Your Majesty!
Slow down!
Your Majesty.
Wasn't he still feeling well this morning?
The vitality of the Former Emperor has been exhausted.
Your Majesty... you must not.
The unhealthy atmosphere around the Former Emperor
is too grave. You must not approach him.
The Former Emperor has passed on !
Imperial Father...
What's wrong, my son?
Afraid now?
You're that jerk from Soul Hall...
you can't fool me.
I don't plan to deceive you.
From the start—
It's you...
It's you who killed my Imperial Father.
Your Imperial Father...
Mediocre and incompetent. A good empire
became half-dead in his hands.
When I entered his body,
the Chu Yun Empire started to turn around, didn't it?
Don't be nervous.
I just want to chat with you.
You want to enter my body?
That's not that easy.
My son's age is the same as yours.
Too bad, he's dead.
These next few days,
I don't want to kill anyone
and don't want to possess anyone.
Whatever you say now,
I won't believe you.
You don't know my name?
My name is Fan Lao. My son is Fan Ling.
He disappeared with the Mystical Mountain Painting.
He will never return.
You are the father of Fan Ling?
You're a slave of Soul Hall!
In my opinion, there are only two
kinds of people in this world.
Slaves and those who want to be enslaved
but are not given the chance.
What's wrong with being a slave for Soul Hall?
When a rabbit gets eaten by an eagle,
it becomes a part of the eagle.
The rabbit also becomes stronger.
Rotten reasoning.
I'll talk and you listen.
Let's see who between us is the rotten one.
The so-called Five Great Clans... the Xiao Clan
only has that friend of yours, Xiao Yan left.
If Soul Hall deals with him,
I think that it will be easier
than killing an ant. Right?
Cloud Mist Sect, Star Fall Pavilion,
they all have Soul Hall forces among them.
Gu Clan? They are far across the sea
and they have unending troubles.
They don't really want to meddle in your problems.
As for the Nalan Clan,
that little girl is not worthy
of being mentioned at all.
Think about it.
Who else can help you go up against the Soul Hall?
Is that rotten reasoning then?
Do you really want to go
against a boulder with an egg?
But if you're willing to work with us,
I can put down seeking vengeance for my son's death
and... I can give you unimaginable power.
But I'm already the Emperor.
There are still a lot of empires
on the Fight Qi Continent and a lot of citizens.
The Master of Soul Hall
has no interest in ruling over the world.
If you work for him,
he can help you become the Emperor of the World.
Your name will inspire awe throughout the world
and be remembered forever.
The younger generations will know
that you are a mighty emperor
and no one will know that the person
behind you is the Soul Hall Master.
What will I have to give in exchange?
Your heart's loyalty.
How about it?
I don't understand.
Listen to the words of the Master of Soul Hall.
Do the things he wants you to do.
Our enemy is the Five Great Clans.
After they are eliminated,
the whole world will be yours.
Go back and tell him then
that my loyalty belongs to my ancestors.
The ancestors of the Chu Yun Empire followed
the Fight God in sealing in Hun Miesheng.
If I became a slave of Soul Hall today,
I fear that I won't be able to face them in death.
You're too stubborn. If I am your Imperial Father, too,
I also urge you to accept it.
When I was little, my Imperial Father once
told me a vulgar commoner saying.
In one's life, you'd rather freely eat shit,
than eat meat in a lowly manner.
You... are not my Imperial Father.
You dare refuse me.
What's waiting for you
is an unending nightmare.
Unending...nightmare.
Unending... nightmare.
I have an idea.
Let's draw portraits of Elder Tengshan
and then paste them everywhere.
Below it, we'll write, "Anyone who sees
this person will be heavily rewarded."
- What will you use to reward them?
- Put it on our account first.
The Soul Energy requires that you draw the Fight Qi
from your four limbs and hundreds of bones into your heart.
Imagine that your root chakra is
turning into a red lotus flower.
If you have one moon above you,
the sacral chakra becomes the yellow lotus flower.
If you have two moons above you,
the heart chakra turns into a white lotus flower.
If you have one sun above you,
the throat chakra turns into a red lotus flower.
With the sun and moon rising,
your Fight Qi will shoot straight up toward the crown chakra.
In the crown comfortably sits the black supreme nothingness.
Within the nothingness are numerous stars
forming and dying in an instant. Using this Soul Energy,
you can be released from your body.
A thousand mile journey can be done in a moment.
Oceans and all the people are just in front of you.
- Without form or traces, this is the first technique.
- Jerk...
Do you know what it is you're doing?
Don't mind me!
What are you saying?
You better believe I'll kill you with one hit!
Why did you secretly remove the spatial ring?
Say it!
I'm trying to learn the martial arts techniques
written on the Mystical Heavy Ruler.
Didn't I tell you not to learn the things written
on the Mystical Heavy Ruler? Didn't I?!
Why must you learn them?!
You think I really want to?!
This is my only way. I can only do this!
I claim to be the world's number one.
Never thought that in these past years,
I've raised a child for the Soul Hall.
I wasn't raised by you!
My mother gave birth to me and my father raised me.
I know what I'm doing!
I won't kill you. Leave now.
I disappointed your mother's hopes for you.
When everything is doomed,
don't blame me for not warning you.
I knew you wouldn't like it,
that's why I removed the spatial ring.
Medicine Elder, I won't become a lackey of Soul Hall.
Elder Tengshan has been so kind to me.
If I learn only this one technique,
there will be a chance for me to save him.
It was written on the Mystical Heavy Ruler
that this technique can make you invisible.
In looking for a person or an item,
despite how far the distance,
as long as you imagine it, you can appear there.
I am also out of any other ideas.
I really was left with no other choice,
that's why I'm learning this technique.
Soul Energy...
Is there a problem with this technique?
Or did I learn it wrong?
So what if you correctly learn it?
Training in this technique from Soul Hall indeed
can help you immediately find Mi Tengshan.
From now on, you don't need to find people
by searching from place to place.
Even if he is thousands of miles from here,
as long as you desire it,
you can casually kill people.
I won't.
Have you ever thought how those people
started to follow the Soul Hall?
You couldn't even control one little temptation
and you're falling deeper and deeper.
I thought that with you being from the Xiao Clan,
you could resist these temptations.
I was wrong.
I only want to find Elder Mi Tengshan.
Why must you assume that I will surely become evil?
Since time immemorial, a blade killing people
is never the blade's fault,
but the fault of the person wielding it.
Because there is no good or evil
with martial arts techniques,
the ones determining if they're used
for good or bad are the people.
Are you the only person who has ever figured that out?!
There are so many great fighters on our Fight Qi Continent,
but how come they don't train in the Soul Hall techniques?
Is it because they are inferior to you?
The frightening thing about the Soul Hall
is not that they'll destroy you,
but that they slowly lure you into becoming another person.
Once your desire begins to blossom,
you will want to train in higher ranking martial arts techniques,
achieve more outstanding feats, or have even greater power.
By then, Soul Hall will readily offer you a contract
and what will you do?
I will never become like that.
I surely can control myself.
I've heard so many people say those words.
Just do as you want.
If you have time, think about my words,
that is if you're still alive.
Medicine Elder! Medicine Elder!
Throw away the spatial ring.
Don't come here again.
Medicine Elder! Medicine Elder!
Medicine Elder!
Why are you here?
Do you know how long you fainted?
I'm fine.
I was just too tired.
Liar! I heard you arguing with someone.
Who is it?
I want to learn a martial arts technique of the Soul Hall.
Then I want to find Elder Tengshan and save him.
A martial arts technique of the Soul Hall?
We don't know if Elder Tengshan is still alive or not.
This is the only way.
- Then... You still can't—
- Do you trust me?
I do.
That's good.
I never lie to you.
I don't believe that a person will become evil
just because he learned some Fight Qi Technique.
It is not like that.
A man should do what he can do.
If you have a way but you don't do it,
that is being irresponsible.
Elder Tengshan must have been taken by someone.
One day more in the hands of the bad people
is one day more of danger.
I can find him.
Elder Tengshan!
Elder Tengshan...
Elder Mi, have you been well?
I'm well and not well.
Really?
After staying here for some days,
my stomach has become smaller from the hunger.
If you lock me up for a few more days,
no one will be able to recognize me anymore.
Would you like to go out?
Sure you would.
I can let you out now,
but it will be a bit hard to explain
where you've been these past few days.
Tell them that I got lost.
This reason is not that great.
I'm already this old,
so how could I still get lost?
Or... you went to visit a friend,
had drinks every day and forgot about it.
That's impossible.
Students are my life.
How could I forget about them?
I'll say that I got captured by bad people
and then I escaped.
Which bad people?
State Teacher Fa Ma.
We were chatting quite well,
so why are you suddenly hitting me?
You are still being tough-mouthed, even now.
Tomorrow, the envoys of Soul Hall will be arriving.
I'll hand you over to them.
I'll let you experience how it is
to get imprisoned in Soul Hall.
A place in the Extreme North.
Dark and bitterly cold.
I hope that your body will be
tough enough to endure it.
Sure, all right.
I have never been to Soul Hall.
I'll wait for your answer tomorrow morning.
This is your last chance.
In dealing with Fa Ma, we should use speed.
If we alarm him,
that's equivalent to having no chance of succeeding.
Do you still have the heartbreaking herbs from last time?
I do.
We'll go look for State Teacher.
We'll say that we found
a small multicolored snake for him to see.
When I open the lid,
immediately throw the heartbreaking herb
toward his neck. When Queen pounces on him,
I'll make my three kinds of flames appear and burn him.
I got this from the market.
When Fa Ma stands up,
I'll stab his foot with this
and let him get beaten by you.
Correct. I'll then stuff his mouth,
so that he can't shout even if he's getting battered.
Xun'er, you and Hu Jia will guard the door
and kill anyone who comes.
All right.
That is the State Teacher.
What if we're unable to suppress him?
We still have to make him half-dead.
And then? Let's not talk about
being able to escape or not first.
The person we are dealing against is the State Teacher.
What if he dies?
What if he doesn't die?
Xun'er, if you're afraid—
What are you saying?
All right, all right already.
So what if he's the State Teacher?
It's as if we didn't fight with an emperor before.
If we don't act now,
Elder Tengshan will get imprisoned
by the Soul Hall forever.
Why then are we still learning Fight Qi?
Xiao Yan, are you sure that
Elder Tengshan is with the State Teacher?
That matter,
I've already explained it the whole morning.
Are you all in or not?
Let's do it!
State Teacher, this is their visitation letter.
Why did these kids come here?
Not only are they here,
I'm even unable to refuse them
after these words of theirs.
"I, Xiao Yan, with Xiao Xun'er,
Han Xian, Hao Tian, and Hu Jia, we five people
were decreed by His Majesty
to thank the State Teacher for your guidance during
the Alchemist Competition.
We have also prepared a gift.
Bowing to you..."
In just a few moments,
the envoy from Soul Hall will be coming.
You have no time to talk with them.
Just let them go back.
Xiao Yan is currently a favorite of the Emperor.
He even used the name of the Emperor to come here.
It's not proper to drive him away.
It will cause us trouble.
Could it be...
they have smelled something fishy?
Impossible.
No one can easily come in and out of my place.
Show them in.
Yes.
Hide for a while first.
State Teacher, the guests are here.
- Leave now.
- Yes.
Seeing people from the younger generation,
I am really happy.
Greetings, State Teacher!
Forego with the formalities.
I've seen your heroic might during the competition.
I feel that the Alchemist Guild has promising future members.
The guild has decided
that all those who passed the first round of competition
will be given a First-Grade Alchemist Badge.
As for Xiao Yan, he's a young outstanding talent.
Not only are his alchemy skills good,
he even saved so many people
in the Mystical Mountain Painting.
The guild has decided to make an exception
and grant you a Third-Grade Alchemist Badge.
Thank you, State Teacher, for the promotion.
I will never forget this.
Why did you all come here?
We have a treasure that we want to show you.
Really?
At the Magical Beast Mountain Range before,
we were able to find a very small
Multicolored Ingesting Heavenly Python.
Really? Ancient legends say
this kind of magical beast has become extinct.
That's right. The treasures in this world
are usually controlled by a virtuous one.
Kids like us can't possibly control
this kind of magical beast.
Hence, we especially brought it for you to see.
State Teacher!
- You have a guest.
- Who?
It's the special guest that you've been waiting for today.
May Lord go greet him.
Really so sorry. I'll be back right away.
Is it very hot here?
Not hot.
You all are perspiring a lot.
Drink more tea to cool your internal heat.
I was so scared.
My heart... was about to jump out of my mouth.
Don't be nervous. Once he comes back,
we'll do as we originally planned.
I'm so nervous. This is such a torment.
State Teacher, Lord Fan is here.
Greetings, Lord Fan.
State Teacher, you have worked hard.
I dare not say that.
Lord, Mi Tengshan is here.
You can take him away at anytime.
One more thing.
When you hear this, you surely will be happy.
- The person who killed your son just came.
He's in the study. -Really?
Xiao Yan and his four accomplices.
I know my Lord hates them a lot.
Why don't you kill them too today?
Let Mi Tengshan go!
Let him go?
Mi Tengshan was just our springboard
to control the Jia Nan Academy.
If he won't listen, just change to another one.
Making such a grand move
is going to make people suspicious.
Yes. Lord has thought about this thoroughly.
As for Xiao Yan, my son didn't die in vain.
When I arrived here, I already sensed Xiao Yan.
Within him is the scent of Soul Hall.
He is already half a Soul Hall disciple.
In the future, he will surely provide us good assistance.
Lord, you're saying
that he's also a member of Soul Hall now?
Not now, but soon.
The Lord Hun Miesheng is very interested in him.
Yes...
I initially wanted to deal with your enemy
and bring his head to you. That was close.
The Lord Hun Miesheng asked me to send you a message...
Let me tell you some good news.
Your teacher, Mi Tengshan, has been found.
Take Elder Tengshan back to the inn first.
If there are any mishaps, you can find me anytime.
I'll go to the palace now to see His Majesty.
I have finally fulfilled
the task given to me by His Majesty.
State Teacher, where was Elder Tengshan found?
What happened to him? Why is he unconscious?
Look at his chest.
The Blood Sect.
At the time, there were a lot of Blood Sect disciples
that came and caused trouble.
My men kept following them.
Finally, in a cave where they were hiding,
my men also found Mi Tengshan.
This foiled their evil scheme
and Elder Tengshan was rescued.
It was really fortunate.
Was he not harmed further?
I already had him take a life-saving pellet.
He will wake up later.
Whatever really happened,
you can ask him yourself.
Elder Tengshan, how are you?
In these past days, how did you survive it?
Elder Tengshan...
I don't remember anymore.
I'm sleepy.
I want to sleep.
Elder Tengshan...
Brother Xiao Yan, just let Elder Tengshan
recover a little before asking.
Go make preparations.
We'll immediately escort Elder Tengshan
back to the academy.
Let's go out.
Medicine Elder!
♫ If you want change, battle it out with no fear of chaos ♫
♫ The sky is dark, there’s misery on earth,
the people are living in a terrible state ♫
♫ Constant hatred and bitter attachment become evident ♫
♫ In this lifetime, you will see your feat
such as has been tempered with fire ♫
♫ Confide in me your aspiration, that constant dream
in your heart that’s difficult to fulfill ♫
♫ To fulfill my promise,
I conceal an arrow inside my gold-threaded sleeve ♫
♫ Being mesmerized for a moment
by the purgatory and the lava ♫
♫ Jumping in with a leap with
neither grace nor resentment ♫
♫ Young but bothered by undiminishing worries ♫
♫ Worries adding on to worries,
the mountain calls and the sea roars ♫
♫ Rushing headlong even if
heaven is narrow and earth is small ♫
♫ Chaos in fighting the evil and foreign forces ♫
♫ Disturbances that no one can escape from ♫
♫ Disadvantaged but don’t belittle or take advantage ♫
♫ of the young ♫
♫ Heroes never ask for names ♫
♫ or titles ♫
♫ On the board of notables ♫
♫ I’ll showcase my martial arts skills ♫
♫ It’s opportune to take advantage of youth ♫
♫ and become famous sooner ♫
♫ Proud and aloof, holding a heavy sword in one hand ♫
♫ Young but bothered by undiminishing worries ♫
♫ Worries adding on to worries, ♫
♫ the mountain calls and the sea roars ♫
♫ Rushing headlong even if
heaven is narrow and earth is small ♫
♫ Chaos in fighting the evil and foreign forces ♫
♫ Disturbances that no one can escape from ♫
♫ Disadvantaged but don’t belittle or take advantage ♫
♫ of the young ♫
♫ Heroes never ask for names ♫
♫ or titles ♫
♫ On the board of notables ♫
♫ I’ll showcase my martial arts skills ♫
♫ It’s opportune to take advantage of youth ♫
♫ and become famous sooner ♫