=Fights Break Sphere=
=Episode 43=
Medicine Elder,
that is not a prophecy.
- That is...
- What is it?
It was my memory.
It was my memory from growing up.
It was everything
that happened to me all these years.
It didn't mention any savior.
Isn't that you?
Medicine Elder,
I have confidence in myself.
I will become the strongest in this land.
But could it really be me...
who will save the people on this land?
Nobody was born a hero.
People write their own history.
God doesn't write it.
To be or not to be,
it's only a matter of choice.
I have been thinking all night
but still can't figure it out.
Is that so?
If what that roll said was true,
the prophecy is...
I will lead everyone in this land...
and seal Hun Miesheng.
Get rid of the darkness once and for all.
But how is that possible?
How could I lead everyone in this land?
How could I defeat Hun Miesheng?
If this prophecy isn't true,
how could my memory exist in that roll?
Do you think you're not capable enough
or are you not responsible enough?
It's simple if you think
you don't have enough skills.
You can train properly to improve
your Qi and skills in a short time.
That would be easy to do.
But, that doesn't mean...
you're the hero in the prophecy.
The Fight God was so strong.
He is no longer around.
What makes people miss him so much...
is not only the fact that he beat Hun Miesheng.
It's his mercy and kindness.
He sealed the darkness and divided the land.
He founded Jia Nan Academy
and left us so much heritage.
His kindness is still being spread
around in this world.
So,
what's strong doesn't necessary last long.
What's soft... will last forever.
What the hero cares about...
shouldn't be his own death or loss.
He should accept the fate that he will sacrifice...
himself for others anytime.
Ask yourself, are you ready?
But in this prophecy...
There's no prophecy.
No prophecy?
The darkness has come. Anything can happen.
Even though you are the hero in the prophecy,
you could become a traitor.
You could die young.
But as long as this prophecy doesn't come true,
it will be passed along in this world.
It's just there will be a different person.
One after another, generation after generation.
Until this prophecy comes true.
You mean...
this prophecy means it could be anyone?
So called prophecy...it just gives us faith.
The darkness will be gone
and a hero will come along eventually.
It gives us hope to live and keep fighting.
Who I am now...
is not ready.
Of course not.
To become that person in the prophecy,
you need to go through a lot of tests.
You can choose to not accept it
and no one will blame you.
Thank you for clearing my doubt.
If that day really comes,
I will be ready.
Oh right,
this is the Three Changes of Heavenly Fire.
The earth core python said Fight God used
these 3 attackes to defeat Hun Miesheng.
I left the pagoda so abruptly.
So I only learned very little.
The heritage from Fight God isn't that easy to learn.
You're about to go to the three year pact.
I hope you are fully ready.
We will face many enemies.
Yes.
Nalan family, Cloud Mist Sect,
and Star Fall Pavillion.
There are much more traitors than we imagined.
Three Changes of Heavenly Fire!
The secret of heaven and earth...
is to keep generating prosperity.
This first change...
is to live with fire and keep on.
The change of heaven and earth!
When the universe started, there was nothing.
Fire came from the sky and dominated the nature.
I will go with you.
The 3 year pact is my own thing.
You can't help me.
What if you lose?
I heard she got the skills passed along
from Nalan family and Cloud Mist Sect.
Brother Xiao Yan, I know...
you value this 3 year pact greatly.
I will not stop you from training.
But I'm scared.
I'm scared too.
As the day comes closer,
I get more scared.
This time I go to Cloud Mist Sect,
nobody knows what will happen.
Xun'er. Do you know?
Dad kicked me out of the family back then...
He was doing it to protect me.
He hoped that I could receive
Xiao family's heritage in safety.
Elder Tengshan wished I could stay in school,
focus on training and become the hero in this prophecy.
My friends including Lin Xiuya
hope I can bring them...
and fight the Soul Hall head-on.
Everyone was expecting something from me.
Everyone has things they want me to do.
Only this three year pact.
I want to do it out of my own will.
I want to do it for Xiao family and myself.
If this was a few years ago,
I would drill so many holes on her.
But since I became the Dragon Mother,
Brother Xiao Yan, when she did those things,
she was just a kid.
Since you two couldn't be together anyway,
why not just let go?
I can let go some people.
But some things... I can't forget.
This is the other scroll of the Three Thousand
Thunder Movement that Dragon Mother gave me.
Brother Xiao Yan,
I can't help you in any other way.
I just hope you would be safe
this time you go to Cloud Mist Sect.
Before I leave, let's take a trip home first.
Ok.
Let's go back together.
What's wrong, Senior?
You, you...
What's going on with you?
You have made it!
Go!
My skills are not enough.
This Black Dragon Blade...
should be controlled by mind.
It can kill a person from thousands of miles away.
Such a treasure.
No wonder they are all after it.
That makes sense.
What makes sense?
The Sect Leader suspected I stole the blade.
I explained myself for a long time.
When I left,
I saw he left the roll on the floor.
He knows whoever stole the blade...
will try everything to get that roll.
Tell me, what is he trying to do?
What does that mean?
This Black Dragon Blade needs to be nurtured with blood.
Once it's nurtured enough it will go on forever.
It will become greedy to the master's blood.
Once blood sucking stops, it will bite back.
Why didn't you tell me this earlier?
I already told you. You wouldn't listen to me.
You...You have become half human half ghost.
Since I became the leader of the Nalan family,
I have become half human half ghost.
Grandpa said, if thousands of
coffins come out of the door,
then the family will be prosper.
Before he died, he asked me to swear...
not to let Nalan family die.
Even if that means I have to die.
All of my emotions...
But he died.
Thousands of people in Nalan family are still alive.
They stand on my shoulder day and night, judging me.
If Nalan family really dies in my hands,
I can't even imagine.
Senior, you need to help me!
You have trained such evil skills.
You're no weaker than the Sect Leader.
I can't help you.
When I become the Sect Leader,
Nalan family will devour Cloud Mist Sect.
And Xiao Yan. I will not let him win.
Brother Xiao Yan.
Blood?
This was cut open by sword.
There's no one good at swords in Xiao family.
Anyone here?
Anyone?
No one is here. Father is not here either.
This wine is made by father. When it happened,
he hadn't finished his wine.
Xiao family is one of the 5 big families.
It's got hundreds of people and many Fight Spirits.
Soul Hall can't take them all and kill them.
It's not Soul Hall.
This is not their style.
Who is it then?
No one is there.
Young Master Xiao, you're back.
Tell me,
what happened to Xiao family?
Who did this?
We went far away and came back to this.
No one is here. What's going on?
Two months ago, a group of people came.
They warned people on the streets not to go outside.
They look so evil.
We were scared so we closed our doors.
After a few days when we stepped out again,
Xiao family was gone.
What do they look like?
They were all dressed in white.
One of them is called Cloud Covering Hand.
It was said they killed Xiao family
and took away the Clan Leader Xiao.
Cloud Covering Hand is one of
the 13 masters in Cloud Mist Sect.
These 13 masters are independent.
They never take orders from each other.
Now they're interfering with Xiao family's affairs.
Looks like they have been infuriated by Soul Hall.
Cloud Mist Sect.
I will kill all of you.
Soul Hall has been more and more active.
Now they're showing their dominance with Xiao family.
Anyone who doesn't obey will end up like Xiao family.
It's not only showing dominance.
So many people died in the internal dispute in Gu clan.
They were only after that piece of ancient jade.
Now they killed everyone in my family...
for the same purpose, I suppose.
That's right.
So now the most urgent thing is not revenge.
You need to find your father
and ask him where the jade is.
What is that jade anyway?
Back then the Fight God led the 5 families
and defeated the Soul Hall.
After that, Fight God was dead.
5 families buried their skills,
and their treasures with Fight God.
The jade is the key
that opens the Fight God's grave.
Fight God asked to divide the jade into 5 pieces.
The leaders of 5 families had one each.
Why?
Because Fight God had mercy.
When he defeated the Hun Miesheng, he didn't kill him.
Just sealed him.
He was worried that one day
Hun Miesheng will break loose.
So he created a curse.
If 5 families can't resist,
they can reunite the 5 pieces of jade,
and therefore open the grave of the Fight God.
So that the most talented person can train inside of it,
and become the new leader.
It's been a thousand years again.
The 5 families never stopped fighting.
To be honest,
they still want to have the 5 pieces of jade
and become the supreme leader of the world.
The supreme leader.
Does it worth so many deaths?
Why didn't my father tell me that earlier?
Maybe one day you really become the leader,
he will tell you all the secrets then.
Don't you worry though.
The Soul Hall won't do anything to your father yet.
What does that mean?
Your father was so cautious.
He didn't even tell you.
Of course he won't let Hun Miesheng have
any clues of the whereabouts of the jade.
So, he will only be imprisoned for a long time.
Soul Hall will look forward to the day he gives up.
Imprisonment?
Would that be the altar?
I will only use this once.
I don't care how many times you use it.
I was worried...
once you go in, you won't be able to get out.
Your Fight Qi has improved a lot.
But it's not good enough to challenge him.
Medicine Elder,
I will give the ring to Xun'er.
Silly boy, are you getting bold?
You want to leave me behind on your adventure?
I'll go with you.
Brother Xiao Yan. Eat some more.
I will go find father.
What? Where would you go?
I will go find out now. Protect me.
You...
Xun'er. No matter what happens later,
leave me alone.
If anything happens...
What's going to happen?
I am coming with you.
You can't go.
If my face changes color,
or if I don't come back in two hours,
kill me.
Why?
Promise me. Do it.
Father!
[Xiao Zhan]
We can't go on like this.
Their organs have been blocked by evil tricks.
I will awaken them with Fight Qi.
Father!
Father, wake up! Father!
Go back!
Ta Ge'er!
Father!
Go back!
Xiao Yan, let's go!
I can't go.
Little guy, we meet again.
You locked so many heroes here...
for what?
These metal chains are my bones.
They have been sealed
by the Fight God for thousands of years.
I will use these people's rage, fear and hatred...
to melt the ice.
Fight God is dead.
What else do you want?
There's something that belongs to me in his grave.
I have to get it back.
Leave your family's jade.
The jade is the mascot to guard the Fight God.
I will die before I give it to you!
The 5 families are like ants to me.
You're different.
I once chose you and gave you my weapon.
I taught you my skills.
Even though it's the entire continent,
I can let you run it if you like.
But what did you do?
Maybe I should consider someone else.
Go deeper into the ship.
Don't get caught by the red fog.
Fan Lao!
You... your Fight Qi.
Don't forget...
this is our Soul Hall's altar.
Boy, I will show you what it's like
to have buring sword in your body!
What, you were defeated just like that?
Angry Buddha and Firey Lotus.
You're getting it.
Medicine Elder.
I don't have more skills.
I can only go this far.
Once I throw out this lotus,
what will happen to us?
You will lose your body and soul and become ashes.
Do you regret it?
Regret?
I just have some regrets.
I'm afraid I can't make it to
the three year pact after all.
The person in that prophecy
doesn't seem to be me either.
It's good to be flying dust.
Medicine Elder, I owe you a title.
Even though you never called me teacher,
Xiao Yan, you are the best student I've ever had.
Teacher, thank you
for supporting me for so long.
This boy is so stubborn!
♫ If you want change, battle it out with no fear of chaos ♫
♫ The sky is dark, there’s misery on earth,
the people are living in a terrible state ♫
♫ Constant hatred and bitter attachment become evident ♫
♫ In this lifetime, you will see your feat
such as has been tempered with fire ♫
♫ Confide in me your aspiration, that constant dream
in your heart that’s difficult to fulfill ♫
♫ To fulfill my promise,
I conceal an arrow inside my gold-threaded sleeve ♫
♫ Being mesmerized for a moment
by the purgatory and the lava ♫
♫ Jumping in with a leap with
neither grace nor resentment ♫
♫ Young but bothered by undiminishing worries ♫
♫ Worries adding on to worries,
the mountain calls and the sea roars ♫
♫ Rushing headlong even if
heaven is narrow and earth is small ♫
♫ Chaos in fighting the evil and foreign forces ♫
♫ Disturbances that no one can escape from ♫
♫ Disadvantaged but don’t belittle or take advantage ♫
♫ of the young ♫
♫ Heroes never ask for names ♫
♫ or titles ♫
♫ On the board of notables ♫
♫ I’ll showcase my martial arts skills ♫
♫ It’s opportune to take advantage of youth ♫
♫ and become famous sooner ♫
♫ Proud and aloof, holding a heavy sword in one hand ♫
♫ Young but bothered by undiminishing worries ♫
♫ Worries adding on to worries, ♫
♫ the mountain calls and the sea roars ♫
♫ Rushing headlong even if
heaven is narrow and earth is small ♫
♫ Chaos in fighting the evil and foreign forces ♫
♫ Disturbances that no one can escape from ♫
♫ Disadvantaged but don’t belittle or take advantage ♫
♫ of the young ♫
♫ Heroes never ask for names ♫
♫ or titles ♫
♫ On the board of notables ♫
♫ I’ll showcase my martial arts skills ♫
♫ It’s opportune to take advantage of youth ♫
♫ and become famous sooner ♫