=Fights Break Sphere=
=Episode 8=
We don't want to rent it. Not renting it anymore!
Although your shop is big,
the location isn't good.
It's also too expensive.
- We don't want to rent it. Not renting it anymore. Let's go...
- Indeed so...
Yeah, I know someone at the Department of Alchemy
who can rent us a shop front
at a much cheaper rate.
Why didn't you say it earlier?
How much is it?
It's only several hundred energy talismans per day.
Let's go...
Let's go. That's much cheaper.
Let's go. We're not renting.
Not renting anymore.
Senior,
whether we'll rent or not, we'll figure it out. But even if
we can't make a deal, we should maintain friendly relations.
This is the High Level Gather Qi Powder medicine
that was refined by my Brother Xiao Yan.
Eat it and you will elevate your Fight Qi
to another stage right away.
It can also last for two hours.
Why didn't you bring out such a good item earlier?
Elevate to another stage of Fight Qi?
This can't be real, right?
Originally, I didn't want to waste even one pill.
Brother Xiao Yan worked very hard to refine these.
I was planning on selling all of them.
Are you saying it's a waste for me to eat it?
No. Senior, just try it.
It works great.
It's not going to kill anyone, right?
Shouldn't be too dangerous, I think.
Two-Star Fight Master. Impressive.
It's quite interesting.
Previously, I'd bought some from the Medicine Sect.
They also told me it could elevate
my Fight Qi to the next stage.
But it was not factually true.
Yours here is authentic and the price is fair.
How much does one cost?
Three hundred! We are planning on
selling one pellet for 300 energy talismans.
It's cheaper by half the price
than the Medicine Sect.
Let's do this.
Give me twenty pellets of medicine each time
and I won't collect any rent.
As for the shop front,
all of you can occupy half of it.
- That's great...
- Thank you, Senior. Thank you...
That's great.
Hao Tian, go back and help Brother Xiao Yan
to refine the medicine.
Hu Jia and Lin Xiuya, stay here and tidy up the store.
Sell the medicine first.
Next, we can rotate our work shifts in the afternoon.
- Agreed.
- Leave this to me.
After learning alchemy for so many years,
I would be better off learning Fight Qi instead.
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
Come... Be careful.
Today, I'm too tired. Let's stop here.
Thank you for the hard work.
You are back.
Already refined so much medicine?
Don't you want to live?
Why do you look like a corpse?
Have a pill.
I won't eat it.
I will just meditate later and I'll be fine.
How is it today? Made much money?
We made more than ninety thousand!
We can use the money to change
the floor and the wood on the wall!
Right, and the winding hallway that Xun'er wanted.
If it's not enough, we can sell these.
And if it's still not enough,
I will refine some more.
I... I don't want the winding hallway.
You will die if you work like this.
He uses his Fight Qi to light the fire.
Who could endure that kind of firing?
Xiao Yan, you didn't go to the market today.
There's a huge crowd of seniors
who jostle each other to buy our medicine.
Across from us, there's the Medicine Sect's medicine store.
Guess how they did?
They couldn't even sell any of their medicine.
Sect Leader, we have a guest.
Guest?
Good morning, juniors.
I am Han Xian from the Medicine Sect.
I'm here to meet and pay my respect officially.
Who is Sect Leader Xiao?
I am.
About this matter, I'm the one at fault.
I didn't know you were also
in the business of selling pellet medicine.
If I had known about the medicinal ingredients
and the need for a shop front earlier,
I would have taken care of those matters for you.
There's no need for you all
to go through so much trouble.
Now that we have acquainted ourselves,
we will be a family from now on.
If you encounter any difficulty,
come and look for the Medicine Sect.
In that case, many thanks to Sect Leader Han.
I have a few words
that are unpleasant to listen to,
that I'd like to discuss with you.
Please go ahead.
The Medicine Sect had over eighty leaders before me.
We have been providing all kinds of pellet medicines
for the students of Jia Nan Academy.
Our Medicine Sect disciples are all directly
taught by the Pellet King, Elder Gu He.
So, everyone trusts and accepts us.
But I realized only today
that there are some juniors here
who are also working on the same product.
The price is surprisingly cheaper than mine by half.
Are you all here trying to purposely
trample all over our Medicine Sect's store?
Or that you have a criticism of our Medicine Sect?
This is our fault. We just started to sell medicine.
We still don't have enough confidence
in the medicines we refine.
That's why we're selling it at such a low price.
We won't do that in the future.
Please forgive us, Sect Leader Han.
Also, where did you get your medicines?
Did you refine them yourself?
Are you a student from the Department of Alchemy?
Is your name on Elder Gu He's list of direct disciples?
A bunch of newly enrolled students
out here selling medicine?
And you are also not from the Medicine Sect.
If anyone really ends up being sick or suffers
any side effects due to their consumption of your medicine,
is the fault on you
or on me?
Of course, the fault is on me.
If anyone has any problems
after taking Yan Sect's medicine,
it will all be my personal responsibility.
Yan Sect? It's just a name.
Why not have the Yan Sect just directly
become part of our Medicine Sect?
Just hang our Medicine Sect's banner in your store
and that will take care of the problem.
From then on, 40% of your profits
from the sale of your medicine will be mine.
That way, everyone will be in solidarity
and we can all get rich together.
40% share for you? Are you trying to rob us?
Is a banner from the Medicine Sect
worth that much?
Although our Yan Sect is small,
we have never thought of merging with any other sect.
You can walk on the paths of the world and so can I.
Sect Leader Han, thanks again for your good intentions.
If you merge with us,
I will let you
be the Second Leader of the Medicine Sect.
That should be fine, right?
Why don't you come over to us instead?
Come and be Yan Sect's Second Leader.
Right. Yes.
Xiao Yan! Don't be disrespectful
when respect is given!
You just got into the academy and you want to
trample all over our Medicine Sect's store?
Let me tell you, you are too young!
Don't think that a few of you, first years,
can gain any result from it.
It's no big deal to have fought in the water room.
Those were just worthless seniors.
What the real side of Jia Nan academy looks like,
you haven't seen it yet.
This is the Medicine Sect's "fight challenge" letter.
To defend the reputation of the Medicine Sect,
I will see you in the ring.
If you don't dare to take up the challenge,
don't ever step foot in the marketplace again.
Let's go.
What is Han Xian's rank?
He is just a Three-Star Fight Master.
Th-Three-Star Fight Master?
We are in trouble, again.
What's going on?
Students, our weekly Feibo show will start very soon.
Next, let's give a round of applause to welcome
the academy's gold host, Feibobo, to the stage!
Good...
All right. Enough. Hello, my fellow students!
I am your Bobo!
- Good. Good.
- Good
Bobo!
Wow.
Our weekly Feibo show is sponsored by the Medicine Sect.
The Medicine Sect's Gather Qi Powder can
gather Fight Qi and not let you lose your handsomeness.
- Wow.
- Good.
Thank you for the warm welcome, everyone.
What good news do I have for you today?
Let's welcome...
Honorable Elders, teachers,
and our dear fellow students.
For a very long time, our Medicine Sect has been following
the strict standards and traditions of refining medicine.
Making good, stable, and safe pellet medicines
is the foundation of the sect.
Along with a forward-looking initiative by taking
the responsibility to supervise the medicine market.
Thus, receiving great recognition and approval
by the Elders and students in the academy.
Recently, there was a formation
of a new interest group, the Yan Sect.
By not abiding by the traditions in refining medicine and
using old improper methods, their products are inferior.
They are selling their inferior products in the marketplace.
A lot of the students and teachers
used their hard earned energy talismans
to buy such home produced pellet medicine
and ended up being fooled and defrauded.
Sect Leader Han Xian of the Medicine Sect tried
to communicate with them in a friendly manner,
but the Yan Sect responded in a disrespectful way
and were not repentant.
They insisted on continuing to refine medicine
with the old methods.
In this situation, in order to create a pure field
in which to work on refining medicines
for the students and teachers of the academy,
we have to show our sword of justice
to make them realize their mistakes. Let's have a round
of applause for all the members of the Medicine Sect.
The response from the Yan Sect...
- Here.
- So big?
The response from the Yan Sect is
the Medicine Sect needs a good beating.
All members from the Yan Sect
accept the challenge from the Medicine Sect.
- Sect Leader, impressive ability.
You all tell me. How many stars am I at now?
Looks like it's three-star.
No, it looks like four-star.
Can't you tell the difference
between three-star and four-star?
This is clearly four-star.
Back then, who was it that told me
that their medicine wasn't useful?
- It was you, right?
- No, it wasn't.
Who was it? I remember it was you.
I was afraid you'd be unhappy if I told you
that their medicine was useful.
Then you all tell me.
Is their medicine useful
or our medicine useful?
You say it.
To be honest.
It seems like their medicine
works a little better after consumption.
Sect Leader, as the strategist for this sect,
I have a few ideas.
Before I crush your stupid head,
speak now!
Number one: We'll all consume their medicine.
You are looking for a beating, aren't you?
Sect Leader, hear me out. Second...?
I won't listen.
I thought you'd have some good ideas.
Sect Leader. In this contest, the limit stated
by both sides is five people from each sect.
There's no difficulty in finding five
Three-Star Fight Masters from within our sect, right?
Then, we consume their medicine to clearly
make sure we are all four-star.
Then, these new students,
no matter how hard they practice,
they will have to listen to our fists.
Once we win, we will confiscate
all their pellet medicine.
How are they going to live from then on?
They will have to come over to beg us.
Then in the future, we will have them produce
the High-Level Gather Qi Powder market products for us.
Not only do we keep the business
in the Medicine Sect,
but we can also earn lots of energy talismans!
Surprisingly, that stupid brain of yours
is actually quite smart. Isn't it?
Let's get on with this matter.
Let's select the people needed and start training.
This Five Spiritual Pythons Formation
was our mercenary army's
most important formation when we were in the
Magical Beast Mountain Range hunting for magical beasts.
Tomorrow, when we are at the challenge,
Han Xian will surely be in the center
and will be protected by his men.
So, our triangle formation move could
tear up their defensive formation.
Just like tearing a hole opening
to stab right into their core;
thus, separating Han Xian from his men.
Remember, this formation needs everyone's support.
We must not lose our positions.
As long as we make them lose their leader
and become troubled and confused,
we can greatly destroy their morale.
Brother Xiao Yan, I'm fast.
I can attract the enemies at the front.
And you can use the Mystical Heavy Ruler
to break them down one-by-one.
Good.
Being fast is useless.
The key is to have more Qi and apply more pressure.
These few are not doing this for the first time, like us.
Don't know how many times they have fought.
Once the Fight Qi energy is blocked, no one can get through.
I think it's better if I am in front,
breaking down their defense with my spear.
"The leader has to be caught first."
I will attack Han Xian first.
Xun'er and Lin Xiuya will attack simultaneously.
Hu Jia, you will cover us from behind
and protect Hao Tian as well.
I won't have the time to protect him.
Xiao Yan, can't you find a few capable ones
to go to the challenge?
Listen to yourself. During the contest,
you are allowed to consume pellet medicine.
In our Yan Sect, the best and the fastest
pellet medicine seeker
is Hao Tian.
We can't find anyone better than him.
Of course! I can help all of you
to supplement your lives.
I will definitely not get into any trouble!
It's settled then.
I will attack Han Xian first.
Xun'er and Lin Xiuya will attack simultaneously.
Lin Xiuya, you can use the most aggressive
Fight Qi skills to guard the frontline.
Xun'er, you are fast,
so you will attack these two quickly.
Hu Jia, you will reinforce
Xun'er and me in the front, and
also protect Hao Tian in the back.
This way, we will always have a backup support,
and be able to attack or retreat freely.
- Good...!
But Xun'er and I are Nine-Star Fight Practitioners,
Hu Jia is an Eight-Star. But Hao Tian...
has only just progressed to the Fight Practitioner stage.
Our five opponents are all Three-Star Fight Masters.
It will be a hard bone to gnaw on.
Right, it is not easy to gnaw on that.
Since it's difficult to gnaw on it,
we'll just swallow it.
Hehe.
If I eat two High-Level Gather Qi Powder medicine at once,
will I directly progress two levels?
Then, if you ate eighty at once,
wouldn't you directly become a Fight Sage?
Is that even possible?
A human body can only contain a limited level of Fight Qi.
Each pill of our Yan Sect's High-Level Gather Qi Powder
can improve your Fight Qi by one stage for two hours.
But if you have three or four at once,
that would be suicide. Your vital channels and your body
will go "boom!" and explode straight away.
Then your insides will spew out all over us.
No one could even bury you.
So disgusting.
This is the core secret of Flame-Splitting
Wave-Devouring Ruler's third pattern. Memorize it.
I can memorize it. But with such a heavy thing in hand
and having to use it above water is too difficult.
As long as you free up your heart and make it
become a void, you can lift anything.
Let me ask you. What do plants need to survive?
Sunlight and water.
Then, why are there plants that can survive
in dark, dry places?
Why can rainstorms flood and destroy a city,
and lightning split a rocky mountain?
That's because there is a natural form
of energy all around us.
It's bigger than anything you can imagine.
You need to erase the bias in your heart
in order to feel it.
To harness Fight Qi energy
is to harness the natural energy in the universe.
Understand?
Understood.
Can you see that waterfall?
All right. Go stop it.
What?
Go ahead. You can do it.
As long as you believe it can be stopped,
it will stop.
Hold in your Fight Qi and stop fighting against it.
Imagine yourself as a rock.
A rock that has been underground
in a deep slumber for a millennium.
This rock needs a bath now.
Wake up! Wake up!
Lin Xiuya! Hu Jia! Xun'er!
Lin Xiuya! Lin Xiuya! Lin Xiuya!
He is not usually a heavy sleeper.
What happened to him?
- Lin Xiuya?
Why is his body so warm?
He has a fever.
Everyone has been overly exhausted
these past few days.
I am fine. Don't leave me behind.
Where is Xiao Yan?
I will go look.
Brother Xiao Yan! Brother Xiao Yan!
Brother Xiao Yan! The fight will start in two hours.
Brother Xiao Yan's not opening his door.
What should we do?
- Brother Xiao Yan?
- His breathing feels even.
- Why can't he wake up?
We are done for.
All of our good ones are "paralyzed."
What is he working on?
Lin Xiuya is probably no good, either.
I've got an idea.
Let's carry Brother Xiao Yan over there.
Why?
He said he would participate. Then,
he will definitely be able to participate.
Wait. Let me think.
Without Lin Xiuya, four against five
is still manageable for a win.
What if Xiao Yan can't participate in
the fight and I'm useless trash?
We should just quit.
What are you talking about?
Let's carry him!
Han Xian...!
-Han Xian!
-The Medicine Sect!
This person looks good.
What a special entrance!
He probably has big moves to get Han Xian
to pass out with one fist.
Look! What an entrance!
Look, it's such fun.
Xiao Yan! Why are you still not awake.
We should probably get him out of here.
The whole audience will jeer at us.
What if he wakes up? He can't fight
if he is not in the ring.
But even if we carried him here,
we still can't let him go and fight first.
Then we will change our plan.
Put him in Hao Tian's position.
I will fight first, you second, Hao Tian last.
If he wakes up, he can still help us.
- If he can't, it still won't hurt
if he's placed in the rear. - Okay.
Brothers, good morning.
Sect Leader Xiao.
Sect Leader Xiao?
What happened to him?
Did he faint due to fear?
- Yes!
- Yeah!
Yes, he did.
He is practicing his martial arts skills.
Practicing his martial arts skills now?
Isn't it too late?
I saw them carrying this "Buddha" from afar.
Sect Leader Xiao, you made quite an entrance!
You!
Xiao Yan!
How can you fight like this?
Go home!
Why are there just the four of you?
What happened to him? Is the fight on or not?
He will wake up.
If he doesn't wake up after a while,
it will be you three against five.
Are you sure you will not employ another person?
Let me reiterate the principles.
Weapons have no eyes, fists and kicks are heartless.
During the fight,
if anyone is seriously injured or dying,
I will intervene to help save the person.
Other than that, the judge will not intervene.
All right, now I need to examine your weapons.
Where is your weapon, Hao Tian?
This is it.
I can fight and defend myself with it.
Good!
Attack!
Xun'er! Hu Jia! Catch!
Xiao Yan! Xiao Yan! Xiao Yan!
Hurry. Wake up!
Xiao Yan! Wake Up! Quick!
- Sect Leader. That was a good move!
- That was a good move, Sect Leader!
Xiao Yan! Hurry. Wake up!
I'll give it all I have now!
Go!
I will help you fight back.
Xiao Yan.
Flame-Splitting Wave-Devouring Ruler!
You are seeking death.
Don't you know?
Flame-Splitting Wave-Devouring Ruler!
- Xiao Yan!
Yan Sect wins.
- Let's go.
- Xiao Yan!
Classmates, the result of the challenge is out.
We officially believe that the Medicine Sect
under Han Xian's leadership
has been using their power to take advantage
of other weaker and smaller sects.
Any attempt to dominate on campus is wrong.
With this fight,
we see that victory belongs to the just.
A round of applause.
Good.
So whose medicine is more useful?
- That...
- That's right. Yes.
So whose medicine is more useful?
Let me explain. Let me explain.
Now, the Student's Council has officially signed a sale
and purchase contract with the Yan Sect.
It's a 20% discount to buy it through the Student's Council.
A round of applause, please.
♫ If you want change, battle it out with no fear of chaos ♫
♫ The sky is dark, there’s misery on earth,
the people are living in a terrible state ♫
♫ Constant hatred and bitter attachment become evident ♫
♫ In this lifetime, you will see your feat
such as has been tempered with fire ♫
♫ Confide in me your aspiration, that constant dream
in your heart that’s difficult to fulfill ♫
♫ To fulfill my promise,
I conceal an arrow inside my gold-threaded sleeve ♫
♫ Being mesmerized for a moment
by the purgatory and the lava ♫
♫ Jumping in with a leap with
neither grace nor resentment ♫
♫ Young but bothered by undiminishing worries ♫
♫ Worries adding on to worries,
the mountain calls and the sea roars ♫
♫ Rushing headlong even if
heaven is narrow and earth is small ♫
♫ Chaos in fighting the evil and foreign forces ♫
♫ Disturbances that no one can escape from ♫
♫ Disadvantaged but don’t belittle or take advantage ♫
♫ of the young ♫
♫ Heroes never ask for names ♫
♫ or titles ♫
♫ On the board of notables ♫
♫ I’ll showcase my martial arts skills ♫
♫ It’s opportune to take advantage of youth ♫
♫ and become famous sooner ♫
♫ Proud and aloof, holding a heavy sword in one hand ♫
♫ Young but bothered by undiminishing worries ♫
♫ Worries adding on to worries, ♫
♫ the mountain calls and the sea roars ♫
♫ Rushing headlong even if
heaven is narrow and earth is small ♫
♫ Chaos in fighting the evil and foreign forces ♫
♫ Disturbances that no one can escape from ♫
♫ Disadvantaged but don’t belittle or take advantage ♫
♫ of the young ♫
♫ Heroes never ask for names ♫
♫ or titles ♫
♫ On the board of notables ♫
♫ I’ll showcase my martial arts skills ♫
♫ It’s opportune to take advantage of youth ♫
♫ and become famous sooner ♫