[My Engineer]
[Episode 9]
I think
it's time for the result.
Stop.
Are you satisfied now?
If you ever make my friend sad,
you'll be dead.
That day will never come.
Do you want to die here?
Why did you do that?
Duen, that's enough.
He may die.
Why did you do that?
Duen.
Ram.
Can you go back by yourself?
This punch is to punish your ruthlessness.
No matter what, thank you.
Thank you for always caring for me.
Okay.
Let's go back then.
Let's go.
-See you.
-Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
Are you sure you can go back?
You can't ride. Let me send you.
Oh, right, this is for you.
As an apology for lying to Sister Kumfah
about your sharp voice.
Venus plant.
But it just sprouted.
It's very hard to raise.
It finally sprouted after so long.
I saw that you were interested in it.
So I would like to gift it to you.
When you're interested in it,
it's like you're interested in me.
I
like it a lot.
Thank you.
Oh, my.
You have never spoken so much to me.
Here, take these too.
Let's go home.
You should try raising it too.
Come over here.
Stop the screaming.
Didn't you act very formidably
when you fought Ram?
I was not pretending to be formidable.
I did everything for you.
Puke.
Show me the other side of your face.
Be gentle.
Okay.
Let's do this side first.
Is this gentle enough?
Too gentle. A little rougher, okay?
Okay, what about this?
It really hurts.
For you.
Once again.
No.
Hey, Cool Boy.
What about I buy you 10 more
Venus plants tomorrow?
So you'll talk more to me.
I talk normally too.
Yes, I know.
But why don't you talk
when you're with me?
Try to say more.
More.
No. Say a longer sentence.
A sentence.
Are you looking for trouble?
Speak properly.
I like Senior King.
I like...
Why don't you say it?
Could you really like me?
I like Senior King.
Senior King is cute.
Senior King is the best in the world.
Cool Boy.
Come back and talk to me.
This flower is for someone important to me.
Crazy.
What did you say?
Everyone is watching us.
I can do something even worse.
Then Duen bites the lips of Bohn desperately.
The blazing tongue crawls into
Bohn's mouth gradually.
What are you reading?
Everyone likes to see you
and Duen being together.
So someone wrote a novel about you two
on the "Wretched Kid" website.
The novel is called
"My Doctor - The Wife of Medical Senior"
The author is Momphor.
Besides, do you know, Bohn?
This novel is at the top in the list now.
I think it will be used for a drama series soon.
Actually, I don't care what they write.
But why did they describe me as Duen's wife?
It's not true.
There's a plot in an abandoned house in the woods.
You are his wife there too.
I think this author has misunderstood.
Trust me.
I think it isn't a misunderstanding.
Because I read the reviews.
Where?
Look.
The readers think you're the wife too.
Because they think Duen
is more handsome than you.
That's true.
Maybe even Duen thinks you're the passive one.
Impossible.
Although he's a little silly,
he knows that he's my wife.
Then Duen bites the lips of Bohn desperately.
Oh, my. This speaks my heart.
Although I haven't kissed anyone,
the author knows that, if I progress,
Bohn will surely be shy.
What you mean is
this novel is like the real life
of yours and Senior Bohn?
Yes.
I pushed him to the table,
and then attacked him.
Don't you think that's just like me?
Brother Duen, be clear-headed,
and stop reading novels.
You're just an O.
O?
What O?
In the world of fetish girls, O means passive.
According to your behavior,
you're always obedient to Senior.
So,
you're passive.
Crazy.
I'm so manly. Of course, I'm the active one.
Duen is so silly, he has to be passive.
But he's more handsome than you.
I understand. It's hard to accept at the beginning.
But once you make your first step,
you'll get used to it soon.
Trust me, brother.
Senior looks more progressive than you.
I understand. It's hard to accept at the beginning.
But once you make the first step,
you'll get used to it soon.
I repeat it for the last time,
Duen is my wife.
Hey!
I repeat it for the last time,
Bohn is the passive one.
Let's go.
Brother.
What?
Can I buy snacks, please?
Snacks?
Okay, go ahead.
Let's go, Ben.
Duen.
Here, the tissue paper you told me to buy.
Great, thank you.
What did you buy then?
I was craving for some fried pork.
Good.
You're always obedient to Senior.
No matter what,
you're the passive one.
I changed my mind.
I want to make marinated eggs today.
What's wrong with you?
Don't you normally eat what I want to eat?
I just don't want to listen to you today.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing's wrong.
But from today on,
I'll not obey you anymore.
Brother Duen, what's going on?
I'm fine.
Let's go buy some eggs.
Let's go.
Brother Bohn.
Why is Brother Duen so fierce today?
Mek, open the door for me.
Hubby, it's your wife.
Open the door for me.
Hubby, your wife is here.
Are you at home?
Open the door for your wife.
Next time, can you let me know before you come?
Sorry. I have something urgent
to discuss with you.
Excuse me.
Look at this.
Actor selection.
Look at the organizer's name.
Tri Creation.
Isn't this Fon's company?
Yes. I'm thinking
if I can become an artist too,
I can get nearer to her.
Good idea.
But do you think you'll be selected?
Why can't someone like me be a celebrity?
I'm going to be direct to you.
You can neither sing nor dance.
You can't even breathe properly.
How can you compete?
That's why I came to see you.
Teach me how to play the guitar, okay?
How can you make it in time?
The selection is next week.
Look.
I've prepared clothes to stay here for a week.
I must learn how to play the guitar.
Please teach me.
Except my love for her, I have no competence.
Hey.
Why do you treat me like this, hubby?
Even love isn't your competence.
Most importantly, the bicycle date was my idea.
I was just acting cool.
Teach me how to play the guitar, please.
No.
Most importantly, I don't want to live with you.
I like to live alone.
It's really urgent for me.
Okay, I'll just kneel here and not leave,
until you agree to teach me.
Hey.
Mean hubby, open the door.
Hey, Mek.
Hello.
Are you here for a bouquet?
Can I pay with kisses?
Mother, why are you here?
I told you that you don't have to come to the shop.
I'm so bored at home.
I'll take care of the shop today. Go and rest, child.
Mother, I've discussed with my brother and sister.
We want you to rest at home.
We will take care of making money.
I still can work.
Look, you're still coughing.
Don't work.
Trust me, I can work.
I don't care. I'm going to arrange
some flowers for customers.
Yo.
We meet again.
Do you still have a headache?
Why are you mentioning that?
Okay.
I think you're fine now.
I want three bouquets of jasmine.
You want to do business with me?
If you keep talking, I won't sell it to you.
Okay.
Wow, what are you doing?
It looks yummy.
Marinated eggs.
Marinated eggs. Not bad.
I like whatever you make for me.
There's another reason
that you're the passive one,
because you like to cook for Senior.
You're like a good wife. How can you not be passive?
I don't feel like cooking today.
You should do it.
Hey.
Hold on. Are you serious?
Yes, I'm serious.
I would like to watch you cook too.
Is there a problem?
Yes. I don't want to cook.
If you don't want to cook, then let's not eat.
Brother, who's cooking then?
My honey and I are hungry.
Can Brother Bohn cook?
No. Even the instant noodles he cooks are very bad.
Bohn, the pan is going to be on fire.
Turn off the fire.
Hurry, turn off the fire.
It's burnt.
What are you doing? It's burnt.
Hurry, turn off the fire.
Where?
Over there. Turn it off.
Oh my, turn it off.
Is it off?
Turn it off. Turn it.
Is it actually off?
I don't know. I can't see it.
Turn it, turn it.
Don't worry, Honey.
I was the one who poured the hot water.
If it's not enough,
there's a marinated egg.
Is that edible?
Take your black egg away.
It's edible.
It's crispy.
Let's eat instant noodles.
Let's eat.
Thank you, Father Bohn.
Thank you for sending me home.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
Hey, hold on.
I'm asking you seriously,
what's wrong with you today?
Nothing.
How can it be?
You're normally an obedient and gentle silly boy.
You listen to everything I say.
From now on, you shall get to know me again.
You have to listen to me.
If there's nothing,
I order you to go back immediately.
Yo, how did you sleep?
Good morning.
In my room, you have to obey my rules.
First, you'll go wherever I go.
Second, don't touch anything in my room.
Got it?
Got it.
Hey, that's the latest comic.
Awesome.
I just said, don't touch my things.
Sorry.
Depressing. The mid-term exam is coming soon.
Why are teachers still giving us a test?
Let's get to the battlefield.
Are you okay?
I'll come later.
Okay, hurry up.
Hey, Cool Boy.
Why didn't you go for the test?
I lost my pencil for the test.
Why didn't you borrow one from a friend?
Or else you won't make it.
It isn't the same.
Why?
Is your pencil the pink lady version?
My mother carved my name on it.
Here, use mine first,
or you won't make it.
[Cool Boy]
The pencil my mother gave me brings good luck.
Oh, I forgot about it.
Here, let God King do his magic.
It'll surely work.
It's blessed. Take it.
That's how I get first places in every subject.
Take it. Hurry, or you won't make it.
Hurry up.
Sorry, I borrowed your pencil just now.
I forgot to return it to you.
Here, use mine first.
Here, repeat the fourth chord.
Wrong.
Which fret again?
I forgot.
How many times have I repeated?
One is fret one, two is fret two.
What's the use of your brain?
I forgot since the first fret.
Then...
How to strum?
Oh.
I get the feeling now.
I get it.
Thank you.
Why did you withdraw so quickly?
Your wife is cold. I need warmth.
Have you figured out
which song to play for the selection?
Regarding this,
I'm not planning to play the present songs,
because others may have done it.
So I'm planning to compose a new song.
That's also good. But
do you know how to compose?
This is another reason why I came to see you.
I remember, at the welcome party,
the song you composed sounded good.
Compose a song for me to join the selection.
How much do you need me to help you?
Why don't I just join the contest for you?
Oh, hubby, you're mean.
I'll compensate you with my body.
Okay?
Compose a song for me, please.
Hey, young boy.
Our friend, Wai, is crossed in love.
Let's drink together tonight to comfort her.
Oh, you're with your wife.
Am I here at the wrong time?
No.
I was just teaching him the guitar.
He wants to join the selection.
Oh, really?
We can gather since everyone is here.
Come on. Let's go.
No.
I want to continue the practice.
I'm not going.
Bad Boss.
Even you want to abandon me?
Hey.
It's not like that, Wai. It's...
It's exactly like that.
No one loves me anymore.
I want to die.
I'm going to suffocate myself here.
Hey, she's going to suffocate herself.
Decide it quickly.
You have to go, or she'll die.
You, hurry.
She's going to die.
Look.
He said he wanted to learn guitar this afternoon.
All of you have to be with me
until the shop closes.
Rotter Tee.
How dare you abandon me for another woman?
Every man is like that, right?
It's okay.
Let's continue dancing.
I like this dance step a lot.
Bohn.
Today, your wife...
Your husband, Duen, allows you to have fun here?
Which Duen? I don't know him.
Oh.
This houseman is brave.
What happened? Did you fight?
Not really.
I don't know what happened recently.
He's so stubborn.
He doesn't do anything as I say.
I think, he may prepare himself
to be your husband.
As the wife, just take it, Bohn.
What do you mean by "wife"?
I'm his husband.
Get it?
Yes.
Hey, Fierce Tiger.
Relax.
Hello, senior.
Hello.
Senior Win.
Do you still remember me? I'm Wai.
Save it, Wai. Get here.
You just came back from Singapore, Senior?
Vacation.
Why are you looking so sad?
It's a long story.
Okay. Let's talk about it next time.
You may come and talk to me at my table.
We're having a gathering of college hunks.
Okay.
Do you want to go there?
Bohn, the college hunks are there.
Take me there, please.
I don't want to.
They just pretend to be cool.
Who's scolding me?
Hello, Senior Win.
I'm here. Where are you?
Oh.
It's you.
Are you here to drink as well?
Sorry, Senior.
Are you in there?
Hey, Thara.
Hey, Win.
Oh, Frong.
It's good that everyone's here.
Frong, this is Senior Thara.
Thara, this is Frong,
our junior.
Here, get in.
Let's go.
Oh.
[Rotter Bohn]
Hello.
Rotter Bohn, what's the matter?
Oh, Senior King?
Sorry, senior.
What?
Oh, Duen.
You're here.
Sorry for disturbing you so late.
Bohn said he wouldn't go home
unless you pick him up.
Duen, you're here.
I miss you so much.
Let go of me.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you so drunk?
I'm troubled.
Duen, why are you sulking with me?
Can you be the old Duen again?
I'll do anything you want.
You'll do anything?
Yes. As long as you can be the old Duen,
I'll do anything.
Come here.
You're going to be hammered for drinking so much.
Are you okay?
What, senior?
Yes.
I am
okay.
Are you sure you're okay?
Of course.
Okay, then text me when you arrive home.
Be safe.
Okay. Goodbye, Senior.
-Goodbye.
Hey, you're leaving, brother?
Goodbye.
All the best.
Are you okay?
I am okay.
Let's sit over there, okay?
Hey.
I have taken paracetamol.
Can't I go back now?
I'm tired.
You didn't want paracetamol the last time.
Now you want it.
What do you actually want?
What I know for sure is
I don't want Thara.
(Paracetamol is called Phara)
Here, let me do it.
It won't hurt so much when I do it.
Why aren't you talking?
It doesn't hurt anymore?
No.
Maybe it's better now because I'm drunk.
Are you hungry?
A little.
There's pork porridge.
It's good for sobering up.
Yummy.
Do you want some?
You shall eat first.
I bought this for you.
Yet you don't want to eat it. It's still warm.
Okay, I'll eat first.
What's going on?
Bad Mek.
Mek.
I...
I love you.
You're indeed my best friend.
Thank you.
What's going on?
Sigh.
Brother Bohn.
Let's eat.
Ben.
Do you know who sent me back last night?
Brother Duen.
He went back after he sent me home?
He was in your room for a while.
Oh, my God.
But when he went back,
there was nothing suspicious, right?
Yes.
But at one point,
I heard moaning sound from your room.
What did I say?
You said, "Oh, it hurts."
There's a plot in an abandoned house in the woods.
You're his wife there too.
What actually happened last night?
You don't have to know.
Go downstairs.
Do you think Duen is the active one?
Is there a problem?
He's so silly.
He even looks a little reserved.
This has nothing to do
with being active or passive.
If you don't believe it,
look at the skinny guy.
The buffed guy is my friend.
He's the active one.
Can someone so sweet be active?
Yes. That's why active or passive one
has nothing to do with appearance.
Don't you think Duen is silly.
He may be the active one.
You have to be ready.
Here, sugar water.
What happened last night?
I only remember that
I asked you to compose me a song.
Then Wai came.
Then I went out.
What else? You and Wai were both drunk.
Oh, no.
I was supposed to compose at home.
But you haven't composed a song for me yet.
Hey, hubby. Compose me a song.
Come on.
It's done.
Wow, thank you so much.
Play it for me, please.
Play your own song.
You play it. I don't even know the chords yet.
Play it to me.
So I'll know how to play it.
Come on.
Okay, I'll only play it once.
Thank you so much.
From today on, you two will have new nicknames.
The quiet husband and talkative wife
of Engineering College.
Too many vegetables.
Exchange some meat with me.
Exchange with me.
Too many vegetables.
Hey, did I let you eat that?
I don't have to ask.
Because a hubby like you is always kind.
Right?
Mek, you
played so well.
It even touched my heart.
It's just like my love to Fon
which can't be spoken out loud.
Thank you so much.
I can surely be selected with this song.
Go ahead and play.
[Special scene]
Hubby.
Take your wife to puke.
I can't get up.