I'm sorry.
I don't know what's wrong.
I feel a little dizzy.
Sis!
Sis, what's wrong?
Doctor, is my sister all right?
She's stable and resting.
But this time, the fever is serious.
I suggest you stay in hospital for an observation.
Make sure there's nothing wrong.
She has autism.
She had a fever before.
Is there any problem with her sudden fever?
Did she feel any pressure or stimulation before her fever?
She was scared when she saw her dad vomitting blood.
She almost got hit by a car on the road.
Then she fell on the ground and started to pull.
The pressure or strong emotional fluctuations may be caused by her.
And I saw her medical record.
She was taking medicine to control her emotions.
But she stopped taking medicine and didn't get a regular checkup.
This may also affect her condition.
Because she's not having a fever, we...
I'll prescribe some medicine to help her control her emotions.
It'll lower the risk of her fever.
Thank you, doctor.
Auntie!
Mom, how's dad?
He just finished his gastrointestinal checkup.
The doctor said Mr. Lin was right.
Because he's taking some rare medicines.
They're anti-cancer medicines.
He's having an accident with Chinese medicine.
You're awake, sister.
Sister.
Sister, where are we?
This is the hospital.
We're all here. Don't be afraid.
No, I want to go home.
Luo Ying Ying, you need to take this medicine twice a day.
One every time.
Let's take it now, okay?
No.
Sister, listen to the nurse.
No, I want to go home.
I'll stay with you tonight, okay?
You'll stay with me?
No. You can't stay at home if you don't take your medicine.
But if you stay here for the night,
I'll talk to you on the phone and watch TV with you.
Really?
I really thank you.
I don't know what to do without you.
Don't say that.
Your family is the most important.
But now my sister and my dad are like this.
I think I can't go to work at the company for the time being.
Don't worry about the company.
Now Ying Ying needs your care.
We need to stabilize her mood.
Don't let her get sick again.
When my sister got sick,
you helped her to drink, right?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You've been helping her for a long time, right?
How did you know?
You've learned Chinese medicine?
Actually, I have Chinese medicine qualification.
But I've been taking it off for a long time.
But the situation was more urgent.
I thought you usually read the emperor's inner scriptures.
And your dad has a clinic.
So you know Chinese medicine.
So you really have a certificate.
You really think I'm talking nonsense?
I just didn't expect you to do business and be a Chinese doctor.
I want to ask if Chinese medicine's salary is really low?
I saw it on TV.
It's lower than nurses.
Forget it.
But it's a little bit different from western medicine.
No wonder you don't want to be a Chinese doctor.
You have a big business.
It must be better than your daily business.
You'll make a lot of money.
Will you be like those heroes in the martial arts drama?
You'll be a good student.
I'm not like that.
But when you were giving my sister the wine,
you were like a god.
You're so cool.
Teach me some moves.
Jiajun, it's time to eat.
I'm not eating.
You're going out?
I'm going to go. I'm afraid I'll be late.
Be careful.
Afraid of being late?
He's meeting someone?
Flying Dumplings.
Interesting.
The dumplings are cute.
The photographer we hired this time needs to cooperate with the exhibition.
We'll be in many different exhibitions.
Even going to overseas exhibitions.
The photographer has to go to many different places.
Even do live activities.
Based on your current situation,
I think there are a lot of problems in terms of cooperation.
Our company doesn't have this resource for the time being.
How about this?
How about changing the shape?
Flying Dumplings really has a lot of market potential.
I want to buy this IP.
With our design team,
if we continue to develop,
it will definitely work.
Thank you for appreciating me so much.
But I'm sorry.
I will only cooperate with those who respect the original.
I won't sell Flying Dumplings no matter how much money I have.
How is it? What do they think?
Good.
You're still very knowledgeable.
You're just praising my words.
You're just not satisfied with me.
It doesn't matter.
Your family doesn't have money.
My cousin bought your grandmother's house.
He paid so much.
You don't have to go to work, right?
I don't lack money.
Not lacking money doesn't mean I have to be trapped at home all day long.
Lie down at home.
I don't want to be a useless person.
I'm not talking about you.
No, I understand.
The so-called useless person is like me.
I know how to play games at home.
Then I'm hungry and eat instant noodles.
I sleep when I'm tired.
Is this what you call useless?
Compared to me, I don't think you're useless.
It's just that you don't think I'm useless.
But in the eyes of others,
I'm still a useless person.
Do you want to know how useless I am?
Come with me.
I'd better go get some oil.
Come on.
Didn't you say that it was for no advantage for you?
This is not a conversation mode.
Why do we come here?
It's pretty. Did you draw this?
This painting shows that this girl has been feeling lonely since she was young.
She thinks that everyone around her won't understand.
But it's good that she has the company of the flying dumplings
so that she feels that life is full of hope.
She can face life with strength.
This painting is very meaningful.
It should be seen by more people.
You can see what's going on here.
Do you think that someone will really care about this painting?
Actually, this exhibition is not art for them.
It's decoration.
The reason why they left this position to us
is because they want to tell us that
we have already tolerated you.
This exhibition also talks about paying attention to mental health.
Drawing like this
is a waste of your work.
I won't tolerate this time.
Can you do it?
What can't I do? Is this my own painting?
The man next to you is looking at us.
So what?
Give it to me.
Is this right?
I'm leaving.
Why did you take so many painkillers?
Come.
I can't stop taking them.
Every time I finish taking them,
my head hurts a lot.
I can't tell
if it's because my body is inflamed
or if the painkiller is working.
I can't tell.
How about I ask my brother to help you?
Sister, it's a bit busy later.
But don't be afraid.
Brother, I believe you.
Why are you looking at the needle and going crazy?
You want to use the needle to needle someone for a long time?
I finally picked up the needle today
and helped someone.
Who is it?
Is it very serious?
Sister Rachel has a stroke today.
I helped her to get the needle after her condition was stable.
How is she now?
I called an ambulance to take her to the hospital.
She needs to be hospitalized, but it's okay.
Look at you.
You always carry the needle bag on your back.
Isn't it just in case
to see when it will be useful?
I understand.
There are many things that are really hard to let go.
There are many things that you can't control.
Well, you've broken the ring.
It doesn't matter later, right?
I hurt my back when I moved the goods today.
It hurts a little. Help me to help you.
Come on.
You're so stupid.
You're tired, so you ask others to massage you.
Don't insult my needle.
Speaking of which, why did you buy so many dust skins?
These are the authentic dust skins of ten years.
I bought them to boil water for my family.
You're being fooled again.
What?
Look at it yourself.
It doesn't taste like dust.
It's a fake.
What? Is there a fake dust skin?
This is the good stuff.
Smell it first.
Wait a minute.
I'm so happy to borrow it and dry it myself.
I can't buy it with the money I have.
This is really delicious.
What's wrong? Are you going to cook it for Nana?
Yes. She has a bad stomach.
Nana is a person who has a bad stomach.
So I'm going to add some two blackberries.
And a few slices of ginger.
Remember to drink hot water.
The skin is warm and the blackberries are golden.
The ginger is warm and suitable for her.
Boil it on high heat and simmer for ten minutes on low heat.
Okay, it's done.
You're so petty.
You're so generous this time.
What? It's like eating someone.
What do you mean? I'm just eating her.
I'm just a dad.
What time do you have a appointment with the guest?
One hour left. Don't worry.
You can take your time.
What are you doing here?
I made some orange peel water for you.
I'm going to work. I want to see the guests.
It's okay. You can take it to see the guests.
Orange peel water is good for your skin.
You must drink it while it's hot.
It can be the most effective.
Okay, okay, okay. Give it to me.
I'm leaving.
I'll take you to eat something delicious after work.
Bye.
This middle-aged girl can't stand her.
She used this orange peel water to show her affection.
Did she look in the mirror?
Do you think she can catch up with you?
This low-class old man is really a dog.
He thinks he's embarrassing you.
Don't let him get close to you.
Otherwise, people will think you have a bad taste.
Are you done?
I'm done.
I'm the one who takes care of the dog.
I'm the one who takes care of everything.
But being my dog is my person.
So you don't have to have so many opinions.
A'Zou.
Yes.
Take me to see the guests.
Okay, get in the car.
Drink it while it's hot. It's warm.
Thank you.
If you like it,
I can cook it for you every day.
Hello, sir.
Why is the beggar's car here?
What is he doing?
Where is it?
Miss, I want to ask where Mr. Deng is.
I don't know.
What a coincidence.
Mr. Deng,
shouldn't you tell me first
when you bring your friend here?
Young Master Keng,
your friend is quite rude.
Ignore them.
Forget it.
I'd better go.
I'll contact you later.
I'll have a guest to see the house later.
If you make a mess here
and make the house so messy,
how can I rent it for you?
Why are you so petty?
I'm not petty.
Since your father gave me the key,
I'll bring someone to see the house at any time.
You're blocking my work.
It's not because I care about you.
You think my dad and your key
really want to find a tenant?
He's looking for an excuse to see you.
He's really sick.
Hello.
Yes, Mr. Zhang.
You're here.
Yes, I'm in the house.
I'll pick you up now.
Okay, bye.
Stop making trouble.
You're not old enough to wear pants.
You've seen it before.
That day we were in the bar.
You saw the photo
that Nell took for me.
Delete Nell's photo.
Okay.
But the photo is a bit old.
I need to find it.
Give it to me.
But in this world,
there's not only Nell.
Do you like empty-braided girls?
Do you like backup girls?
Delete it.
Delete it?
Okay.
Delete it yourself.
Give it to me.
I won't give it to you.
You're sick.
Take your time.
Actually, it's really neat here.
The living room in front of you
is your favorite...
You can sit there.
Don't rain.
Honey, this house is nice.
Mrs. Zhang, I'm glad you like it.
If you think about it,
you can call me anytime.
It's raining outside.
Do you have an umbrella?
I'll get you an umbrella.
Okay, thank you.
You're welcome.
A-Zhu!
It's raining!
What are you doing here?
Yes, it's raining.
Go inside. I'm looking for something.
What are you looking for?
Come up here.
There's your photo in the phone of that loser.
Go inside.
Photo?
Leave it.
I don't care.
I care.
I found it!
Come up here!
It's broken!
Come on!
Look at you!
It's broken!
Her phone is broken!
She can't use it anymore!
You'll get sick if you go inside.
I'm not sick.
It should be ready.
This is wolfberry and mandarin orange soup.
It's my family's five-leaf clover.
It's good for your health.
It's very suitable for your sister.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Since my dad drank the soup and the Western medicine,
my mom has been afraid to cook the soup.
But you've been a Chinese doctor.
You can rest assured.
That's right.
The soup is medicinal.
Everyone has a different body type.
You should ask the Chinese doctor.
And the Chinese medicine.
You'd better eat it in two hours.
And,
does your sister still need to take medicine after getting discharged?
Yes.
Ok.
The patient can be discharged at any time.
But you should take the medicine on time.
That way you can stabilize your mood.
Doctors,
In fact,
My sister has taken this medicine for a while.
But after she took it,
she will feel tired.
She is very tired all day.
She is tired even when walking.
I...
Miss Luo,
If you stop taking medicine,
the disease will repeat.
We don't suggest you do it.
It's better to take the medicine.
I think it's better to use the medicine
My sister felt much better after you gave her acupuncture
Can you continue to give her acupuncture so she won't need the medicine?
Me?
No! No!
Sis, I'm here
Don't touch me!
Don't be afraid
Let me see if there's any medicine
Yes, I'll get it
Relax, don't be afraid
You're at home now
Your sister and I are here to protect you
Relax
Yaoyong!
Sis, don't be afraid
Relax
Ling Weiming and I are here
You're dreaming! It's not true
Don't be afraid
I think it's better
I'll get it for you
My sister often has nightmares when she's asleep
I wish I could have a dark sleep like you
Relax, it's nothing
Don't worry
It's late. You should go to bed early
Thank you for the soup. See you at work
Bye
Aunt, Uncle
Mr. Ling, you're here
Dad, you're out of the hospital
Yes, I went for a walk and bought some food
Hello, Uncle
Hello, Mr. Ling
I can finally see you
You brought Yingchen home?
No, he brought the soup for Sis
He's a good boss. He even takes care of the soup
Mom, don't talk nonsense
It's late. I won't bother you
I'll have tea with you another day
Bye
Thank you. Bye
Mr. Ling, come and play
Bye
Ming-di, come in
Mr. Ling is nice, polite and willing to help
He even cares about Sis
He's a man of the house. He's rare
Don't think too much. He's my boss
I'm not saying that. I'm just being nice
You should take the initiative
Yes, Sis will take care of you more
Yes, good night
Wait, I'll get an umbrella
A-zuo, those two...
Are you going to take a walk?
No, I'm going to enjoy my life
I'm worried that I might be too tired
I'll see you tomorrow
Okay
Xiao-xing, it's very slippery
Thank you
You're welcome
Go inside
Thank you
Have a rest
Call me if you need anything
No, but...
It's okay. Just go inside
I'm going inside. Bye
I'm fine.
What do you mean you're fine?
You have a fever.
What?
You can't drive in such a heavy rain.
I'm fine. I can sit down.
How can you do that? Listen to me.
Hurry up.
Just put it anywhere.
Okay.
Here.
Be careful.
Okay.
Sit down.
How is it? Is it cold?
A little.
It's so hot.
Wipe your body first.
Then I see you with me
The fog lifting lonely when
Come on.
Take the medicine first.
Okay.
Thank you.
If I find myself in trouble
No matter where I am
Take another one.
You'll feel better after taking it.
I don't need you to take my hand
It's cold.
scolded
A little
How about that?
I want to say
Stop talking.
You're sick.
Hurry up and go to sleep.
I'm so happy with you with me.
You're must be fooled by Yuling.
Actually, Deng Shikeng is just playing with you.
You were really fooled by him.
Actually,
you don't have to do so much for me.
Not much.
I don't think it's enough.
I want to protect you.
I don't want Deng Shikang to continue to bully you.
I'm fine.
The photos have been taken.
If you don't get your phone back,
the photos will be gone.
They're all over the internet.
Whatever.
I'm so stupid.
Don't underestimate yourself.
You're not stupid.
In my heart,
you're a very good girl.
I'll always protect you.
I'll always be by your side.
All right.
Go to bed early.
Brother,
am I not getting better?
Can I stop swimming?
Brother,
why do you look so pale recently?
Is the clinic busy?
The clinic has been closed for a while.
Why?
Because I don't have time to take care of so many patients.
I only have one goal now.
To take care of you.
There's no place to see the doctor.
It's good that you know.
So you have to get well soon.
Inflammatory dyslipidemia
is usually a disease of multiple-signal
Inflammatory dyslipidemia is usually a disease of multiple-signal
dyslipidemia.
Because of this,
the patient's lungs will be severely contaminated.
This will lead to blood loss and organ failure.
You wanted to take care of your sister
in the hospital.
But why don't you start over
and close the clinic?
You can't even cure your sister.
What's the point of opening a clinic?
Why are you looking so weak?
You're here at this hour?
It's rare that my parents are back home.
They can take care of my sister.
So I came out to practice archery.
You don't have to worry about me.
I can follow what you taught me that day.
I'll try it.
I'm free. I'll pay you.
You told me that the most important thing in archery is your breath.
You must breathe deeply.
You're in a hurry to shoot the second arrow
before you can adjust your breathing.
You can't shoot it.
I didn't expect you to say that about me.
Yes, I have a guilty conscience.
I can't do it right.
Don't learn from me.
You do it.
I'll do it.
You're a good boy.
Remember,
hold your feet and ears.
You should only attack with your hands.
You can shoot after you're stable.
Actually, I'm not qualified to say that.
It's not easy to be calm.
That's the world.
I envy you. You envy me.
I have a hard time.
You can let go of everything else.
But your family,
no matter how much pressure you have,
you can't just let go.
Because they're my closest relatives.
I can't get rid of them.
There's a bitter and sweet side to it.
It's you.
Come and sit down.
You're hurt.
You want to call an ambulance?
I'll call it.
Don't call it.
I can't go to the hospital.
Please help me.
Help me get the emergency kit.
Your knife is injured.
But it's good that it's not internal injury.
I'll go get you a drink.
I finally helped you stop bleeding.
You're so bruised.
It's not a heart injury or an old injury.
I told you many times to be careful of your back.
Your spine is protruding.
When you touch it,
it's the third and fourth vertebrae
that are pressed into the bone nerves.
You need to go to the hospital for a check-up.
You're walking in the martial arts world.
It's either you hit me or I hit you.
You can't go on like this.
When I was in the KMT,
I was so poor that I couldn't even eat.
I could only go to college.
If I don't fight in Hong Kong,
what else can I do?
So you're the leader of the KMT.
But you don't have to sell your life to them.
You're trying to make money to fight for your life.
No one is blaming you.
But you only have one life.
How many times can you fight?
Survival is not the only way.
People are in the martial arts world.
There's no hurry.
I only believe in what people do.
But I won't force you.
Don't walk around today.
Stay here and rest.
We'll talk about tomorrow.
There's a good thing about riding a bike.
It's raining without an umbrella.
You don't have to wait for me.
You should go back.
That bear is badly injured.
I'll wait for you in the car.
I'll leave when you get in the car.
When I saw you helping Zhixiong,
I really thought you were a real Chinese doctor.
Why do you say that?
I came to see you.
When I saw you reading the Chinese medicine certificate,
I felt a little bit of longing in your eyes.
You bought this house to fulfill your father's wish.
But your father's wish is to open a clinic here.
But why don't you take one more step and open a clinic yourself?
I'm busy with the medicine and oil business.
You're busy.
You won't shoot arrows here every day.
The car is here.
Be careful there.
Be careful.
You're a very good girl in my heart.
You're a very good guy.
I like you too.
You're awake.
Yes.
You have a fever.
Take the medicine first.
No need to eat.
You won't die from the rain.
By the way, Anan, yesterday we...
Yesterday, you were snoring so much that I almost couldn't sleep.
But you're sick, so I won't scold you.
Take it.
By the way, you have a fever.
So I'll drive your car and send you back.
Okay?
One more.
Okay.
Hurry up and eat.
This is our pulse-tube.
It contains Chinese medicine.
It can help to relieve pain and relax muscles.
Thank you.
The pulse-tube can only help you relieve symptoms temporarily.
The protruding part of the shoulder is a structural damage.
You need to be treated formally.
I'll listen to you and go to the hospital for a shoot.
I'll tell you again.
You can't keep your waist like this.
It won't be easy to get hurt again.
Anyway, thank you so much.
Doctor Ling...
I'm sorry.
Please let me see it before.
I won't stop you from seeing it.
I will let you see it.
Who gives you the right to believe that it's all my fault?
You think I'm a fool?
What are you afraid of?
Don't lie.
Don't you think it's too zou?
Who told you to make no mistakes?
Who told you...
Stop it.
Is there something on your mind?
Mom,
I'm often asked to reopen the clinic
and become a doctor.
It's like I hear a voice
saying that you've had enough rest,
and you should wear white clothes and get acupuncture.
It's a sign of your success.
Many patients are waiting for you outside.
So many years have passed since I got the job.
I can't get past this.
I'm afraid
that the result will be the same.
Although I gave them hope,
in the end,
I let them down.
I'm sorry.
Where have you been all night?
I didn't answer your call.
Ming, we bought breakfast.
We bought yours.
Sit down.
Okay, thank you.
Brother, I'm a hero.
I was so busy yesterday
that I helped Ned find his phone.
I even successfully escorted him home.
But he had a fever
when he was in the rain.
A fever?
He had a high fever.
So I didn't let him drive back.
Yes.
Then Nana asked me to stay at his house for the night.
Then she helped me to wipe my body on the bed.
She even helped me to sweat.
So I feel much better.
How did she help you to sweat?
There are many ways to sweat.
I'm not Mudan.
What is Mudan?
Mudan means
a man who has never been in love,
or met a girl,
or a man who has never been in love.
So you and her are already...
that kind of men.
What's wrong?
What are you talking about?
Why are you laughing?
Nothing.
Besides, a boy
is a wonderful journey
for a man.
Then we can get chola for sure.
Okay.
All right, wait a moment, please.
Don't laugh so loudly.
I was lucky.
You did a great job.
Don't look at me.
You...
Ali, what happened?
Are you not feeling much?
It seems to be torn at the top.
What about the belly?
Try pressing it to see if it hurts.
It's a little uncomfortable.
Is the menstrual cycle accurate?
Is it more or less?
What color is it?
And then is there any blood?
I usually come to the menstrual cycle
which is not accurate and will be delayed.
The color is dark red.
It's a little less and there's blood.
And I will feel pain.
Can you stick out your tongue and show me?
Your tongue is dark purple.
And there's a fishbone on the side of the tongue.
It should be the blood circulation and blood pressure.
The blood flow is not clear.
And the meridians are involved in your skin.
And the problem of the lower jaw
makes your upper abdomen uncomfortable.
Then what is the lower jaw?
It's your uterus and the lower jaw.
I would suggest you go to the doctor
to do a detailed re-examination.
I made you some water.
What's wrong?
It's stomach pain.
Then don't eat breakfast.
You drink this water
and go home and have a good rest.
Thank you.
I hope you remember my suggestion.
Don't worry, I understand.
Thank you, A Min.
Stop laughing.
People may think you have a bad brain
or you are possessed.
No, brother.
I remember that I was very weak
when I was with Ned.
Don't you know that?
I was very confused yesterday.
I said some mean words.
I hugged him.
But I must have been wearing his clothes
when I woke up this morning.
Then you should ask him clearly.
Of course not.
If I ask him,
he will think I pretend not to remember
and I don't want to be responsible.
Brother, should I be responsible?
Of course you should be responsible.
You should be nice to him.
Of course I will.
I only have Ned in my heart.
I will be responsible.
The reason why the shoulder is protruding
is often an accident.
Or it is affected by long-term sitting.
In addition to back pain,
it will also affect the width,
knee joints and the
shoulder muscles.
Left hand, press the table to balance.
Right hand, hold the left foot.
Left and right, open the bow and stretch back.
Then you can stretch the spine
and push it to the side.
Let's go.