SE-YEON
JUNG-YUN
SEO-YEONG
SEO-HYEON
SANG-WON
HEE-JI
JI-MIN
YE-RIN
JI-WOO
PYEONG-SEOK
NINETEEN TO TWENTY
I heard what Jung-yun said about you.
What? When?
Jung-yun said, "For me, it's Ji-woo."
The others were saying,
"You were only looking at Ji-woo."
-And he said, "I couldn't help it."
-No way!
Why can't he say that to me?
That's what I want to hear,
but when I ask him,
he won't say it. So I'm confused again.
He's making my heart flutter.
Jung-yun's so funny.
-He's so funny.
-Doesn't he have a cute smile?
-No.
-Well…
He's so handsome and he smiles differently
when he's fooling around
and when he can't help it.
The corners of his lips…
-Right.
-You can see that he's trying to hide it.
It's driving me nuts.
Why is he so handsome?
Ji-woo's expressing her feelings.
-She's so into him.
-I didn't know it was this much.
Ji-woo was really serious about him.
-He's weird. Why can't he just…
-She's blushing.
Why can't he tell me how he feels?
I do know how he feels,
but I wish he would express himself more.
You guys are so cute.
What about you, Ji-min?
Yeah, I want to know how he feels.
-Who is it?
-I…
Be honest.
I'm not sure.
-Who are you torn between?
-You must be interested in someone.
Between Ye-rin and Ji-woo.
-Ye-rin and Ji-woo?
-My feelings for them keep changing.
He feels the same way as Se-yeon then.
Right. They're interested
in the same girls.
Yes.
-Jung-yun only likes Ji-woo. These three…
-Right.
It's complicated.
I like Ji-woo,
but I'm starting to like Ye-rin
after going on a date with her today.
I keep going back and forth between them.
-How was it?
-It was really fun.
Really?
Did she feel more like a friend? Or…
-Was it romantic?
-Were there sparks?
It felt like we were starting to like each
other romantically, not as friends.
I told her that I'm interested
in her and Ji-woo.
Don't you have something to share?
Me? Well…
Nothing like that?
-Oh, to Hee-ji?
-Yes.
-Yes, we talked.
-About what?
I asked her if she likes anyone.
Did she say it was you?
-Did she?
-Yes.
She was like, "No one else but you."
So everyone's saying that kind of stuff.
Everyone is…
You're the only one
who hasn't said anything!
You should say something.
-Jung-yun.
-It was basically spoon-fed to him.
But I bet he realized
while listening to them.
-He'll know he should say something.
-Please!
I think he will now.
-She was so honest.
-I'm not sure about how Ye-rin feels.
-I opened up about everything.
-I don't know where to start.
You want to do something
with Pyeong-seok, right?
-You're curious about him?
-Yes.
I can tell.
I'd like to get to know him more.
-And he's a friend.
-Yeah.
How did it go with Ji-min?
We hung out as friends, but in the end…
Ji-min said that he doesn't think of me
as just a friend anymore.
That's crazy.
He's good at saying stuff like that.
-He's good at expressing himself.
-He is.
He says it feels completely different
when he's alone with me.
He said he never thought
he'd feel this way.
-But…
-This is interesting.
I also just thought of him as a friend,
-Was it different?
-but it feels a bit more romantic now.
He started being so sweet after he started
to see me as a love interest.
But I don't know
what will happen with Ji-min.
Right. No one knows.
Let's go.
LOTTE WORLD ADVENTURE
-You said you wanted
-Let's go.
-a picture of the castle.
-Yeah.
-This is crazy.
-Tell me about it.
I just got goose bumps.
-Not everyone gets to experience that.
-Seriously.
Except for the Chairman of Lotte, maybe.
Right.
I can't believe this.
Hey.
This is so awesome.
-The constellations…
-Yeah.
-This is so cool.
-Seriously.
I can't believe it.
This is crazy.
-Hey…
-Holy…
-It's so pretty.
-Yeah.
Seriously.
And we're the only ones here.
Yeah. This is so…
I'm so happy right now.
This is amazing.
-This is a dream date.
-Yes, for real.
-Look!
-My gosh.
-Should we take a photo at the castle?
-Yes. I've never taken one there before.
-At the castle?
-Yes, there was always a long line.
-It was impossible.
-I always took photos there by myself.
That's lit up just for the two of us.
I can't believe it. I love it.
The castle's beautiful.
I feel dizzy.
-From happiness?
-I'm really dizzy.
I'm dizzy with excitement.
-Should we take a photo?
-Yes.
Are you good at taking photos?
Of course. I'm a good at posing too.
-I'm not that good.
-Really?
-I'm not good at taking photos.
-I'll help you.
-Yes, help me out.
-Okay.
Ten seconds? Three?
-Three is too short.
-Right.
-Nine seconds. What should I do?
-Do a cool pose.
-Here?
-What do I do?
-It took so many.
-Next.
Next, stand right here.
-Okay.
-Stand closer.
Eye contact? Can you?
You can't keep eye contact.
How can we do that pose?
-This is hard.
-There.
All right.
Hey, this looks really good.
It's great.
It's awesome.
-This one's good.
-Nice.
It's been a long time since I got
on a carousel.
Same here.
-Five years? Ten?
-Ten years?
-I was 10 years old 10 years ago.
-We're 20 now.
We're 20.
Surprise!
It's so pretty!
That's awesome.
I got goose bumps.
This reminds me of Shin Hyun-joon.
-Stairway to Heaven?
-Yes.
Do I look like Prince Charming?
-Come on.
-I can ride without holding onto this.
I only rode this when I was little.
It goes up and down quite a lot.
Right?
-Okay.
-Well, I…
Should we take a photo?
-Shall we?
-Yes.
-You look great.
-Make me look pretty.
-Should I get your feet in the picture?
-Yes.
You look good.
I can't wink.
-Hey, why are you…
-Hey.
-This one looks good.
-Are you sure?
-Pick the one you look good in.
-What about this one?
-Okay, this one looks good.
-Okay.
Safety check complete.
Let's set sail. Ready, go!
THE SPANISH PIRATE SHIP
THE CONQUISTADOR
-There's no one here.
-This is crazy.
Calm down.
-Relax.
-Raise your arms.
Raise your hands!
What do I do? Let's calm down.
-Come on, just once more!
-Relax.
I think I lowered my arms first.
They're the first ones to hold hands
in this show.
They're practically dating right now.
But…
They're dating for sure.
What?
He crossed his arms.
-You want me to cover your bangs?
-Wait.
-Should I cover it?
-Yeah.
-Hey!
-Watch out.
-Please!
-Here we go.
Compared to the last time I…
Why is this so scary?
Are you scared?
Please.
-I love this.
-Oh, please.
-What's happening?
-Here we go!
No!
Yes!
-Here we go.
-Wait.
Here we go. Watch out.
This is it.
That was so much fun.
Thank you for riding.
That was…
Seriously…
-You all right?
-Please.
-My legs are shaking.
-Let's go.
Be careful.
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
Are you okay?
Should we rest here?
Where should we sit?
-I'm hungry.
-It looks great. I'm so happy.
-Let's eat.
Do you like it?
It's really delicious.
It's really good.
-How was today?
-I had so much fun.
-Was it fun?
-Yes.
I think I'm going to dream
about this tonight.
This? Same here.
It was amazing
when the lights of the castle lit up.
It was so pretty.
What?
I can't believe it.
We can hear the echo of our voices
in Lotte World Adventure.
-It's nice to have it all to ourselves.
-Yes.
-I'm happy I'm here with you.
-Right.
What?
Why do you keep reacting like that?
-What?
-You keep doing…
No, I…
There was something on my face.
That kind of reaction is funny, though.
Everything was prepared
just for the two of us,
and I was with someone
I got along with and liked.
It's hard to describe,
but it was literally a dream date.
You always have to wait more than
two and a half hours
to ride the roller coaster.
But it was so nice to just go up there
and ride it right away.
It was like a dream.
Having this whole place to ourselves
is what I would call a dream date.
It was so much fun.
So who will you take on your date?
Come on.
-I'm just teasing you.
-My dream date…
-You can go out on a date.
-Yes.
-This is amazing.
-Yeah.
I wonder what the other dates will be.
They must have their names
up there already.
-But I bet this one was the best.
-Yeah.
-It was awesome.
-I agree.
It was amazing.
Why doesn't it feel romantic anymore?
I have a lot to say.
I've been watching them carefully.
We talked about how they were
the first ones to hold hands.
They did hold hands,
but Seo-hyeon simply raised her hand
and Sang-won grabbed it.
-You're right.
-He grabbed her hand.
And Sang-won kept saying he was happy
and that he loved their date.
But Seo-hyeon
just seemed happy
about having the park to themselves.
Right.
-I think so too.
-Right?
-It seemed that way.
-Yeah.
She might actually feel uncomfortable now.
Sang-won keeps asking how their date was
and who she will go with on her date.
She may be uncomfortable.
This is really difficult.
Some girls want the guys
to express their feelings,
-but others feel uncomfortable if they do.
-Yeah.
-Right.
-You have to balance it well.
That's what they'll learn over time.
-Right.
-They're new to this.
It comes with experience.
Guys!
-It's 11:59 p.m. Come on.
-It's 11:59 p.m.
Does the other person
have to agree with it?
-Yes.
You have to ask.
-What?
-It's nothing.
Hey!
-It's out.
-Hey!
No way!
DREAM DATES: FULL RENTAL OF A MOVIE
THEATER, HANWOO OMAKASE
FULL RENTAL OF A MOVIE THEATER
HANWOO OMAKASE
-Omakase? They should pick that!
-Yes!
-Hang on.
-No way.
-Choose that.
-Choose hanwoo omakase.
-But the movie theater…
-What?
-If you go at right time…
-It's like a full rental.
If you go at dawn.
-It has to be the right time.
-Either very early or late.
-The hanwoo looks better.
-You should try it.
That looks delicious!
Ye-rin will probably go for it.
Wait!
No, this isn't it.
Omakase?
FULL RENTAL OF A MOVIE THEATER
JEONG SEO-YEONG
-Who is Seo-yeong going with?
-Right.
Sang-won.
I wanted to get to know Sang-won better.
So I told him I wanted to hang out
with him.
EARLIER TODAY
-So actually…
-Yes?
-I want to go on my next date with you.
-Okay.
-Sure, I'd like that. But…
-Really?
As long as it's not eating hoe, it's fine.
-I don't like hoe.
Anything else is fine.
-Sang-won's busy.
-That's right.
He's running all over the place.
-Today and tomorrow.
-Lotte World Adventure, the movie theater…
He's having so much fun.
I'm so full right now that
I don't feel like eating hanwoo.
No, Jung-yun.
Hanwoo isn't the problem.
-Hanwoo omakase.
-It'll be delicious.
I know, but I'm not hungry.
They'll serve yukhoe and beef sashimi.
-It's kind of disappointing, isn't it?
-Yes.
It's not that great.
Then that's gone for nothing.
I seriously considered
hanwoo omakase date,
but Hee-ji didn't seem
to like it that much.
So I didn't write my name.
If Hee-ji had liked it,
I would have written my name up there.
I wanted to go on a better type of date.
Those were not the kind of dream dates
that I had in mind.
So I wasn't that sad about it.
-It's because they've never tried it.
-They've never tried it.
You'll regret it later.
I guess a meal
isn't a dream date for them.
We all thought the hanwoo omakase
was the best option.
It's because it came
after the theme park date.
Why do you all look tired?
-It's hard to adjust.
-You're crying, you know that?
A tear just fell from your eye.
Ji-min's crying on the outside.
I'm crying on the inside.
-Hey, that's mine. No, you can drink it.
-Here.
-I want some coffee too.
-Copy?
I also heard "copy."
Just drink it.
Just open that one and drink it.
-Should I make you one?
-No, I'm done.
-You can drink it.
-It's fine.
-Where did he go?
-Drink it.
-No, it's…
-We can both drink it.
-Let's talk.
-Okay.
Let's just talk over here.
-Maybe somewhere else?
-That was refreshing.
Want to go to the Room of Truth?
Where's the Room of Truth?
-In the basement.
-Should we go?
-Really?
-I don't mind.
-I'm so tired.
-You should get some sleep.
I'm tired, but I can't sleep.
Careful, you might spill it.
I was trying not to think about it,
but I couldn't help it.
I thought, "If I don't say anything,
she might start liking someone else."
Do you know where you want to go?
-What about you?
-I want nice food.
Let's do some research.
We can go have something nice.
Okay.
Great.
How was your date today?
The sushi was really good,
and to be honest,
I wanted to know how Jung-yun felt.
He knows about us. You told him too.
He also saw me and Ji-min
talking a while ago.
So, I actually
wanted him to feel a bit jealous.
But he didn't really give me
the answer that I wanted.
If somebody likes me,
I'd like them to be more expressive.
But nobody's doing that right now.
You guys say you're interested in me,
but I'm having a hard time believing that.
So I feel confused.
Then who's the one
you like the most right now?
It's Jung-yun, of course.
I also want to get to know
you and Ji-min better,
but I only had romantic feelings
for Jung-yun.
I still feel the same way right now.
I haven't done much with you.
But… Can I be honest?
Frankly, you said
that you're interested in me,
but I can't really tell if that's true.
I was wondering if you said that
because you were drunk.
That's what I was thinking today.
Do you really like me?
Are you actually interested in me?
I didn't say that to you
just because I was drunk.
I mustered up the courage
and honestly told you how I feel.
I said this yesterday too,
but I really thought that was admirable.
If I were you,
I wouldn't have said anything,
so I did feel attracted to you
because of that.
Right. But…
I didn't know I'd feel
emotionally exhausted.
Don't be like that.
You should go out on dates
with other girls.
And have fun.
You're telling me to do
what I want to do, right?
Yes.
That's what I was planning to do.
Then why are you feeling so exhausted?
No, I'm not!
You looked awful.
You were always with Pyeong-seok
on the terrace talking and drinking beer.
You were always talking so seriously.
Then you'd keep quiet
and just go about your day,
then talk to him again.
-Why did you come here then?
-That stings!
Why did you even come here?
If you're having a hard time,
you should do something about it.
If not, just try to have fun.
At this rate, you'll just keep…
I haven't even seen you smile
except when we held hands yesterday.
Just kidding.
-Ji-woo's so cool.
-Wow, Ji-woo.
Just kidding.
Let's just talk like this.
Oh, come on.
Don't be like that.
Then let me ask, how did you feel
when we held hands yesterday?
It made my heart flutter.
And during our dancing class,
we were holding hands the whole time.
It felt really romantic to me.
But I ignored that feeling
and tried to forget about it
because I thought
there was no connection between us,
and you didn't seem interested in me.
So I just…
I tried to forget about it
and told myself it didn't mean anything.
Well, if I'm being honest,
when I saw the other girls
on my first day here,
none of them were really my type.
But then…
A few days later,
they said a transfer student is coming.
And this tiny girl comes in
with a huge backpack as big as her.
I took one look at you,
and I thought,
-"She's the one."
-Really?
You were staring at me
the whole time, weren't you?
-Yes.
-I kept meeting your eyes.
DURING THE BEAUTY CLASS
Just write down what you see.
If there's only one, just write one.
MIRROR
He winked through the mirror.
I felt it through the mirror.
You looked really pretty in the mirror.
-Really?
-Yes.
-It's kind of…
-Wait.
-This is nice.
-It's hot. Should I open the door?
-No, it's perfect.
-Really?
-The fire's too strong.
-Right?
-Let's remove some logs.
-Good idea.
We should remove some.
I thought you'd wink back at me though.
I'm actually good at winking.
Aren't I?
What?
-Did she just wink at him?
-She did!
I'm actually good at winking.
Aren't I?
Aren't I good?
Way better than me.
Right? Some people scrunch up
their faces when they try to wink.
But I can do it much more naturally.
Why is it so hot?
It's cold!
-You're cold?
-Go outside.
-My gosh.
-Go get some fresh air.
I can't think straight.
You seem kind of drunk.
-What?
-You seem drunk.
It's because of you.
I wanted Jung-yun to express
his feelings for me.
But he didn't say anything,
even when I gave him the chance to do so.
But Se-yeon asked me
if we could talk privately
and said things
that made my heart flutter.
So I felt really attracted to him.
And for the first time, I talked with him
without thinking about Jung-yun.
After our second serious conversation,
I feel that we confirmed
that we had feelings for each other.
You're sleepy, aren't you?
It feels like it's 8 a.m.
-Really?
-Yes.
Then we can talk for 12 more hours.
-No, maybe 16 hours.
-Yes.
I can talk for 24 hours.
Ms. Ji-woo is really honest.
-"Ms. Ji-woo"?
-Oh, right.
-She seems more mature than me.
-You can't think straight right now.
You're right.
Ji-woo is being so honest.
It seems like she literally has her
hand in his heart and is controlling it.
-He can't think straight.
-That's accurate.
Anyway, Se-yeon's talking with Ji-woo more
and expressing his feelings for her.
I think Jung-yun should watch out.
-Right.
-Yeah.
She wants Jung-yun to express how he
feels, but others keep doing it instead.
I think she might be attracted to him,
but she still seems to like Jung-yun more.
-I won't work out tomorrow.
-Sit.
I'm exhausted.
The hills around here are steep.
What is it?
How do you feel?
-How do I feel?
-Yes.
I like Ji-woo.
-I like Ji-woo.
-Okay.
But recently, I am a bit confused.
Why are you confused?
There must be a reason.
I don't know what to do. You know?
Well, I think you should
express yourself more.
Be bolder too.
I just can't do it.
-You have to.
-I have to?
-You should.
-Really?
Right.
From my conversations with Ji-woo so far,
she's still interested in you the most.
-We just talked about that.
-Yeah.
If you don't want her
to fall for someone else,
then you should do something about it.
If you keep this up,
who knows what'll happen?
If there's something you want to say,
just say it.
If you want to tell her something,
then tell her. Please!
I feel frustrated seeing you.
I'm frustrated with myself.
Then do something about it.
Please.
-Yes.
-Please.
I'm frustrated, too.
Please.
Hee-ji…
-Thank you.
-Jung-yun is so hard to figure out.
-Some just can't do it.
-He's never done this before.
-I understand.
-He has to try.
He should try.
I want to go there.
-Where the lights are?
-Yes.
I was talking with the others.
They said that whenever we talk about you,
I'm always smiling.
I guess I can't hide my feelings.
It's because of this.
-They're so cute!
-So cute!
They're so romantic.
I love watching them.
It's because of this.
-You can't hide it.
-It's my dimples.
They can't lie.
-What are you thinking about?
-What?
Well, Ye-rin…
asked me out on a date.
-A date?
-Yes.
She said…
that she's suddenly…
interested in me,
but I didn't do anything.
I don't get why she's doing this.
Oh, no. I can't let her find out
how cute you are.
-Well, I can go on a date with her.
-Okay.
But she asked me out on a dream date.
A dream date?
-She asked you out on a dream date?
-Yes.
You guys didn't talk?
We just did.
-But she wants a dream date with you.
-Right.
That sounds…
It's a bit, just…
Yeah…
I didn't see that coming.
Me neither.
Well, have fun tomorrow.
So Pyeong-seok will go on a date
with Ye-rin tomorrow.
I'm not worried
about Pyeong-seok and Hee-ji.
-Right. They seem…
-I'm not worried,
-but you never know.
-Ye-rin is…
-Like Ye-rin and Ji-min. You never know.
-You never know.
What if Ye-rin ties her hair up again?
What if she ties her hair up?
But Ye-rin liked Ji-min…
-But I don't know.
-No one knows.
-I'm not sure.
-Who knows what'll happen?
No one knows.
DAY THREE AS 20-YEAR-OLDS
Seo-yeong, what happened yesterday?
Did you run up to the board
and write your name?
The movie theater date?
Did you run up there immediately?
Or did everyone seem to hesitate?
I was right in front of it
when it appeared.
Amazing.
I want my orange and mango juice.
It's probably gone.
-My orange and mango juice.
-What's that?
You have to be kidding me.
-The Capri Sun?
-Yes.
-Someone drank it.
-Who?
-It wasn't me.
-Who was it?
Probably Jung-yun.
-Who?
-Jung-yun.
Jung-yun? Darn it.
I'm not letting this slide.
I'll show him who's the boss.
Lim Jung-yun!
Lim Jung-yun, what's that?
-Come here.
-A Capri Sun.
-Is it yours?
-She wanted to drink it.
-Oh, it's yours?
-Have you lost your mind?
It was yours?
Have you lost it?
Oh, it was yours.
-Did you enjoy it?
-Yes, it was good.
All right then, as long as you enjoyed it.
Seo-hyeon is so cute.
Those two are just friends.
Yeah, close friends.
Mild flavor? Mozzarella cheese?
Seo-yeong!
No way. You can't go out like that.
-Should I stay with you?
-Who told you to dress like that?
I'm going to fall for you.
I've already fallen for you.
Why aren't you wearing blue?
This is my outfit.
-For today?
-Yes.
You all dress up so nicely.
Look at you, Seo-yeong.
You look so pretty.
I don't know if Seo-hyeon
was joking or not,
but she kept saying I dressed up nicely.
I kept thinking about that.
I was worried that our relationship
would get affected by that.
So I felt a bit conflicted.
Seo-hyeon, hold on.
-The Room of Truth.
-Why?
Am I getting scolded?
It's my first time in this room.
-Really?
-Yes.
-What?
-It's just funny.
How do you feel about my date today?
A bit…
Are you okay?
-Just a bit…
-Yes?
It's the first time I'm feeling this way.
Kind of uneasy.
-Uneasy?
-But you can go.
Have fun today.
I intentionally didn't match with her.
Is that what you were talking about?
I have a sweater in the same blue,
but I didn't wear it.
Is that so?
But Seo-yeong is so pretty.
You look prettier to me.
I… What?
I think I need to train my mind
or something.
Is it weird hearing me
say stuff like that?
Totally!
-Why?
-I'm not used to it.
Even after all the things
I've said to you?
I mean, I've never met a guy like you.
Am I too straightforward?
-Very.
-Is it too much?
No, it's not like that.
It's…
something new to me.
I'll keep it up if you don't mind it.
How about giving me
a break every now and then?
-A break?
-Give me time to take in what you say.
Will it take you long?
-Yes, of course.
-Really?
I'll probably never get used to it.
Compared to when we were at school, he's
been expressing his feelings more here.
I'm really grateful that he's being honest
about his feelings,
but it makes me worry
about how I should react
to his behavior.
I don't know how to react to his words.
She doesn't know how to react.
-Right.
-I get it.
She feels uncomfortable.
Sang-won's going too fast.
He's already fully focused on her,
but Seo-hyeon…
-Right.
-She's not sure yet.
He's going way too fast,
so even if she tries to keep up,
-she's backing out a little.
-Right.
And Seo-hyeon has been wanting
to get to know other guys, too.
-That's right.
-But whatever the case may be,
the other guys may think
that Sang-won and Seo-hyeon
are already a couple
and no one else would try
to approach her now.
Seo-hyeon may feel uncomfortable
about others seeing her like that.
-I agree.
-Then she could just tell him
-to slow down or stop.
-Right.
She could ask other guys out on a date,
but she's not doing that.
It seems like
she's not the type to do that.
Maybe.
-It'll be difficult.
-Right.
The others think
they're practically dating,
so she can't really
ask someone else out on a date.
I understand.
This is complicated.
I'll do the dishes.
Eat up.
-I'll rinse them.
-No, it's fine.
-All right.
-Okay.
Come back soon.
I might die of boredom.
Okay.
So, I'm going to do my lips now.
Let me do my lips.
-Hey, Pyeong-seok.
-Yes?
How do I look?
Nice.
-Should I wear this?
-Yes.
-Should I wear it or not?
-Go for it.
-The headband. Should I wear it?
-It's pretty.
-Is it?
-Yes, totally.
-Totally?
-Yes, it's perfect.
Let's go.
Okay.
See you later.
-Have fun.
-Okay.
This headband's so pretty.
Bye guysquirrel.
Won't you be cold?
I don't want to bring a jacket.
-He's jealous.
-Right?
-Totally.
-He's so cute.
He's the jealous type.
It seems like Ji-min's feelings for Ye-rin
have grown a lot.
Right.
YE-RIN & PYEONG-SEOK'S DATE
-Is it far?
-The comic book cafe?
When's the last time you've been to one?
Me? Ninth grade.
-Me, too.
-Really?
-My last time was in ninth grade.
-With who?
My friend.
What about you?
-I went with my friend, too.
-Girlfriend?
Just a friend.
-Really?
-Yes.
I wonder what Se-yeon's doing.
-He went to work out.
-He's going on a date today.
Oh, right.
-With Ji-woo.
-Right.
-But I'm here with you.
-I wonder what they'll do.
Those two have been talking a lot lately.
Who?
-Se-yeon and Ji-woo.
-Right.
They were talking a lot yesterday, too.
I wonder what they're up to.
They were being so obvious.
It makes me curious.
But I'm also curious
when you're talking to Hee-ji.
Why am I so curious about everything?
-I'm not usually like this.
-Really?
My accent is pretty strong
because of my dialect, isn't it?
-You?
-Yes.
-I like it though.
-Really?
Yes. Try speaking standard Korean.
-Standard Korean?
-Yes.
-I'm not good at it.
-I'll give you a sentence.
"Where are we going?"
Standard Korean really does sound softer.
Yes, a bit.
"Where are we going?"
Oh, no.
"We're going to a comic book cafe."
-"A comic book cafe."
-Right.
"We're going to a comic book cafe."
I can't do it.
Like this, "We're going
to a comic book cafe."
"We're going to a comic book cafe."
"A comic book cafe."
-This is hard.
-It's hard.
COMIC BOOK CAFE
Look, there's a cat up there.
This cat is huge.
-Stop staring at me.
-Why?
I'm scared.
He's so cute!
-I get why Hee-ji thinks he's cute.
-She should see this.
-Right?
-He's cute.
Let's pick a book for each other.
Yeah.
I heard that the others
exchanged books before I transferred.
I suddenly remembered that,
so I suggested picking out books
for each other.
I fell asleep during the movie.
-Isn't this a romance comic book?
-Romance is good.
-Let's go.
-Yeah.
Let's exchange. One, two, three.
Here you go.
-Your Name.
-Yes.
YOUR NAME.
Your Name.
Maybe she likes my name?
Q. WHAT BOOK DID YOU PICK FOR YE-RIN?
I chose one that had
a similar vibe as Ye-rin.
I think I gave it to her because the girl
on the cover looked like her.
HIRING A FIANCÉ
"Fiancé"?
Let's read it.
-I'm hungry.
-Should we order something?
It looks delicious.
The smell's awesome.
It smells so nice!
Try it.
-Let's eat.
-Yes, let's eat.
-Is it good?
-Yes.
You seem to like it.
What do you talk about with Hee-ji?
First impressions, current impression,
and things like that?
Yeah, we talked about that.
What did you think about me?
Didn't you want to get to know me better?
You looked like a celebrity.
-Really?
-Yeah.
You are tall.
And you looked cool.
Why didn't you tell me that earlier?
Which guy did you want to
get close to the most?
Se-yeon.
-When I first saw Se-yeon, I was shocked.
-He's like a doll, right?
Would you date him if you were a girl?
If I were a girl,
I'd date me.
For real.
Who do you like now?
-Me?
-Yes.
Be honest.
I like
-Hee-ji the most.
-Right.
Anyone else?
No one else.
-No one?
-No one.
This is what I'm talking about.
He has his guard up.
-He's so cool.
-Right?
No one else.
-No one?
-No one.
Is this alcohol?
-But…
-Yes?
The girls talk about the guys too, right?
We do.
We always talk about you girls.
Really? You must talk about Hee-ji.
Right.
And no one else?
I've talked about you too.
In a good or a bad way?
Just the facts.
-That you asked me out on a date.
-Yeah.
-That I was surprised.
-Right.
Then the guys said,
-"Have fun."
-I see.
What did Se-yeon say?
Se-yeon?
I told Se-yeon…
-about the dream date.
-Why did you do that?
But still, things can change.
-So?
So who is he going to ask?
He's still not sure.
About asking me or Ji-woo or…
I don't know.
What?
You seem pretty concerned.
But if Se-yeon uses his dream date
to go out with Ji-woo, then I think…
I'd feel heartbroken.
I mean…
During my date with Ye-rin,
whenever I looked at her face,
she seemed so serious and troubled.
I thought, "She must be thinking a lot
about Se-yeon."
Who are you going out
on your dream date with? Hee-ji?
Yes, I think so.
We were always together in school too.
-Right.
-We were seatmates.
We never changed seats.
I was always with Jung-yun.
-The entire time.
-That's too bad.
There won't be a next time for that.
-Right.
-That's sad.
-Where is everyone?
-Maybe downstairs?
-It's cold.
-It's so cold.
So cold.
-How was the workout?
-Great. I feel good.
You're eating already?
-Boneless chicken.
-Should we eat some? But…
-Just have some.
-No, I have to eat in an hour and a half.
-Why? Oh, right.
-For dinner.
I need to take a shower.
-You can shower first. You have to go.
-Right.
Here.
-I found another one.
-Okay.
He'll want to talk to her before she goes.
-Right. I wish he does.
-Yeah.
I'm leaving.
-Just talk to her.
-Do it now.
-Do it.
-Talk to her.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
-You're going?
-Bye.
I'll take this upstairs.
Come on!
Just talk for five minutes.
But you can tell from his face
how he feels.
-He has to talk to her.
-He needs to. She wants to hear it.
I had a few opportunities to talk
to Ji-woo before she left for her date,
but I didn't do it on purpose.
I just thought it would…
seem too obvious
that I was jealous,
so I tried not to show it.
-You should!
-You have to show it, Jung-yun.
-You should.
He's still clueless about this.
You're supposed to show her how you feel.
The timing is important too.
That was the right moment.
He's wearing perfume.
I feel like today's date
is really important.
It is.
Se-yeon always keeps his bed
neat and tidy.
-But it's messy today.
-It is.
That says how anxious
he is about his date.
-I think so.
-I'm excited for this.
-Hello.
-Welcome.
JI-WOO & SE-YEON'S DATE
Are you hungry?
-Yes, I think I'll really enjoy the food.
-Right?
What kind of workout did you do?
Me? I ran a bit…
-Is there a gym nearby?
-Yes.
There are these bands.
You know what they are?
What is that?
Resistance bands for exercising.
Oh, right. You use it like this.
-Right? And what else?
-Well…
-I did many things.
-Sounds like you did.
You were out a long time.
-Didn't I come back quickly?
-No. The food…
-You waited for me?
-Yes.
Oh, really?
Of course I waited to eat together.
What did you eat with Jung-yun yesterday?
Yesterday? We had Japanese food.
-Like an izakaya?
-Yes.
-I see.
-We had Nagasaki champon,
sushi,
and stir-fried beef with bean sprouts.
-Are we here?
-This must be it.
It's really close by.
-This is it, right?
-Let's go.
Thank you.
What else did you do today?
I really didn't do much, but time flew by.
Right?
But it seems like everything happens
in the evening at House 20.
-Right, that's when everyone goes out.
-Yes.
That's why we're here.
It's when things happen.
Why do you keep smiling?
What? It's nothing.
It's just funny when you think about it.
-Why are you smiling?
-What?
Why are you smiling?
Same reason as you.
I see.
Where would you like the pasta?
-In the middle.
-Can you just put it here?
It looks delicious. Eat up.
-You too.
-This looks good.
-Here, let me.
-It's okay.
It has scallops too.
-It was shrimp, scallop something.
-Let's eat.
-Thank you.
-Let's just…
-Take it from the dish?
-Yes.
-Isn't it good?
-The scallops are really good.
-This is great.
-This is really delicious.
Is this too big? Should I slice it?
Here, open up.
I like this better too.
Right?
Se-yeon is really bold.
He's bold once he makes up his mind.
Right.
-What are you doing?
-I can see you through the glass.
You're inside my glass.
-You see me?
-Yes.
This is so good.
This tastes good. Peppermint tea.
It smells nice.
It feels different
being outside like this.
Right.
Everyone's been asking me what we were
talking about for so long yesterday.
-The girls?
-Yes.
They said we talked for two hours.
What did you say?
That we were just talking
about meaningless stuff.
It'd be weird to tell them
all the details.
"Meaningless stuff"?
-I mean, I didn't say…
-Meaningless?
I couldn't tell them
we were winking at each other.
Why not? You could.
-All right. I'll tell them next time.
-No.
-Let's be secretive.
-Okay. Sure.
-It'll be our secret.
-Yes, our secret.
What kind of person are you
when you're in a relationship?
When I'm getting to know someone,
I'm pretty cautious and careful.
I usually don't make it that obvious.
It's actually pretty hard for me
to show my feelings.
But I did it with you.
-You should know.
-I know.
But back then,
I had no idea.
I also talk to guys for a long time
before I start dating them.
The longest time was more than six months.
It takes me months to open up to someone.
What are you like when you date someone?
Me?
I am a bit cute.
-You act cute?
-Yes, but not intentionally.
I just start acting like that
without realizing it.
So you act cute.
-Doesn't it seem like I would?
-Not at all…
-Do you think I'll be mean?
-I'm not sure.
How cute do you get?
It drives the guys crazy.
-Really?
-Yes.
All right. I'm not sure.
I'm curious, what's your ideal type?
Well, I like bright people.
And someone I can talk to easily
and who shares my sense of humor.
During my date with Ji-woo,
it seemed like
the more I got to know her,
the more I felt she was my ideal type.
I was really happy.
-I almost winked at you.
-Me too.
I almost did it without thinking.
I had fun spending time with Jung-yun,
but I felt pretty disappointed.
My date with Se-yeon
made me feel much happier,
and it felt like a real date.
Se-yeon seems to like Ji-woo a lot.
He was acting a bit shy in front of her.
I can see that he likes her a lot,
but I can't tell how Ji-woo feels.
To me, this is going to be a decision
between a relationship
where she feels loved
and a relationship with someone
she likes more.
You're right.
I think Ji-woo would prefer to date
a guy she likes more.
I'm not sure about that.
You're cute.
-Me?
-What?
-Am I cute?
-Yes.
It's cool how your nostrils flare.
-It…
-My nostrils?
My nostrils…
Did I just flare my nostrils?
We talked so much today, didn't we?
-Wasn't it fun?
-Yes.
-Wasn't it nice?
-It was.
-Yes, it was so nice.
-It was really nice.
-It's easy to talk to you.
-You too.
-Then I'm kind of your ideal type, right?
-What?
-Someone you can talk to easily.
-Right.
You're right.
You are my ideal type.
-You totally are.
-Really?
Yes, your looks too.
Seriously…
I wonder what the others are doing?
ONE HOUR LATER
Are you done?
Take me home.
-Why?
-Take me home.
-You know what's funny though?
-What?
I feel like they're playing with me.
Why?
I mean, then he shouldn't have
made it sound like he liked me.
It's so mean.
I just wanted to enjoy my time here.
-I know.
-But they messed with my feelings and…
Subtitle translation by: Songmi