SE-YEON
JUNG-YUN
SEO-YEONG
SEO-HYEON
SANG-WON
HEE-JI
JI-MIN
YE-RIN
JI-WOO
PYEONG-SEOK
NINETEEN TO TWENTY
-Last time, I talked to Ye-rin in here.
-Really? What did you talk about?
-That I can't tell you.
-Oh, sorry.
-Okay. Let's talk.
-Sure.
Finally.
-And so the battle begins.
-Isn't that Se-yeon's bed?
-I don't know much about you.
-Right.
Because we weren't that close
when you first came to school.
-Right.
-We're closer now.
-We got closer after cooking class.
-Right?
I like spending time with you
because I feel like we have good banter.
It's fun to be with you.
-And you're pretty.
-How can--
I thought you were really pretty.
-What?
-What's he doing?
-That was unexpected.
-Just like that?
-Ji-woo must be so confused.
-He's going so fast.
I thought you were pretty
when we first met.
How was my first impression?
You were very pretty.
-Really?
-You were pretty.
I kind of fell for you.
-I can't believe it.
-I fell for you.
I liked you ever since then.
I wanted to approach you,
but Jung-yun was faster.
-So I was just watching.
-Really?
-Yeah. I have feelings for you.
-I had no idea.
-That's cool.
-Cool?
If you hadn't told me,
I would've never known.
I'm actually very shy.
I've never done this with anybody before.
-That's crazy.
-Right?
I'm telling you because I thought
I should tell you how I feel.
I want to get to know you better
by going on dates.
-I'd love that.
-Now that you know how I feel,
-I hope we can talk more often.
-Sounds good.
I seriously had no idea.
Really? We've never had
a serious conversation before.
-We never had a chance to.
-So you had no idea.
-I want to go on the dream date with you.
-Okay.
If I ask you, will you say yes?
-Of course.
-Then I'll…
-This is funny.
-I'll walk fast.
I'll move super fast and write my name.
Sure. Okay.
-Let's go on a date.
-Yeah.
Think about what you want to do.
Let's go on the dream date.
When should we go?
I have a date with Se-yeon tomorrow.
I'm free after that.
The day after tomorrow
-or any days after that.
-Really?
It's a shame
that you have a date tomorrow.
I'm going to
try to get closer to you.
-So give me a chance, okay?
-Sure.
This is crazy.
I never imagined this would happen.
This is interesting.
He finally confessed the feelings
he had for her since school.
-And he did it in broad daylight.
-I know. I didn't see it coming.
-I thought he'd do it while he's drunk.
-It was unexpected.
He confessed his feelings to Ji-woo.
I wonder how Ji-woo received it.
She's just surprised.
She had no idea. She was thankful.
That's all.
She looked more excited
when Se-yeon confessed.
-Right.
-Yeah.
She was happy about it. She was excited.
I mean, we could feel it too.
But now she's just…
-Is it because it's daytime?
-That's what I was thinking.
Is it because there was no alcohol?
Well, it's a pretty long story.
Ye-rin was the one I liked the most.
But after coming here,
I keep seeing Ji-woo
and Jung-yun together.
It doesn't make me feel so good.
It's been bothering me.
So I thought I should have
an honest conversation about this.
Ye-rin told me not to worry, but…
-Being honest is best.
-Yeah, I told her my honest feelings.
Ji-woo and I talked for a long time, too.
And we told each other how we feel.
Even though I confessed how I felt,
I still can't organize my thoughts.
-I see.
-I don't know what my heart wants.
-It's hard. It's a lot to handle.
-Yeah.
-Didn't you have ramyeon yesterday too?
-Yes.
You had cup noodles, right?
The two Ye-rin wants are all there.
Oh, you're right.
-You're right.
-Pyeong-seok and Se-yeon.
Do you want a bowl?
-A bowl?
-Yes.
Are you giving me some?
-You… You want this?
-Yes.
Sure.
Thank you.
-I suddenly feel like drinking.
-Me too.
You can go if you're done.
-What?
-Weren't you going to get up?
-No. You want me to?
-Then I'm going to stay.
-What?
-I'm going to stay.
-What? You want me to leave?
-No.
Does anyone want this?
This is really good.
It's so hot here.
I'm going outside. It's too hot.
-Really?
-It's too hot.
After Se-yeon and I talked, we agreed
to not let this situation burden us.
But we feel more burdensome
than before.
Ever since that day,
I get the feeling
Se-yeon is trying to keep a distance
from me.
I'm a bit disappointed,
and I'm not sure what I should do.
Want to go to the basement?
-Is everyone else downstairs?
-Yes.
-They're all playing a game.
-What game? We should go play too.
Let's go. Are you coming?
-Why not?
-You go first. I'll go after this.
-Got it.
-Let me wash my hands.
Se-yeon, are we still going
on a date tomorrow?
-What?
-Are we going on a date?
Have you decided where you want to go?
Already?
-You said that yesterday too.
-I know. I…
Think about it.
Are we going?
Let's talk about it later.
I guess I should say
that I was flustered and a bit stumped.
If I'm being honest,
when Ye-rin, Ji-woo, and I are together,
I don't feel comfortable.
Oh, Ji-woo.
What?
Everything that I see happening right now…
-It's interesting. Very interesting.
-I'm curious about what you think of this.
Yesterday, I…
I heard you talked to Ji-woo.
I plucked up my courage big time.
Yeah.
This is so interesting.
It's like watching a drama.
-What about you?
-What?
-What about me?
What about me?
Don't act like you have nothing…
Since I moved to House 20,
I've been enjoying talking to Pyeong-seok
more and more.
I'm getting more certain
about my feelings for Pyeong-seok.
It keeps getting more fun.
-I wonder if anything will happen to them.
-Something might happen to Pyeong-seok.
That's what I was thinking too.
-Bowling.
-Oh, bowling…
You want to bowl?
How many points can you score?
About 200.
That's high. You must be very good.
The best score I got was 150.
Wait. I have something
to show Pyeong-seok.
Come here.
-What?
-I have something to show you.
It got in my shoes.
Where should we go?
-Come on.
-What is it?
I have something to show you.
It's so messy in here.
Here.
What is it?
Did you think I had something?
I don't have anything.
-Hey. Oh, I thought you were leaving.
-What?
What?
-What are you doing tomorrow?
-Tomorrow?
I got nothing.
Let's go.
-For dinner.
-Should we go? For dinner?
But tonight…
-The dream dates will be revealed tonight.
-Yes.
If the dream date is something I want,
I'm going to take you with me.
-What do you think?
-Okay.
Okay? Then if it's something I want,
I'm going to dash out.
-I got your consent.
-Okay.
-Okay?
But if I don't like it,
then we should just go
for dinner tomorrow.
But if it's something you like
and you want to go with someone else,
-just go ask for her consent.
-Okay.
If it's something you like,
write your name.
-Okay?
-Okay.
-That's it.
That was easy, right?
-You're so cool.
-I know.
You too.
I really didn't see it coming.
If it was just a casual date,
I'd go with no pressure.
But she wants to go on a dream date too.
I had a lot to think about.
If I use my dream date on Se-yeon,
he's going to use his on someone else.
I don't want to watch that happen.
Besides, I also want to
get to know Pyeong-seok better.
So I asked Pyeong-seok out
on the dream date
because I want to figure
this situation out.
So, in the end,
Ye-rin chose Pyeong-seok, not Se-yeon.
Instead of using up her own date,
she is letting Se-yeon think
and choose between her and Ji-woo
for his dream date.
She left that up to him.
And she asked Pyeong-seok.
I think that was smart.
There's no guarantee that Se-yeon will
go with Ye-rin.
It's not guaranteed.
But it'd still make him contemplate.
-She cornered herself.
-Right.
She put herself all the way to the line
in the sand.
-She's putting up a fight there.
-What's going to happen to Pyeong-seok?
Would that sway him or not?
It might sway him a bit
because that was his first time.
Yeah. I think it's like
-an intervention of a third party. Right?
-Yeah, it is.
This is the first time for Pyeong-seok
to have a third party intervene.
-It might be his first time ever.
-Yes.
It's not that he's swayed by Ye-rin,
but he might be swayed by the situation.
-Do you want to try this?
-Sure, but it looks scary.
-It's scary.
-Who wants to start?
I'm nervous.
"I'm one of the top three
prettiest girls here."
No.
-I'm really not.
-It'd be funny
-if it said you're lying.
-Yes. I'm scared.
I'm really not.
LIE
-That was a good one.
-Come on.
Okay, all right.
Ji-woo. Oh, my gosh.
It's because I moved in the middle.
Hee-ji.
"If I arm wrestle with Pyeong-seok,
I'd win."
Pyeong-seok is strong.
I wouldn't win.
It's a lie.
LIE
Pyeong-seok!
-I want to see them try.
-Pyeong-seok!
-Liars.
-I have a question.
"The date last night was boring."
It was fun.
It was really fun!
TRUTH
No wonder you were nervous.
It wasn't easy.
-The last one.
-Sure. I'll ask.
"I want my next date to be
someone other than Sang-won."
-No, it's not like that.
-Okay.
I don't.
It stings. I don't.
LIE
Why are you surprised?
I thought she saw a ghost.
Wait.
This is not true.
-We'll leave you two alone.
-Wait.
Hey. Wait.
-She doesn't want to be here with me.
-Seo-hyeon.
If you're staying here,
check on the order.
-That's not it.
-Call us when it's here.
This keeps saying everything's a lie.
So you have someone in mind
for your next date.
-Wait.
-I'm out.
I'm a woman.
TRUTH
We need to throw this out.
"We need to throw this out."
-That device works well.
-That's very reliable.
Hey, can we go out…
You can. We went out yesterday.
You don't remember
what happened yesterday?
-I remember.
-You don't remember, do you?
I remember.
-I sulked because you didn't respond.
-So you remember.
Is there anybody you want to go on a date
with besides me?
-No.
-What if you include me?
It's a secret.
-What did you talk about yesterday?
-Yesterday?
About how Se-yeon feels.
-I heard it too.
-You did?
We had a beer outside.
You must have been busy then.
I was surprised.
-Why? How did you feel at the time?
-Me?
It is what it is.
That's it?
So is that all you talked about?
-That's all you talked about?
-Yes.
I just kept listening and got surprised.
I had no idea.
Who are you going on your dream date with?
Did you decide who?
-The dream date?
-Yes.
Ji-min asked me.
Ji-min?
Ji-min all of a sudden?
He's surprised again.
Ji-min?
I had no idea that Ji-min would do that.
I was surprised.
I had no idea.
You're busy.
So what if I'm busy?
If you're busy…
I don't know.
Have fun.
Seriously…
You always… You're such a fool.
-Me?
-Yes.
He should've told her not to go.
She wants to hear that he's jealous.
That she should go with him.
But when Jung-yun said that,
he didn't actually mean what he said.
Perhaps he didn't know.
He's heartbroken.
But she definitely likes
Jung-yun the most.
Yes, I can tell.
This is great.
"You're such a fool."
-That's such a great expression.
-"You're such a fool."
"You're such a fool."
-You have to turn your head and say it.
-"Fool. You have no idea how I feel."
-Yeah.
Let's go.
YE-RIN & JI-MIN'S DATE
-What?
Right. They decided to go to eat.
Oh, right.
Put your seatbelt on.
Bowling is such a difficult sport.
Let's make it look cool.
-Make it look cool.
-Yeah, cool.
-Make me say, "Ye-rin, you look so cool."
-"Did you fall for me?"
"Ye-rin, I fell for you!"
I'll make you fall for me with bowling.
-Bowling.
-It's going to be fun.
What do you like about Ji-woo?
I don't really know about girls,
-For me…
-because I'm also a girl.
Ji-woo has a really innocent look.
-Yes.
-She looks like a cat.
We have good banter.
Yes.
So it's easy to talk to her.
She's charming.
It's important to know
why you like someone.
-Why do you like him?
-I don't know.
Because he's hot?
You think that I'd fall for somebody
because they're hot?
-It's not about looks--
-But he is hot.
-Se-yeon?
-Yes, when someone's good-looking,
you fall for them easily.
You can't help it.
You can't just look at
what's on the inside.
So you don't need to be like that.
Just be honest.
The thing is,
I don't need to feel this way.
There's no need for me to feel bad.
But I feel bad for my number one
to become number two.
I believe I shouldn't feel that way here.
-Right. This place is…
-It's a battlefield.
-You don't know what will happen.
-Choi.
-Lee.
-Choi… Cross.
-Cross.
One more time in sync.
You say it.
-Lee.
-Choi.
-Cross.
-Cross. Okay.
I'm hungry.
Get some alcohol.
BOWLING ALLEY
I haven't been to the bowling alley
for so long.
-Why don't you go first?
-Sure.
-Show me what you've got.
-Want to see?
Yeah.
Good luck. Go for a strike.
Come on.
-I'm terrible.
-You're amazing.
Wait. Let me just…
Oh, no.
Show me what you've got.
Gosh, that was too…
I haven't played in a while.
It's okay.
-I'm surprisingly terrible.
-I might win.
Why am I so terrible?
No way.
-I might win.
-Well, there's nothing I can do about it.
-Watch me.
-Good luck.
But why…
Hey.
That's what you call talent.
Why are you so good?
Good job.
Show me what you got.
You really showed me.
-Oh, my god.
-I showed you.
-You're so cool.
-It's a strike.
Really? Seriously?
-Awesome.
-I knew it.
That was a mistake.
Nice!
-Bam!
-That was good.
They look okay so far, right?
They look like friends.
Se-woon, you don't look like you agree.
-He crossed his arms.
-What do you think?
I don't think it meant anything really.
-Right?
-Honestly, that's what I think.
-It's their first time bowling together.
-Me, too.
I mean, they're playing a sport right now.
It's hard to to know what they're feeling.
-They need to talk.
-I'm excited for their dinner.
Something might happen.
Nothing is certain.
This is one scary show.
One minute together and things start
to head in a different direction.
Spending time is important.
JUNG-YUN & JI-WOO'S DATE
-What's that look on your face?
-What?
What's that look on your face?
-I'm just thinking.
-About?
-Nothing.
-What?
Tell me.
I'll tell you later.
I want to know.
I have another question.
-What?
-Before I got here,
-Yes.
-was there anyone you were interested in?
Back then, I didn't have anyone.
I mean, it's not that I didn't
have anyone. They were just… You know.
Just friends?
Yes.
Then am I the first?
-To have feelings?
-What? Yes.
That's crazy.
I thought you weren't interested in me.
-Really?
-You never looked at me.
Because I couldn't.
-Why not?
-What?
How can I stare at you?
At the time, I thought
no one was interested in me.
But now…
I had no idea.
-Did you know?
-About what?
-That they like me…
-I didn't know.
Yeah, me neither. I didn't know.
-So you found out yesterday?
-Yes.
That's why you just said,
"It is what it is"?
I mean, it is…
But it is what it is.
-It happens.
-Yeah.
It is…
How did you feel when they told you?
At first, I was very surprised.
And I thought it was kind of cool because…
Everyone was already kind of saying
that you and I are already set.
Se-yeon and Ji-min thought that too.
If I were them, I would've given up.
I was impressed by their courage.
-Show some courage.
-This will drive him crazy.
-Jung-yun, win her over.
-Show some courage.
-Hold her hand.
-Oh, you scared me.
-Sorry, I got too invested.
-I thought you said something else.
CANDLE STUDIO
-Hello.
-Do you want to put on an apron?
-Yes.
Can you tie…
-I'll tie it for you.
-Sure.
-Done.
-Done? I'll tie yours.
All done.
-Have you made candles before?
-No, it's my first time.
-Is it your first time?
-Yes.
Here are some fragrances.
-Okay.
-You can open them like this
-and smell them.
-Okay.
You can each pick out a fragrance.
-You can try smelling them.
-I like fragrances.
-Remove the cap.
-The cap.
No wonder I couldn't smell anything.
If it's too strong,
open the small cap on the top.
-Why did you do it like…
-Oh, I didn't know.
What? I like this one.
-Smell this.
-Okay.
What do you think?
-Should I set it aside?
-It's nice.
-Is it nice?
-It's vanilla.
I like this too.
-Let's go with this.
-This?
-Yes.
-Okay.
Nine.
Eleven. It's perfect.
This one looks special.
-I'll use one of those.
-You immediately…
-Do I cut it?
-Yeah.
It's cute.
I like it.
Let's make it similar.
I'll go for the blue one.
So cute…
-So good.
-Indeed.
-I'll add some of this.
-Okay.
This is it.
Done.
Me too.
This is really cute.
Cheers. Yours looks nice.
I went to the table tennis club
and practiced on my own.
I was feeling very conflicted.
And I had a lot of mixed emotions as well.
When I play table tennis,
I don't think of anything else,
so I wanted to play.
What should we get?
-Sushi?
-Sure.
-Can you tell me now?
-What?
-Can you tell me?
You said you'd tell me later.
-What's that look on your face?
-What?
What's that look on your face?
-I'm just thinking.
-About?
I'll tell you later.
Well, not yet.
-Your draft beer is here.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Bon appétit.
-Looks good.
-Soy sauce.
I've never had this before.
-It's good.
-Is it?
I'm starving. Let's eat.
I'll have some sushi.
-Bon appétit.
-Do you like it?
-Yes.
I like it too.
I'm curious.
-What?
-What you were going to say.
Are we going to communicate by breathing?
I just have a lot to think
about right now.
I'm serious.
Q. WHAT WERE YOU GOING TO SAY?
It's not that I had something to say.
I just wanted to say
we should go on a date again next time.
But I couldn't say it in front of her.
Jung-yun never says how he really feels.
It was frustrating.
-It's frustrating. It really is.
-Other boys are being so straightforward.
He must have a lot on his mind.
Where are you going tomorrow?
We're deciding it later.
You're busy.
You keep saying that.
Do you like being busy?
You're not happy?
No.
Because…
I was so surprised.
And you feel conflicted
when you're surprised.
-You feel conflicted?
-Yes. I hate it.
So you feel conflicted.
That happens.
You really don't say much.
I can't figure you out.
It's rare to meet someone like me. Even if
I don't talk, you can still read me.
-I don't know if you don't talk.
-But don't you know even if I don't talk?
-Honestly…
-I need to hear the details.
-People should follow their hearts.
-Is that so?
Like Se-yeon and Ji-min.
They follow their hearts.
I should…
I should learn from them.
Follow my heart…
It's good.
When they told you how they were feeling,
did you have a change of heart?
Nothing changed.
I talked to Ji-min about it.
That you are…
number one in my heart.
That didn't change,
but my perspectives have changed.
Before Se-yeon and Ji-min confessed,
you're all I cared about,
but after Se-yeon confessed,
I started to pay attention to him.
It's the same for Ji-min too.
That's it for now.
Let's order more.
-You want to drink more?
-Are you okay?
-Do you think you can drink one more?
-Yes.
Is there a stronger one?
Didn't you say
you wanted to try a highball?
Hee-ji said it's tasty.
-Sure.
-I trust Hee-ji.
We'll get two Suntory Highballs.
-Two Suntory Highballs?
-Yes.
Okay. Coming right up.
Excuse me. Two Suntory Highballs.
-Thank you.
Enjoy.
Cheers.
-Cheers.
-Enjoy.
-How do you think your date will go?
-Tomorrow?
I never talked to Se-yeon before
until yesterday.
That was my first time.
I think we're going to talk a lot.
We'll probably eat something.
Don't have too much fun.
-How much fun then?
-Not too much.
-Not too much?
-Yes.
-He finally said it.
-Just a little bit.
But it's not completely satisfactory.
Yet Ji-woo smiled.
Still, that's a big improvement for him.
That's good enough.
You're not going to come back drunk
tomorrow, are you?
What if I do?
You'll be back before 11 p.m., right?
Are you getting jealous?
Do you have a lot on your mind
because you're jealous?
-Come on.
-She asked him straight up.
I dare you to say no.
-Don't just laugh.
-Please say you're jealous.
Just say it.
Do you have a lot on your mind
because you're jealous?
Are you getting anxious?
-Not that much?
-What?
I'm really full.
What?
-He has to tell her.
-He's got to tell her.
Whether it's a date or a friend,
you have to talk.
Are you thinking again?
What if I go out on the day you're home?
That could happen.
Because I'm going out when you're not.
Everyone can go on a date here.
If you want to go on a date
or there's someone
you want to get to know, you can go.
It sounds like I'm giving you permission,
but I don't mind.
-But you need to talk to me about it.
-Okay.
Before or after your date.
If you don't, I'll be mad.
I was very straightforward
just now, right?
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
You frustrating punk.
No, you're not frustrating.
That's just the way you are. I respect it.
But you need to take responsibility
for your frustrating actions. Got it?
It means you shouldn't do that.
-Yes.
-She's scaring him.
"Take responsibility."
"If you keep frustrating me,
I might choose someone else."
"It's up to you."
-Ji-woo is…
-She is just…
She's very patient.
Ji-woo is charming and shrewd.
-I know, that's what makes her charming.
-Jung-yun is like,
"I don't want you to go.
If you go, I'll be jealous."
He wants to say,
"So, I don't want you to go."
-But if he says it,
-It's right up here.
he doesn't know what'll happen.
He's not sure how she'll receive it.
He keeps beating around the bush
because he's not confident.
-That shows he's still young.
-Right.
-He doesn't want to intervene.
-He lacks experience.
Right. He really doesn't have a lot
of experience, so I think he's scared.
This is bad.
It feels like Ji-woo
is helping Jung-yun grow.
I might be getting ahead of myself,
they might not work out,
but things like this pile up
and bring some kind of change.
-When will Se-yeon be back?
-After training.
Maybe around 7 or 8 p.m.
Do you want to eat?
Are we ordering in or cooking?
I'll be the chef today.
You can rest.
-Okay.
-Sit down. Grab your seat.
I'll be the chef today.
What's for dinner tonight, chef?
-I can't tie the apron.
-Let me help you.
She was far away.
-She ran to him.
-She ran to him right away.
Yes, yes.
Okay.
All right. It's perfect.
Ramyeon is also a proper dish, okay?
I don't think ramyeon is a proper dish.
-But bibimmyeon is.
-Bibimmyeon is.
-Bibimmyeon is beyond that. You feel me?
-Yes.
Do we get to try your
thinly sliced pork belly?
-Don't be surprised.
-Chef Kim.
-Oh, my.
-Oh, my goodness.
They're so happy.
It's peaceful over here.
-I hope nothing more happens.
-It's therapeutic.
Let's have wine.
-Oh, sure.
-Fruity?
Sure.
We're ready to place an order.
I'll take your order.
Do you have any questions for me?
-You and Ji-woo.
-Ji-woo?
I can kind of tell that
you are interested in her.
I can see that.
Right. I don't care anymore.
You don't care if everyone knows?
Well, nothing is set in stone.
-True.
-I don't know yet. My heart can change.
I might start liking you more.
Me more?
-You want to try?
-It's possible.
What on earth is he saying
all of a sudden?
Keep going.
-Ji-min is…
-Su-hyun, you were right.
-Things can change in just one minute.
-I told you.
Hold on.
This is refreshing.
It feels refreshing to hear you say
something like that.
Really?
You had a talk with Pyeong-seok earlier.
I was curious what you talked about.
-With Pyeong-seok?
-Yes, tell me.
Pyeong-seok's a new student.
When he first arrived,
I didn't have any feelings
for him whatsoever.
I was like, "New student. Cool."
But after moving to House 20,
I wanted to get to know him more.
So I decided to approach him first
and asked what he's doing tomorrow.
And that we should have dinner together.
-So are you going on a date?
-Yes, just a date.
Awesome.
Bam.
When I first saw you,
I thought you'd be the last person
I got close with.
Or that we wouldn't become friends
until we graduate.
How come?
You seemed a bit cold.
I thought that way
because you seemed cold.
Of course I think you're pretty.
-And--
-It's too late now, Ji-min.
No, it's not too late.
Pretty, but with a cold vibe.
That's what I thought.
But after we became close,
out of all the people here,
I have the most fun when I'm with you.
I'm being honest.
-Me too.
-After we became close,
I realized you're very funny.
You have good reactions.
And you're kind.
Thanks.
Even at this very moment,
I think it's kind of crazy.
On our first day, I probably had no idea
we'd become so close.
That's what I thought too.
I never thought
we'd become close,
but on the second or third day,
I realized our sense of humor is similar.
Then I knew we could be friends.
I thought I should get close to you.
When we first met,
I opened the door,
and you were the first person I saw.
It was you.
For me, your eyes were super fierce.
So when I first entered the classroom,
your face was all I saw.
-"Oh, he's handsome."
-Really?
FIRST DAY AT SCHOOL 19
Oh, my goodness.
-Hi.
-Hello.
Hello.
When I first opened the door
and walked in,
the first boy I saw was Lee Ji-min.
"Oh, he's handsome."
I want to get to know Ye-rin.
When I first saw her, she seemed cold.
I wonder what she'd be like
when we become friends.
It was like, "I want to get to know him."
"We have the same sense of humor."
And now, it's like,
"This is awesome."
We're best friends. Right?
-They're not friends.
-They're not.
-Because there is
-There's something.
a slight sense of push and pull
between them.
It's very subtle, though.
They say they're friends,
-but they're definitely not friends.
-Right.
-That's why I'm excited.
-They're not friends.
-I'll pour you a glass.
-Okay.
Oh, look at this.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
-The vibe is so nice. Right?
-Yes.
-I really like cozy places.
-The vibe is nice.
-Yeah.
-They have this too.
-What about me? I'm here too.
-Yes.
You make it the best.
What?
What was that?
What's it like to be on a date with me?
The best decision you've ever made, right?
Of course.
-No regrets.
-Me too.
At first, I was planning on spending time
with you as friends,
but this is even better.
-Really?
-Yes.
Why is he so shy?
Oh, my.
I told you. You can never be certain
about anything here.
You're my first date
after I became an adult.
So you're my first date.
-Here's your order.
-Thank you.
This is seasoned brisket.
-You can enjoy it with salad.
-Looks good.
-The cold pasta tastes better mixed.
-Okay.
Enjoy.
-Thank you.
-Brisket.
-Yes.
-Let me tie my hair first.
-Wine, nice.
Wine.
I need to tie my hair before eating.
Does it look okay?
No?
Take your time.
Good?
Does it look good?
-You look pretty.
-It is? Let's eat.
He fell for her.
He fell for her right there.
-He can't take his eyes off her.
-He totally fell for her.
I don't know what's going to
happen between them.
-Done. Bon appétit.
-Bon appétit.
-Cheers.
-How do I drink with this glass?
I don't know.
This is the least bitter among
all the ones I've tried.
-Yes. It's sweet and tasty.
-Let's enjoy.
-It's so good.
-Yes.
Do you not like it?
Help me, brisket.
Help her.
Being an adult is hard.
Drinking is hard.
-I like it.
-Really?
Hey, excuse me.
Are you drunk?
-No.
-The cap.
I'm not drunk. I didn't know.
It was closed.
How can I be so dumb?
-What if…
-Yes.
-I go on a dream date…
-Say that I ask you out on that date.
-Okay.
Would that feel different
from when I asked you yesterday?
It's completely different.
Really?
Honestly, as I spend time with you,
I feel different about you.
Yesterday, we just wanted to go
to the amusement park.
But we were both feeling uncertain.
So, when you sent me a sign,
I was grateful.
It meant you'd use your dream date on me.
Right.
If you ask me now, I'll be delighted.
But no pressure. I wouldn't mind
even if you go with Ji-woo.
When do you plan to go on your dream date?
I haven't thought about it.
If there's something I want to do,
I'd do anything to do it.
It's completely up to you,
but just so you know,
I'm willing to go if you ask me.
But if I ask you, we can never go again.
-Right.
-Then you get an option to go with Ji-woo.
I won't let that happen.
You're jealous.
-I like it.
-You can get kind of jealous, right?
Super jealous.
I think I like you more now.
Me?
Yes.
Are you starting to like me more
right now?
Yeah.
I am. What about you?
Nice.
The more I think that we get along,
we do get along well.
It's perfect. We have fun when it's fun,
and we're serious when we have to be.
I'm suddenly worried about Ji-woo.
You are
-starting to like me more, right?
-Yes.
I wish you like me more than Se-yeon.
I wish I can beat him.
You could.
-I think he will have a change of heart.
-Yeah.
Because he's getting tired.
-Now he feels stable.
-Right.
He felt the joy that comes from stability.
This is fun.
I was curious.
I wanted to know whether this feeling
I have for you is friendship or love.
I was kind of surprised.
You looked pretty
when you were tying your hair.
Can I untie my hair and tie it again?
-Did you finish it?
-Do you want to finish it now?
-Yes.
-Do you want to share what's left?
It's full.
Oh, no.
-This is bad.
-We'll go back to the house so drunk.
I don't mind.
I can't see clearly.
Try your best.
It feels good getting tipsy.
Give me your glass.
It's barley tea.
I can't see clearly either.
Your aim is way off right now.
That's good.
Okay, I feel a bit more sober now.
The others will be surprised to see
how drunk we are.
-Let's go.
-Let's go home.
Yes, let's go.
It's going the way we want.
-I was totally immersed.
-That was so entertaining.
I think there's going to be a big change
in Ji-min's heart.
Today, they were like,
"Let's grab dinner, buddy."
-But after she tied her hair…
-That was no joke.
Do guys really like that stuff?
-We go crazy for it. Seriously.
-Really?
-Is that true?
-I don't know.
But if they're already attracted
to each other,
-it feels…
-You go crazy?
Personally, if a girl ties her hair
in front of me, I can't help but stare.
-You go crazy?
-Like Ji-min?
-Not that serious.
-Ji-min was…
Like Su-hyun said,
it only takes a split second.
So much can change in a split second.
Ji-min is honest, and Ye-rin is too.
-They're just…
-They were perfect.
-They were honest with each other.
-Right. I like this couple.
-I enjoyed watching them.
-Right.
Be careful.
-What's going on?
-What?
-Why are you back so early?
-What? I think we were out for 3 hours.
Someone's here.
Who?
Is it Ji-min and Ye-rin?
Why did they…
-Did you drink?
-A lot.
You drank a lot.
-What?
-What's wrong?
Is Ye-rin drunk?
Hee-ji, you should go help her.
Are you okay?
Ye-rin.
-He can barely stand.
-We drank a whole bottle.
-What's up with you?
-I don't smell alcohol on him.
I can sober up.
-Be quiet.
-Okay.
Where to?
Ji-min, let's go.
-I'll be upstairs.
-Okay.
Get changed. Wash up with cold water
and rest on your bed.
Okay, okay.
How much did you drink?
EXCESSIVE ALCOHOL CONSUMPTION IS HARMFUL
IF YOU'RE CAUGHT DRINKING TOO MUCH,
YOU'LL LOSE YOUR DREAM DATE
-Come here.
-That's right.
-I agree.
-I agree. Count me in.
Who wrote…
-It just popped up.
It says right there.
You'll lose your dream date
if you drink too much.
Does two people sharing one bottle
count as excessive drinking?
-It means don't get drunk.
-Know your limit.
So stop before you get drunk?
You need to be in bed.
-Ye-rin, just eat this.
-That looks good.
-Eat just this.
-Okay.
Don't put any alcohol near her.
Thank you.
You should eat to sober up fast.
You've got to stay alert
when you're not home.
I only had one glass and a half.
That might be too much for you.
-It all depends on the person.
-He's right.
You want more? You seem to like it.
Eat mine. You can finish it.
-Drink only half a glass of wine, okay?
-Okay.
Not full, but only half.
Yes.
-Do you want to take a shower?
-Yes.
I going to take a shower.
-Don't sleep in the shower.
-Okay.
Let's go.
SANG-WON & SEO-HYEON'S DREAM DATE
-It's going to be so much fun.
-I know.
Lotte World Adventure?
-They're finally going.
-I'm so jealous.
-It'll be so pretty at night.
-Yeah.
And it's just the two of them.
No way. I can't believe this.
-I signed up as soon as I saw it.
-I know.
Oh, your dream date
will be with somebody else.
Hey.
-What…
-Let's talk in the car.
-Hello.
-I'm so excited.
-Me too.
-Are you excited?
-Totally.
-I'm glad.
-This is going to be fun.
How do I look today?
You're wearing black, white, and denim.
-Like it?
-Your fashion. I do.
-What about me? Not my fashion.
-Of course I like you.
This is intense.
-What?
-Is that how you…
Okay.
-I should stay on my toes.
-Why?
I should stay on my toes.
-Is there something you want to do there?
-Me?
I want to take a picture there.
That place where everyone takes a picture.
-The carousel or the castle?
-The castle.
-There was always a long line.
-It's very long.
I never got to take a picture there.
Just two of us there?
-Need any help?
-I'm good.
Can you just clean the table?
What? You want to take over?
I'll do it.
Wash your hands and go.
-I'm really going to hit the shower.
-Go shower.
Chef Kim.
Chef Kim, are you tired?
-You look tired.
-A little.
Your ears are still red.
Why are my ears so red?
Why are your ears always red?
I wonder why.
That was really good today.
I didn't eat much, but I'm full.
Right.
You were good at cooking.
Do you cook often?
-Sometimes.
-Sometimes?
Sometimes.
I like trying recipes.
It doesn't really roll up.
You're so muscular.
-Pyeong-seok is…
-Oh, Pyeong-seok.
Pyeong-seok.
-That's nothing special…
-But that makes your heart flutter.
Thank you.
It won't go up easily.
It's getting clean.
Final check.
-They look great together.
-Why do they look like newlyweds?
-They're driving me crazy.
-Tell me about it.
They're so cute.
Hello. I am…
-I'm…
-We're on our way to go bowling.
We're going bowling.
Doesn't it sound fun?
He's going through the pictures.
That's cute. He's looking at the pictures
from the date before going to bed.
He is…
He's so innocent.
How was it?
-Is this everyone?
-What are you doing?
Let me get changed first.
-You're finally up.
-Are you going to take a shower?
-Did you sleep?
-Me? No, I was awake the whole time.
-And that was changed!
-Did you drink?
-It changed.
-What changed?
Come here. Did you see the warning?
I think it changed 'cause of us.
It says we'll lose our dream date
if we drink too much.
I think we caused that.
Don't drink too much.
I couldn't even walk straight.
-Do you even remember?
-What? Remember what?
-Yeah, I remember.
-You sure you didn't forget everything?
-I didn't.
-Your brain is reset.
Is my heart supposed to pound this fast
when I'm drunk? You know?
I had to touch my chest. I didn't know.
-Pounding.
-I could hear it.
It was like this.
When I got undressed to take a shower,
my whole body was red.
I was so surprised.
-I went through the photos.
-Yeah.
I found this photo.
Did I send you all the photos?
-I sent you this.
-No.
-This one.
-That's all you sent me.
-How come you look good in that picture?
-This one?
It's like the goldfish meme.
I should stop eating.
I'll be chubby when I leave this place.
Chubby.
-It's dangerous.
-Chubby.
That's just adorable.
You want to go upstairs?
Upstairs? Anywhere is fine.
-She's watching.
-She's watching them leave.
-It's obvious that Ye-rin still…
-She still cares.
-She seems to care more about Se-yeon.
-Yeah.
It's hard to describe how I feel today.
What is this feeling?
I've never had this feeling before
my whole life.
Nineteen years. Twenty now.
I don't know what my heart wants.
I feel like I'm on edge.
That must be complicated.
-It's really is.
-Yeah.
This is actually for the best.
I'm glad I talked to Ye-rin
about it first.
If I hadn't talked to her
and dragged this out,
she would've kept having feelings for me…
I can tell that something's different
with the two of them.
-But why do I feel
-Yeah.
so confused and conflicted?
I'm still feeling this way
even after telling her how I feel.
I don't know
if I did the right thing yesterday.
Gosh, I don't know.
When you and Hee-ji were talking,
I talked to Ye-rin upstairs.
-Really?
-Yeah.
She asked me to go on a date
with her tomorrow.
-She asked you?
-Yes.
-Ye-rin?
-Really?
-She said she wants to
-get to know everyone.
-Really?
And I thought she meant a regular date.
-Did she mean a dream date?
-Yes.
-Really?
I didn't see that coming.
-Really? The dream date?
-Yes.
I was like, "What's going on?"
The dream date.
What are you going to do
about your dream date?
For my dream date,
I really want to think it through.
Even if I'm not completely sure,
I want to go with someone
I feel somewhat certain about.
Because it means a lot.
I only get one chance.
Right.
Se-yeon was kind of
trying to distance himself from Ye-rin
-until now.
-Yeah, and now he's…
But now that
she's getting close to Ji-min,
he feels…
-He's not happy about it.
-He has mixed feelings.
Don't you think that Ye-rin still
has feelings for Se-yeon?
-I want Ye-rin to be loved.
-Right.
I want her to get over
her feelings for Se-yeon
-and just be with Ji-min.
-Right.
Seo-yeong, are you okay?
Who is it? Oh, it's you.
I'm feeling under the weather.
I guess we can talk.
How are you?
How would you rank the guys
that you like right now?
There's only one at the top.
-Pyeong-seok?
-Yes.
I'm curious.
What do you like about Pyeong-seok?
He's cute.
I love his smile.
And he's shy,
so I become more curious about him.
-I want to get to know him more.
-Because you don't know about him.
I want to know what's on his mind.
I was curious. He was the one
that I was most curious about.
So he made you curious?
-I was curious.
-I see.
And how was Pyeong-seok
when you first started to approach him?
-I kept asking him questions nonstop.
-Yeah.
He was shy.
-I guess he still responded well.
-Yeah.
-I mean, he didn't ignore me or anything.
-I see.
What about you?
At first, I liked Ji-min.
But after talking to him, I realized
he's nothing more than a friend.
There's someone I want to get to know.
-Who?
-Sang-won.
-Sang-won?
-Yes.
I can see why.
-Sang-won is so nice when he talks.
-Yeah, he is.
Because he graduated high school
before we did,
he seems more mature than others.
I mean, it's not like we have to
be attracted to somebody here.
Just focus on having fun.
Right. I want to get to know
Sang-won more.
It's time for a deep talk.
Yeah.
It's fun to watch.
Right?
For you…
It's giving me a headache.
I'm off to the restroom.
-What are you doing tomorrow?
-Tomorrow?
I don't know. No plans yet.
What are you doing tomorrow?
-I think I'll go on a date.
-Ji-woo?
Yeah, they are. I heard earlier.
-What are you doing tomorrow?
-Me? I don't know.
-It's undecided.
-Try going out with other girls.
I'm actually going crazy right now.
Are you tired?
I'm rather confused.
-What's wrong?
-Things are so complicated.
-I'm going up.
-Come up here.
You have something to tell us
about Jung-yun?
I have a question, Ji-woo.
Jung-yun and Se-yeon both
made a move on you at the same time.
-Honestly--
-Do you like him?
-Se-yeon?
-Yes.
I don't know. I found him charming
when he told me about his feelings.
I liked it, and I still do.
But I don't know.
Even though
he confessed his true feelings,
he doesn't look that way at all.
-Because he doesn't express it.
-Because he doesn't.
So, I was like,
"Is what he said true?"
What confuses me even more
is that despite all that,
Jung-yun keeps hiding his feelings.
I can see that he's jealous.
He just keeps sighing.
But if I ask him,
he won't answer.
I want to hear how he feels.
That's normal.
You wonder if he really likes you
or what he's thinking.
My feelings for Jung-yun is way bigger
than my feelings for Se-yeon or Ji-min.
If Jung-yun expresses his heart,
even a little,
I think he'll keep being my number one.
But if I ask him about his feelings,
he says he's shy and avoids answering me.
I heard what Jung-yun said about you.
What? When?
Jung-yun said…
Yes?
Subtitle translation by: Songmi