(SAVE ME)
(Please help me
accept you with all of my heart.)
(I need just a little more time.)
(Until the day the fruit will ripen
to perfection,)
I will wait.
(You should never swallow the pills
Apostle Kang gives you from now on.)
(Listen to me if you want
to save Sang-mi.)
(I feel like there are so many devils
in this place these days.)
Shove her head in there.
(Oh, yes. I remember now.)
(That place is being broadcasted
on the internet these days.)
(What do you mean?)
(Oh, you used to go to a church
in Daegu that just got broadcasted?)
(I bet you're now realizing
whom you guys were messing with.)
(I think they caught Jeong-hun
and took him there.)
I think we should test Sang-mi
(if she's truly capable of becoming)
(our Spiritual Mother.)
With the fire of our Almighty
With his hot fire
Hong So-rin.
I look forward to working with you.
(If you go that way into the forest,)
(you'll get to a stream
with a small bridge.)
(You can meet my friend there
and get help from him.)
(EPISODE 15)
Almighty must love me very much.
I mean, who thought
I would run into you right here?
Aren't I right,
Reporter Hong So-rin?
No! Please forgive me.
Please don't
Gosh Don't kill me.
Please don't kill me!
No! Please don't!
Why did you sneak into
Guseonwon to begin with?
You graduated from a good university
and became a reporter.
If your parents see this,
their hearts will shatter to pieces.
Aren't I right?
I hope you go to the paradise
and gain salvation, Ms. Reporter.
(Dong-cheol, I just got here,)
(but that reporter isn't here.
Something must have happened to her.)
(I'll file a missing person report.)
(If I report her missing,
those jerks will try to bury it again.)
(It might actually give us
a chance to catch them.)
Hello?
(Sang...)
(Hwan...)
Mom?
(It's your mom.)
Are you sure that Reporter Hong
escaped safely?
Yes, but I'm worried
because it seems like
she didn't meet Sang-hwan yet.
For now, let's wait until he calls us.
Excuse me.
Spiritual Mother,
did you see Apostle Kang today?
What is the matter?
She's supposed to be leading
the vigil today.
But she doesn't seem to be here.
I'll be doing it today.
As you all know,
for the last three years,
I was a sinner.
I showed hatred
for the Almighty and the Spiritual Father
in front of you.
-However,
(-Jo Wan-tae isn't here.)
the Almighty and the Spiritual Father
(-Did he...)
-They chose me
as the Spiritual Mother of Guseonwon.
Brothers and Sisters of Guseonwon,
thanks to the Almighty
and the Spiritual Father,
I have become a whole new person.
I am so happy right now.
(He's wearing something different.)
(It's different.)
When I think of meeting the Almighty
next to the Spiritual Father
as the Spiritual Mother,.
my heart feels so warm
that I don't know what to do about it.
-Our wishes will be fulfilled.
-We believe it.
Do you believe that I am the scapegoat
that will help you
get rid of your original sin?
-We believe it.
-Our wishes will be fulfilled.
In that case,
let's give a big round of applause
of gratefulness
to the Almighty and the Spiritual Father
who have blessed everyone here with grace.
(I need to check what he was up to.)
Man-hui, how is Jeong-hun?
(Fortunately, he's fine.)
(I got the medical certificates
as evidence.)
(I'll go to the police station
tomorrow with him.)
All right.
Take good care of him today.
See you at the police station tomorrow.
(All right.)
Bye.
If we make it a big hospital
with a sanatorium,
people will welcome it
and stop opposing it.
This is probably
what Baek Jeong-gi wanted.
If we use him wisely,
we will be competitive with
the henchman and Senator Park,
and we will get a better chance
at earning more votes.
And I think it would be better
to move your wife.
What do you mean?
It seems like Sang-hwan has
made a big fuss at Guseonwon.
They called us.
And it seems like
he's been going to the police
and working with Detective Lee.
Really? I must have overlooked my son,
thinking he was too young to do anything.
If we get a hold of your wife,
Sang-hwan won't be able
to do anything much.
Mom. Mom.
Mom.
Mom. Did you move by yourself?
Your father...
Where is he?
Man-hui.
I need to ask you a favor.
(You just need to help me take my mom
out of the hospital room)
(and take her to my uncle's.)
Okay, I will be there.
See you later.
What? Is there a problem?
I need to go outside for a moment.
Do you have time to watch over him
until I come back?
I'm late for work.
We're only disturbing him
by making noises here.
Let him sleep well.
Let's leave him to rest alone.
Okay.
Spiritual Mother.
Why
are you cleaning this room?
Apostle Jo asked us to clean this room.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Apostle Kang is looking for you.
It's all right. You should go.
It seemed urgent.
In that case, we'll be right back.
Yes.
Did he find her?
I think
something must have happened.
It was like this
when Jeong-gu died.
They cleaned his room afterwards.
Killing someone
is no big deal for these people.
(MUJI DAILY)
(Sang-hwan, I think something
must have happened to the reporter.)
(I'm at Muji Daily.)
(I'll check right away.)
This is what he was wearing
in the morning.
(What is this?)
(KARAOKE BAR, BIXIE)
It's wet.
He did change his clothes.
If you go over the mountain,
you'll find a river with a bridge.
The river.
You really didn't get any calls
from Reporter Hong?
No.
But what is this about?
I know everything.
She escaped from Guseonwon,
and she was going to meet me.
But I can neither find her nor call her.
Is this true?
We need to report her to the police
as a missing person.
The chief of police and Guseonwon
have joined hands,
so they might not process it.
Then write an article about her
going missing after infiltrating
a religious cult undercover
to do a story on them.
The police chief and Guseonwon
have joined hands?
He's not the only one.
My dad too. Everyone is connected.
You mean Governor Han?
Will you really be able
to disclose all this?
You're basically strangling
your father with your own hands.
If I tell you
that I can't do it,
will you be able to bury the truth
fully knowing it?
Hey, Man-hui.
What did you say?
(KARAOKE BAR, BIXIE)
Where's your mind at these days?
Go back to Seoul if you'll keep this up.
What did you do to Mom?
How dare you glare at me like that?
I moved her to a better hospital.
-I was worried about her, so--
-Worried?
Dad.
Do you know what this is?
That's your mom's voice recorder.
That's right.
Why did you bring it?
I must say, you've said
so many things to her.
Remember when I pushed you?
Do you know how it made me feel?
The thrill you get
when you slaughter an animal.
That's when I realized how much I really
hate you.
Dad.
You've done horrible things to Mom,
and you're such a cruel person.
I'll tell the whole world about it.
Sang-hwan.
I think there's been a misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
How can you lie to me again
when there's evidence right here?
Give me that.
No.
Dad.
Don't forget everything you have done
because you'll have
to pay for all of them.
Sang-hwan!
Will you really corner me like this?
Mr. Han.
How can this be happening?
If Sang-hwan finds out
that we're keeping his mom,
he won't be
able to disclose it.
After all this time...
That voice recording
must not be disclosed.
Ji-hui.
Yes.
You and I are on the same boat, you know.
If they take me down,
you'll go down with me.
You got that?
Yes, Mr. Han.
Chief Lee, I need you
to unleash your hound.
Whom do you need to hunt down?
Han Sang-hwan.
My son.
Pardon?
Hello, are you looking for someone?
Oh, did Mr. Jo leave anything here?
Mr. Jo? Who is that?
Mr. Jo Wan-tae.
-Oh, Wan-tae.
-Yes.
He didn't leave anything here.
That's weird. He told me that
he left his wallet here earlier
and asked me to pick it up.
He is a regular here,
but he didn't come today.
I guess he's becoming forgetful
because he's been drinking a lot.
-Sorry to bother you. Take care.
-Wait!
Gosh, you're pretty cute.
You should stay for a drink.
I'll come with Mr. Jo another time.
-I'm sorry.
-Will you do that?
(BIXIE)
Sang-hwan,
(I know that you're looking
for your mom.)
Give us that voice recorder.
(Then you can meet your mom
right away.)
Listen. If you lay
even a finger on my mom,
I'll teach you a lesson.
You got that?
Hey there, prince.
Come on. I think we have
some business to take care of.
Get out of my way.
If you get on my nerves now,
I'll make you regret it.
Just give me that voice recorder,
and you won't have to see me again.
I told you to get out of my way.
You little...
I have to take this to make
some money off of it, okay?
Sang-hwan!
Sang-hwan, are you okay?
By any chance, did you hear
to which hospital my mom was
being transferred
when she was checking out?
Mr. Han's secretary said that
the order came from him,
so we just did it for her.
We don't know anything else.
Sang-hwan.
I'm trying to get elected
as governor again
for your mom.
If I become the governor,
your mother will wake up again.
Three years ago,
I made a wrong choice
because of my mom.
And I couldn't help
Sang-mi
or Dong-cheol.
I don't want
to regret the same thing again.
First,
we need to go to the police
and Guseonwon.
Yes.
Hello.
If you're listening to this,
you must have
done something you shouldn't have.
Father, I have trusted you until the end.
But now I know
that a wrong trust can be dangerous.
Now I know exactly how
it can hurt so many people.
You shouldn't do this.
It's too late.
You should come back tomorrow.
I need to see someone.
Gosh, how dare you!
I said you can't come here.
Let me go.
You two should go now.
But, Spiritual Father...
It's all right.
I have Apostle Im by my side.
-Yes.
Come in.
Sergeant Woo is like a father to me.
When I was young,
my father died in a car accident,
and I lived with my sick mother.
And he even paid for
my university tuition fees.
Is that so?
You must be grateful.
Don't you think so too?
Yes, Sergeant Woo has a pure heart.
That must be why he was chosen
by the Almighty.
You are all crazy.
Pastor Baek, you must know very well
what I am talking about.
If you take advantage of him
again like this,
I won't let it slide.
Do you understand?
Officer Choe,
there must be a misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding?
Apostle Im,
please give us some space.
Of course.
I know that there are dozens of
homeless people
that Sergeant Woo is taking care of.
Do you think it would be okay
if a father-figure like him gets hurt
because of you?
What?
Do you think that's all?
His son and wife would be so shocked.
Do you think that Sergeant Woo
and his family would be
able to withstand the criticism
of the world?
What if
he makes the wrong choice?
Do you think you will be able to
cope with all of this?
(POLICE)
If you really think of him
as your father,
you should go home quietly.
That's the only way you can repay him
for what he has done for you.
It's all right.
Lift your head, and look at me.
Now.
You will be
of great use to the Almighty.
If you listen to me carefully
and finish this job well,
you can get out
and go to paradise.
Do you understand?
I can
get out?
If you go outside, you will see the devil
in the form of a female police officer.
The devil.
Female police officer.
Devil. Female police officer.
Don't be afraid.
You just need to trust me.
Yes, Governor Han.
How have you been?
(Hello,)
you're the Spiritual Father, right?
Why did you call me
at such a late hour?
I came to pray at night,
and you came into my mind.
Really?
You must be so upset
because of the protests
from the villagers.
(The Almighty has told me)
to help you get rid of
such worries
during my prayer.
(Really?)
I heard that many of the villagers
who were protesting
were believers of Guseonwon.
It is my mission to lead
such believers well
in times like this.
Then how do you want me
to show my appreciation?
You crazy scum. Gosh.
I need a loyal guard that will be able
to protect the Almighty.
What is this?
There's a place called Guseonwon
far away from here.
You should go and stay there
until it gets quiet.
Did you say Guseonwon?
What? You know about it too?
There's a place called
Guseonwon 20 minutes away from town.
It's a great church.
You should come visit.
I'll make you a better person.
Do you want me to repent or something?
Don't do anything stupid and
watch someone called Baek Jeong-gi
until the governor gives orders.
Gosh, is the governor
trying to become
the master of everything?
Gosh, he is greedy.
Have you seen anyone who's not?
-Oh, my.
-Here.
Someone went missing.
Help me find her.
Who?
A woman called Hong So-rin.
-She's a reporter.
-A reporter?
Are you talking about
that reporter
who just got reported
missing by Muji Daily?
Yes.
Does she have something to do
with Guseonwon as well?
Her identity got revealed while
she was working undercover.
She was locked up,
but she managed to run away.
She went missing at Muji River
that's near Guseonwon.
I'm going to start investigating
Guseonwon tomorrow morning.
Really?
So come with your friend tomorrow,
and tell me where
-your friend was locked up.
-Okay.
Just a second.
(Dong-cheol, we need to meet right now.)
Dong-cheol. Dong-cheol.
The police and I are going to that place
where Jeong-hun was locked up.
Jeong-hun told me that there
were other people locked up there.
He even saw some people die there too.
But they might expect Jeong-hun
to tell everything to the police.
Do you think they still keep them there?
You're right.
I'm kind of worried about that.
If you fail to catch them tomorrow,
I'll just reveal my identity
and get locked up myself.
Then I'll try to look for other
people who got locked up.
-That's too dangerous.
-We have no other choice now.
We have to do this.
I don't even know what's going
on inside Sang-mi's head anymore.
Jeong-hun.
What brings you here?
Did my dad go somewhere?
He's out on patrol.
Is he not answering his phone?
No, I just came in
while I was passing by.
I'm glad you're here. Stay here
until I come back from the bathroom.
Okay.
My mom's birthday.
My birthday?
My goodness.
What are you doing here?
I just came by.
Why didn't you answer my calls?
Where are you?
Jeong-hun, you should go home first.
(If you want to know where
that reporter went,)
(come look for me quietly.)
Are you okay now?
You're in this with them,
aren't you?
No, I'm not in this with anyone.
They're just my friends.
What do you want?
Why do you keep trying
to get in our way?
Do you really believe that
Spiritual Father leads you to paradise?
Or do you just wish to believe so?
The believers here told me that
you also once sacrificed
your daughter into becoming
the Spiritual Mother.
Did your daughter also tell you
that Spiritual Father was real?
-What do you know?
-If you
really believe that Spiritual Father
leads you to paradise,
you can go ahead, and tell him
about my identity.
But if you wish to see
if he's real or fake,
you should sit back and watch.
Because we're going to reveal
that he's fake.
I'm sure the Almighty will
cleanse this place.
Right?
You're going to burn all the bad sins
of this place
with your hot fire,
and make it into a brand new place, right?
Am I right?
Yeong-hui.
Yeong-hui, listen to me.
I think you're mistaken.
-Yeong-hui.
-Why did you do this?
You said I should be careful of
what I eat.
No, that's not it.
Mr. Woo.
-You should just confess.
-Yeong-hui, let me explain.
I didn't do it on purpose.
I just kind of got myself
involved unknowingly.
Yeong-hui, watch out!
Mr. Woo!
You devil!
You must die
-in order for us to go to paradise.
-Mr. Woo.
Are you okay?
Please wait a little bit.
I might as well just
break everything into pieces.
Dad.
Dad. Dad.
What What happened?
Don't worry. Fortunately,
he didn't get severely injured.
They said he's good to go.
Are you okay, Dad?
Can you excuse us for a while?
Sit down.
Jeong-hun.
You're not going to
hate me, right?
What are you talking about
all of a sudden?
Jeong-hun.
I want you to
listen carefully to what
I'm about to tell you.
Well...
He's the one who entered our property
without permission.
Doesn't that make us the victims?
Yes, you can report him.
He'll have to pay a fine.
Chief, there's nothing here.
-What?
-I think
he came in here out of curiosity
and just lied
because he thought he wouldn't be able
to get out of it.
What? I saw it with my own two eyes.
Hey!
It was built during the Korean War.
We're using it as a warehouse.
How many times must I tell you
that there's nothing here?
Why can't you trust me?
Did you find what you were looking for?
I guess there was a misunderstanding.
I'm sorry to have caused a fuss
from so early in the morning.
How strange.
We have nothing against you.
But you seem to disagree with
our religion,
and you keep trying to defame us.
From what I know, you even
secretly came in here once before.
I came in because this place
smelled nasty.
Hey.
If you keep doing this,
we're no longer just going
to sit back and watch.
Why? Are you going to kidnap me
and lock me up?
-What did you say?
-I'll forgive you.
So please leave.
This is how generous he is.
He forgives everyone for everything.
"Forgive"?
I never asked you for your forgiveness.
Chief, these guys are all lying right now.
They're all in this together!
Stop it. That's enough.
My gosh.
Hey.
You shouldn't do this.
Please leave.
(SPIRITUAL FATHER'S ROOM)
Yes, come in.
Don't just stand there.
Please sit down.
From now on, you and Dong-cheol
will stay by my side and guard me.
-Pardon?
-It is your duty
to act as gatekeeper of paradise.
Okay.
What are you doing right now?
Do you have a problem with
what our Almighty wishes to do?
What are you doing?
I'm gatekeeping.
My gosh, this is ridiculous.
I'll see you again, Mr. Gatekeeper.
Mr. Gatekeeper, Mr. Gatekeeper
I can't believe this.
See?
He may have met our Almighty
long before you,
but if you fail to pray diligently,
your heart will be filled with distrust
and arrogance like him.
Both of you will be able to get
on the first class seats
of the Boat of Salvation on
the Day of Salvation.
Our wishes will be fulfilled.
What's going on?
I don't know what
the governor's hiding here,
but he asked me to stay here,
and keep an eye on him.
Sang-hwan's dad asked you
to come here?
But I heard he asked the governor
to send him someone to guard him.
That means he doesn't trust anyone here.
I can already sense that
Jo Wan-tae has done
some dirty deeds.
They're all just similar people
fighting for similar things.
-Jo Wan-tae?
-Yes.
How do you know him?
I saw him once at a karaoke bar.
("Karaoke bar"?)
Jun-gu.
I'm pretty sure you already know,
but this isn't an ordinary church.
You should be careful.
(KARAOKE BAR, BIXIE)
(I wonder when he's going to
go here again.)
Apostle Jo.
Our wishes will be fulfilled.
Shouldn't you be
by Spiritual Father's side?
I just got really worried.
I heard that the police might do
an open search on Guseonwon
because Hong So-rin suddenly disappeared.
This place is special, so they won't
be able to enter without permission.
So don't worry.
By the way,
I'm not going to be back tonight.
So call me if you need me for anything.
Okay?
(It must be today.)
Oh, okay.
Drive safely.
Okay.
(I think he's going to Bixie right now.)
(I THINK HE IS GOING TO BIXIE RIGHT NOW.)
He's really here.
I'm glad we listened to Dong-cheol
and waited here for him.
My gosh, do you think we'll be okay?
When did we ever think about that
before we did anything?
Let's begin.
Hello? Dong-cheol?
What do you think?
I'm here to spread the honor and
glory of our Almighty.
Why did you call?
The Spiritual Father?
Why does he want to see me?
I'll call you later.
Are you Jo Wan-tae?
The police are going to investigate
Guseonwon soon.
That means you won't be able
to walk around like this for long.
You must be acting up
Do you think things will go your way?
Guseonwon was built on a special
land that was chosen by Almighty.
How many times must I tell you
that it's not a place
where you can enter without permission?
I think things will go my way.
The police told me so.
You should talk more politely
for someone who's younger than me.
Do you think the police will even
be able to find anything?
You already checked with the police
that there's nothing strange there.
If we
find the person you murdered,
the story will unfold differently.
-What?
-I already know that
you were at Muji River last night.
I also know that you met
Reporter Hong So-rin there.
You took her into Muji River
and killed her,
didn't you?
What kind of nonsense
are you talking about?
I know you weren't
in Guseonwon at that hour.
The clothes you were wearing
were also wet in muddy water.
I heard they found Reporter Hong's
shoe at Muji River.
Thankfully,
we have a witness, so we've already
recorded that person's testimony.
As soon as the police investigates
and finds her body,
I'll be able to send you to prison.
Really? Then I guess
I should check that recording.
You foolish scum.
I even killed Hong So-rin.
Killing you will be a piece of cake.
Let's hear that witness' testimony.
Let me hear it.
Come here.
These rats...
You little...
You pieces of How dare you!
Hey, you guys. Break it up.
Stop.
You punks.
What do you mean I killed someone?
Me?
Whom did I kill? You saw everything.
All three of these punks came at me.
They randomly accused me of killing
someone and started beating me up.
Chief, you know
that I believe Almighty.
How can I kill anyone?
(I even killed Hong So-rin.
Killing you will be a piece of cake.)
(You punk. I'll teach you a lesson.)
I lied to him and said that I have
a recording of a witness statement,
but he tried to kill me
as soon as he heard it.
And whether we assaulted him
or acted in self-defense
will become clear if you watch
the CCTV footage from that camera.
-Arrest him.
-Yes, sir.
Chief, I can explain...
Gosh, what are you doing?
I'll recite your Miranda rights.
-You have the right to remain
-You scum.
You have the right to remain silent.
How dare you tell me to keep still?
You punk. If I catch you, I'll...
-Hey, Han Sang-hwan!
-Guys, bring him to the car.
-Yes, sir.
-Why are you doing this to me?
I really didn't do anything!
I'll be sure to teach you punks a lesson.
How dare you!
-Shut it, and get in the car.
-I really didn't do it!
I did nothing wrong! Darn it!
We have a recording of your confession
to killing Hong So-rin.
You were also behind
Officer Choe getting stabbed.
I heard you paid
the homeless guy to do it.
Why did you do that?
What? Stab whom?
He confessed to us
that you asked him to do it.
I asked him to do it?
Baek Jeong-gi, that piece of...
Mr. Jo.
Let's not waste our energy like this.
Let me use the washroom.
It looks like this will take a long time.
Aren't I right?
Jo Wan-tae just got arrested.
Seriously?
Then is he the one
who killed Reporter Hong?
Listen to me carefully.
Go to the cult leader,
and tell him who I really am.
-What?
-This is the only way we can
shake that place upside down.
What on earth are you thinking?
If he finds out
that I'm Sang-hwan's friend,
he'll lock me up in the basement storage
with other people.
Those people who disappeared today
are the most crucial evidence.
You need to blow my cover in order
for us to bring the truth to light.
You have to do it to gain his full trust.
I can't do that.
It'll be too dangerous for you.
I'll go down there.
Don't. I'll do my very best,
so you should do your best too.
Dong-cheol.
I'll do what you asked me to do,
but you have to do me a favor too.
I'll have
a spiritual wedding with him.
What?
I'll record everything that
disgusting jerk does to have me.
It's the most solid evidence we can get.
-Sang-mi.
-Baek Jeong-gi, that scum.
He let me go once, but he absolutely
won't give up this time.
I know that he'll try to have me
at all costs.
-Have you lost your mind?
-No.
I'm totally sane.
I finally have a clear idea
of what I can do to take him down.
You guys should come to where I am.
Just before he gets
what he wants,
barge in and save me.
Do you really have to do this?
I came back here because
I no longer
want to fear them
or run away from them.
I plan to destroy
this place with my own hands
so that I can save Sang-jin, Mom,
and Dad who's lost his mind
because of those scoundrels.
I will
save them at all costs.
-Detective.
-What?
I can't unzip my pants
because of these cuffs.
Please help me out here.
Hey, get him!
That rat!
Don't let him get away!
Get him!
Hurry!
Hey, stop right there!
-Get him!
-Gosh!
Hey!
That crazy jerk.
Stop right there!
It's here.
Why are you so dressed up?
I told you to wear something comfortable.
I had no idea there was
a place like this here.
This is the paradise,
the true paradise.
Yes, totally.
Here, all of your pain
and loneliness will go away
because Spiritual Father will heal you.
-That's right.
-Oh, really?
-Let's go in.
-Okay, let's go.
(GUSEONWON)
-Hello.
-Our wishes will be fulfilled.
You must know it too.
Evil energy started to fill up this place.
If we don't purify ourselves
of this evil energy soon,
the Boat of Salvation
might sink.
-Pardon me?
-If that happens,
Sang-jin, Sang-mi,
and your wife
won't be able
to reach the paradise.
Well... Spiritual Father.
Is there any way we can prevent it?
After the morning service tomorrow,
Sang-mi and I
will have our spiritual wedding.
Okay.
To stop the evil energy
from growing further,
you must
prepare for the spiritual wedding
as soon as possible.
Okay. Our wishes will be fulfilled.
Apostle Kang.
What did Spiritual Father
say to you?
He gave me a new revelation
in regards to the spiritual wedding.
By any chance,
did he say
that the Boat of Salvation might sink?
Apostle Kang.
Evil energy started
filling up this place.
If we don't purify ourselves
of this evil energy soon,
the Boat of Salvation might sink.
The spiritual wedding between Yu Ra and I
should be expedited.
Apostle Kang.
I'll take care of the preparation
from now on.
Please continue to pray
and help me out.
-We believe it!
-Our wishes will be fulfilled!
Sang-mi.
Come forward.
Now, the time is here.
Tomorrow at dawn,
you and I
will have a spiritual wedding
and become one.
I will be
at your service.
My savior.
My eternal life.
My
Spiritual Father.
(SAVE ME)
You use those who are powerless
to fulfill your ambitions.
You're just like the cult leader.
Both you and my dad
are exactly like that cult leader.
When you're a little older,
you'll realize
that there isn't much difference
between what's fake and real.
Is that how you lead your life?
I'll never live like that.
I told you to bring the voice recorder
if you want to see your mom.
I think
she misses you a lot.