(SAVE ME)
I saw Sang-mi.
(EPISODE 8)
I think she's in big trouble.
I ran into her after three years,
and she asked me
to save her.
She asked me,
not anyone else.
I know
that I hurt
you and her.
This time,
I won't run away.
I want to save her
before it's too late.
Sang-mi.
Do you know how startled I was earlier?
How dare you touch Spiritual Father?
What are you going to do
if you get into trouble?
What about me?
Do you even care about
the fact that I got hurt too?
Of course, I do.
I'm worried about you too.
-But Sang-mi
-He has abilities, doesn't he?
You said he can touch fire
and cure diseases as a savior.
What's the problem then?
He only shed a drop of blood.
What's the big deal about it?
I'm just worried that
Almighty might punish you.
-Dad.
-Yes?
I remember you
as a loving and caring dad.
I hope those memories won't disappear.
Mom has been sick,
but I was able to withstand it
only because I still remember you
at that time.
But
whenever I see you changing like this,
I'm scared that those memories
will disappear.
So please.
For my sake,
stop pushing me
into something strange, okay?
Please.
I beg you to stop.
Sang-mi.
I'm doing this because I love you,
and I worry about you.
If you
can be saved by becoming Spiritual Mother,
I will do anything.
Dad.
(Mom, can you hear me?)
(It's your son, Sang-hwan.)
(I got into a college in Seoul.)
(If you had seen me, you would've
said you're proud of me.)
It must've been boring for you
to keep listening to the same thing.
Mom.
There is a girl that I used to like.
She moved here from Seoul
when we were in high school.
I fell in love with her at first sight.
But
when she asked me to help her,
do you know what I did?
I ran away.
Well...
I don't know
what she's doing now,
or
why she asked me to save her.
I don't know that,
but I can't
stop worrying about her.
Gosh, Jun-gu.
It's been a long time.
How is your work going?
This is a small town. It's the same.
-What is it? Is it broken?
-No.
What is it then?
Can you let someone work here?
Who?
Who else? It's me.
Gosh, why would you work
at a place like this?
What's the problem?
Is it because I'm an ex-convict?
No, that's not what I meant.
Oh, hello.
Hey. You're Man-hui, right?
Gosh, look at you.
You've put on so much weight.
-Don't say that.
-It's good to see you.
The thing is, the pay is low.
It's a tough job.
I just need enough to sustain myself.
What shall I start with?
Do you go to church?
What? Oh, this.
No, I don't.
There's something I heard
from a pastor while I was in jail.
"Only those who have never
sinned can hurl stones at me."
Let's say that someone who has sinned
threw a stone at me.
Then I'll teach that person a lesson
regardless of who he is.
What do you think?
-It has a great meaning.
-Yes.
Bring me some work clothes.
(DRIVABLE DISTANCE 346KM)
Gosh, it's acting up again.
I should scrap this clunker
and get a new car.
Friend.
I must bring luck wherever I go.
I see that we're already getting
so many customers.
Jun-gu.
Go inside.
Did you guys bring thugs
from other areas just to kill me?
What are you waiting for?
-Whack him!
-Go, guys!
Sergeant Woo,
there's a fight going on here.
A bunch of thugs are vandalizing my store.
Please get here
as soon as possible. Thank you.
Hey, you guys...
You guys aren't punks.
You're in the family.
Don't embarrass other thugs.
You little Come here.
Gosh, I shouldn't have come this way.
Detective Kim, come to
the auto shop with a few guys.
There's a big fight going on here.
My goodness.
It looks like even those who beat up
people and walk all over others
go to church these days to be redeemed.
Why is that?
Do you feel like someone will save you
if you come here?
Don't just wish for good luck and fortune.
You guys should repent your sins.
Hey.
Did Lee Jin-seok tell you to whack me?
Lee Jin-seok?
There are guys who get
in the way of everything
the governor is trying to do.
He is Mr. Cheon's henchman.
(His name is Lee Jin-seok.)
Answer me.
Gosh, you jerk.
You never even visited me in jail,
and you're trying to stab me now.
Please forgive me this once.
I just did what I was told to do.
Right.
I know.
Today
I won't tell your boss.
I heard that you're hung up there
to pay for others' sins,
not for what you did.
Stop being so stupid.
Come down already.
Can't you thugs fight elsewhere?
Even governmental authorities
leave religious facilities alone.
Look at me.
I was waiting for you at the door.
You rats.
My gosh, Chief Lee. What brings you here?
How did you hear about the fight?
The owner of the auto shop called us.
I'll take this guy to the station.
There's another one inside.
Hang on.
This happened within our jurisdiction.
We should take them
to the substation first...
Oh, this guy is...
Why? Do you know him?
-Officer Choe.
-Yes.
Escort him to Muji Police Station.
Well Sure.
He got released from jail recently.
He's on our list of ex-offenders
to keep an eye on.
Which family does he belong to?
He doesn't even belong anywhere.
He's on his own.
I heard he's very weird.
You should be careful.
Don't you know who I am?
I'm Lee Gang-su.
Oh, right.
I heard about your achievements
back in your prime.
You're notorious among those
who work at the bars and lounges.
Thugs tried to whack him
as soon as he got released.
You should be my dog.
Bark, you jerk. Bark all you want.
Look at you.
-Sir.
-Yes.
Chief Lee Gang-su would like
to meet with you.
He's doing a good job with
what I asked him to do, right?
He wants to move back to Seoul, you know.
He'll figure out what's important.
Don't trust him too much though.
Those who betrayed you once
will always betray you again.
I'll meet up with him for a meal soon.
Got it, sir. Oh, Senator Park called too.
He must want to talk to me
about relocating the terminal.
It was one of his promises,
yet he dumped it on Mr. Cheon.
And now what? Does he want me
to clean up his mess?
It was one of Senator Park's promises,
but you can turn it
into your achievement, sir.
But for me to deal with that sly old man,
I'll need insurance, don't you think?
Yes, I'll let Chief Lee know.
All right.
-Sir.
-Yes?
You left this yesterday.
Ji-hui.
Do you know how precious
that watch is to me?
My father, who couldn't even graduate
from elementary school,
got that watch when he became
a village foreman.
He must've been so proud of it.
He never took it off until he passed away.
He said this one thing
as he was giving it to me
in his final moments.
"You must become successful."
Those were his last words.
You should become
the next provincial governor.
Ji-hui.
It looks like
you're completely my person now.
You've been here for a while.
You should go back to Seoul
and get ready for the law school.
He's right, Sang-hwan. If you study hard,
it would make your mom happy.
Do you think you're my mom now?
Of course not.
-I respect your mother very much.
-Respect?
Are you kidding me right now?
Han Sang-hwan.
Why are you being so rude to Ms. Lee?
Dad. Do you know how lonely
Mom is right now?
Of course, I do.
Are you going to keep breaking my heart?
Sang-hwan. I think you misunderstood us.
I'm just helping him as his assistant--
Look.
Do you still see me as a kid?
If you touch my mom
with those filthy hands again,
I won't just let it slide.
Detective.
You scratched that car.
We know you did.
-You two beat him up, right?
-That's not what happened.
Let me explain.
-Chief.
-What's the conclusion?
It was a self-defense.
Those thugs hit him first.
The owner of the auto repair shop
says the same thing,
and the security camera recorded it.
What about the thing
I asked you about?
Oh, as soon as he was released,
he went to see the nightclub owner,
Lee Jin-seok of Bull Gang.
They had a big fight,
and Lee Jin-seok was crushed by him.
Did something happen between them?
Lee Jin-seok was under the charge
of attempted murder nine years ago.
That guy said he did it,
and he went to jail instead of Jin-seok.
It looks like Jin-seok abandoned him
and betrayed him
after that.
I got it. Go out and deal
with the ones we arrested.
Yes, sir.
You want to destroy Lee Jin-seok, right?
You see, I'm a detective.
What do detectives do?
You had something unfair happen to you,
and I can make it right.
That's what detectives do, right?
My gosh.
What kind of nonsense
are you trying to tell me?
You need strength for sure,
but you need to use your brain
from time to time.
I'm saying I will be your brain.
Even if you keep doing this,
Lee Jin-seok won't go down.
Why? He has a powerful boss
who is watching his back.
You know this, don't you?
What are you saying?
Are you saying you will back me up?
Would I be enough for you?
Do you know who the boss of
everyone in Muji-gun is?
Wisely choose whom you'll work for,
so both of us
can survive.
Let's eat something.
Do you like tough beef soup?
Everyone in Muji-gun
likes tough beef soup.
Gosh, that's good.
This is why I like Muji-gun.
It's full of love and passion.
Let's go.
Hey, I said no.
I'll get into trouble if I get caught.
Come on, we're friends.
Don't be petty.
It's something I can't do.
We're not even that close.
My gosh. Hey.
He has ordered food
from your restaurant countless times.
Is this how you treat your VVIP customer?
If you keep doing this,
I will make a campaign about
the hair we found in your food
the other day.
It's a complaint, not a campaign.
-Complaint.
Sang-hwan, what are you up to?
We need to hide someone and run away.
You're not trying to kidnap someone,
are you?
Hey, what are you talking about?
You're right. It's kidnapping.
-What?
We're not the kidnappers.
We're trying to save someone
who has been kidnapped.
That's right.
Listen. Please help us out this once.
Come on.
What are you all saying?
How will I deliver food then?
There.
Take your pick.
We have a white one and a black one.
(KIM BO-EUN)
-Our wishes will be fulfilled.
-Excuse me.
Have you seen my mom
who is staying in this room?
-Ms. Kim Bo-eun?
-Yes.
She told the nurses that
she'd like to go and pray.
I see. Thank you.
Wait.
I heard a rumor that
you will become Spiritual Mother.
Is it true?
Do you even know what
Spiritual Mother is?
She's the mother of all spirits,
isn't she?
Why did you come here?
Because I want to be saved
and go to the paradise, of course.
Leave while you can.
-I'm sorry?
-If you can't leave, run away.
If you stay here,
both your body and soul will die.
Why aren't you leaving then?
Our wishes will be fulfilled.
Su-ri. What are you doing here?
She asked me where the patient is.
Didn't you hear
what Apostle Kang said?
You can't casually talk
to Sang-mi from now on.
-Do you understand?
-Yes.
If you're done here,
go to Room 303,
and help the patients bathe.
-Room 304? Okay.
-It's Room 303.
She doesn't know anything
because she's from Seoul.
Sang-mi.
You still have soft hair like a baby.
-Help me!
-They scream
from time to time.
Almighty.
Help me.
-I love you, Almighty.
-Almighty.
Please be here with me.
(GRAPEVINE)
Mom.
My daughter, it's you.
What brings you here, Sang-mi?
What on earth are you trying to do now?
Be respectful, will you?
You know that I'm an apostle.
Apostle Jo Wan-tae.
If you
laid a finger on my mom,
I'll be sure to kill you.
How scary.
Your eyes look so spiteful right now.
Sang-mi, I've seen many people
with those eyes.
They didn't even have a chance
to make eye contact with me though.
Do you know why?
Because I killed them first.
Do you think I'm lying right now?
Do you?
Earlier today,
Apostle Jo told me
about playing soccer with Sang-jin.
It was such a funny story.
You should've heard it too.
It's true, right?
Sang-jin really scored a goal, right?
Mom, Sang-jin is--
Of course.
He's so good at soccer.
He's so skilled.
What are you doing now?
Three years have passed,
yet you still have downy hair like a baby.
Right.
You'll become
Spiritual Father's new bride.
I should keep you safe.
Aren't I right, Ms. Kim?
Yes.
Please take good care
of Sang-jin and Sang-mi.
Gosh, have you forgotten who I am?
I'm the manager of Guseonwon
and an apostle.
Have a good time with your mother.
Sang-mi, what's the matter?
Are you feeling sick?
Are you?
Mom.
Let's get you out of here.
Sang-jin also wants you
to stay at a sanitarium instead of here.
Did he really say that?
Yes.
Then I should go.
Both of my twins don't want me
to stay here,
so I should leave.
Right, Sang-mi?
Yes.
Let's go.
Okay.
(ALMIGHTY IS OUR SAVIOR.
ALMIGHTY, PLEASE BLESS US)
"I am"
"showing this as proof
to be redeemed from my sins."
"My faith allowed me
to become a new person"
"and meet Almighty."
"This is paradise
and Almighty's revelation."
Almighty, please don't abandon me.
Please don't desert me
Please forgive and save me.
Please look over me.
Gosh, when will they leave?
I hope it's soon.
Are you sure they'll come out?
What if we're wasting our time?
Just wait. They go to pray
at the break of dawn.
Did you see that?
Yes, I can see too.
-Let's go.
(GUSEONWON)
My gosh, what is this place?
It looks like a castle.
Sang-hwan, we can't sneak in
by climbing over that fence.
I'm out.
Well, I'm sure there's another entrance.
Almighty's message of salvation
completely gets rid
of our spiritual thirst
because his grace quenches us
from within.
-We believe it!
Our wishes will be fulfilled!
Come to me,
and I'll relieve your thirst!
-We believe it!
Those who believe me will be saved
and be eternally free from thirst.
-We believe it!
What are you doing now?
You have to pray.
What do I have to pray for?
Pray so that you can get rid
of that bad attitude!
They're coming out. Over there.
This must be it.
It looks like this place
is their home ground.
What's that on their faces?
Everyone.
Almighty's blessings are with you.
-We believe it!
It's obviously a cult.
Let's wait a few more minutes.
Let's pray once more.
-We believe it!
-Let's get closer.
-All right.
Oh, hold on a second.
Will you do a live broadcast again?
I should record inside of the building
and the leader's face.
My gosh, do you see him?
That man with blond hair.
I bet he's the leader of this cult.
He totally looks like a con artist.
Hey, it's her. It's that girl.
Darn it.
Hey.
How's your hand?
Is your scar gone?
It's not a big deal.
More importantly,
you are our holy spirit.
I'm so sorry for what she did to you.
All scars will heal with time.
That's equal to patience.
Sang-mi, you and your father
have been patiently waiting
for a long time now.
What do you think all of that was for?
It was obviously for
your mother and brother.
My wish is
to help you receive salvation.
Yes.
If you start to obey our Almighty
like this,
he shall exist inside you
with an undying happiness.
Our wishes will be fulfilled.
I believe it.
You did the exact same thing back then.
You
put your hand on me
and my brother's shoulders.
Then you pretentiously acted
as if you were a true pastor.
Sang-mi.
I'm not a fake pastor.
The fake pastors are the ones
who dwell in the world of evil.
I'm not going to give up no matter
how much you threaten me.
I'm going to
reveal how dirty and disgusting
this place is
to the world no matter what.
Okay.
I too shall never give up on you
regardless of how hard the devil tries to
take you away from our Almighty.
Our wishes will be fulfilled.
My gosh, that scared me.
Did you see the look in his eyes?
My gosh.
I knew that would happen
because of your live show.
I'm sorry.
Do you think he saw us?
I don't think so.
We were quite far away.
Hey, isn't he the cult leader?
-Yes, it's him. He has yellow hair.
-Let's get in.
Let's go. Come on. Hurry.
What are you doing? Let's go.
Sang-hwan, don't go. Stop it.
Sang-hwan.
You guys are
the young men who once
got into an accident
with my apostles, right?
Are you the leader of this cult?
"The leader of this cult"?
I'm just a pastor.
What's your purpose?
My gosh,
that was a bit too straightforward.
What purpose?
I'm asking what your purpose is.
I'm going to go to paradise
with everyone who's seeking
to receive salvation.
So you're saying that
you're going to go all the way, right?
You're a foolish young man
who only sees what you wish to see.
This is a sacred place.
When dirty souls try to enter,
they will be doomed.
So stop what you're doing,
go back to your world
and live your lives.
Do you understand?
If you're going to go all the way,
so will we.
Do you understand?
If you decide to go that far,
that place
shall be the valley of death
and a fiery pit.
-Eat up.
-Thank you.
-Tell me if you need more.
It's okay.
I'm going to
drink this from now on.
Ma'am.
Do you feel sick?
By the way,
I heard you're going to become
the Spiritual Mother.
If you really do become
the Spiritual Mother,
please take me with you
on the Boat of Salvation.
I'm sure Jeong-gu's waiting for me
to come see him.
Okay?
Ma'am.
Jeong-gu
didn't die because of an accident.
You need to go to the police
and ask for a reinvestigation.
Jeong-gu is with our Almighty in paradise.
What are you saying?
You're hurting me.
Jeong-gu is in paradise.
He's in paradise.
-He's in paradise!
-Ma'am.
It hurts. Please let go of my hand.
-He's in paradise!
Let me go! Mom, help me!
That's why I need to go to paradise too!
I need to meet Jeong-gu.
Please take me with you
when you become the Spiritual Mother.
Ma'am.
What are you doing right now?
My gosh.
What in the world did I do?
Sang-mi is a very precious person
for us in Guseonwon.
My goodness, what should I do?
I must have become insane.
-Apostle Im.
-Yes?
Apostle Kang, please.
I'm so sorry for what I did.
Take Sang-mi home.
-I still have some more work
-Right now!
Okay.
This person wants her son
to pass the test.
He passed.
"Jeong Mi-yeong".
My gosh, shouldn't she get tired of
doing this now?
She's always asking us to help
her son get married.
If she wants him to get married,
she should send him to a matchmaker.
What's the use of sending this here?
My goodness.
Let's see. Come in.
Hello, sir.
Did you eat?
Is Spiritual Father not here?
No, he's not.
I see.
Please make sure to give this
to Spiritual Father.
I guess you're here to make
a special contribution.
I sold my cows for this.
Please give this
to Spiritual Father.
Our wishes will be fulfilled.
You're filled
with our Almighty's blessings.
If you keep up your faith,
you'll definitely get a first class seat.
My gosh, that's too much.
I still have a long way to go
before I get accepted into
the Boat of Salvation.
Plus, I need to take
my children with me too.
Don't you worry.
I'll ask Spiritual Father
to pray for you.
I hope you keep believing.
-Our wishes will be fulfilled.
I'll be off then.
My gosh.
Hello, Spiritual Father.
I just came in to say hello
to Apostle Jo.
You're leaving already?
You should drink tea
since you're here.
No, it's okay. I need to go
and clean my cows' wastes.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
Spiritual Father, I'll go now.
-Okay. Have a safe trip home.
-Okay.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
My gosh.
My gosh, the peach is very ripe.
You're helping me out a lot.
No, it's nothing.
I'm not doing this for myself.
I'm doing this for our Almighty.
If we make a bigger church
and build a hospital,
it'll benefit our believers.
You're right.
That will be our Almighty's grace
and blessing.
Our Almighty shall
bless the land of Muji.
But I have a question.
Why are you insisting on making
Sang-mi the Spiritual Mother?
She seems to have quite a bad temper.
The world we're living in is full of evil.
In order for all of us
to get on the Boat of Salvation
on the day of judgement,
we need to take in a pure scapegoat.
To me, Sang-mi is the pure scapegoat
that will allow all of us
to receive salvation.
Do you now understand why
I am trying to make Sang-mi
the Spiritual Mother
by getting married to her?
I have to say,
you really are and
always have been peculiar.
(She asked me)
(to save her.)
(LIGHTNING QUICK DELIVERY SERVICE)
My gosh.
Look at how they're looking at him.
I think they've all been brainwashed.
It's weird.
Don't you think
this is going to be dangerous?
You guys, let's do this.
The devils must be causing trouble
because they're jealous that
you're going to become
the Spiritual Mother.
At times like this,
you need to focus on praying more.
Do you really not understand
what they're trying to do to me?
Dad, you're
practically selling me off to them.
Sang-mi, just like what
Spiritual Father said,
I'm never going to give up on you either.
Dad!
(YOU KNOW ME, RIGHT?)
(HAN SANG-HWAN)
(YOU NEED TO BE CLEAR IN ORDER
FOR ME TO HELP YOU.)
(ARE YOU LOCKED UP RIGHT NOW?)
(DID YOU MEAN IT
WHEN YOU ASKED ME TO SAVE YOU?)
(JUST WAIT.
I WILL COME AND SAVE YOU.)
(DONG-CHEOL)
Is she
really in trouble?
I think
she's being locked up
by some weird cult believers.
I also saw a cult believer in prison.
He started believing
in some weird religion,
and he killed his child saying
that his child was possessed.
Sang-hwan.
Are you really
not going to run away this time?
This time,
I'm never going to run away.
Hey, Dong-cheol.
You...
This guy looks good in anything.
Right? Don't you agree?
Hey, do you know how much
I missed you?
Come here, Dong-cheol.
Move.
Have you been doing well?
I know you suffered a lot.
Hey, come on. It's been three years
since we've all gathered together.
Let's drink.
(MUJI ARABIAN NIGHT CLUB)
Then should we sneak into her house
in the middle of the night
and bring her out secretly?
Are you crazy?
That's not going to be easy.
And what if she ends up saying
that she never asked us for help?
That won't happen.
The look in her eyes
was the same as what I saw
three years ago.
She seemed really desperate.
Dong-cheol, aren't you going to work?
Boss will be upset if he finds out
you were here during working hours.
I'm getting up.
-When do you plan on going?
-Early this morning.
When they head for service
will be the perfect chance.
All right.
Then I'll see you at dawn.
All right. Keep up the
good work.
Hey, Han Sang-hwan.
Do you know
how Dong-cheol makes a living?
He makes deliveries during the day
and works here at night.
What are you trying to say?
He's trying to settle down and
make a living. Don't get him in trouble.
If you get in trouble,
you have your father to rely on.
He has no one. You should know that.
Don't think you know everything
based on what you see.
Whatever you say won't change things.
You two clearly come
from different backgrounds.
Face it. It's fate.
Sang-hwan. Don't bother.
Let's go. Let's not make a fuss here.
He's right, Sang-hwan.
Go ahead and hit me.
After all, you have your father
to protect you, don't you?
Background? Fate?
I'm going to change all that.
Let's go. Come on.
Go ahead and drink up.
Hello, senator.
I must be late.
No, not at all. I know how busy
you must be. Have a seat here.
You should sit on this cushion.
Why, thank you, Mr. Kim.
It's been a long time, Governor Han.
You look younger. It must be because
you have such a young assistant.
Director Ji,
you're looking good yourself
considering all you've been through
because of Chairman Kim's scandal.
Goodness.
Hello.
What are you waiting for?
You should exchange handshakes.
The former and current governors
should join hands.
That way, the local community
will be able to develop greatly.
It's been a long time, Governor Han.
It has been a long time, Mr. Cheon.
Dong-cheol.
I know it's none of my business,
but don't do anything stupid.
Don't let them take
advantage of you again.
You and I come from different backgrounds.
They're different.
I can take care of myself.
You may have been friends in school,
but you can't rely on them now.
I'll see you later then.
Hey, guys. Wake up.
I'm up. What is it?
Where are they?
Why isn't Dong-cheol here yet?
Could that guy possibly have
changed Dong-cheol's mind?
Don't say that.
Dong-cheol wouldn't let us down.
I know Dong-cheol
will show up.
-Our wishes will be fulfilled.
The early morning air sure is nice.
Yes, the morning air is full of
Almighty's blessings.
It's summer, but the early morning air
still seems a bit cool.
You'll catch a cold.
Why don't you hurry on into the car?
(IF POSSIBLE, DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
TRY TO STAY HOME.)
Wait a minute.
Do you mind if I stay home
and get some rest today?
-Why?
-I'm not feeling well.
I think I have a cold.
I would like to skip
early morning service today.
Then why don't you rest
at Guseonwon?
Our future Spiritual Mother has been
in a spiritually clean place.
You're sick
because you're in a dirty environment.
I get headaches just by
leaving Guseonwon.
She's right. Go have a glass of
warm life-giving water and get some rest.
We'll be late and miss the words
of blessings. We should go.
She's right.
Sang-hwan.
Are you going to keep
waiting for Dong-cheol?
Let's just go.
You'll be able to be with
your mother again, so don't feel anxious.
Excuse me?
Apostle Im must not have told you yet.
Spiritual Father wants you to return
to Guseonwon starting from today.
It's good news. Spiritual Father has made
an exception for you.
Dad. What are you talking about?
What do you mean we're moving back?
What about our belongings?
Don't you worry. Our brethren
will be bringing everything for you.
Sang-mi, what's that look on your face?
Isn't this what you've been wanting?
Apostle Jo.
Yes?
Once she arrives at Guseonwon,
she'll be starting her training
to become our Spiritual Mother.
You shouldn't refer to her
as Sang-mi from now on.
Forgive me.
I'm so used to calling her Sang-mi.
I don't know what I was thinking.
(GUSEONWON)
Dong-cheol, where are you?
(They've packed all their belongings.)
-What?
(-They're taking away everything.)
(Sang-hwan, you have to stop
that van no matter what.)
All right. Don't worry.
I'll make sure I stop the van.
They found out what we're up to.
Hold on tight.
Gosh.
-Are you guys ready?
-I'm the son of a cop.
I'm on a wrestling team.
Let's go.
They're the evil spirits.
They're here to dare take away
what belongs to Almighty.
Do you know what the most effective
miracle drug is for evil spirits is?
It's this right here.
They need a beating until near death
to know who they're dealing with.
Shall we?
(GUSEONWON)
I'll save you.
(SAVE ME)
Evidence?
Do you think they're fools
to leave behind evidence?
Even if we do find something,
it'll be useless.
What are you talking about?
If you're rich and have
strong connections,
you can make an innocent person guilty.
That's what happened back then,
isn't that right?
That won't happen again.
Trust me.