(SAVE ME)
(EPISODE 10)
(GUSEONWON)
The worship service has begun.
Let's go.
I'll go on my own.
Dong-cheol, I'll block them.
Go inside and get the books.
Hey.
Dong-cheol.
You can't take the books.
You have to understand
that I work for Jin-seok.
Everyone in this world is sinful,
but not everyone repents of their faults.
If a sinful person does not repent
his wrongdoings,
he will be
judged by our Almighty eventually.
-I believe it.
-Our wishes will be fulfilled!
Sang-mi, please come.
Everyone, Sang-mi has
returned to Guseonwon.
Let us applaud her.
Spiritual Father,
I am very sorry.
Sang-mi.
Why did you come back?
As I hear,
you told people that you wanted
to come back to Guseonwon yourself.
-I believe it.
Do you think
I wanted to come back?
I already said no.
It's not grace or salvation
to coerce me into submission.
The true evil
is you.
I came back to protect my mom from you!
Sang-mi.
Sang-mi, it seems like
you are mistaken about something.
The feeling of aversion
that you're having right now
is what's coming from the evil.
-I believe it.
I'm so sick of you
talking about the evil!
You should all get a hold of yourselves.
You've given him your houses,
money, land, and everything else!
All you do here is work.
Do you think that's salvation?
It's no use praying here every day.
Go home and see your family.
Go and see
how frustrated they are because of you!
Get out, everyone.
Stop being fooled,
and get out of here!
See?
This is the evil!
-I believe it!
I can no longer
watch Sang-mi's soul die.
It is now time for everyone in Guseonwon
to stand together and pray with fire.
Stop talking crazy things.
You're insane.
Sang-mi, you are not the pure soul
we used to know anymore.
You're right.
She's not my daughter that I know.
She may look the same way,
but her soul is already
captured by the evil.
Almighty, please.
Please save my daughter.
Do not worry.
Sang-mi will
win the spiritual fight no matter what.
I believe it!
Our wishes will be fulfilled!
You're right.
I am
never going to be defeated by you.
That's right.
There was a time
Apostle Kang's daughter
said the same thing as Sang-mi.
This is how amazing
our Almighty's plan is.
I didn't realize why Almighty would
give Apostle Kang a painful hardship.
He wanted to train Apostle Kang
so that she can help Sang-mi
become our Spiritual Mother.
Don't you think so?
I do.
I will do
everything I can to make
Sang-mi our Spiritual Mother.
-Our wishes will be fulfilled!
I command you
in the name of our divine Almighty.
-Almighty!
-In the name of Almighty!
The evil that resides inside her,
you shall leave my loved one right now!
-I believe it!
Let us all pray together in unison.
You filthy evil!
Leave her right now!
Our wishes will be fulfilled.
Can't you leave the books and go?
Will you leave if I tell you to leave?
Jun-gu.
Could you just let him go?
Do you know him?
What did I tell you back in the prison?
I told you not to trust anyone.
Someone will stab you in the back again.
See? You never know
what people would do.
You would
do anything for money just like others!
If you bare your teeth to me,
I will break them all.
-Gosh, Jeong-hun!
-Dad.
Let me explain.
What did I tell you?
I told you to study hard and
go to college without causing trouble.
Yes, Dad. Gosh, you're killing me.
I'm about to die of anger because of you.
-Wait.
-That's enough.
Gosh, Chief Lee.
We're all in the police force.
This is really embarrassing.
Right.
We're all in the police force.
Everyone! You should hit it harder!
So the evil will scream and run away!
Our wishes will be fulfilled!
Our wishes
-Our wishes will be fulfilled!
No. No!
No! Sang-mi!
Don't hit Sang-mi. Don't hit her.
I'm sorry. I'm begging you.
Please don't hit Sang-mi.
Mom.
Honey, help me.
Help our daughter, Sang-mi.
It looks like the evil that
was clinging on to Sang-mi
has gone over to
her mother now.
You cruel evil!
Please.
Please stop harassing my family.
Get out of my wife's body!
No! Mom! Mom!
You're crazy.
What do you think you're doing?
First, you took my son.
And now, you're trying to take away
my daughter and wife?
Get out! Get out of my wife's body!
-Dad!
-Get lost!
-No, stop.
-Go away!
Get lost!
-Our wishes will be fulfilled.
-I believe it.
(WE WILL STAND STRONG AGAINST CRIME,
AND SUPPORT THE PEOPLE OF MUJI)
The girl's father wants the boys
to get punished.
Detective Lee.
You're here.
My goodness, you're here.
You're finally here.
I need to have a word with you.
The governor's son brought his friend here
saying that she needs help
to get out of a cult.
But her parents had already reported
that she had gotten abducted.
It can be quite a difficult case
if I follow regular procedures.
But I'll take care of this so that
it won't affect the governor.
It sounds as if you want
something in return.
Don't be mistaken.
And about that thing you asked me
to take care of regarding Mr. Cheon
I'll be getting a warrant today,
so it'll be taken care of tomorrow.
You can tell the governor that
he doesn't need to worry.
Are you a criminal?
Why would you get in the back seat?
Listen. Dad.
My friend was in trouble.
I couldn't ignore that.
I was just trying to do a good deed.
Come on, Dad.
Stop it. Just stop!
Just ignore her.
You just need to study hard
and go to university.
Now, that's a good deed.
Do you understand?
Dad.
You should stay here,
repent on your dirty sin,
and cleanse yourself.
You'll
never be able to receive salvation here.
Sang-mi.
You need to become the Spiritual Mother.
That's the only way
our family will be able
to get on the Boat of Salvation.
That's right, Sang-mi.
Please wake up.
Wake up and open your eyes
to this surprising wisdom.
I want Sang-jin to
receive salvation more than anyone.
But that's not going to happen here.
You're only getting fooled
by their dirty tricks and lies.
Apostle Kang.
What's going on?
Is something worrying you these days,
Apostle Kang?
I'm surprised to see that
you're looking out for me.
Thank you for the kind gesture,
but I'm fine. Don't worry.
My gosh, how can I not worry?
Everybody here knows that
you're the best when it comes
to propagating our religion.
Apostle Jo, do you have a will
to receive salvation?
-Sorry?
-I personally think
your will lies not in salvation,
but in something else.
My gosh, Apostle Kang.
You're being way too straightforward.
Your job is to help
Spiritual Father bring out
the spirituality from our believers.
But my job is to make sure
Guseonwon runs well
by taking care of all the business.
You can't say that just because I brought
less people than you have.
Okay.
Then from now on,
let's not be mistaken about each other.
You cannot afford to make
a mistake this time.
You need to make sure Sang-mi
becomes our Spiritual Mother.
That's the only way me,
our Spiritual Father,
you, and your daughter,
will all be able to get on
the Boat of Salvation.
Don't you agree?
You should always stay awake.
It would be a pity
if you fail to get on the Boat of
Salvation all by yourself.
I believe it.
Yes, that's the Kang Eun-sil I know.
I hope your belief continues
to stay strong
forever.
(MUJI HANGIL NURSING HOME)
The look in your eyes
haven't changed at all.
That's exactly how your father
used to look at me.
He always
just thought of me as a butcher's son.
I thought things would all be over
when he passed away.
But one day,
you also started to look at me
with despise, just like your father.
But
Ji-hui
doesn't look at me like you do.
She respects me.
It's something you were never
able to give me.
But Ji-hui is able to give me that.
So you can just stay like that,
and never wake up.
That way, people will remember me
as a loving husband
who cares for his sick wife.
Honey, you should wake up now.
You know how much Sang-hwan
is worried about you.
Dad.
Yes?
This wouldn't have happened
if you stayed in Seoul.
Your mom would've been so worried
if she knew about what happened.
I have a favor to ask of you.
My friend is involved a weird cult.
But she's having trouble
getting out of there.
It's called Guseonwon.
They have a sanitarium,
a collective farm,
and they do a lot of volunteer work.
So they seem like any other normal church.
But they're actually a weird cult.
Please help my friend
so that she can get out of there
and live a proper life.
I'm a politician.
If you want to ask me for a favor,
you need to give me something in return.
Okay.
I'll go back to Seoul.
I'll go back, and become a judge.
Are you satisfied?
Okay.
I'll look into it.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
We're father and son.
Let's go home now so that
your mom can take some rest.
Jun-gu.
I owed you one
since you helped me out in prison.
That's why I didn't ask
what this was all about.
But what's that jerk doing here?
Why? Do you know Detective Lee?
What? We met three years ago, right?
I'm going to go now.
Is today some kind of day?
The governor's son already gave me
enough nonsense this morning.
Are you talking about Sang-hwan?
Do you know him too?
My gosh, this neighborhood is
way too tiny.
What did he do?
He brought this girl saying that
she's involved in some kind of cult.
What happened to her?
Do you know her too?
Her dad took her back.
What do you mean?
You're a cop.
Why did you send her back?
My gosh, you are all so annoying.
Why are you acting up just like Sang-hwan?
You haven't changed at all.
What? Hey, you should know
how to kill your temper
if you've been to prison.
I might as well just lock you up again.
I don't owe you anything anymore.
That little...
Does he work for you?
You should teach him some manners.
Guys like him
can't be tamed.
We just have to let him live his own life.
You got the account book, right?
Can I do whatever I want
with Lee Jin-seok now?
Is she taking her medicine regularly?
Yes.
Okay. You can leave now.
Sister Kim.
Sang-mi left this place,
but she came back.
She could've stayed there,
but she chose to come back.
Do you know why?
She came back because of you.
My daughter
My daughter, Yu-ra, left this place.
Because of that, she made me
commit a big sin
to our Almighty and Spiritual Father.
But Sang-mi came back.
I hate you so much because of that.
You have a daughter who wants
to protect you even when you're crazy.
And I really hate that.
My love.
My savior.
My Almighty.
My loving Spiritual Father.
Yes.
You need to stay here like this forever.
I'm going to make your daughter
into our Spiritual Mother,
and do the best I can for our Almighty.
That way, I'll be able to get
on the Boat of Salvation with my daughter.
So you need to stay here
and keep Sang-mi from leaving.
That's what you must do.
This place is paradise.
Salvation. Eternal life.
Our wishes will be fulfilled.
It feels like I'm shooting a spy movie.
Who should I get for you first?
Mr. Cheon? Senator Park?
-Detective Lee.
-Yes?
You should know how to keep
a straight face.
Otherwise, you won't be able
to gain much from anything.
Okay.
Catch Mr. Park first.
He works for Mr. Cheon.
Okay.
But I have to say,
since the governor's locking up all
the corrupt politicians,.
Muji might soon become
the cleanest town in Korea.
That's only possible thanks
to people like you
who try their best
to make that happen.
Bye then.
What are you jerks trying to
plan this time?
You better not get involved
in gambling, okay?
Come on, Aunt.
It's nothing like that.
Who are you calling "Aunt"?
Just think of me as
your older sister.
(-My gosh, you're Dong-cheol.
-Yes.)
(-What happened to your face?
-It's nothing.)
Hey.
What happened?
Why did she go back?
Sang-mi
already knew that things would
turn out like this.
That cult named Guseonwon
is even capable of controlling the police.
I'm going to try whatever I can
by using my own method.
What are you going to do?
I asked my dad
for help.
I don't trust
adults.
Dong-cheol, I also--
It's all useless.
I'm also going to do things my way now.
What do you mean?
You always used your brain,
and I always used my guts.
-Don't tell me that--
-I want to see for myself
what kind of place that is.
Dong-cheol.
Are you crazy?
That place is too dangerous.
You can't go there alone.
Sang-hwan.
One of us
needs to know that place
in order to help her.
They all know your faces now.
So
I'll go.
Recite the salvation prayer.
If you do,
I'll give you the Spring water
of Salvation.
(POLICE)
Mr. Park, please open the door.
Mr. Cheon, I'm in trouble.
The police are in front of my door
with a warrant.
-They keep knocking on the door.
(-Open the door.)
Mr. Park, we'll open this
ourselves, then.
Sorry?
(Mr. Park Jeong-min!)
Are you serious?
Mr. Park Jeong-min.
Are you going to jump from up there?
Walk out through the door
unless you want a metal rod in your leg.
I'm doomed.
Let's talk about casting a net
for prospective believers.
First, you should carry the bible around,
wearing a cross pendant
most Christians wear.
Then say that you're new
to the area and want to attend church
to befriend people in the area.
I have a question.
Don't people think we're lying?
There's a line that goes like this
in "Book of Salvation".
"False or true,"
"no matter what means you use,"
"spreading Almighty's messages
is a joyous deed,"
"and it will continuously
delight Almighty."
Therefore, we don't call it lying.
Instead, we call it "Salvation Strategy".
If you use this strategy wisely,
you'll receive a big reward.
What we do here is
leading people to salvation through
our faith, which is a good deed.
Almighty will praise
our righteousness.
You all got that, right?
-Our wishes will be fulfilled.
Let's wrap up today's class here.
We'll head out for our mission work
right away,
so please get ready.
-Yes, Apostle Kang.
Oh, Ms. Hong.
Yes.
How long has it been
since you joined Guseonwon?
It's been just over a year.
I've been observing you.
From all the volunteer work
and seminars to the mission work,
you've been serving Almighty
most faithfully.
Both Spiritual Father and Almighty
are delighted with your work.
Our wishes will be fulfilled.
I believe it.
What is your wish, Ms. Hong?
It's getting on the Boat of Salvation,
of course.
If you want to make
that wish come true,
you should assist and
look after Spiritual Mother.
How do you feel about becoming her aide?
Her aide?
You'll work with Spiritual Mother
most closely out of all of us
and serve her as well as Spiritual Father.
Getting the position is a huge honor.
Can I really be given
such an important position?
I'll speak with Spiritual Father about it.
Will you accept the offer
with your faith?
Of course. Our wishes
will be fulfilled. I believe it.
Thank you very much, Apostle Kang.
Sang-mi.
If you memorize
the Prayer of Salvation,
you'll be able to get out of here.
I
won't give up.
You haven't learned your lesson.
-Our wishes will be fulfilled.
-We believe it.
Let's go. You should go this way.
Hey, guys.
Isn't this our first time coming
to a place like this together?
Hey, stop embarrassing us.
We're not here to hang out.
It looks like she's here alone.
And she happens to be reading
one of my favorite books.
-We'll probably click.
-Hey, be quiet.
Hey, Dong-cheol.
Yes, they're at the park now.
All right. Be careful.
Will we get started right away?
We're here to promote a concert
for those in their 20s and 30s.
Would you be able
to fill out this survey?
I'm sorry.
Hello, excuse me.
Hello, we're here to promote
Gosh, the laces came undone again.
Excuse me.
Yes?
I'm sorry I startled you.
It's okay. What is it about?
We're here to promote a concert
for those in 20s and 30s.
We'd like to find out what young people
are concerned about nowadays.
If you fill out this survey,
you'll get a ticket to the concert
as well as a gift certificate.
Could you spare us a minute of your time?
I'm sorry.
My mom wants to have dinner with me today,
so I have to be home early today.
Today is her birthday.
We just need a minute.
They're simple questions.
-This is for you.
-Thank you.
-Gosh, it's so hot!
-Oh, no.
It's okay.
It's all right. I'll do it.
Goodness.
Dong-cheol,
you have such a pure heart.
Aren't I right, So-rin?
Yes, you have such kind eyes.
Gosh, I'm flattered.
My mom always talks about
how weak they look.
Dong-cheol, do you think that
this world will exist eternally?
They say that nothing is eternal.
Then do you think that
we can be given eternal life?
Eternal life? I'm not sure.
Right?
You're not sure.
That's right.
What if someone is
willing to share the secret
to eternal life?
How will that make you feel?
-Is there such a thing?
-Of course.
Us crossing paths like this
wasn't a mere coincidence.
It means that you can
become the chosen one.
I can become the chosen one?
That's right. When you get chosen,
the secret to eternal life
will be revealed to you.
Well, you're not chosen yet,
but the possibility
opened up to you today.
It's a bit difficult to follow.
So-rin, could you explain to him
in easier terms?
Sure.
It doesn't look like this world
will ever come to an end,
but the end will come.
We call it "apocalypse".
But because people are only
preoccupied with the present,
they're not getting ready for it at all.
Totally. We should get ready for it.
Right? We need to be prepared.
When the time comes,
only the awakened ones who are prepared
can get on the Boat of Salvation.
The Boat of Salvation?
I've never heard of it.
Is he actually flirting with her or what?
Why is he taking so long?
That woman is so used to dealing
with people like that, you know.
She'll know if anything seems off.
If he buys it right away,
she'll figure it out,
so he's just being careful.
Dong-cheol must know.
Oh, it looks like they're done.
Yes, we're at the entrance of
the park by the intersection.
We met someone very special.
Okay, we'll wait there.
They're actually in the area.
They'll pick us up right away.
-It's perfect, isn't it?
-Yes, totally.
That works out perfectly.
Wear this.
Why?
They must have rules
about whom to approach.
I bet it comes down to money.
We need bait to catch a fish.
My mom gave it to me as a gift,
so don't lose it.
All right.
And
we'll also need a sign
only we can recognize.
A sign?
Hey, that's our cue.
Okay.
(GUSEONWON)
Please get in.
It's a hot day, isn't it?
Yes, it's scorching hot.
They'll go with us.
I see. It's nice to meet you all.
Guys, look. My goodness.
Dong-cheol is so brave.
He got on that van right away.
He's like Gutsy, you know.
He's always been that way.
From now on,
only happy days await all of you.
-Congratulations.
-I'm very happy to meet you all.
Welcome.
You have such a kind face.
What a nice watch.
Your family must be well-off.
By the way,
did you get your hair done
at a hair salon?
Sorry?
Why do you ask?
My gosh, your hairstyle is so unique.
Is it because you're young?
You're very straightforward.
I'm sorry if I was rude.
Not at all. I like that attitude.
(GUSEONWON)
You can get off now.
I didn't expect to see
such a huge building inside the mountains.
Our wishes will be fulfilled.
-Our wishes will be fulfilled.
This is a holy spot.
It wards off demons.
-Sister So-rin.
-Yes.
Take your time and explain everything
about Guseonwon to them.
I'll see you all
in the chapel later.
Okay.
Then I'll see you guys later.
All right then. Please follow me.
Dong-cheol.
My, this place is so cool.
Gosh.
Why isn't he picking up?
Guys, let's go in.
We should wait inside.
-He'll be okay, right?
-Nothing will happen to him.
Let's go inside.
All right.
This is the main chapel.
-Spiritual Father gives us love
-I love you
Everyone, we have
a few new brethren visiting us
here at Guseonwon today.
Shall we welcome them
with a big round of applause?
Welcome!
Shall we bless each other
before we get started?
Our wishes will be fulfilled.
-Our wishes will be fulfilled!
We believe it.
-We believe it!
These chosen brethren
to get on the Boat of Salvation
with us were sent to us
by Almighty and Spiritual Father.
Let's express our gratitude to them
with a round of applause.
We welcome you all.
Welcome to Guseonwon.
Welcome.
(JEONG-HUN)
Why isn't Dong-cheol picking up?
Stop calling him. What will you do
if something happens to him?
Hey, what if those jerks figured it out?
They might whack him.
It's not like they're thugs.
You're so clueless.
They're much more ruthless than thugs.
Haven't you seen it on TV?
Some of them
beat people up and kill them.
Some cults even bury people alive.
What if that place is one of them?
Stop making ominous remarks, will you?
Well, I was just saying
we should be prepared
for the worse-case scenario.
Guys, I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
-I have to meet someone.
-Who?
I'll tell you guys later.
Call me if Dong-cheol gets back.
All right.
Get home safely.
-Take care.
-Goodbye.
Dong-cheol.
Why are you leaving?
We're having tea with the new brethren.
Please join us.
Oh, right. You said your mom wants you
to come home early today.
Yes, it's her birthday today.
Right, you said that.
How about you bring her here?
We'll throw a birthday party for her.
-What do you think?
-Well
I think I should head home now.
I'm really sorry.
Don't be.
We have a service scheduled for tomorrow.
I'll see you then.
Tomorrow?
Sang-jin?
Sang-mi.
Sang-jin.
Is it really you?
I'm sorry.
This must be so hard for you.
No, don't worry.
I'm fine.
Sang-mi, I know that you can
get through this.
So stay strong for just a little longer.
You can do it.
Okay.
I'll be sure to do it.
I'll make sure
that I can get out of here
and go back out into the world.
Good.
Sang-jin.
I'll do it my way too.
Everyone who is considered
influential in Muji
is affiliated with that cult.
It's safe to assume that everyone
in the prosecution and police
has a connection
with the leader of the cult.
I know.
If the police weren't
under Guseonwon's control,
I wouldn't ask Dad for help.
Your dad?
Then why did you want to see me?
Because I can't
trust Dad.
And you can trust me?
I don't trust you either.
-Then what is this about?
-I know
that Dad is planning
on running for provincial governor.
If I disclose the relationship
between you and him,
it'll ruin the upcoming election for him.
What are you trying to do now?
I'm asking you for a favor in a way
that you won't be able to refuse.
Whom do you think people will
believe more between you
and your dad?
Muji-gun is such a small place.
Whether people believe it or not,
the word will spread.
He'll sort out the situation at all costs
to get elected as provincial governor.
Do you think he'll give up everything
and choose you?
-This sounds like a threat.
-You have to
help me out.
Hello.
-You're Dong-cheol, right?
-Yes.
I'll give you a ride. Hop on.
It's a long walk to the bus station.
I'd appreciate that, but...
It's okay.
We have to go to the market anyway.
Please get in.
-Are you sure?
-Yes, of course.
Thank you.
By the way, how did you hurt
your face like that?
You mean this?
I fell on my face when I was drunk.
Oh, no.
By the way, have you been living here
for a long time?
I think it's been about a year.
I moved here.
I see.
Can I ask why you decided to move here?
My dad wanted to live somewhere quiet.
I guess he's burnt out
from running his business.
What kind of business is it?
Don't worry. It's totally fine.
Go ahead and answer it.
Thank you.
(Hey, why didn't you call us?
We were so worried.)
-I'll call you back later--
(-Hey, cut it out.)
(We've been waiting for you all day long.
Why didn't you call us?)
Darn it. I'll pay you back, okay?
Gosh, how can you treat
your friend like this?
(Hey, what are you talking about now?)
Hey, don't you know how well
my dad's business is doing these days?
Are you really going to be like this
over a few thousand dollars?
Cut it out, okay?
I'll tell my dad to send you
the money right away.
I have to go.
I didn't want to ask Dad for help
because it'd hurt my pride.
What a pathetic loser.
I was too loud, wasn't I?
Gosh, don't worry.
It's totally fine.
By the way, it sounds like
your dad's business
is very successful.
My dad?
No, it's just a small business.
What did he say?
Has he gone crazy?
He talked about money
and some kind of a business.
He must be still with them.
Oh, you're right.
I told you to stop calling him.
I was just worried about him.
If this goes wrong, it's all on you.
-Why would it be my fault?
-Because it is.
I called him because I was worried...
I'm speechless.
Fine. Blame this finger, then.
I dialed him with it.
-Do you want to break it or what?
-Yes, I will.
-Come here.
-I was just kidding. Gosh.
What the heck are you idiots
doing right now?
Can you please stop swearing so much?
It's not like I come here
to get cursed at...
What's that?
Isn't it an assorted skewer platter?
I love skewers.
Ma'am.
Have you lost your mind?
sister
What? Why did you call me?
That's right.Sister,come on.
Your skewers are the most delicious food
on this planet.
Aren't I right? Yes.
Sister,you're the best.
All right, fine. Eat up, guys.
Nicely done. Eat up.
It's good.
(GUSEONWON)
Oh, right. Wait, Dong-cheol.
What's your number?
Give me your phone.
I'll punch it in for you.
Sure.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
-Here.
-Great.
I'll call you tomorrow, then.
That's my number.
Please make sure you save it.
I'm Apostle Jo Wan-tae.
Apostle Jo.
Yes. I'll see you here tomorrow.
-Okay. See you.
-I love you.
Hey, it's me.
Where are you guys?
Do you guys think you live here or what?
Day or night,
all you guys do is fool around.
A pint of beer, please.
Dong-cheol.
Where's Sang-mi? Did you see her?
No, I didn't.
Does that mean she's locked up?
Did you see anything weird
or spooky?
I was quite surprised.
The people there
actually looked happy.
Don't let them fool you.
They look like nice people on the outside,
but they're all rotten inside.
All right.
Well
I'm supposed to see them again tomorrow.
I should be able to find something
if I go back there.
But
don't you guys think
this is too dangerous?
It's a good thing
that we're trying to help her,
but we should think about our safety too.
Just don't turn on your live broadcast.
That's what you can do to help us.
Here. You should eat.
Trying to fight off the demons
has weakened you so much.
I thought about it all night,
and I realized that I tried
to run away every time.
I won't run away anymore though.
I'll be sure
to destroy that place.
Good.
You're doing very well.
"Your patience"
"will earn you a new life."
Sang-mi.
Now, recite
the Prayer of Salvation
for me.
"You are"
"the King of our paradise,"
"our creator,"
"and the absolute true love."
"I confess all of my sins to you"
"and give you my everything."
"Almighty."
"Please allow me
to be in the light of your glory."
"With my utmost gratitude,"
"I will serve you"
"and Spiritual Father."
"I give you"
"all of my heart."
"My love."
"My salvation."
"Our wishes"
"will be fulfilled."
Hello?
(Your dad wants to see you.)
(Come to the sanitarium.)
(GUSEONWON SANITARIUM)
You'll wear it
at the announcement ceremony
during the service today.
Try it on.
After Spiritual Father's announcement,
you'll receive training
to become Spiritual Mother.
Then you'll have a spiritual wedding.
That's why it's important for you
to take great care of yourself.
Come on. Go ahead and try it on.
Ms. Kim, what do you think?
Spiritual Mother looks exquisite.
How beautiful.
You're stunning.
Mom.
Don't worry.
You and I
will be happy again
like we used to be.
Thank you for coming all the way here.
Sang-hwan, you made it.
That's my son.
Your son has such a pure soul.
(SAVE ME)
(SPIRITUAL FATHER'S OFFICE)