(SAVE ME)
(FINAL EPISODE)
Here. I will show you
what is true and what is false.
Apostle Kang.
-No.
-Our wishes will be fulfilled.
Oh, no.
Now, take a look.
Do you think this Book of Salvation
which burned to ashes is the truth?
Or am I, whom even the fire
couldn't hurt, the truth?
-Spiritual Father.
-Goodness.
I shall now stay within you.
I shall declare the truth
through your mouth.
I shall lift your arm
and perform miracles.
And I shall lead you
to the door to salvation.
-Our wishes will be fulfilled.
Why did you want to see me?
Where did you hide my mom?
We didn't hide her.
We just moved her to a better place
for her treatment.
You satisfy your desire
using a powerless person.
It's just like that cult.
You and my dad are
as crazy as them!
You will realize it after a while.
In this world,
what's real and what's false
are not different.
So don't try so hard to distinguish
the real from the false.
It will only make your life harder.
If that's how you live your life,
I will never live mine the same way.
I told you to give me
the voice recorder
if you want to see your mom.
It looked like
your mom misses you a lot.
Your... Your father
He
pushed me.
How could you
How could you do this to me?
Ji-hui is your assistant!
It's a misunderstanding.
There seems to be
a big misunderstanding.
Withdraw your candidacy.
What?
If it's really a misunderstanding
just like you said,
withdraw your candidacy.
Tomorrow is the election.
I want Sang-hwan
to lead an honorable life.
If you don't,
I will give this dash camera footage
to Mr. Cheon, your competitor.
No. Give it to me.
Hi, is this Mr. Cheon's
campaign office?
Yes.
You
and I
will have a spiritual wedding
and become one.
I will be at your service.
My savior.
My eternal life.
My
Spiritual Father.
Your mother will be so happy
when she sees you
wearing this wedding dress.
I'm sure Sang-jin will be happy too.
It was that day.
-What?
-That day,
if I had done everything I could
to stop you,
would things have turned out differently?
Sang-mi.
Your mother shouldn't be taken
to the hospital.
The only place that can treat her
is Guseonwon.
Dad.
I pity you now.
What are you talking about?
Why would you pity me?
Because
you're not aware of how horrible
this situation is.
Sang-mi.
You shouldn't think like that anymore.
You should be grateful for
how blessed you are.
Just look forward to all
the miraculous things
that will come your way.
Okay?
(FLAME RESISTANT)
-My goodness.
-Unbelievable.
Apostle Kang.
What are you doing here?
Our Almighty said
we can use white lies
as strategies for salvation.
Aren't I right?
It doesn't matter whether you
tell the truth or lie.
Spreading our Almighty's words
is a great thing in itself.
Therefore, our Almighty shall
continue to be happy.
Are you
being swayed right now?
No.
My devotion towards our Almighty
will never get swayed.
Then why
do I see
doubt in your eyes?
It's not because I doubt our Almighty.
It's because I doubt you.
Did you just say that
you're doubting me right now?
Evil spirits keep spreading in Guseonwon.
I'm doubtful if you're fulfilling
your duty of spreading
our Almighty's
words.
Doubt.
Anxiety.
Fear.
These are all
thoughts of the devil.
I want you to go
to the prayer room right now
and repent.
If I don't contact you
by tomorrow morning
Will you really be able
to disclose all this?
You're basically strangling
your father with your own hands.
You can
disclose everything about my dad.
Is there a patient named
Chae Min-hwa here?
No.
Can you check again?
Her name is Chae Min-hwa.
Please do me a favor.
Hello? Excuse me!
Hey, Man-hui.
Is she not there either?
Okay.
I'll go downtown to look for her.
Call me if you find anything.
Okay, thanks.
Why isn't anyone coming out?
My goodness.
-Are you okay?
-Please...
call
my son.
You want me to call your son?
What happened?
They They brought me here
against my will.
You were forced to come here?
Han Sang...
-Hwan.
-What?
Han
Han Sang...
-Hwan.
Is that your son's name?
Han Sang-hwan?
Do you know his phone number?
Salvation.
Eternal life.
Salvation. Eternal life.
Go to your room.
You should go to sleep.
Our Almighty.
Our wishes will be fulfilled.
Hello?
(Are you Han Sang-hwan?)
Yes, that's me.
Your mother's safe. Don't worry.
Who are you? No. Where is she?
She's at Guseonwon Sanitarium.
Wait. Wait.
(Sang-hwan, it's going to happen
today at dawn.)
(I'm going to do as we planned.
I'll see you at dawn.)
(RESET SETTINGS: YOU WILL NOT BE
ABLE TO RESTORE ANY INFORMATION)
How dare you
try to seduce my daughter?
That's enough, Apostle Im.
This is the only way we can
shake this place upside down.
If he finds out
that I'm Sang-hwan's friend,
he'll lock me up
in the basement storage
with other people.
He said he had a cellphone
inside that water tank.
Why are you doing this to me?
Stop it. It's all over now.
I found it.
It was true.
Take him.
When you met him outside,
what did he say to you?
He said he would save people here
if I pretend not to know him.
Those evil demons.
This is how foolish people
in the outside world are.
Our wishes will be fulfilled.
I believe it.
Sir. Are you okay?
Home... I want to go home.
Excuse me. Please wake up.
We have to get out of here.
Excuse me.
Please don't hurt me.
You shouldn't have been born
in the first place.
Whenever I see you,
I can feel my rage boiling up, you brat.
You should just die!
Dad.
Why Why are you here?
Why? Why!
Don't hit me. Please don't hit me.
Dad.
Is this why you couldn't be there
when Grandma died?
Please don't kill me. Please.
Please don't kill me.
I am
never going to forgive you all.
I'm going to kill all of you myself.
Please don't kill me.
Please...
Hi, Sang-hwan.
(Jeong-hun, do me a favor.)
What is it?
I'm on my way to Guseonwon now.
We're going with Dong-cheol's plan.
If you don't hear from me until
the morning, report it to the police
(and come to Guseonwon.)
No, Sang-hwan. That's not good.
Hold on.
(Don't go there. Let's just...)
Let's talk in person.
Where are you now?
Jeong-hun, Dong-cheol and Sang-mi
are waiting for me now.
-Please do as I said.
(-Sang-hwan, hang on.)
Sang-hwan. Sang-hwan
Guseonwon's secret funds are
inside the vault
in Spiritual Father's office.
The believers will leave
after the morning worship,
so we'll get inside the office then.
Okay?
Almighty.
Guseonwon,
the Boat of Salvation, is
about to sink to the bottom
of the sea now.
Please,
do not let
this Boat of Salvation sink.
Please protect Guseonwon.
Yes, Almighty.
I will do it.
If you
use me as the guardian
of the Boat of Salvation,
I will change everything here
into something new.
I will do that, Almighty.
Mom!
Hey, carry this around you at all times.
-What is this for?
-It has
a location-tracking device in it,
so I can see where you are.
If we end up going with your plan,
I can find you without searching around.
Sang-hwan.
Although I'm here,
I'm not worried at all.
I know you will come for me.
I know you will come
and tell me to stand tall
just like before.
Let's go.
Are you feeling okay?
I'm fine.
Let's go.
Sang-mi!
There you are, Sang-mi.
Are you ready to do this now?
Yes.
I will save this place
no matter what.
Yes.
There is still enough time.
The fire of our Almighty
will burn away all your sins, and it will
make you become
as light as a feather.
-Our wishes will be fulfilled.
-We believe it!
Those who wish receive
the fire of our Almighty,
please stand up.
The fire of our Almighty shall be
generously given to everyone here.
-We believe it!
-Our wishes will be fulfilled!
Here is the fire of our Almighty!
Fire!
Wan-deok.
Let's go.
Dong-cheol.
Dong-cheol!
Sang-hwan.
Sang-hwan! I'm in here!
Sang-hwan!
Sang-hwan! Over here!
Spiritual Mother.
It's time for you to go now.
-Are you okay, Dong-cheol?
-Yes, I'm okay.
I can't believe this.
It's me. It's me, Jeong-hun.
Dong-cheol.
Dong-cheol, are you okay?
Are you okay? My gosh.
What is this place?
I can't believe this.
Those people that you saw are all here.
You should call the police,
and take everyone here to the hospital.
Okay, okay. What about you guys?
We have to go save Sang-mi.
Okay, leave this place to us.
You guys should go.
Okay.
My dad's
in here as well.
I thought he just left home.
But I guess he was brought here.
Please take good care of him.
Okay. Don't worry.
We'll take good care of him.
Don't worry.
Let's go.
Be careful, okay?
You and your daughter
were being controlled by the devil.
That's why these pills never
worked on you.
I never should have brought
your family here.
You were once a mother yourself.
I heard other people talk about you.
I heard that
you also had a daughter like Sang-mi.
Do you want Sang-mi to die
like your daughter did?
If you were once a mother,
please let her go now.
These are your clothes.
You'll be spotted easily
with that patient gown on.
So you should change into something else
and get out of here.
Your daughter
will be sleeping with
Spiritual Father soon.
Okay.
Let's just burn everything
and start all over again.
Then I'll be able to go to paradise
with my daughter
and meet our Almighty.
Come in, Sang-mi.
(SPRITUAL FATHER)
Apostle Im.
You may now excuse us and go pray.
Okay. Our wishes will be fulfilled.
I believe it.
Do not be afraid.
You will
also enjoy this.
You devils!
How dare you come here?
Get lost right now!
Sang-hwan, you should go save her.
Okay. I'll go first.
Where do you think you're going?
Don't refuse
the touch of Almighty.
You devil.
Die!
I can't watch this anymore.
Dong-cheol.
Let's do some workout, shall we?
You go first.
In order to remove your sin,
you have to share
both your body and soul with me.
Only then will I
be able to give you my best
spiritual energy.
This is just the way you used
to violate women.
With your filthy tongue.
Don't try to fight this
if you do not wish to die
at such a young and beautiful age
just like Apostle Kang's daughter, Yu-ra.
How many were there?
How many people have you killed?
We will all
meet again in the paradise.
Everyone including Sang-jin
and Jeong-gu.
Murderer.
You are a murderer!
I'm not too late, am I?
Let's go.
You crazy jerk.
I'm Almighty.
How dare you!
You're a crazy man.
Do you really believe you're Almighty?
You're wrong. You're just a beast.
Sang-mi.
Sang-mi!
Mom!
-Sang-mi!
-Mom.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry I came too late.
No, Mom. I'm okay.
Are you okay?
Did you get evidence?
The truth of that filthy man is
all recorded in here.
I'm going to reveal it now.
Yes. Everything is over now.
Come on. Let's get out of here.
Let's go.
Where do you think you're going?
Sang-mi!
Put that knife down.
You can never get out of here.
Sang-mi. Sang-mi!
-Mom.
-Move. I said, move!
Sang-mi!
Mom, don't come closer.
Do not follow us.
If you do
Sang-mi
Ms. Kim.
I'll take care of her. Go.
Make sure she's okay.
Ms. Kim, are you all right?
Apostle Kang.
What are you
doing right now?
This is the divine message
Almighty sent me.
I heard a clear and distinct voice.
I will burn down every filthy sin
in this place
and start anew.
Have you lost your mind?
I'm Almighty.
How dare you.
Sang-mi.
Almighty will
turn this place into a new one.
What
are you doing?
I will
burn down this filthy place.
Sang-mi.
What?
Are you afraid?
I... I'm sorry.
Forgive me.
No.
You deserve to die.
Die
and fall into the fire pit!
Sang-mi!
Don't do that.
If you do,
you will become a murderer.
No.
I will
end his life myself no matter what.
Didn't you tell me
you would get out of this horrible place
and go back to the world outside?
Let's let him
be judged by the law.
I am...
I am Almighty.
I have eternal life. I am immortal!
It's dangerous.
Let's get out of here.
Help me!
No!
Are you okay?
It's all over now.
Finally,
the time that felt like
a nightmare is over.
You've been strong.
Can you walk?
Yes.
I will
walk out of here by myself proudly.
This place became a total mess
while I was gone.
This is the paradise.
Those evil devils.
I'm going to kill them.
Sang-mi. Spiritual Father.
No. No!
Listen to it and decide for yourself.
My dad...
I mean,
the governor of Muji-gun.
This will tell you everything
about the relationship
between him and the cult leader.
What if it's a complete
waste of time again?
And we'll get in trouble
if Chief finds out about this.
Shut it, you idiot.
Hey, drive faster.
-You devils!
-Go away!
-Leave our premises!
-How dare you set foot here?
-Get out of our premises!
-Go away!
-Get lost!
-Almighty will punish you all.
-Go away!
-All right. Make way, please.
-Move out of our way!
-Get lost!
How dare you set foot
on these grounds?
Spiritual Father is Almighty.
-Go away, you devils!
-Go away!
Why are you guys just standing?
Arrest them!
-Make way!
-Go away!
How dare you!
-My gosh.
-Who is he?
For goodness' sake.
Aren't you believers of Almighty?
Why are you acting like hoodlums?
-Get that jerk.
-Yes, let's go.
-Get him!
-Stop right there!
-Stop!
-Go away!
No.
My daughter must become Spiritual Mother.
She must. I ought to make her
become Spiritual Mother.
-What about Sang-mi?
-She'll be okay.
Gosh, you rat. Dong-cheol.
My life has become a mess
because of you guys.
You must be ready
for the consequences.
What should we do?
Please don't worry.
Stay right behind me, okay?
Wan-deok.
Dong-cheol!
You rats ruined everything.
Because of you punks.
You jerks. It's all your fault.
Hey, Mr. Curly Hair.
Mr. Gatekeeper.
Mom.
I told you to never trust anybody.
You guys are surely friends.
You're like two peas in a pod.
Hey, aren't you embarrassed that
you're fighting with kids?
How about a showdown with me?
Mr. Curly Hair.
-You piece of...
-Jerk!
You little...
Jerk! You piece of...
You scum. Get a taste of this, jerk!
You rats got me into this mess!
I warned you not to act up,
you scumbag.
Gosh, those crazy pagans.
They sure are persistent.
Bring it on.
Is it you, Apostle Jo?
Oh, look who's here.
Sergeant Woo, it's you.
What happened to you?
What are you doing here?
I must say,
I think Almighty loves me very much.
Who would've thought
I would run into you here?
Please Help me.
Hurry, let's get out of here.
I asked you what you're doing here.
I hope you're not trying to flee alone.
What are you doing now?
You stay out.
I'll take care of this.
Wait.
Do you think
that nothing will happen
to you if I get arrested?
You'll be doomed too. You got that?
Those who have sinned must be punished.
Officer Choe.
Arrest both of us.
-Sorry?
-Didn't you hear me? Arrest us!
Come on.
No.
Apostle Kang.
A new chapter has begun.
Sorry?
This was what Almighty wanted.
Yes, Almighty.
I'll rise again
and spread your word
to the entire world.
Will we really be able
to rise again?
Of course.
-Come on!
-Let go of us!
Dong-cheol.
Take care of the rest for me.
I need to find my mom.
All right. I know that you'll find her,
Sang-hwan.
Just a second.
Is your name Han Sang-hwan?
Yes.
Han
-Sang Hwan.
-Sang?
Is your mother ill by any chance?
Are you the one who called me?
Yes, it was me.
I'll show you where your mom is.
-I'll get going.
-All right. I'll see you later.
Sang-hwan.
Thanks.
Had you not heard what I said
in the van that day, I would have
fallen apart a long time ago.
Save me.
What a surprise.
I didn't think you'd ever thank me.
See you later.
-Mom.
-Yes?
If an omnipotent being
really exists up there,
he'll be sure to punish them, right?
Of course.
He will definitely answer our prayers.
(In mountains in Muji-gun,
North Gyeongsang Province,)
(many dead bodies have been found,
and the news has left many in shock.)
(They're speculated to have been
buried by a religious organization,)
(and wounds that could have been
caused by assault have been found,)
(so it looks like the police
will carry out autopsies.)
My father, Governor Han Yong-min,
colluded with a religious cult
and tried to build a sanitarium
in order to obtain
and launder illegal funds.
Also, in order to conceal
his corrupt deeds,
on June 29, 2016,
he pushed my mother,
Chae Min-hwa, down a mountain hill
in an attempt to kill her.
I would like to take this chance
to report my father,
Governor Han Yong-min,
-to the police.
-How do you feel now?
Don't worry.
Things will quiet down very soon.
You should hire lawyers first
so that we can
This must be the end.
I wanted to see how high you can go up,
but I ended up seeing you
fall hard instead.
Ji-hui.
You should get going.
Please come with us, Mr. Han.
There he is! He's coming!
-There he is.
-He's here.
He's here.
Sir, do you admit that you attempted
to murder your wife?
Do you admit that you colluded
with a religious cult?
A reporter who was working
on a story about them was murdered.
Please say a few words.
I will answer all questions
in detail in court.
-How do you feel now?
-Say a few words.
-Sir, please say a few words.
-Sir!
Hello, Senator Choe.
It's me, Lee Ji-hui.
How have you been?
I'm thinking of moving back
to Yeouido.
If you have some time--
Ms. Lee, where do you think you're going?
Sorry?
You need to be interviewed as a witness.
You were in the same boat
with Mr. Han, you know.
Sir, I'll call you back in a bit.
Go on. I'll follow you.
-There he is.
-It must be him.
Sir, how do you feel now?
Please say a few words.
-Please say a few words!
-Are the allegations true?
Sir!
-We love you
-Almighty
-Spiritual Father gives us joy
Do you really believe that
your leader is still alive?
How dare you!
-I saw it with my own two eyes.
-That's right.
Spiritual Father ascended
to the sky in a big whiff of smoke.
He even waved his hand at me like this.
I know that he'll be resurrected.
Totally. Look at this. This is
his autograph.
Salvation and immortal life.
He'll be resurrected and return to us!
That's right!
You devils. If you look down on us,
three generations of your family
will end up in the fiery pit!
His grace and kindness saved us.
-He never duped us!
-Exactly!
She's absolutely right.
-Spiritual Father gives me joy
-I love you, Almighty
All of you survived
the Day of Judgment because
you were chosen by Almighty.
Do you all believe it?
-We believe it.
"Ask,"
"and you shall receive."
"Seek,"
"and you shall find the answer."
"Knock,"
"and the door will open."
All those who ask shall receive,
all those who seek
will find the answer,
and the door will open
for all those who knock.
So far, we've been
trying to find a way to make
the Boat of Salvation float again
by asking and praying to Almighty
with all of our hearts
to find the answer.
And finally, Almighty
spoke clearly to me.
He told me
that this place will become
Guseonwon's new sanctuary.
Do you all believe it?
-We believe it, Spiritual Mother!
(IM SANG-JIN,
AUGUST 2, 1998 - MARCH 10, 2014)
Sang-jin.
I'll never become weak like that again.
Sang-mi and I will try to live
our lives to the fullest,
so you should rest in peace now.
Sang-jin.
Mom and I want to be happy now
so that
you don't have to worry about us
and smile in the real paradise.
Bye, My lovely son.
Have you eaten yet?
What about you?
Not yet.
Do you want to eat jjajangmyeon?
Sure.
My dad and I will challenge
ourselves and see if we can do this.
In how many minutes?
All right. If we finish this
in five minutes, we don't have to pay.
-Do you think you can do it?
-Yes, sure.
-Will you be okay?
-Of course.
Then before we pick up
our chopsticks,
we should drink this
to protect our stomachs.
-Cheers.
All right, here we go.
Start!
Gosh, it's so spicy!
Look at this idiot. I'm out.
My mouth is on fire!
Goodness, why is this beer so bland?
Here.
Goodness, cut it out.
Come on.
-Me?
-Yes.
Make sure you chew well.
My gosh, what on earth
has gotten into you two?
Pil-su, this guy can be
so sweet like this.
Aren't I right?
Okay, I heard you.
Eat up.
Jun-gu, you should try this too.
-Drink up, guys.
-You too, Jun-gu.
-Let's do this.
-All right, cheers.
Cheers.
-I'll see you all soon.
-All right.
Sang-hwan, what you need in order
to thrive here isn't your brain
but your guts. You know that, right?
Is that right?
Is that why you got fired
from the courier service?
I hope you're not proud of that.
You need to use your brain.
You little...
Sang-hwan, Sang-hwan.
Gosh, my eyes are welling up with tears.
When he was a toddler,
I changed his diapers
and fed him.
-I even carried him around--
-Isn't your enlistment next week?
Shut it! I want to pause time.
Time will keep flowing.
Make sure you don't skip meals, okay?
Don't you worry.
You should try to eat less, okay?
I should go in now. Here, guys.
Good luck.
See you soon.
I'll follow you soon.
I'll see you guys soon.
Has everything been well?
You'll visit us too, right?
We're all friends, you know.
Yes.
(People ask me)
(how I was able to hold out
at a place like that.)
(The hope that I'll be able
to get out of there one day.)
(The hope that the real omnipotent
being must be watching over us.)
(The hope that someone will answer)
(upon hearing my desperate cry.)
(Such hopes are
what got me through those days.)
(I believe)
(that such hopes still exist
in this world.)
(SAVE ME)
Almighty is the king
and the creator of the paradise.
You must believe Almighty!
The day of judgment is coming.
All of us must pray and repent our sins.
This world is filled with evil souls.
You must believe Almighty.
Spiritual Father is still alive.
Pray and repent your sins.
The day of judgment
is just around the corner.
The day of salvation is near.
I'm certain that Spiritual Father
will return to us!