♪Having seen thousands of peaks♪
♪And the wilderness
where you traveled with me♪
♪Memories are intertwined♪
♪Thoughts are revealed♪
♪Forgetting is the hardest thing of all♪
♪Even though my heart
and mind are full of you♪
♪It's all turned into a thousand knots♪
♪How can the knots in my heart be untied
when I miss you?♪
♪Let me rise and fall with the wind,
with the moon's cycle♪
♪Perish with the phantom♪
♪And head for the fireworks with you♪
♪Even though my heart
and mind are full of you♪
♪It's all turned into a thousand knots♪
♪How can the knots in my heart be untied
when I miss you?♪
♪Let me rise and fall with the wind,
with the moon's cycle♪
♪Perish with the phantom♪
♪And head for the fireworks with you♪
♪Our hearts belong to each other♪
=The Glamorous Revenge=
=Episode 19=
(Two Months Later)
(Blooming Beauty Parlor)
(Grand Opening)
Let's toast to our new life.
Cheers!
Miss Zhaozhao,
why aren't you eating?
I'm not hungry. You guys eat.
Here you go.
These are all your favorites.
Miss Zhaozhao,
don't you already have a lot of money?
Why do you open a shop?
You're worn out
and become slimmer.
Let me tell you,
money will run out one day.
If someday
I'm no longer here,
at least you all
will have a skill to rely on
and a place to go.
What's wrong with you today?
Your words
sound as if you won't be
here anymore tomorrow.
You're overthinking.
I'm just hoping
that even without me,
they all can live well.
Come on,
let's drink.
Let me go check it out.
(Blooming Beauty Parlor)
(A brew from days gone by,
a toast to new beginnings.)
Thank you for coming, see you next time.
Zhaozhao,
why do you look so pale?
I'm fine.
I might not
have slept well last night.
There wasn't any business
a few days ago.
And, today,
we have so many customers showing up.
You don't know?
Recently, a famous painter came to town,
and he's been recommending
this place to every guest.
A painter?
Could it be...
Just ignore that.
We've got business now,
why not we just carry on?
Let's just do the work.
You're welcome.
Thanks.
Take care.
Miss,
what kind of makeup would you like?
I'd like the shopkeeper
to help me cover this injury on my face.
How did you hurt?
I...
I fell by accident.
Did you people hide my wife here?
Get her out!
You, come out!
Is he your husband?
You wench,
I've got you here.
Trying to have makeup like the others?
Look in the mirror yourself.
You disgrace!
Let's see how I deal with you
when we get home.
Come with me.
Hey!
You're not allowed to leave.
You cause trouble
in this Blooming Beauty Parlor.
I'll report you
to the government office.
What...
What's the matter with you?
This...
This is my family matter.
You want to get my husband
locked up in prison?
How can you do that?
Wait...
But he's beaten you to this extent,
and you're still defending him?
Aren't you getting no enough of it?
And you,
if she leaves you one day,
won't you regret it?
Regret?
You can ask her.
She is just a woman with no strengths,
where can she go without me?
Either way, I'll just
apologize to her afterwards.
She'll still have to follow me.
You women
are all the same.
What you experienced today
is what you brought upon yourself.
You know if this man truly loved you,
he wouldn't let you suffer
even a little.
You cling
to the bit of sweetness.
Even though you're being
treated as just a plaything,
and being pushed around here and there,
you still obsess about it.
What did you say?
I said,
all this misery
is what you brought on yourself.
You!
What?
Both of you, get out of here.
Leave my Blooming Beauty Parlor now.
Let's go.
Quickly!
You!
Don't force me to hit you.
Faster!
How dare you run away!
Zhaozhao,
are you okay?
Did that scare you?
Let me call you a doctor here.
I'm fine.
Look at you now,
since when did you become so fussy?
I care about you,
and you're teasing me!
How ungrateful you are!
I should ignore you now.
I'm going to sleep.
Aren't you curious what this is?
Whether it's Intestine-Piercing Powder
or Puppet String Medicine,
it's just to make sure
I won't turn on you.
Xu Zhaozhao,
to Lin Muxuan, you're just a pawn.
Is it worth it for you
to do so much for him?
(Lin Muxuan,)
(for that jar of wine,)
(A toast to new beginnings.)
(I'm afraid I won't ever drink it.)
(The heavens and earth are too far apart.)
(Let our relationship)
(be buried along with that wine.)
When you
have the first sip of this wine,
it tastes strong.
But the more you drink,
the better it gets.
If you like it,
how about we find a day
to bury a jar of the wine together
and dig it up to drink
in coming year?
Why wait until another day?
Let's do it today.
Faster!
Keep crying.
You always cry.
Who are you?
Apologize to your wife!
Why...
Why should I apologize?
After all, she is my wife.
Why should I...
Apologize now.
I'm sorry.
She's been defending you
out of her love for you.
That's not an excuse
for you to mistreat her.
As a man, you can't uphold
the most basic principle of trust,
and you can't even
protect her wholeheartedly,
don't you feel ashamed?
And you!
Shopkeeper Xu has been defending you.
But, what you did today
has broken her heart.
The two of you go to the Blooming Beauty
Parlor and apologize to her tomorrow.
If she doesn't forgive you,
I won't either.
Understand?
- Understood.
Hubby.
Shopkeeper Xu,
it was my fault for yesterday.
I'm not even human.
I came today to apologize.
Shopkeeper Xu,
I'm sorry.
I didn't acknowledge
your good intentions.
Alright.
But
I don't have much to say.
Go back
and treat your wife nicely.
Shopkeeper Xu,
if you don't forgive me,
that man won't let me off.
Who's he?
♪The boat is already covered in snow♪
♪Unable to bear the weight of longing,
thus I bid farewell to you♪
♪You shine like the moon
surrounded by myriads of stars♪
♪While I am a flickering light♪
♪Keeping watch whole night
on the empty long street♪
♪Having seen thousands of peaks♪
♪And the wilderness
where you traveled with me♪
It's about to rain.
Let's find a place to take shelter.
♪A brilliant stroke caught
in a painting of smoky willows♪
♪Flying flowers hover
in front of the window♪
♪The stars and the moonlight
shine brightly♪
♪The world is bustling with life♪
♪Looking back to my love,
it's hard to realise♪
♪The past comes back to me
in a flood of memories♪
♪The first glance brings
a long-held dream to life♪
♪Tossing and turning in the night
with sorrow and joy in heart♪
♪Put on some make-up♪
♪The changes in the world won't change♪
♪My love for you♪
♪From day to day and from year to year♪
♪Our fate is fading♪
♪Tears are scorching my eyes♪
♪In the twinkling of an eye,
the clouds roll with the wind♪
♪Touching my fingertips,
no amount of reincarnation♪
♪Can erase our memories of each other♪
♪From day to day and from year to year♪
♪Where to find a graceful presence?♪
♪No one in the world
is in charge of their own fate♪
♪The best years are dyed with frost,
the lanterns are lit♪
♪The musical instruments are chorded,
autumn cicadas are leaning on the tree♪
♪But I say with a smile
that I have no regrets in my life♪
♪I will not betray your heart♪
♪And soul♪