♪Having seen thousands of peaks♪
♪And the wilderness
where you traveled with me♪
♪Memories are intertwined♪
♪Thoughts are revealed♪
♪Forgetting is the hardest thing of all♪
♪Even though my heart
and mind are full of you♪
♪It's all turned into a thousand knots♪
♪How can the knots in my heart be untied
when I miss you?♪
♪Let me rise and fall with the wind,
with the moon's cycle♪
♪Perish with the phantom♪
♪And head for the fireworks with you♪
♪Even though my heart
and mind are full of you♪
♪It's all turned into a thousand knots♪
♪How can the knots in my heart be untied
when I miss you?♪
♪Let me rise and fall with the wind,
with the moon's cycle♪
♪Perish with the phantom♪
♪And head for the fireworks with you♪
♪Our hearts belong to each other♪
=The Glamorous Revenge=
=Episode 13=
You...
are from the Bai family.
Lin Muxuan
planned all of this
just to save you.
He
doesn't know that I'm still alive.
On the day
the Bai family was annihilated,
he was the only one
who escaped.
He
was adopted by my father.
We grew up together,
like siblings.
He planned all of this for you.
He deserves the title of a true sibling.
Is he
doing well?
He is
doing well.
He made a lot of money.
He established a secret organization,
and many people work for him.
He also opened
a beauty service shop.
The business is very well.
That's good.
I knew
he would
live well.
Master,
you leave first.
Go to save Miss Xu.
Lin Muxuan.
I'm sorry.
I'm late.
You came to save me?
Let's seize the time.
The others can't hold them
off for so long.
Alright.
Muxuan.
Shiwan.
You're still alive.
I'll get you out too.
Lin Muxuan, leave here quickly.
Just leave me here.
I won't leave you here.
There's no way
you can get both of us out
of this dungeon by yourself.
You need to go now.
Never try,
never know.
Be careful.
If you insist on staying here,
all three of us will die here.
Take her and leave.
Zhaozhao.
Hurry!
Leave now.
Go.
Leave here!
Lin Fan!
Master!
I can only accompany you this far.
Lin Fan!
Leave now!
Let me ask you,
do you
know about
the Color-Changing Flower?
Do you know the Color-Changing Flower?
Xu Zhaozhao.
If there's a lipstick
that could show different colors
on different people's lips,
that means each of us
has our own unique color.
This Blossom Contest requires
a most iconic makeup product.
If I can find this flower
and make a lipstick from it,
we will surely stand out.
Lin Muxuan!
Don't try to dampen my spirit.
I
will never give up.
(Book of The Floral)
(Lin Muxuan.)
(If you got this,)
(it means I didn't win the champion
of the Blossom Contest.)
(Please)
(consider this as
my compensation to you.)
(I hope you won't be angry.)
(I've tried my best.)
♪A brilliant stroke caught
in a painting of smoky willows♪
♪Flying flowers hover
in front of the window♪
♪The stars and the moonlight
shine brightly♪
♪The world is bustling with life♪
♪Looking back to my love,
it's hard to realise♪
♪The past comes back to me
in a flood of memories♪
♪The first glance brings
a long-held dream to life♪
♪Tossing and turning in the night
with sorrow and joy in heart♪
♪Put on some make-up♪
♪The changes in the world won't change♪
♪My love for you♪
♪From day to day and from year to year♪
♪Our fate is fading♪
♪Tears are scorching my eyes♪
♪In the twinkling of an eye,
the clouds roll with the wind♪
♪Touching my fingertips,
no amount of reincarnation♪
♪Can erase our memories of each other♪
♪From day to day and from year to year♪
♪Where to find a graceful presence?♪
♪No one in the world
is in charge of their own fate♪
♪The best years are dyed with frost,
the lanterns are lit♪
♪The musical instruments are chorded,
autumn cicadas are leaning on the tree♪
♪But I say with a smile
that I have no regrets in my life♪
♪I will not betray your heart♪
♪And soul♪