♪Having seen thousands of peaks♪
♪And the wilderness
where you traveled with me♪
♪Memories are intertwined♪
♪Thoughts are revealed♪
♪Forgetting is the hardest thing of all♪
♪Even though my heart
and mind are full of you♪
♪It's all turned into a thousand knots♪
♪How can the knots in my heart be untied
when I miss you?♪
♪Let me rise and fall with the wind,
with the moon's cycle♪
♪Perish with the phantom♪
♪And head for the fireworks with you♪
♪Even though my heart
and mind are full of you♪
♪It's all turned into a thousand knots♪
♪How can the knots in my heart be untied
when I miss you?♪
♪Let me rise and fall with the wind,
with the moon's cycle♪
♪Perish with the phantom♪
♪And head for the fireworks with you♪
♪Our hearts belong to each other♪
=The Glamorous Revenge=
=Episode 16=
Zhaozhao.
Let's leave here quickly.
You were also a part
of Lin Muxuan's plan.
Meeting you
was indeed arranged by him.
So, you knew from the beginning
that Lin Muxuan never liked me.
You told me
that he liked me
just to avoid raising my suspicions
and keep me by his side.
I'm sorry, Zhaozhao.
So, you became friends with me
also because of Bai Shiwan?
No.
I truly saw you as a friend.
Truly?
I don't even know
what "truly" means anymore.
Zhaozhao.
Zhaozhao!
I've never considered you
as just an outsider.
Lin Muxuan wasn't indifferent
to you either.
Anyway,
he told me to wait for you here.
Where is he now?
He'll stay
at the Chancellor Residence.
He said
that after finding Bai Shiwan,
his desires had changed.
He will live happily
with Bai Shiwan
in the Chancellor Residence.
Let's leave here first.
What's inside here is exactly
the Bai family's
Disguise Technique secret book.
Bring it here.
The Chancellor may not know this,
but this box is designed
with a special mechanism.
If anyone other than
a Bai family descendant opens it,
the contents will be destroyed.
If that's the case,
then you open it.
You still dare to play games
with me even at this point?
Do you really think
I can't see through your trick?
I ask you one last time,
where exactly is
the Bai family's
Disguise Technique secret book?
There never was any
Bai family's Disguise Technique.
It was all
just a figment
of your delusional obsession.
Is that so?
I have plenty of ways
to torture you
until you feel neither living
nor dying,
until you hand over the secret book.
Take him away.
(Inner Pier)
You should leave now.
I've already prepared a boat.
The children at the Ciyou Hall
are still waiting for you.
What about you?
Where else could I go?
Of course,
I'll have to go back to being a dancer.
You're lying.
It's already come to this point.
There's nothing else
you should hide from me.
I did deceive you alongside Lin Muxuan.
But from now on,
you should live well
with the children in the Ciyou Hall.
I'll go back to my Twilight Pavilion.
Do you still need this
to return to Twilight Pavilion?
This is my...
If you don't tell me the truth,
I won't leave.
It's Lin Muxuan,
right?
He told me there was a way to save you,
but I never expected
that way
would be a life for a life.
Hold on.
He told me
that he's going to marry
Bai Shiwan after two days
at the Chancellor Residence.
Bai Shiwan
has already died.
You're such a glutton for punishment.
You feel suffered for not being beaten,
huh?
The Bai family's integrity
is something a treacherous man
like you won't understand.
Integrity?
The so-called integrity
is just because
it hasn't touched a person's
weakest spot yet.
You came here alone
to exchange your life for hers.
You must have planned a way out for her,
right?
The children in the Ciyou Hall
are being well taken care of,
which shows that
she is a kind person.
Don't ever try to hurt them.
You're willing to risk your life
for the Bai family's secret book,
but what about Miss Xu?
You don't care
about her life either?
It seems you truly believe
in the existence
of the Bai family's Disguise Technique.
In that case,
if I die,
the Bai family's Disguise Technique
will disappear with me.
If you dare hurt her,
you'll never get
the Bai family's Disguise Technique.
After all,
I'm the only one left
who knows anything about the Bai family.
If you don't want me to hurt her,
hand over the secret book.
Someone!
Keep questioning him. If he still
insists on not telling anything,
beat him
until he does.
Yes, sir.
What a stubborn man!
Keep beating him!
♪A brilliant stroke caught
in a painting of smoky willows♪
♪Flying flowers hover
in front of the window♪
♪The stars and the moonlight
shine brightly♪
♪The world is bustling with life♪
♪Looking back to my love,
it's hard to realise♪
♪The past comes back to me
in a flood of memories♪
♪The first glance brings
a long-held dream to life♪
♪Tossing and turning in the night
with sorrow and joy in heart♪
♪Put on some make-up♪
♪The changes in the world won't change♪
♪My love for you♪
♪From day to day and from year to year♪
♪Our fate is fading♪
♪Tears are scorching my eyes♪
♪In the twinkling of an eye,
the clouds roll with the wind♪
♪Touching my fingertips,
no amount of reincarnation♪
♪Can erase our memories of each other♪
♪From day to day and from year to year♪
♪Where to find a graceful presence?♪
♪No one in the world
is in charge of their own fate♪
♪The best years are dyed with frost,
the lanterns are lit♪
♪The musical instruments are chorded,
autumn cicadas are leaning on the tree♪
♪But I say with a smile
that I have no regrets in my life♪
♪I will not betray your heart♪
♪And soul♪