Light Shop
She must have been
in a lot of pain.
That's why we clean and shroud,
so painful reminders are put out of sight.
Right.
When she moves on...
she'll forget things,
like what went on here.
- Let's put her in.
- Okay.
- Do you know why we do a three-day wake?
- Uh.
Isn't it so that those in mourning
can have some time
to gather after a death?
Partly yes, but it's not just that.
So, what else?
It's our tradition.
We've done it for centuries.
We waited three days...
in the hopes that the deceased
might come back to life.
So it's the family's last chance
to hold onto hope
before they have to say
their final goodbyes.
Not just the living need to say goodbye.
The deceased need to say goodbye, too.
To the deceased, those days are a gift.
One last courtesy.
That's why it's a three-day wake.
Or in other words,
three days is all that remains
before there is nothing left.
Episode 6: Three-day Funeral
I love you.
I love you, Lee Jiyoung! Can you hear me?
Me, too!
Jiyoung, I love you, too.
Hhhh... huhh...
Hhh... huh...
Kim...
Hyun...
Min.
Kim...
Hyun...
Min.
Love you.
Miss you so much.
NOT IN SERVICE
Pay respects.
Ms. Lee Jiyoung, 32 years of age.
We are now going to remove
that which was left behind.
Um, I feel like a burglar
doing this at night, you know?
The landlord's trying to keep it quiet.
Oh, jeez.
You have no heart at all.
The lady only passed away just last night.
She's at rest, wherever she is.
Let's start with the store.
- Then we'll do her room.
- Right.
Let's start.
PRESS THE BUTTON IN CASE OF ABSENCE
Oh... she's a deaf per--
What's wrong?
- We need to go.
- What?
I don't think
she's left just yet.
What are you saying?
We'll come back later.
We're leaving.
Get the light.
What the hell.
What is this place?
Jeez.
Do you hear that sound?
What sound?
It's like a cutting sound.
Is it coming from the movie?
Hey, what are you doing?
There was a suitcase right here.
Wait, what?
Right here,
the seat's still down.
Maybe it's broken.
- I'm scared. I wanna go.
- Hey. Wait for me.
Don't... you recognize me?
Have we met already?
Sorry if that was forward.
I'll, uh, leave you.
Yeah. Yeah. Of course.
We met right here yesterday
and we talked and everything.
Oh, this is...
'Cause you saw me today, and yesterday,
and the day before that?
What about tomorrow?
What?
Well, it's nearly midnight,
and the day's ending soon.
Three days is all that remains
before there's nothing left.
I don't have much time left.
Hey, what is it?
- We have a problem, sir.
- Problem?
We need to clean the body,
but the door won't open.
Hmm?
That's odd.
The fridge is still working,
but the door is stuck.
Should I get someone to come take it off?
She must be resentful.
Let's give her time.
Uh, resentful?
Oh.
NAME: LEE JIYOUNG
AGE: 32
GENDER: FEMALE
REMARKS: FUNERAL ARRANGEMENT CONFIRMED
Why don't you stay a while?
It's raining hard.
I'll be fine.
You don't have an umbrella.
This is the only place open
at this hour.
The one you're looking for
could end up coming around.
You mind if it's instant coffee?
It's fine. Thanks.
What's with the look?
You've been studying my face
for quite some time now.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You always keep
a close eye on people, huh?
Well, it's my job to deal with customers.
You're wearing sunglasses,
I assume, because it's so bright?
Yes.
The young lady from before.
Young lady, stop.
Oh, that young lady.
It seems as if...
when you look at someone,
you seem to notice something's off.
Yeah, well, that's my job, you know.
Someone made that for me.
The girl who was here?
Yes.
You don't look old enough
to have a daughter her age.
My line of work has taught me
how to get a decent read on someone
with just a look.
Yet I just can't figure out
how old you are.
I had a daughter.
Do you have any children?
Yes, I did.
Named her, too.
We had a miscarriage.
The rain has stopped.
That's enough for now.
Will you look for him all night?
It's what I do.
Why are you working so hard to find him?
There isn't anything else I have left.
See you again.
Yeah.
I should be showing already,
don't you think?
I'll buy some meat in the morning, okay?
You need to slow down.
You working today?
They need me on the night shift,
last minute.
Why do you work all the time, huh?
It's about saving lives.
I need to do it.
I'm sorry.
ILKWANG GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
EUTTEUM
BOBAE
SOMANG
SARANG
HAETSAL
I was four months along...
and I wasn't showing at all.
It was a miscarriage.
I was alone at the hospital
and they told me.
I knitted her a hat,
I bought her shoes,
gave her a name, and a nickname too.
Your health... are you okay?
Hm.
I think so.
I'm just, uh...
I'm sorry.
Truly.
You feel sorry for our child?
Of course I do.
You're that dog, aren't you?
Stay quite.
There's a strange guy looking for you.
You'll get in trouble if he finds you.
Hey, hey.
Go away.
I said go away. Go. Go.
Hey, Mom! Mom! I'm home! Can--
Excuse me.
Do you live there?
What? Oh, yes.
Have you seen me before by chance?
Uh... no.
When did I even move in?
How long have you been living there?
Uh... uh...
Mister!
Leave him.
He's mine.
What?
Move. I'm in a hurry.
You two... remember each other.
We are the same, but...
...why am I different?
Why?
Mom! Mom, she's gone.
She's gone already!
Ah, jeez.
Mom, couldn't you hear me?
Didn't you hear me calling for you?
Why didn't you open the door?
And-- And what did that woman just say?
Mom, will you answer me?
You've been acting really weird lately.
Aw, come on,
just give me an answer!
What?
Light bulb?
No, I didn't buy a light bulb.
I can't go to the light shop anymore.
I'm scared to go!
I can't go, Mom!
I said I don't have a light bulb.
I've been running
into a lot of really weird people lately.
Mom, are you listening to me?
This is so frustrating!
You don't care about me at all!
I have no friends.
They ignore what I say
and pretend they don't even know me,
and think I'm weird.
Get rid of this!
You broke all this stuff!
If you're going to break it,
then why make me buy more?
I'm not going to buy a light bulb,
I can't do it!
I'm not leaving here again!
I don't know why...
you can't remember me.
Where do we go now?
Ma'am, what are you doing here?
Oh.
You can see me?
Yes.
Are you dead?
No.
I nearly died once.
Oh, my goodness. That's a new one.
The world is full of all sorts of people,
including those who are different.
Is that so?
May I ask what you're doing here?
They're crying.
And it's because of me. I can't stand it.
So I left.
- Hm.
- It was my time,
but they're all crying.
Who was that young man
who was sitting next to you earlier?
My youngest grandson.
I doted on him all the time.
He's a good-looking guy.
Right? So good-looking.
I'm going to forget my grandson.
That's the one thing I regret.
You will?
I get shrouded today.
Next day, I go.
Oh.
I'll forget
about this world when I go,
everything I knew.
Hmm.
Huh...
You have to forget it all.
It's the way it is.
Today is my last day.
I'm supposed to forget everything.
Yet I can't stop thinking
about my grandson.
I'd love it if someone could say I'm fine.
Could you do that?
Uh...
What is that?
It's my lunch.
Oh, you have to eat something hot,
it's not enough for you.
There's yukgaejang inside.
I'm eating this because it's good.
Tell me more about your grandson.
- Should I?
- Mm.
I loved and cared for him very much...
and I raised him
since he was just a little baby.
Mm.
Every time
I changed his dirty diaper,
he would smile so beautifully.
That's how I raised him.
And he is such a good boy.
He always put me first...
Hm.
What?
Huh? Nothing.
You have a cotton swab?
My ears are so itchy.
It's like I'm hearing things.
Maybe tinnitus?
Maybe your ears are sensitive.
Sensitive? Not tinnitus?
We've already done
everything we could for him.
There's nothing more that we can do.
His will to live is what's key now.
I'm sorry.
Where he'll find it...
is unfortunately something I don't know.
Maybe... I don't know...
there's a chance...
that will might not be his and his alone.
I have no idea
what kind of forces are keeping him alive.
It's a mystery.
Your guess is as good as mine.
This patient remains unconscious.
Where does his will come from?
You're in the way.
Go away, fuck!
Sounds like you're saying it's my fault
and we shouldn't see each other anymore.
- I'm the reason we--
- We?
We?
Then what the fuck are we gonna do?
- Sunhae, we should--
- Ugh, don't, don't!
I don't want you to say my name like that.
I don't ever wanna hear you say my name
like you care about me,
so just don't say it!
Her clasped hands are stuck
due to postmortem rigor mortis.
The person behind
saved the person in front.
EUGENE UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
I don't even know
how to look you in the eye right now.
I don't wanna be around you anymore, okay?
Turn around and get out of my sight!
IT WAS SUCH A TRAGIC ACCIDENT.
IT SHOULD NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN.
I HOPE YOU ARE WELL AND BE HAPPY THERE.
RESTRICTED AREA
OUTSIDERS NOT ALLOWED
- I'm going home.
- Ugh, I should go home, too.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
What are you doing here?
Huh?
Shouldn't you be in school?
I was looking for someone who's in there.
Who?
Visitors can't see patients
unless they're family.
He's a friend though,
and there's something I wanna give him.
Hmm, what should I do?
You're not allowed
to bring stuff from the outside.
What do you wanna give him?
I wanted to return this.
Who's it for?
I don't know his name,
but he put this around my neck
on the day of the accident.
I guess he really liked basketball.
Uh...
I know who that is.
I can return it to him.
- Do you mean it?
- Yes.
That's what I do.
What is it that you do?
Give me the ball.
- That thing you just did there...
- What?
...was an assist.
Shit.
Could I get another coffee?
It's weird.
It's not hot, and I can't taste it.
I suspected as much.
But I couldn't just go off a feeling.
You had to see yourself.
Yeah, so I was wandering around...
and noticed what was wrong.
It was my body.
How did you realize it?
A housewarming gift.
We've been saving for this house,
and I never got you anything to celebrate.
Hope you like.
I could see something was weird about it.
Other people don't notice anything at all.
- Other people?
- Yes.
A lot of different people
come into this light shop.
This is just a light shop.
So then where is this place?
I feel like... it's different.
How is it different?
The night never ends.
I need to know if I'm weird or if...
this place is weird.
Where is this place?
I used to ask the same question.
Translated by Sang Hee Park