Light Shop
And, there's a festival to enjoy.
ONE MONTH AGO
- ...108 times, something like that.
- ...no lanterns or anything.
It's only a matter of time
before Korea follows suit.
Don't you think we should keep up
the tradition though?
Damn it, fuck.
You bastard, I know it's you out there!
I told you I'm done with you!
I don't wanna see you anymore!
Fucker, I called the police, so go away!
You better stay away from me,
you son of a bitch!
Attention, please.
Passengers taking the 11:15 p.m.
late night bus
to Gangneung should board at platform 13.
Departing now.
Sir, open up.
- I'd appreciate your cooperation.
- Sure.
Could you turn off the engine, please?
This will only take a moment.
All passengers, please exit the bus.
I know it's inconvenient. I apologize.
Young lady, let's go.
Those windows don't open
for a reason.
Can't have an open window on the highway.
Too dangerous.
Just think about it.
What would you do if there's a fire?
Burning to death is one thing,
but the smoke you'd inhale...
You know...
a person died in a Cheonho-dong villa.
She lived alone on the third floor.
Smoke inhalation.
There's a fire, you see.
It was arson.
You did it.
Why do you look so shocked?
Hey, watch out.
- You're with the Eastern station, right?
- Yeah.
We're your support.
From here on, we'll take the suspect in.
- Sure, thanks.
- Okay.
Oh, wait. I didn't read that bastard
his Miranda rights.
Why not?
You're a newbie. Am I right?
Yeah.
He didn't deserve the courtesy. You do it.
- Uh, detective?
- Yeah? What?
This is a no-smoking zone.
Thank you, sir.
Ah, shit.
What the hell?
Great.
Come on, seriously?
Is nothing working?
Episode 3: The Detective
Boiling it
made it very tender,
which is exactly what we want because--
And the broth!
The taste of the broth
is top-notch, isn't it?
Yeah.
You should seriously try the galbi!
And know what?
The pork is so good on its own.
You don't even need side dishes.
Just add
some green onions as you go,
and then you eat it at home
with a slice of warm kimchi.
- So delicious.
- It turned out great.
- There's nothing else like it.
- I can't wait to try it at home.
Who is it?
The cooking time only-
PENDING CASES
SEOUL EASTERN POLICE AGENCY
CHEONHO VILLA ARSON CASE REPORT
CASE CLOSED
GANGDONG-GU MISUNG APARTMENT
DEATH CASE REPORT
Tsk. Why doesn't anything work?
Dispatch, we're at the scene.
Sorry for the trouble.
The charges have been cleared
following the investigation.
If you could just please sign here,
and then you're free to go.
Acknowledged.
Thank you.
Take care.
What?
The Amsa-dong elderly death case.
Yeah, and?
According to the witness,
that man was there at the scene,
so I called him in, but...
WITNESS KIM SANGHOON
This whole thing was an accident,
as it turns out.
Accident?
Well, the medical examiner
took one look at him
and confirmed it was a sudden death
from a stroke.
The Cheonho Villa
arson case is closed, right?
When we got the confession,
we learned
that he was the victim's stalker.
Since she refused to leave her house,
he just set it on fire.
Her ghost should punish that asshole
and send him to hell.
Nothing to report.
You haven't had lunch, right?
- What do you want?
- Uh, do you mean it's your treat?
How about this new
kimchi jjim restaurant--
- Let's eat jjajang.
- Jjajang.
The line isn't drawn.
That's right, sir,
'cause it's unnecessary.
Is this a case, or an accident?
It looks like an accident.
Your mole's gone.
Oh, yes.
You can't smoke around here.
- You removed your mole?
- Yeah.
Wow, that's crazy.
We met in passing when I was called in
for the arson case, you know.
How did he even remember that?
He's famous for his keen eye.
He remembers a face from just a look.
Captures every little detail.
Wow, you know
he has to have the best record.
Well, uh, no, not really.
I mean, if anything catches his eye,
then the case isn't truly closed.
He'll keep at it until everything
is completely settled.
His arrest rate is high,
but his performance rate is low.
His persistence is a waste.
- Oh, you made it here.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Why do I have to work so late?
- Tell me about it.
Who found the body?
The landlord.
Sir.
Examination record?
We'll get it soon.
And the presumed cause of death?
Sudden death.
Likely an acute myocardial infarction.
- Family?
- None present.
His wife passed away years ago.
And his children went overseas,
so he was alone.
So this acute myocardial infection...
Infarction.
Okay, sure. That one.
An infarction would mean
signs of squeezing
his heart in agony, is that right?
Then why is his expression like that?
Peaceful.
Maybe it wasn't acute.
You're right, who knows why?
In some cases, people become lively
before they really die, you know.
Yeah... Terminal lucidness.
Uh... "Terminal lucidity."
Well done. You want a medal?
I think it was
an acute myocardial infarction.
The deceased was taking
cardiovascular medication regularly.
Don't all old people have heart issues?
Uh... true.
Why? What's going on?
This expression is familiar.
Give me his cellphone.
RECENT CALL LIST
Look at that.
Guess he didn't know
how to set a password.
It's, uh, not a smartphone.
Well done. You want a medal?
He called his children and grandchildren,
one after another.
So, you're suspecting suicide?
Not possible with an acute infarction,
don't you agree?
And committing suicide
is usually something you plan in advance.
Yeah.
An acute infarction
means it's sudden.
- You can't really prepare that.
- Yeah.
- Not possible.
- You hear that?
Huh? Wait. This show wasn't live?
2018 WORLD THEME TRAVEL
Oh, I guess it was his first time
using replay.
He didn't know how to use it, I bet.
So, then, why is it on right now?
Only the channel buttons are worn out.
Honey, my period's late.
Now that
the Sujan tour is starting,
Papa Anoj should be able
to take some pressure off himself.
I think he'll definitely let loose.
For Papa Anoj,
his real journey begins now.
This whole trip has only revolved
around his kids so far!
He's a real dedicated dad,
isn't he?
So, which one do you like?
I'm so conflicted.
- How about I choose?
- Mmm.
That one.
Oh, it's too difficult.
Then how about something cheerful?
HAETSAL
This one.
Oh, good choice.
Yeah?
Got it.
I'll come right back after my shift,
so don't worry, we'll sort it all out.
- Take your car keys and police ID.
- Yeah, right.
See you soon.
You be careful.
HAETSAL
SEOUL EASTERN POLICE AGENCY
INVESTIGATION HEADQUARTERS
This way.
I prefer instant stuff.
When it's hot, it tastes better.
Then buy it yourself.
Give me.
The Seongnae-dong file.
Wait, we already caught
the culprit from that case!
Couldn't find the victim though.
But we've wrapped everything up,
and the search...
Uh, never mind.
"Unsolved" means unresolved.
- Don't confuse it with a solved case.
- Okay.
Exam record shows
it was likely an infarction.
"Likely"?
- I mean, it was.
- Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
This the one?
Blood samples from the deceased
were collected
- and his troponin levels were checked.
- Autopsy?
The examiner said
an autopsy wasn't needed,
based on the condition
and history of the deceased.
The family didn't want one either.
They don't want their loved one's
body cut open,
so the deceased has already
been handed over to them.
This case is closed.
Got it. You can go.
Yes.
SEOUL EASTERN POLICE AGENCY
It's hard to specify
since it rained the night before,
plus the CCTV has a high traffic volume.
We could request dash cam footage
since we have cars in the alleys.
Technically, the case is closed.
If it's already closed, why...
- Search the jurisdiction data.
- Okay.
Chinese restaurants.
So, Chinese, then...
Sergeant Mun,
here's your iced coffee!
Huh? Why are you here, sir?
- More like why are you here?
- Uh...
Coffee.
Ah, have you eaten yet, sir?
- Jjajangmyeon sound good?
- I'm good.
Uh, take care.
Huh?
- I like hot.
- Hot.
Oh, yeah, why did he come down here?
He wanted to go over the case.
Oh, the lonely man
in Seongnae-dong?
- It was ruled a natural death.
- I know.
There has to be something about it
that's still on his mind.
He's just lonely, too, that's all.
Do they order alcohol? Or not?
- Now and then. It's more often now.
- Deliveries?
IMPERIAL PALACE
IMPERIAL PALACE CHINESE RESTAURANT
How far do you deliver in the area?
Just this neighborhood?
- Well, we cover almost all of it.
- Oh, the whole area?
Seongnae-dong is too far from here.
CHEONRI JANGSEONG DUMPLINGS
Okay, hurry home. Go on.
Then you'll get to eat tonkatsu
with your mom.
MINSEO'S JJAJANG -
DAEDONGGAK - SHANGHAI RESTAURANT
IMPERIAL CHINESE RESTAURANT - JUNGHARU
GONGRI JJAMPPONG - BAEKMIHYANG
HAN JJAJANG
JANGSU CHINESE RESTAURANT
TAEYANGWON SHANGHAI DINER - THE GREAT WALL
BEIJING JJAMPPONG
AUTHENTIC CHINESE JJAJANG
BOKSUNGWON CHINESE RESTAURANT
I have a lot of customers
waiting for me right now.
Okay, thank you.
SANGIL MYEONGA
BANQUET NOODLES, SPICY NOODLES,
JJAJANGMYEON, UDON
SEOUL GANGDONG
MI 8525
Welcome.
What would you like to order?
Jjajangmyeon's good.
All right, one moment, please.
QUICK DELIVERY
If you could just please sign here,
and then you're free to go.
I searched all day
for a Chinese restaurant.
Please enjoy your meal.
Do you also deliver?
Sometimes I do.
Delivery apps don't list you.
I don't get many orders.
So how did he order?
Customers always find a way to order food.
He called his children and grandchildren,
one after another.
RECENT CALL LIST
The truth is
he didn't order at all.
From here to Seongnae-dong
is too far though.
It is. Jjajangmyeon would get soggy.
I never said what he got.
Even though they declared it
a natural death...
to me, it was suspicious.
His calm expression
was anything but natural.
What went on, I wonder.
Crime scenes reveal the truth, you know.
TV replay.
I guess it was his first time
using replay.
That was just the first clue.
He was a right-handed person.
But the remote control was on his left.
So that's why I thought...
someone was clearly there and then gone.
The liver spots I saw...
...were jjajang sauce.
You did it.
And who are you?
You dense? A detective.
Then why are you talking so impolitely?
I'm afraid I have no idea
what you're talking about, sir.
- You sure?
- So... impolite.
You sure, sir?
Yes.
Well, now what? My hands are tied.
Guess I'll keep watch.
Talking to myself.
Sir.
You ought to say "see you again!"
Shouldn't you?
See you again.
That's right.
KIM SANGHOON
The hell
is this bastard doing? Shit.
NATURAL DEATH
ONE MONTH LATER
"See you again," right?
Get off!
Impolite. Huh?
Hey, asshole.
What were you trying to do?
You trying to kill again?
You piece of shit murderer.
Hey, young lady, are you okay?
- You see that woman, too?
- You just stay still!
You okay over there?
Can you stand on your own?
ASPHYXIATION FROM SMOKE AND ASH
You're already dead.
You have a good eye, detective.
- If she's here, she can't be human.
- What?
Hey!
What's with your eyes?
Anything you're looking for?
Perhaps you'll know what it is.
Just tell me what you need.
Maybe I can find it for you.
Can I ask some questions?
What brings you here?
I'm with the police.
What is this about?
I'm looking for a suspect.
A man, about mid-30s, 180, short hair.
He looks... plain.
Why are you looking here?
I lost him in this neighborhood.
Have you seen him, by chance?
This is the only place open at this hour.
Young lady, stop.
Are you injured?
Uh, no.
My body isn't well today.
Like you said, this is the only place
open at this hour.
I was trying to avoid the rain,
but it's never-ending.
Wear this.
Take it with you. I have other coats.
Your mother.
Go.
Oh, no.
Ah, Mom told me to buy a bulb though.
Geez.
Sir!
Hyunju. Go home now.
Your mother must be waiting.
I'm all right, okay?
Okay.
You have a lot of customers late at night.
Well, I was also drawn here in a way.
This place is strange.
And what is it
that brings you to this place?
The store's noticeable
with all these lights on.
No.
I'm not talking about the store.
Translated by You-ji Kim