♫  Nowhere to escape  ♫
♫  No one to rely on  ♫
♫  Withdrawing smiles  ♫
♫  Never give in  ♫
♫  Forget about one's youth  ♫
♫  I've never been afraid of loneliness when
embarking on this journey  ♫
♫  Tears and regrets go hand in hand  ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot ♫
♫ To the distance ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken ♫
♫ I will keep flying ♫
♫ Following the direction of the light ♫
♫ I'll forget you ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness ♫
[The Long Ballad]
[Episode 3]
Yesterday you were still fine.
And today you're injured.
Did you meet your enemy?
Eat something at least, brave man.
Then you can recover quickly.
I've been wandering in the streets since little.
And I've met all kinds of people.
I can conclude that you recently are having some tough days
or you having a blood feud.
Did you just have a tough fight with your enemy today?
If you say one more word, you will die.
No. No. No.
Brave man. No... Master.
Though I don't know who you are,
you can't be an ordinary person.
I, A'Dou, live a poor life.
Even if I die someday, I'm afraid that no one will realize it.
If I can follow you and do something great, it would be worth it, even if I'd die.
Search carefully!
Master, why are soldiers here?
They've found this place from Rongen Temple so quickly.
Rongen Temple?
I heard that the soldiers guarding Rongen Temple were poisoned.
Was that you?
I knew that I was right about you.
You even dare poison soldiers.
Master, you're indeed not ordinary.
[Pinxiang Store]
Brother Du, it's so late now.
I didn't expect you would be still investigating here.
Brother Du.
Why are you here, Brother Fang?
I heard that Pinxiang Store
[Pinxiang Store]
has the best pastries in Chang'an.
My wife wants to taste them,
so I'm here on my own to see how good they are.
When I was downstairs, I got stopped by soldiers.
After inquiry, it turns out Brother Du is investigating here.
You're really well-informed, Brother Fang.
[Pinxiang Store]
Why is it on fire?
It looks like I can't buy pastries today.
Father.
Advisor Fang.
Brother Fang.
Do you really insist on breeding evil?
I don't understand, Brother Du.
I'm confused.
Brother Du, I have to go.
I need to go home now to tell my wife about it.
See you.
[Pinxiang Store]
Master, why is it on fire?
Father, it's weird about the fire.
I'm afraid...
Please be assured, Father.
I'll investigate it thoroughly.
No need.
Since someone wants to protect her,
he won't leave a trace.
Is it possible... that Advisor Fang set it on fire?
Don't draw a conclusion so soon.
Pinxiang Store is empty today.
That person might not want to hurt innocent people.
Let's leave here.
Send people to put the fire out first.
Master, the fire is so strong.
What should we do?
Run.
Master, wait. Stop.
Master, why is it suddenly on fire?
And that ladder.
Looks like someone prepared it for you.
What's going on?
Master, why don't you say anything?
Remove my trace with fire.
There won't be any evidence there.
Then that's a favor for you, right?
A favor?
My mother's body is still in Rongen Temple.
I won't accept that favor.
Rongen Temple?
So, Madam Jin is your mother?
Knowing too much won't do you any good.
Whoever you are, you're my master.
Pinxiang Store is burned.
From now on, I have no place to stay.
Master, please let me follow you.
Let me say it again. I'm not your master.
Following me means you'll die at any time.
Leave me alone.
Master...
[Crown Prince and Prince Qi were killed. All their subordinates were annihilated.]
Fang Yi.
[Harmony Brings Serenity]
Yes, Your Highness.
Go to the battalion suburbs and send my order,
that the rebellion stops at Jian City and Yuanji.
I won't blame their followers.
Your Highness, that's...
What happened in Xuanwu Gate was not what I wanted.
No more people should die of it.
Yes.
[Harmony Brings Serenity]
That was an unexpected disturbance. I can't help with that.
I wish after the disturbance, Great Tang will be fine
and people will be safe.
[Crown Prince and Prince Qi were killed. All their subordinates were annihilated.]
Changge,
didn't you say that you'll accept the one hundred amulets that I prayed for you?
You haven't got any, and now you're missing.
Please be safe.
Bodhisattva, please.
Please make sure that Changge stays safe.
[Yining Fang]
[Prince Qin ordered that the rebellion stops at Jiancheng...]
General, how is it?
Our effort was in vain.
Prince Qin has suppressed the turmoil among soldiers.
How can he be so quick?
I didn't expect him to be so capable and broad-minded.
He pardoned all followers of the two princes.
With only an order, he eliminated the turmoil among soldiers.
I underestimated him before.
What should we do now?
Prince Qin isn't an ordinary man.
Even if we continue staying in Chang'an, he eliminated the turmoil among soldiers.
Let's leave here now and go to You State.
You State? Why are we going there?
We can't gain anything here in Chang'an during this visit.
Father Khan has been suspicious.
If I go back with no gain, my brother will make a fuss.
You State is like a gateway to Chang'an.
We need to achieve something there
so that we can keep him quiet.
I understand.
Mr. Fang, I'm on my way to meet you at your home.
Greetings to Princess Yongan.
Princess?
Princess might haven't heard about it.
During the meeting this morning, Your Majesty has conferred Prince Qin as Crown Prince.
Naturally, you are a princess now.
Thanks to Your Majesty.
Why did Your Highness want to meet me?
Mr. Fang, I want to ask for your help.
Changge?
I know that Mr. Fang cherishes Changge most.
I also know that you won't catch Changge.
Today, I'm here because I want to know the truth from you.
How is Changge?
Please don't worry, Princess.
Princess Yongning hasn't been caught.
I knew it.
I knew Changge would be fine.
Please be assured, Princess.
She was taught by Your Highness and Wei Zheng.
I also spent a lot of time on her.
How can she be caught easily?
Just... it will be tough on her.
[Elegant Heavenly Devotion]
About Your Highness's intention to pardon them, I can understand that.
But I think Your Highness can't pardon everyone.
What do you mean?
The leader of Tianjie Army, Luo Yi, has been good friends with Li Jiancheng.
If he wants to revolt, it will be huge trouble.
Also, Li Changge, the daughter of Li Jiancheng, will do harm to...
Keming, the essence to make the country in harmony is to win people's hearts.
If officers keep suspecting each other,
and I get strict and abuse punishment,
I'm afraid that I'll be like Emperor Yang of Sui.
Have you heard the saying?
Civilizing people after the turmoil will be much more effective.
I'm too ignorant.
Not surprising.
This saying is from Wei Zheng.
Xuanling just recommended him to me.
Your Highness, Wei Zheng has always been stubborn.
And now Your Highness wants to recruit him.
I'm afraid that it won't be easy.
Stubborn?
Wouldn't that just match your flavor?
Mr. Du.
[Crown Prince and Prince Qi were killed. All their subordinates were annihilated.]
It's about the safety of Chang'an City.
Be careful. Don't leave any trace.
Besides, it's a period of trouble now.
Send more people to guard every city gate.
Don't let any related person sneak out.
Please be assured.
I'll try my best to do it for His Highness.
[Tonghua Gate]
Does the officer from East Palace also need to hide in Chang'an City?
Move away.
You can even criticize soldiers on the street in public.
What are you afraid of?
So it's you.
Why are you following me?
Following you?
It's you that ran into me.
What do you want?
You're from East Palace and you haven't pledged allegiance.
Why can you go in and out at your will?
None of your business.
What are you doing?
Someone's coming.
Why do you look like this? As if I'm bullying you.
From now on, soldiers will guard the city gate and check those in and out.
Yes.
If it weren't for that guy, we would have been out of this city now.
Let's figure out another way.
Let's go back first.
Let's go.
[Quite Calm to Move Forward]
It seems that Advisor Wei is determined to keep sleeping today until it's dark.
I'm sorry, Mr. Du.
My father hasn't been feeling well recently.
It's not convenient for him to meet guests.
Your father doesn't feel bad physically, but psychologically.
My father won't listen to anyone.
I apologize on behalf of my father.
Shuyu, do you have siblings?
I have three brothers and one sister in my hometown.
They're with my mother now.
Your father is so stubborn.
Just like a tall tree, it'll get broken if it's too tough.
If your father has a bad ending, can your family survive?
It's just a shame for your Wei family.
Don't you understand the gains and losses of it?
I understand.
Good.
You're at a similar age with my foster son Hao Du.
He acts very properly.
You should learn more from him.
Seeing him is like seeing me.
Can you understand my words?
[Wei Manor]
Li Shimin's soldiers.
Is Mr. Wei...
Mr. Du.
Please wait, Mr. Du.
[Wei Manor]
I'll do my best to persuade my father.
Good boy.
His Highness gives this Fish Token especially to you.
From now on, you're with us, working for the crown prince.
You can use it to get in and out of the palace,
and meet His Highness and me at any time.
[Wei Manor]
What's that?
There. Look.
Look there.
[Official Notice]
About the case of Li Jiancheng and Li Yuanji's rebellion,
since the principal culprits were killed,
the crown prince asked His Majesty to pardon the others.
As long as they pledge allegiance on their own,
they'll be pardoned.
That's really a kind crown prince.
Right.
With such a crown prince, it's our fortune.
Changge, that was really you.
You caught me.
And you can get promoted with that, right?
Why would you think of me like that?
I won't do it no matter what.
Then, why did you surrender to Du Ruhui?
Answer me.
My father was the advisor to the former crown prince.
Given what happened in East Palace,
the Wei family is in danger and it's going to be ruined anytime.
If I treat Mr. Du indifferently, how can I save my parents?
But, Changge, it won't last long. Please trust me.
I don't trust anyone now.
Changge,
His Highness has ordered that anyone pledging allegiance will be pardoned.
Am I guilty? I don't need to be pardoned.
You're not guilty.
Neither am I. Everyone isn't guilty.
So you have to trust me. I'll accompany you.
No one can accompany me now.
My mother died.
They all died.
Changge.
No. The Fish Token.
She probably wants to use the Fish Token to get in the palace.
Why does she want to go back?
[Hongyi Palace]
The Ashile Tribe has been very cunning. They often betray their allies.
We can't reckon them like others.
I'm afraid the turbulence these days was also from them.
It's late now.
You can go back.
- Yes.
Your Highness!
It's me.
Congratulations!
His Majesty asked me to send the seal of the crown prince here,
Your Highness.
Mother died. The East Palace was in a disaster.
So many people died just for such a thing.
Put it here.
If you don't have anything else, you can go back.
Yes, Your Highness.
It looks like something is wrong.
Changge, you can show yourself.
You knew I was here.
You can hide from others,
but not from me.
I've let them record
that Princess Yongning has died.
You killed so many people in the East Palace.
Why would you like to let me go now?
Is it that you finally find your humanity?
So you can do me a favor
and comfort yourself because you suffered from a sense of guilt.
Or is it because...
I'm just a woman without the status of a princess?
So I can't be a threat to you.
Changge.
Changge, stop.
Even if I might die,
I'll get revenge for my mother.
Changge, just leave!
Your Highness.
Your Highness's safety matters to society.
How can you be in such danger?
Traitor, you can't escape now.
Take Li Changge away.
- Yes.
Stop. That dagger belongs to her.
I'll use this dagger that took my mother's life to kill
the murderer.
How dare you! Guards!
Put her into the death prison.
Wait!
Take Princess Yongning to the wing room,
and take good care of her.
Your Highness, you're breeding evil.
Keming, I'm tired.
About what happened today,
you can't tell anyone else.
Yes.
Take her away.
- Move!
- Go.
Father, it's already well arranged.
I've set lookouts everywhere in Hongyi Palace.
Please be assured.
Father, how is His Highness going to deal with Li Changge?
Breeding evil will cause lots of trouble.
Father, don't get too tired.
What should I do next?
Double the soldiers.
And let them secretly guard the wing room at every corner of it.
Give her the illusion that she's not well guarded.
If she wants to run away,
kill her on the spot.
Yes.
Why are they guarding me with so few soldiers?
Mother, what should I do?
Your Highness.
Advisor Fang, I can't fall asleep.
Play chess with me.
Yes.
How dare you!
I haven't started. How dare you make your move?
Isn't Your Highness waiting for others to make a move first?
You can't know me better than myself.
Changge isn't a girl easy to deal with.
Your Highness is busy with official duties.
No need to bother with that.
Your Highness urgently summoned me here for that.
Your Highness, I'll deal with that.
She's your student.
You have to be responsible for her.
Yes.
[Assassination at Prince Qin Manor. The assassin failed and is locked in the wing room]
Assassination at Prince Qin Manor?
I didn't expect him to be so dauntless.
General, who are you talking about?
The guy that won against us in the cuju arena.
So he's not an ordinary man.
Needless to say.
He's more than uncommon.
He also has an uncommon relationship with Prince Qin.
Prince Qin didn't put him into prison,
but let him live in the wing room.
So we'll be friends with him.
Friends?
The enemy of our enemy is our friend.
What? Changge was caught by my father.
And she got locked?
I heard servants talking about it this morning.
And they were seriously scolded by Commander Hao Du.
As for where she is now, I didn't hear that.
Changge.
What should we do?
Mr. Fang.
Mr. Fang must know where they locked Changge.
Princess.
I was going to visit you.
Mr. Fang is really like a prophet.
The rain tonight is our biggest helper.
Are you really prepared, Princess?
I'm afraid.
Don't be afraid, Princess.
Think of every step that Mr. Fang has taught you.
And just do as he said.
Things will be okay.
I believe Mr. Fang.
Since little, it was Changge that protected me.
Now it's time for me to save her.
As stubborn as she is, Changge won't eat anything these days.
But Your Highness ordered that
they should take good care of her.
Those guards are also worrying about that,
because no one can afford to neglect the princess.
Only your appearance will let Changge eat something.
The guards will pretend to stop you.
Actually they wish that you can show up.
Only by this can they avoid responsibility.
Remember. Don't be afraid.
The guards will definitely let you get in.
How dare you! This is the princess.
Advisor Du said that no one can get close to the wing room.
Please don't make things difficult for us.
I heard that Princess Yongning hasn't been eating for 24 hours.
My father said that you should take good care of her.
If something bad happens to her,
can you afford that?
That's...
Princess just wants to send her some food.
She won't stay long.
Or are you doubting the princess?
Please, Princess.
Wait for me here.
Changge.
Chang... Changge.
I'm Yueyan.
Why are you here?
Who sent you here?
Don't let Changge know that I sent you there.
She won't accept this favor.
What you should do is to show flaws deliberately.
Give her the information to run away.
Let Changge run away by herself instead of being rescued.
That's what Changge will accept.
It's raining tonight and suddenly became cold.
The guards in the backyard went home due to the chill.
So I brought you hot soup and pastries.
Eat it when it's still hot.
How did you get in?
I'm a princess now.
They dare not stop me.
Your father killed my father.
You became a princess.
Princess Yongan.
Changge, it's not like what you think.
I don't care about being a princess or whatever.
From your room to this wing room, you won't pass the backyard.
How did you know that there were no guards in the backyard?
Who taught you that?
Changge is extremely smart.
If she finds out you're lying,
you don't need to hide anything from her.
Changge, leave here now.
The door of the backyard is open.
The guards were also kept away.
Go as far as you can.
Don't ever come back.
How can I believe you?
Is it your father's trap, or Du Ruhui's?
Then you'll declare that Princess Yongning died from arrows when she was running away.
Yes or no?
Changge,
do you really think that I'll hurt you?
It's Mr. Fang.
Mr. Fang taught me that.
He said that you're stubborn.
Only by this can you run away.
Fang Xuanling.
Tell Fang Xuanling,
it's my business. I'll try to think of a way it on my own.
He doesn't need to have pity on me.
I don't want to owe him anything.
The only thing that can dispel her misgivings
is your sisterhood since little.
The only one who can save Changge is actually you.
Changge, this is the amulet that I had prayed for you recently.
Wear it on you.
Then you'll definitely be safe.
Amulet?
The people of Prince Qin Manor killed everyone in our East Palace.
Your father killed my mother and father.
Now you want me to be safe?
I'm sorry, Changge. I didn't know that.
I...
I'm sorry.
Princess Yongan,
from now on, we two are foes and absolutely irreconcilable.
Changge...
We have been best sisters since childhood.
Changge.
Sisters?
How can I be sisters with the daughter of the man that murdered my father?
I'll count down from three.
Leave here now.
Otherwise, don't blame me for being cold-blooded.
Three.
Two.
One.
Changge, I don't believe you really want me to leave.
If my death can relieve your hatred for my father,
I won't regret it.
Changge.
Yueyan.
Sorry.
Princess, why don't you say anything?
Is it because Mr. Fang's strategy didn't work?
His Majesty asked me to send the seal of the crown prince here,
Your Highness.
Anything abnormal?
Princess Yongan was here with some food.
I have checked. Nothing abnormal.
Princess Yongan?
Right.
Princess?
- Guards.
- Yes.
Lockdown Hongyi Palace.
The rest go after her with me.
Yes!
Princess. Princess!
Princess!
Call the imperial doctor.
Your Highness, Li Changge is serious trouble of Great Tang.
Your Highness,
we found the princess' maidservant knocked unconscious outside of the study.
The study?
Hurry. Back to the study.
Keming, it's gone.
Guards, you have to catch Li Changge.
Yes.
Go!
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter ♫
♫ As your silhouette weaves ♫
♫ and locks in my nostalgic dream ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the yearning flowing through thoughts ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ where the wilderness burns in my heart ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which froze everything between you and me ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon ♫
♫ Layer after layer ♫
♫ It turns into an eternity ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ where the wilderness burns in my heart ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which froze everything between you and me ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon ♫
♫ Layer after layer ♫
♫ It turns into an eternity ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night ♫
♫ It is sleepless ♫
[The Long Ballad]