♫   Nowhere to escape   ♫
♫   No one to rely on   ♫
♫   Withdrawing smiles   ♫
♫   Never give in   ♫
♫   Forget about one's youth   ♫
♫   I've never been afraid of loneliness when
embarking on this journey   ♫
♫   Tears and regrets go hand in hand   ♫
♫   But my heart is still fiery-hot   ♫
♫  To the distance  ♫
♫  The miserable past is like a dagger  ♫
♫  Though my wings are broken  ♫
♫  I will keep flying  ♫
♫  Following the direction of the light  ♫
♫  I'll forget you  ♫
♫  The memory shaped my stubbornness  ♫
♫  By virtue of the light in the dark night  ♫
♫  I'll return it with a long ballad  ♫
♫  The river of life is under my feet  ♫
♫  I don't regret my craziness  ♫
Shuyu, along the way, sometimes I was reckless,
and, at other times, I've misunderstood you.
Thank you for your tolerance and help all this time.
I know you don't want me to be courteous,
but I really want to thank you.
If we part today, I don't know when we'll meet again.
Changge, take care.
Take care.
Take good care of Changge.
I wish you happiness.
Brother Wei, thank you.
Sun, do you think Mimi will like this place?
What if she dislikes it?
When you dream of her, you may ask her.
It's wooded and wide here.
She'll like it for sure.
Changge, when breaking into the execution ground,
did you think you might not have returned?
Have you thought of your life when saving me in Chang'an?
In fact, I saw the letter you wrote to my mother about marrying me.
So...
what do you think?
I think...
we don't need too much red tape.
It's enough to have you in my life.
I think the same.
By the way, how did you contact General Li?
After you were taken to Dingxiang, were you still in contact with him?
In fact, before leaving Chang'an,
I made an agreement with him.
Brother Li,
no, General Li.
Brother Qin, we meet again.
I'm afraid we can't take each other as mere friends.
It doesn't matter.
Brother Qin, do you remember what I said
when we parted in Luoyang?
The benevolent has no enemy.
That's it.
But now Princess Yicheng takes Khan hostage to control all tribes,
manipulating the grasslands and desert,
and caring nothing about the public,
so the war expands and lasts, plunging the people into misery.
We're on different sides.
Customs of the grasslands and central plains differ as well,
but our people all fear war and long for peace.
I want to know whether
you can forget about the differences and save people from suffering.
I have one condition.
Please speak.
I want your side to help me get Khan Yanli out.
Okay, I promise you.
Though warlike Ashile Duobi broke up our alliance many times,
he still kept his promise after the battle on Wei River.
His death can be spared.
Thanks for your righteousness.
But now I'm in jail,
and am unable to live in either Dingxiang or the central plains.
How can I help you?
You have to return to Dingxiang and reclaim Eagle Division.
But it'll be too dangerous.
If you want to succeed unharmed, it's harder than flying to the moon.
Ashile Sun, you hid things from me again.
You're so unteachable.
I dare not.
I dare not in the future.
Sun, do you like Chang'an?
Want to go back?
I'd better not.
It may be troublesome to have many acquaintances.
So where do you want to go?
I haven't decided yet.
Sun, I'm sorry.
I promised you to live freely far from secular strife
and to enjoy sightseeing over the world.
But if I turn a blind eye to the current situation,
I can't be at ease.
My promise may be fulfilled a bit later.
Changge, I know the second thing I want you to do.
Come on!  Why haven't you given it up?
You may as well forget it.
Last time as soon as you told me the first thing, you got shot with an arrow.
I'm afraid it brings bad luck. Just forget it.
It's the first time I've seen a guy easily breaking a promise like you.
It's not the case.
Well, speak.
The second thing I want you to do is to never say sorry or thanks to me.
These words are not needed between the two of us.
That's it?
Isn't the second thing too easy?
Just do as I said.
Tell me the third thing all at once, so I'll fulfill my promise earlier.
The third thing...
Leave it for later.
We still have a long way to go.
Hao Du, why are you here?
I'm under Princess's order.
Aren't you getting married soon?
We've been married.
That's great.
Wait!  You shouldn't have come here.
I have to protect the people Yueyan cherishes.
All right, all right.
Consort Prince is a great help to us.
Report!
Go ahead.
According to scouts in the east, Dingxiang troops were found in Baidao.
It seems Yicheng wants to break through Baidao by way of Qikou.
Go ask Li Ji to intercept the enemy from the front,
and I from the back.
Yes.
General Li, you dispatched two troops of scouts,
but one of them hasn't returned yet.
There's a possibility.
What possibility?
It doesn't mean there's no enemy in this direction.
Maybe scouts have been ambushed and can't return.
I'll go have a look with Eagle Division,
so the main forces can stay here.
I'll go with you.
No, you can't.
It's just my guess.
I may return empty-handed or face danger.
You'd better stay with General Li as his adviser.
But...
Princess, I'm afraid I can't let you go with him.
We'll take the main force with us out, leaving no one in our camp.
There must be one dealing with important messages,
or our military plan may be delayed.
Consort Prince is skillful in battles.
Can you stay with Princess here just in case?
If any emergency, you two can join hands and play it by ear.
I won't let you down.
Unexpectedly, the previously unruly and arrogant little princess
making trouble with horses,
now rises to the occasion to guard your country.
I have really appreciated your hard work all this time.
I'm flattered.
I just want to do my bit for the world's peace.
Yicheng's so cunning. Please be very careful.
Don't worry. She's at her wits' end.
This time, we must root her out for our country, the grasslands, and the desert.
Sun, I'll go with you.
Mu Jin, but you just...
I'm not only your brother but the military counselor of Eagle Division.
How can I be a coward and let you a commander-in-chief resist the enemy?
Okay.
We're followed by many soldiers.
Tuluk, take Young Khan away.
- The rest is on me.
- Yes.
Wait!
On you?
You mean killing more people?
You can live without killing people because such things are all on us.
I'll do evil so that you can be innocent.
If it's really for the sake of my mother, please stop here
and avoid committing crimes.
Your mother's education to you was all in vain.
Piss off!
Tuluk.
Let's go, Young Khan.
We're so lucky.
God seems to be on our side.
It's not up to you to decide what luck you have today.
God knows you'd be here.
If you want to take revenge, just do your best.
Sun, you go first.
Leave him to me.
Okay.
Stop them.
She'er.
Sun.
I said I'd neither go with you nor surrender to you.
Just like you'll never surrender to me.
All stand back.
Don't you understand?
Yes, I do.
You don't understand what Mimi died for.
She died for freedom rather than your arrow.
A person like you, who only obeys orders
and tramples on lives instead of valuing your own life,
will never understand.
I'm not ordered but entrusted to do so.
I have to keep my promise.
She'er, must you be like this?
Were you moved because I set you free in Dingxiang?
Don't show mercy later.
Come on, you're more merciful.
You...
Why?
I'm tired.
If there's one in the world that can kill me, it must be you.
She'er, don't punish yourself because of someone else's fault.
You're innocent.
I'll atone for my mother's crimes.
Sun, promise me to set my men in Wolf Division free.
They're warriors of Ashile Tribe and shouldn't fight for Dingxiang.
You're Young Khan.
You ought to lead them to a free life yourself.
Sun, I want to have another fight and drink with you.
I wonder if there's a chance.
There is, of course.
When the war ceases and the grass sprouts again,
we'll meet again for sure.
Go west.
As far as possible.
Wolf Division!
Let Wolf Division go!
General Du, General Li broke through the enemy's ambush in Qikou.
Now both sides are at war.
- Get more news.
- Yes.
General Li is so fast.
My second uncle fought here and there after overturning Sui Dynasty
to "govern" the country.
Governor Gongsun had guarded Shuo State for years to "protect" the city.
But General Li's different.
Speed is valued in war.
He just wants to "expedite" the war.
Charge!
General Du, leaders of all tribes fled from the western mountain pass following Yicheng's carriage.
General Li's delayed and needs cavalry to block them.
I'll be on it. I can't let Yicheng run away.
Take enough men and take care.
What about Eagle Division?
It encountered an enemy troop at the mouth of Wuduo Valley.
The leader Lei Meng was killed.
The General of Eagle Division detoured to block Ashile's Young Khan.
I see, go on.
Yes.
No! Let's go.
Everybody. The alliance between Tang and your tribes
is for common prosperity and long-term well-being.
Yicheng got you all involved for her own benefit.
Do you still want to work for her?
Our country doesn't want to be your enemy.
If you stop fighting against us now, you can give up the sword for the plow,
look after your family, and lead your tribe to water
and grass-oriented life with many flocks.
But if you're too stubborn to agree, and go on fighting against us,
our country will never give in!
Never give in!
I'll go home to look after my family.
I won't fight anymore.
We won't fight as well.
Good news! We've won!
General Li's back.
Congratulations on your defeating the enemy!
Please be assured.
Hao Du went to arrest Yicheng.
He won't let Yicheng go.
Well done.
Hao Du, have you arrested her?
Leaders of all tribes surrendered,
but Yicheng wasn't in the carriage at all.
She's neither in the camp nor running away by carriage.
Where's she then?
Maybe she didn't want to escape at all.
Are you here to ridicule me?
I just feel afraid that I almost went the same way as you.
Trash!
To achieve your goal, a lot of people died from your schemes.
I'd rather be trash than being like you.
You don't understand.
You'll never understand.
I'm the Princess of Sui Dynasty.
I was born and grown up in Sui Dynasty.
That's my homeland.
I must save it!
Your homeland is still here.
It didn't disappear.
Its land is still here.
Its people are here, too.
It was the people who suffered the most.
What's gone is just the glory of your royal family.
Does the glory really matter?
Royal family?
I'm not exactly one of the royal family at all.
I just bear the royal surname.
The most glorious day of my life
was the day when I was promoted to Princess.
I had neither been to the royal palace
nor been so well-dressed, praised by the entire public
and welcomed by all officials.
They said from then on, I'd be the Princess of Sui.
I would have to marry a khan of the grasslands.
From now on, you'll be my company.
I, Lei Meng, will do my best to protect Your Highness till death.
I agreed to marry Khan.
That was not only my glory but also my fate.
I'm the Princess of Sui.
I'm willing to sacrifice for it.
I don't need your or anyone else's sympathy.
Those so-called princesses or princes of the royal family all far lagged behind me.
They knelt down and begged for mercy.
They cast their country aside just to survive.
Only me.
For thirty years, only I, confined to the grasslands,
haven't discarded our country.
Come back.
Sui Dynasty had been overturned.
Where shall I go back?
Your homeland is still here.
Chang'an is still here.
Daxing Palace is still here.
Trees in the palace were planted during Sui Dynasty.
In my childhood, I used to climb up the tree with friends to play truant.
As long as you can go back and be subject to Tang Dynasty,
according to my knowledge of Second Uncle, he won't kill you.
If I had been willing to beg for my life,
how could I have chosen this path?
Will you even go back to Chang'an?
Yes.
I was wrong.
My life is nothing but a humiliating joke.
I won't beg for mercy,
but thank you
for accompanying me at the end of my life.
♫   The past can't blow away the moonlight,   ♫
♫   I can't forget   ♫
♫   where to look back   ♫
♫   The dark side of the world turns to frost   ♫
♫   What if persistence disappears like fleeting glory?   ♫
♫   It's okay to forget   ♫
Grandma, is this Chang'an?
Yes, we're back home.
Father.
We won Dingxiang back. We won Yinshan back.
Father, don't worry.
I'll take good care of Li Yueyan.
Father... we'll take good care of each other.
You can rest in peace now.
Your Majesty, my condolences.
Did she die a painful death?
You mean Li Changge?
Princess achieved her goal, so she can rest in peace.
What did she say at last?
She said she was grateful to you.
Anything else?
She said... she liked reading.
On each year's Cold Food Day, please burn books as sacrificial offerings.
I've watched her growing up, but I never knew she liked reading.
Didn't she like reading?
She seems to like it.
Li Yaoshi.
How dare you trick me?
I'm sorry, but it's all because of Li Changge.
I was forced to do so.
You may rise.
What happened, after all?
Changge!
Didn't you promise me to never to...
Never to risk my life alone.
So why did you rush in instead of waiting for me?
I know I was wrong. Don't be mad at me.
Princess, are you not going back to Chang'an with me?
General Li, what are you talking about?
Everything has gone with the fire.
There's no princess.
You're so determined.
I'm the one who paid a double cost.
General Li, if His Majesty asks about me,
let him remove my name from historical records.
There'll be no Li Change in the world from now on.
Thank you, General Li.
I know nothing.
So where are you going?
Don't mention it.
Anyway, someplace in the world from which no one can escape.
If His Majesty asks, tell him just to let it be.
Fine.
Maybe one day you'll meet again.
Changge, is such a prosperous Tang Dynasty what you want?
Having traveled around for long,
I'm increasingly aware that only when the country is in peace
can the people live in contentment;
only when the country is strong can the people be fearless.
The old scores are all personal trifles.
Now I can finally leave them behind.
Today the country is well-governed;
people benefit a lot from His Majesty's grace; each performs its own functions;
the world is in peace, and is ushering in a flourishing age.
Second Uncle, thank you so much
for not letting our country and people down.
Huge thanks to the The Ode to Love Team!
Many thanks to our segmenters: bjohnsonwong (Chief), kitty100, nmelova, ma_xt_26, valneijr, nicefly09, brengbo, sheli, geralgoeprieto_664!
Sending love to our Chief Editor, kakashiandme!
Thank you for your hard work as TE, trangxlnguyen_197!
I'm very grateful for cerejacult for being our GE!
I really appreciate the work of all our other language moderators! Thank you all!
Also, a million thanks to every other subtitler who has worked on this project with us!
♫  The heart gradually responds,  ♫
♫  gradually revives,  ♫
♫  gradually swims towards you  ♫
♫  Before bidding farewell,  ♫
♫  we expect an encounter  ♫
♫  As your silhouette weaves  ♫
♫  and locks in my nostalgic dream  ♫
♫  Before the daybreak,  ♫
♫  through the obsession of love,  ♫
♫  the yearning flowing through thoughts  ♫
♫  There's always a moment  ♫
♫  where the wilderness burns in my heart  ♫
♫  There's always solicitude  ♫
♫  which froze everything between you and me  ♫
♫  Meet each other in different time  ♫
♫  Encourage each other in different worlds  ♫
♫  My longings become a cocoon  ♫
♫  Layer after layer  ♫
♫  It turns into an eternity  ♫
♫  The cocoon in the dark night  ♫
♫  There's always a moment  ♫
♫  where the wilderness burns in my heart  ♫
♫  There's always solicitude  ♫
♫  which froze everything between you and me  ♫
♫  Meet each other in different time  ♫
♫  Encourage each other in different worlds  ♫
♫  My longings become a cocoon  ♫
♫  Layer after layer  ♫
♫  It turns into an eternity  ♫
♫  The cocoon in the dark night  ♫
♫  It is sleepless  ♫