♫   Nowhere to escape   ♫
♫   No one to rely on   ♫
♫   Withdrawing smiles   ♫
♫   Never give in   ♫
♫   Forget about one's youth   ♫
♫   I've never been afraid of loneliness when
embarking on this journey   ♫
♫   Tears and regrets go hand in hand   ♫
♫  But my heart is still fiery-hot  ♫
♫  To the distance  ♫
♫  The miserable past is like a dagger  ♫
♫  Though my wings are broken  ♫
♫  I will keep flying  ♫
♫  Following the direction of the light  ♫
♫  I'll forget you  ♫
♫  The memory shaped my stubbornness  ♫
♫  By virtue of the light in the dark night  ♫
♫  I'll return it with a long ballad  ♫
♫  The river of life is under my feet  ♫
♫  I don't regret my craziness  ♫
Well, he's really strong.
Come on, buddies!
We have nearly defeated him!
A bet is a bet.
You win.
You're more powerful than I thought.
You're now the winner.
You don't need to taunt us.
If we had been powerful,
why would our governor have sacrificed himself?
Gongsun Heng is a hero.
You know nothing!
I just... I just envy him
for having brothers like you to fight for him.
His sacrifice is worthwhile.
Why are you laughing?
At that time, I was drinking with Changge like this.
We later became brothers.
Brothers?
You as a grassland person, how can you be her brother?
Can't I?
You're really an interesting guy.
Come on. Let's drink!
Don't you drink?
Ask someone to clean up here;
otherwise, we might be driven away.
Cheers!
Come on!
Just set it here.
Okay.
Come with me.
Your Highness.
Young Master Wei, you're here.
See. It's grand here.
When I saw the palace,
I knew that, as long as it was lightened,
even the palaces in Chang'an would be overshadowed.
Your Highness, the curfew is in force,
so how could you do such an absurd thing?
Oh, yes. There's a curfew here.
So there are no high buildings with lights along this road, right?
Your Highness, it's the routine.
Please do not let others get the goods on you.
If you keep it secret, who else knows it?
Can Father monitor me far from here?
Have you thought...
about how many people would notice the brilliant lights here?
Would they all keep it a secret?
Do you want to be impeached by the officials?
It's enough!
As long as you can keep it secret, nobody else will care about it!
Curfew...
The rest of Luoyang is all under curfew.
By the way, what I've done
is all to pray for the refugees.
From now on, Ziwei Palace will be out of the darkness.
Your Highness...
Princess, what about telling Young Master Hao first?
If he finds out that I let you leave alone,
he might kill me.
He looks scary, but he won't hurt you. What are you afraid of?
Just tell him I've gone to South Hill
and he won't press about it.
I'll make an early return.
Princess!
Do what I've told you.
Are you going to South Hill again?
Young Master Hao, she hopes you can accompany her to the streets and markets.
Though she's been in Luoyang for a while,
she has no time to wander around here
for worrying about the crown prince.
Weren't you going to walk around?
Let's go.
Is he an old hand at flattering kids?
Yuan really likes him.
We fail to get Young Master's news as we're in Luoyang.
Young Master Qin might be sad about it.
Though Yuan is a kid, she's sensible.
We're not sure about whether
Young Master Qin plays with her or if Yuan makes him happy?
Miser.
Whom are you calling?
You're envying him.
I'm not.
Need another fight.
Good!
Pretty nice!
I want to go there.
- Okay.
- Awesome!
Once again!
Nice!
I want to go there!
Colored umbrellas!
Colored umbrellas here!
- I want it! One, please.
- I want one! So do I!
Don't crowd!
Don't jostle!
Hao Du.
As the shop is quite popular,
the food here must be delicious.
- Please give me one!
- Two, please!
So many people there stop me from getting inside.
Could you buy it for me?
Mind your own.
Don't push!
I want to buy it as well.
Fine. Then stay here. Don't leave here.
- One more, please!
- Hold on.
- Here's the money.
- I have the money for it.
Princess!
Ready or not?
Is it my turn?
I want to buy some!
Which taste do you want?
Sweet.
- Sir! Ready or not?
- I want it, too!
Hurry up! Two, please!
Excuse me.
Changge.
So many people here. Let's find another place to talk.
Yueyan, you have changed a lot.
How would you have dared to come out like this in the past?
You're the same. Always making fun of me.
I don't.
I'm just happy for you.
You always hid behind others.
You were too timid and needed protection.
You're quite different now.
I know what I want.
I want to be the princess of Great Tang.
A real princess.
I don't want to see people starving
or kids having no rice to eat.
I want to be like you.
I want to be a girl fearing nothing.
Yueyan, you're really different.
Someone told me that
I could walk around for I was a man.
But I still can walk around as I'm a girl.
No matter who you are,
the one who likes rabbits or the one who wants to be a princess,
you can be whoever you want.
- And mine!
- Don't push!
Don't push me!
Is mine ready?
I want two, please.
Princess!
Yueyan!
Don't push!
Ready or not, Sir?
I've experienced so many things all the way here.
I thought I would embrace you
and cry bitterly after I met you.
Well, now for me, it's not a big deal.
Quite right. We've all grown up.
Changge, where do you live?
How can I find you later on?
I'm now in Liuyun Taoist Temple.
You don't need to find me especially
for I'll sometimes come to South Hill.
It means we can meet again.
By the way, Hao Du is now in the town.
You need to be careful when you're out.
He'll catch you as soon as he sees you.
Hao... Hao Du... Changge, I have to go now.
Be cautious.
Watch out!
Oh, come on.
♫  My fate brings me nothing  ♫
♫  but loneliness  ♫
I... saw someone was selling sugar figurines,
so I went to buy one for I was greedy...
I wasn't on purpose to leave...
I know I'm wrong. Sorry about that.
I won't do that again.
I'll give it all to you.
♫   I've loved you from our first meeting   ♫
♫  In this lifetime, I'm devoted to you   ♫
♫  What is love?  ♫
♫   There is no escape from this world   ♫
- I...
- I thought I lost you.
You didn't. I...
♫  I only want you to be happy   ♫
You said it's for me.
You're not mad now?
Hao Du, you're not as fierce as your look. Is that right?
♫   Putting in our best efforts   ♫
♫   We won't be afraid of what may come   ♫
Hao Du, where are my desserts?
- I've eaten them.
- Eaten?
I didn't ask you to do so.
Nothing left?
Answer my question.
Hao Du! Hao Du!
Young Master Du.
Greetings to Your Highness.
Why are you here?
His Majesty has gotten the news of Princess's arrival in Luoyang
but he is still worried about you.
That's why I'm here personally
to see whether you're fine or not.
You...
His Majesty could be at ease now.
Never mind. Thanks for your care.
As it's getting dark, you'd better have an early rest.
You didn't let His Majesty down at last.
As you've found her, I can be at ease now.
Father, we haven't seen each other for just a few days.
What's the matter...
As I'm old, it's easier for me to get sick.
But it doesn't matter.
Place what's in your hand properly.
Let's have a talk in the main hall.
Yes.
Father, you're not only visiting Princess here, right?
Yes. But also to deal with my privacy.
Tell me what she has experienced.
I finally found her as I was in Luoyang.
She has suffered a lot.
She walked from the border to Luoyang all the way.
Well, it's good that you'd found her.
It's not peaceful here.
Escort her back to Chang'an early tomorrow morning.
What? Any problems?
No. But...
Don't beat around the bush. Get to the point.
Letting her stay in Luoyang to appease people
is better than asking her to go back.
Someone told me that Crown Prince...
As Princess is here, the refugees can be under control.
What's wrong with Crown Prince?
He...
He has been feeling unwell for a long time,
and everything about the disaster relief
is all up to Princess.
People here trust Princess more.
In order to stabilize the situation,
please allow her to stay in Luoyang
and do what she likes.
I will give her close supervision.
Nothing will go amiss.
Hao Du, you really take her into consideration.
Of course. She's the princess after all.
Is it the only reason?
When I was as young as you,
I always failed to know
my mind or the mind of others.
Father, I don't.
You don't need to explain.
I won't interfere in young people's matters.
Have some tea.
Princess? Or Yueyan?
What am I thinking?
Good!
Nice job!
Come here.
Here you are.
You... It's you!
Your Highness, we meet again.
Your Highness, Young Master Wei is here again.
I'm chatting with my old friend. Why is he here?
Sorry for hindering your time.
Farewell, Your Highness.
Don't leave!
Your Highness! Your Highness!
I see!
Your Highness!
If you're free, why not go to South Hill to help my sister?
How can a man like you let a lady roam around in South Hill?
I'm ashamed of you!
Your Highness!
Madam.
Greetings to Madam.
Here's what's sent from Ziwei Palace.
As I've seen you, what else should I complain about?
It seems to be a good choice
to ask Sheng Xin to go to meet him.
- Cui Tong.
- Yes.
Everything in Luoyang has been dry recently.
I'm afraid it'll have a blazing fire.
Yes, Madam.
Silly girl,
I don't think you should always come to see me.
Don't worry, Hao Du won't know it.
Changge, Minister Du is now in Luoyang.
Be cautious as you're out.
I think you'd better stay here rather than go out.
I could do nothing with the past.
But from now on,
I'll keep you safe at all costs.
I'll look after myself.
You too.
Here you are. Be careful.
Slow down.
Thank you, Sister.
You need to have a good rest.
- Your wound can't be delayed anymore.
- Okay.
Have a try.
It won't hinder your action.
Thank you so much.
My wound is almost healed.
It's said you're a noble from Changan.
I don't think you're a noble.
I think you're a Bodhisattva.
Oh, my wife. She's a princess. Not just any noble!
The heavens bless our nation!
Your Highness is as kindhearted as a Bodhisattva!
Don't be like this.
It is said those from Liuyun Temple are very kind.
I think there's still a Bodhisattva here!
- He's right!
- That's it!
We've seen all the nobles from Luoyang
only except the crown prince.
Actually, he cares for you.
That's why I'm here to look after you.
That's why it's said
His Highness stays in Ziwei Palace in seclusion
with the lights on all night.
Well, he's praying for us.
But it's a palace of the former dynasty...
Is it really a blessing for us?
Forget it. Just remember he's praying for us.
- He's right!
- I agree!
His Highness must do it for the good of us!
Thanks, Bodhisattva!
Miss Quan, what are you doing?
It's said there's an abnormal astronomical phenomenon in Luoyang
and a conflagration will break out in three days.
Though it's hearsay, we still need to be on guard for many people here.
Changge, about the conflagration...
Don't be too worried.
It's just hearsay.
These refugees have left their hometown
and now they can have an unclaimed field to farm.
It's a way of living for them.
This place is not a part of the unclaimed lands.
It's Liuyun Taoist Temple's fields.
The rich in Luoyang are worried about their unknown backgrounds
so they dare not let them farm.
But Master cares nothing about it.
She lends them not only fields but also grains and foods.
She's really a Bodhisattva of Luoyang.
Changge.
Brother Shuyu.
Last time, we parted in Weishui. How are you these days?
I'm fine. Everything is okay.
I'll be fine as long as you're okay.
When did you come back? Why hadn't you told me?
And why are you now with Yan?
Where had you gone?
- And...
- Wei Shuyu, you have too many questions.
Fine. I'll ask nothing.
I won't ask you.
Everything will be fine as long as you're okay.
As you're here, will you leave again?
I don't know.
It's not my home.
I can go nowhere.
You can come with us!
After the things here are settled, we can return to Chang'an together.
You, Yan'er, and I can stay together like before.
Changge.
Li Changge has died.
You can call me A'Li.
No matter what you are called,
you are always my Changge.
I'm really glad to see
you're the same as before, staying together and looking after each other.
Chang...
A'Li.
Can we have a private conversation?
I still have many refugees to nurse
so I can't chat with you.
As you come with Crown Prince,
you must have many things to do.
But...
Anyway, I won't leave here as of yet.
You can take Yueyan first.
We still have chances to chat later on.
Master, Luoyang has become rife with rumors these days.
It's said there must be a conflagration in three days.
As the good and the bad mix up together,
if someone wants to make trouble,
I'm afraid it'll do harm to us.
I hope you have a plan in place.
Don't worry.
Everything has its own fate.
It's good for you to know what to do.
No. I don't know what to do.
A'Li, even if it's a fish, I dare not tell you
I can control all its actions.
So how can I control people?
Reckoning accurately or finding a foolproof way.
It all depends on one's skills.
The Dao should be the core.
What does it mean?
How can you not save someone in need right in front of you?
If you decide to save, it means you can't plan for the future.
Then so what?
Dao only depends on your heart.
Take the consequences.
Everyone in the world should obey it.
Brother Shuyu.
Brother Shuyu?
What are you thinking?
Nothing.
By the way, Crown Prince parties in Ziwei Palace every day.
If he keeps on doing so, things will go wrong.
He's spoiled.
If you...
If you don't know what to do, go to tell Minister Du.
He fears him the most.
Nowadays, the refugees in South Hill are starting to discuss it.
If he keeps acting recklessly, what should we do?
Does Changge know he's here?
Are you worried she will make trouble with him?
You don't believe her!
I promise she won't do such things.
I know.
- Your Highness.
- Have you found him?
Report to Your Highness.
He says that you need to pick him out first
and then he will come to meet you.
Okay.
Nice.
It's so interesting.
Tell me! What are the rules?
You can do whatever you want
except getting close or talking to them.
Can't get close...
Fine. Watch what I do, then you try!
Yes.
Do it.
It's you! You're the one I want!
Your Highness is so smart.
Sheng Xin greets Your Highness.
Stand up.
Nice. I want you to stay with me!
Your Highness, please let us all stay with you.
More people, more fun.
You're right.
Okay. You can all stay.
Thanks, Your Highness.
Minister Du.
Thank you.
Do you want to find Young Master Li?
Well, maybe he isn't at home.
He isn't in Luoyang?
Yes, he is.
Maybe he's at the tea-house in West Market,
or at the tavern in the South Market.
He could be anywhere in Luoyang except his home.
He's in Luoyang but out of home all the time?
No one can tell whether he'll return during the curfew.
I've heard that he married a shrewish woman.
How can he not hide outside?
Minister.
Young Master Wei, why do you come in a hurry?
Report to Minister Du.
I've already dealt out all the relief funds and materials.
Now the situation here is getting better.
But...
Go ahead.
But Crown Prince hasn't come out since he moved to Ziwei Palace.
It's Princess Yongan who's in charge of everything.
People are starting to gossip about it.
And...
And he mixes with a group of jugglers all day...
Absurd!
Your Highness.
- Your Highness!
Your Highness, are you okay?
Yes. What about you, Sheng Xin?
It's good to hear that.
Unfortunately, I forgot to bring a recorder with me;
otherwise, I would let him record all that you've done for the people
and report to His Majesty.
Minister Du, my father is busy with affairs every day.
It's unnecessary to let him know such a trifle.
There's hearsay that Your Highness indulges in a lavish lifestyle every day.
At this rate, His Majesty will finally know it.
Minister Du, I feel grateful listening to your advice.
Thanks for the trouble.
He's my friend in Luoyang.
If you're unsatisfied with it,
I'll ask him to go back where he comes.
I hope you can behave yourself.
Your Highness, if you want me to leave, you can tell me straight.
As I've seen you, what else should I complain about?
It's my great honor
to see such a brilliant person like Your Highness.
I've told him that
I'll ask you to go back where you come.
As you're a young musician of Taichang Temple in Chang'an,
where else should you go back except Changan?
Thanks, Your Highness!
I've already searched there and here.
Where's Ashile Sun? Aren't we going to find her?
He went out before dawn.
He has a map of Luoyang.
He goes to find and then crosses out one by one.
As he finished, he'll then start a new round.
How can he find her by an aimless search?
Everything depends on us.
Sorry.
Unaware.
You smart girl. Wait for my good news!
Let's go.
A'Li, do you like the dishes today?
A'Li, it's no good for you to stay here all day.
Let's go to buy some medicines and you can limber up.
I think it's pretty nice staying here. Self-cultivation.
Then it'll be good.
That's it.
- Sit well, please.
-  Okay.
A'Li...
Don't be narrow-minded.
Do you know what I've learned today?
I feel tired after walking all day.
Well, massage my legs and then I'll tell you.
What? Are you unwilling?
I think you have no manners.
We rent the house and asked for news.
So don't you think...
Cut them. Then you won't be tired.
Any clues?
I'll let you off this time.
Yes. There's one.
It's said a Taoist called Sun Simiao
came from the grasslands and saved a young lady with a lot of work.
Isn't Commandant Li a young lady?
What else?
Why are you not surprised?
I didn't think you guys knew.
Cut the crap! Any other news?
His whereabouts are always unknown.
It's known he will diagnose refugees,
but no one knows where he is now.
Any shelters for the refugees in Luoyang
A place called Liuyun Taoist Temple in South Hill.
Liuyun Taoist Temple?
Why did he run away again?
Anyone here?
Sir, there's no visit today.
Only people with acute diseases are allowed in.
Could you do me a favor? I'm here to find a lady.
Is there anyone called Li Changge? Or Li Shisi?
Li Changge?
There's no Li Changge here.
I think you've come to the wrong place. Please leave at once.
What about Sun Simiao? Is Sun Simiao here?
How can you call Taoist Sun's name?
That's it! Taoist Sun! Has he saved a lady?
He has saved innumerable people,
so how can I remember all of them?
- Please forgive my offense.
- Changge!
You intruder! I'll call others to catch you!
Changge!
Changge! Changge!
♫  The heart gradually responds,  ♫
♫  gradually revives,  ♫
♫  gradually swims towards you  ♫
♫  Before bidding farewell,  ♫
♫  we expect an encounter  ♫
♫  As your silhouette weaves  ♫
♫  and locks in my nostalgic dream  ♫
♫  Before the daybreak,  ♫
♫  through the obsession of love,  ♫
♫  the yearning flowing through thoughts  ♫
♫  There's always a moment  ♫
♫  where the wilderness burns in my heart  ♫
♫  There's always solicitude  ♫
♫  which froze everything between you and me  ♫
♫  Meet each other in different time  ♫
♫  Encourage each other in different worlds  ♫
♫  My longings become a cocoon  ♫
♫  Layer after layer  ♫
♫  It turns into an eternity  ♫
♫  The cocoon in the dark night  ♫
♫  There's always a moment  ♫
♫  where the wilderness burns in my heart  ♫
♫  There's always solicitude  ♫
♫  which froze everything between you and me  ♫
♫  Meet each other in different time  ♫
♫  Encourage each other in different worlds  ♫
♫  My longings become a cocoon  ♫
♫  Layer after layer  ♫
♫  It turns into an eternity  ♫
♫  The cocoon in the dark night  ♫
♫  It is sleepless  ♫