❝ Wild Soul ❞
Lyricist: Fang Jie - Composer: Tian Zuan Fang Xiong - Singer: Zhang Liao
♫  Ah, ah, the story starts  ♫
♫  I am a bad boy  ♫
♫  Oh, oh, the storyline is pretty good
♫  Ah, ah, the story starts  ♫
♫  I am a bad boy  ♫
♫  Oh, oh, the storyline is pretty good  ♫
♫  Tell me why, tell me why  ♫
♫  The ending can't be re-done  ♫
♫  Fate can't be changed?  ♫
♫  This waiting in the afternoon  ♫
[Win The Future]
♫ Will be what I expect  ♫
♫  This waiting in the afternoon  ♫
[Episode 33]
- Don't call anymore!
- I just don't believe that I can't find him.
Don't call anymore!
We've lost this round.
What about your sales performance?
If I'm willing to gamble, I have to accept the loss.
If we're going to lose, then let's lose together.
Don't even think that!
Fang Wei, stay calm!
Do what you are supposed to do.
Boss, come and take a look.
- Come!
- Everyone, come and take a look, too.
Everyone, come here!
From the time Luo Jia caught Guo Han to intercepting him,
it only took her a few days.
Huikang using a dimensional reduction attack this time and was particularly harmful to us.
What exactly are you trying to say?
My instinct tells me that Luo Jia won't stop.
My turn!
Everyone, take a look!
Luo Jia told a horror story
to create fear in Guo Han. Why?
I Think it's pretty simple, customers indeed don't trust new technology.
If you think about it from a more complicated angle,
it's possible that Guo Han wants to cause destruction to both sides.
I'd rather believe the latter.
Me, too.
Boss, can I ask something I shouldn't ask?
Did you hurt Luo Jia a lot?
When trouble comes, let's deal with it.
We'll find a solution.
The first step, surround the target to attack their reinforcements.
Their people will intercept in our building's downstairs coffeeshop.
- Hi, I'm from Huikang Company.
- Sorry.
- Hello! Are you going to Jieke?
- Yes.
- Be careful!
Hello! I'm from Huikang Company.
- How about learning more about it?
- No. Thank you.
Are you Director Xu from Jieke?
It's because many customers will buy a cup of coffee downstairs when they come to visit us.
The second step, go deep into the tiger's den.
They'll also put promotional materials of their high-end solutions in the most eye-catching places.
Even though this isn't a B2B sales technique,
(TN: business to business)
she wants to use a method of humiliation to enrage us.
Who put this here?!
What are you doing? What are you doing?
What are you guys doing?
Why are you moving it?
- What are you doing?
- Don't fight!
But, don't worry!
The ones they surround and intercept are only a portion of the customers.
They can't get close to our actual, more valuable core customers.
So you must safeguard your customer info and not let them get leaked.
- Understood?
- Don't move!
- What are you doing?
- You touched me.
- No, I didn't.
Who touched you?
- Don't... don't be like that. Don't be like that, okay?
- Don't touch it!
Why are you being so unreasonable?
I'll move it. I'll move it. Okay?
It's fine. It's fine.
It's fine.
Boss.
Boss, since we've considered Huikang's every step,
why aren't we fighting back?
Fighting back?
And cause destruction to us both in the end?
A small-to-middle sized client like Guo Han
is insignificant to them.
But to us, we can't lose even one.
Isn't that all the more reason to fight then?
I don't want to live like that anymore.
I don't know what this kind of fighting is for.
- Director Zhou.
- Why are you here?
It's getting late.
Why is the almighty Sales Director of Jieke
still living in a rental apartment?
Who told you I'm renting?
Why are you here?
I came to give you a KPI.
(TN: referring to helping his sales performance)
A basket of eggs will help me meet the sales performance that I can't meet?
Director Zhou,
I have a few shell companies.
We can do fake contracts.
That's illegal!
Then I... I still have a little over two million in personal savings.
Is that enough?
You come to my place first thing in the morning to force me.
Are you considering me your brother?
I don't care if you acknowledge it or not, but I definitely think of you as a brother.
However, that isn't what I'm here to talk about.
I came here today because of this basket of eggs.
A client of mine gave me this basket of eggs.
Originally, he had the eggs, but couldn't sell them.
He only makes a few thousand bucks a month.
But now, because he has my Fast's rural logistics system,
last month, he earned thirty thousand yuan.
Even the chickens are exhausted!
You don't have the servers anymore, do you?
How did you do it?
I moved all the data to the cloud.
It's cloud computing, Zhou Rui.
This is still not what I wanted to say.
Then... Then... Then what do you want to say?
No! You taught me this.
To benefit others, they have to need you.
Have you forgotten?
Old Cao, this doesn't sound like something you'd say.
How is it? How does it feel to be needed by others?
Does it feel amazing?
How do I say this?
It really feels more amazing than making money.
Old Cao,
thank you for coming over this morning.
Why do I always keep paying attention
to those projects worth more than tens of millions of dollars,
but forget that those small stores, small workshops, and small businesses
are the ones that really need Fast logistics?
Cloud computing logistics.
"Cloud computing logistics."
- So am I a part of your plans?
- What a question!
Do you think I'll let you eat this basket of eggs for free?
Okay.
- We're brothers now.
- We already were.
[Beijing Jia An Building]
Director Zhou.
Instead of waiting for you to come, I may as well wait for you here.
Come!
Sir, your coffee.
My apology, Director Zhou! I've already decided to sign a contract with Director Luo.
Then... President Guo, you spending time waiting for me here,
it isn't just to apologize to me, is it?
First, it's to apologize, and then, it's to explain.
Then can I say a few words first?
Alright.
To a business, what is the reason to find customers?
What is the standard when choosing a collaboration partner?
Ultimately, what's the most important is probably still the quantity of customer flow.
The flow that you mentioned, our management calls it consumer flow.
It isn't a frigid concept, but a living person.
It's you, it's me, and it's them.
Do you really think these people care about your "free of charge?"
- Can you let me finish talking first?
- Director Zhou, please listen to me first.
- But once I finish talking, you can understand what I mean—
- No, no. It's like this.
It's like this!
Listen to me first!
Okay, please.
Your scale is only ten percent of the cardinal number, but it can't satisfy me.
Yes. Your solution may be very cheap, but sorry!
My affiliated group has over a dozen people who work hard every year to earn money.
Each year will burn two million.
Sometimes, they burn tens of millions just to hear a sound.
- If we don't have direct profit; of course, I have to withdraw.
- Okay, I'll admit it to you.
Free of charge is indeed a gimmick.
In the future, you still have to pay for our operating cost, maintenance fee, and service charge.
It is indeed a huge cost, but do you know?
What I'm doing now is the real direction of the future.
You have to be patient to see that I'll be able to gradually incubate it.
First of all, I can't wait for you, and secondly, what you call "cost" isn't a cost.
- Time is the real cost.
- Time is...
Sorry, Director Zhou! Can you lower your voices over here?
- We still have other customers here.
- Sorry, sorry!
Thank you, Director Zhou.
President Guo, first of all, I wish you a happy collaboration with Director Luo.
However, I firmly believe that you'll come back to find me.
Because, to me, you all are a bunch of fat rabbits.
[Jieke Company]
What is this? An appeal before sentencing?
- No, this is sales performance.
- Sales performance?
Can this be given to the finance department to book into the account?
Or, maybe you can tell me whose name we put on the invoice for your sales performance?
Master, I remember when I first entered this field,
someone once told me something.
He said, "For our internet industry, C-end
(TN: C-end is business-to-consumer business model.)"
"and only C-end is the real future."
(TN: C-end = A model where products/services are delivered directly to the end user.)
That person told me that before, too.
After all these years, this is the first time
that you've quoted his words.
This has nothing to do with personal feelings,
but I've been feeling more and more these past few years that
- he makes sense.
- It makes sense technically.
In our internet field, technology and sales can't be separated.
Master, you taught me this.
How much of the cash flow can your C-end clients maintain every month?
How much does it cost the company every month for your C-end clients?
I've included the project estimate and the expected revenue for the next five years.
You can call the marketing and finance departments over to discuss it.
I thought you wanted to shirk responsibility and didn't want to shoulder it.
It appears you aren't like that.
You're insane.
- Master, why don't you look at it first before we discuss?
- There's no need to look at it.
I'll ask you two questions.
First of all, among your customer resources,
how many are B-end (business-to-business model), and how many are C-end?
I only have B-end, no C-end.
Second question.
Among all the big sales regions, from South China to Northeast China,
how many are B-end and how many are C-end customers?
There are only B-end and there isn't a single C-end client.
- It appears you know it well.
- However, this is exactly the biggest problem we're currently facing.
What's the problem? Give up B-end clients and turn to C-end clients?
Ruin the Great Wall ourselves and disable our own martial arts skills?
Master, it's because our company has no C-end clients.
Our entire company relies only on B-end customers to support our cash flow.
Then if there is any trouble in the B-end customers,
or if the competitor fights a price war, we'll become very passive.
We can only choose to lower or even give up profit
to maintain it, then... then is this an effective solution?
No, it isn't! We can only choose between loss and bankruptcy, whichever is the lessor of the two evils.
Master, this is a road that waits for death.
It looks like you aren't waiting to die.
You're looking for an early death.
Master. Master, listen to me!
For the past ten years, our work has been gearing towards B-end clients.
However, it's a fact that we're almost reaching the end of this road.
If we don't get ahead before the next industrial wave arrives
and expand our business to C-end,
I really worry if we'll even be qualified to take part in the next round.
With what you said, I fear it isn't just Jieke that is waiting to die.
You want to tell me that I'm waiting to die.
Master,
no one stands taller than you in Jieke,
and no one sees farther than you do.
If even I can see it, then you must've seen it long ago.
However, I really don't understand.
Why do you keep delaying on taking action?
There is a hurtful phrase.
Back then, I said it to someone else.
I even pledged an oath
that I would never say it to anyone else in this lifetime.
But today,
I can't help but say it to you.
What is it?
In your entire life, you've only ever been able to be a tech person.
After you said this back then, he left.
That was the last thing I said to him.
I won't shirk from responsibility, and I didn't want to anger you.
But Master, you're wrong.
You're exactly like him.
Consider that I'm blind then.
The established reality is already in front of us.
I don't want to sit and wait for death.
I also don't want to see Jieke, the company that I've fought alongside you these past ten years,
and the Master whom I've followed for ten years to slowly fall into an abyss.
I'll wait for my death, and you can seek your own death.
Master, then you'll live a life that's worse than death.
- Then what about you?
- Me?
I'll go towards death in order to stay alive.
[Have Moral Integrity, There Exists Promising]
Grandma, what did you forget to take with you again?
I was just about to look for you.
What's the matter?
I installed an app on my grandma's phone to prevent her from going missing.
It needs two emergency contacts.
I know.
The other one is me.
In 1967,
Cellist Jacqueline du Pré married the pianist and conductor, Daniel Barenboim.
It's a great love story from the classical music world.
This is one of the best cello performances that I've ever heard.
I'm giving you this album.
I don't think you've ever used your vinyl player before.
No, I haven't.
Why are you leaving suddenly?
It's because of you.
"Because of me?"
Every knife you cut sees blood. Didn't you know?
I can't pretend that I have no feelings, can I?
I can only wipe the blood on my body clean
- and bury it—
- Zhuo Rui, I don't want to hear you ramble.
I want to open up a new battlefield.
I'm leaving for Northwest China
to start from the bottom with the small-to-mid sized businesses.
Zhou Rui,
from this moment on, don't look at me or interrupt me while I'm talking.
I'm afraid I'll change my mind.
When I mentioned breaking up before,
I was emotional. Did you know?
Every time after I get emotional,
I would regret that I hurled those hurtful words to you.
But actually, you're in my heart.
Do you know that?
I don't want to love many people.
I also don't want to love many times.
I only want to know,
if you must have someone in your future plans, why can't that person be me?
- Luo Jia—
- Don't interrupt!
I have to interrupt.
You're in my heart.
It's only outside of your work and during leisure time, isn't it?
Aren't all men like this?
However, you don't have much free time.
- Luo Jia—
- I told you not to interrupt me.
Zhou Rui,
I know you already tried your best.
However, what I want,
you still can't give it to me.
It's because neither of us will change for the other.
We loved each other before.
We've had each other in our hearts before.
To be honest,
that's enough...
Therefore,
I want to tell you,
let's break up this time for real.
♫  The sun is only shining halfway  ♫
I don't have the strength to love you anymore.
♫  The freckles on my face are bright and dark  ♫
♫  Oh...  ♫
♫  Who sung the song halfway through  ♫
♫  Leaving behind the roars of the chorus in an empty room  ♫
♫  I...  ♫
♫  Slowly tidied up the embarrassment of the dispersing crowd  ♫
♫  Who would abruptly break off the lingering care of the past?  ♫
♫  You deserved it, someone said  ♫
What are you doing?!
Director Zhou!
- Are you getting use to blocking my car?
- Director Zhou.
Don't you think something good happens whenever I stop your car?
Something good? Such as?
Such as, look behind you!
Boss!
[Penalty Notification]
[Our company's employee, Zhou Rui, Sales Director, has disobeyed the company's decision, and is now punished with leave without pay.]
Leave without pay
is the best that I can do for you.
Hi!
Mister, here.
For you! You've worked hard.
You've worked hard, Mister.
Who's seen the bottled waters?
Fang Wei, hyou seen those bottled waters?
You must've forgotten it.
Twist it! Twist the legs counterclockwise.
Everyone, come over here for a bit!
This is the local village officer that I previously mentioned to you all before.
He's called Shi Peng Fei who can help us resolve many local problems.
- This is Old Cao.
- I'm Cao Tian You.
- Call me Xiao Shi.
- Fang Wei. Bei Yao Yao.
- Hello.
- Hello. Hello!
- Sit. Sit. Have a seat!
Come, come, come!
I'll go to get something to eat first.
- Sit down first!
- Drink whatever you want. Open it and drink it.
- Help me hold it for a bit.
- Okay.
You Shi guy, where are you running to?
- I just don't believe your four wheels can run faster than my four hoofs.
- No, wait! What are you doing?
- What do you mean "what am I doing?"
- They are guests. What are you doing?
- What guests?
- What are you doing?
I lost my cattle again!
- I know that.
- If you know, why did you run away and didn't help me search for it?
- What's going on?
- He lost his cattle.
Lost his cattle?
Come with me to search for the cattle!
- It tastes good.
- Boss.
Thanks.
- Director Zhou,
- Go over there and get us something to eat.
be the judge for us!
I pleaded with Hasi Bagen
not to contract out the ranch.
Those city people will occupy your land and won't do any work.
If you... you've done ranching half your lifetime,
then you go to work in the city, what kind of work can you do?
What kind of money can you make, right?
Shi guy, what money can you talk about with me?
You made us tear down our fences,
and put some rings on the cattle saying it's high-tech, and what's the result?
Don't you know how many cattle have been lost?
I-I already promised you.
I'll find each and every one of your cattle for you.
If they aren't found, I'll compensate you.
You'll compensate me?
- What are you going to compensate me with?
- Eat that.
- Use money to compensate.
- Do I look like I need money?
We've been ranching for several generations.
We don't need money! I'm bored with it.
Anyway, I-I'm telling you,
you can't contract out the ranch to the city people.
They will ruin the legacy of several decades of ranching culture.
Xiao Shi, I have a general idea...
A general...
I have a general understanding about your standpoint.
But can you tell me exactly what happened?
You say it!
You say it.
Y-You say it!
He tore down our fences.
He insisted on putting on some rings on our cattle.
Some high-tech rings, right?
- In the end, we lost the cattle.
- Electronic collar.
- How is the signal transmitted?
- By radio transmission.
The signal machine is in my car, but the signal keeps disconnecting.
Just think! I studied liberal arts.
- Another cup.
- I don't know how to tinker with that machine sometimes.
Even when I drive the car in front of the cattle, the machine still doesn't do anything.
I get it. I get it!
The cattle are lost, then you're in trouble.
It's trouble to him, but it's a loss to us.
Each ox costs over ten thousand yuan.
You want to compensate? Can you afford to?
- Director Zhou, let's not talk about cloud computing today.
- Okay.
I need to drive the car to help him search for the cattle right now.
As for the proposal for Sky and Earth,
I won't give it to you for now.
I'll think of a solution to help you solve your problem.
Th-Thank you, Director Zhou.
I'm leaving then.
Brother, what's your name?
Hasi Bagen.
Come!
Jieke Faster Company.
I'll help you find the cattle.
The cattle are really difficult to find.
The radio transmission has problems.
Using radio transmissi is too weak.
I think it's because of the Beidou.
(TN: Beidou Navigation Satellite System)
- Go!
- Here!
- You're impressive, Mr. Lin.
- Let me try!
- Okay.
- Try it.
Please tell President Lin that I'm here.
- President Lin,
- What?
there's a Mr. Wei outside.
- He said he has an appointment with you.
- I got it.
- Okay. Continue to play first! I'll go and see.
- Go ahead.
Open your mouth! Go in.
President Lin.
You're 15 minutes late.
Do you know that in 15 minutes,
- you can negotiate a neither too big nor too small deal?
- I'm sorry.
I had to take care of some things at home.
Why do you smell like the hospital?
- President Lin, last time you said—
- Change your bad habits!
Don't just get straight to the point.
That's all I know to do.
Our suppliers are putting off supplying our materials and now they're raising their prices.
These are signs that Americans give off before they they cut off supply.
Director Wei, the Americans have talked about cutting off the Chinese's chip supply for many years now.
Whether people believe it or not, and even if they really do cut us off,
then Jieke still won't be the only one who'll have problems.
Internet companies throughout China will all be affected.
You're a salesman.
Do you have to be that worried?
Okay.
Let me talk about another matter then.
O&T's Chairman Liu, Liu Feng, is also interested in Jieke.
You should know about this, shouldn't you?
If this matter
is true, it still can't be said with certainty if it's a blessing or a curse.
But for you, it's definitely not a blessing.
To show sincerity,
I've already sent a client's information to Director Luo last time.
In here, it's everything.
Is the agreement between us still valid?
Of course, it's still valid.
Come on, President Lin!
- Bye-bye.
- Goodbye!
- Bye-bye!
- Bye bye!
- Thank you!
- Thanks!
Come back again next time, Brother!
What's the matter, Big Guy?
We should at least, give a gift on the first meeting upon coming here.
Are you trying to be a do gooder again and save people from disaster?
Bei Yao Yao.
A free drone! You take care of it.
- Okay.
- Fang Wei!
I know what I need to do.
Hello, this is Zhong Lian Technology Company, is it?
I am O&T's Director Zhao's friend.
Right, Zhao Lan.
- Hello!
- We want to request the approximate location
- Chairman Wang.
- of something that uses a radio transmitter.
- Hello, hello!
- Cattle. It's cattle.
Have you received the beef jerky I sent you?
Why are you thankful? It wasn't worth much.
- It's a small gift, but holds a lot of meaning.
- What else do we need to install for it?
Yes, please give me your email. I'll send you the configuration right away.
I'm really not asking about the loan.
I'm really not.
- Go ahead and tell me.
- Quantity?
- It won't end up being a small quantity.
- Okay, all right. I understand.
Gao Jian, have you received my email?
Yes, the main meaning is that.
Hurry! I'll be waiting for your news.
Thank you.
[Text Posting]
[I am looking for a drone. Da Jiang drone will do. If there's no JD30, I086 is fine.]
[I'll wait online. It's quite urgent.]
[I have only the Hellfire. Do you want that?]
[Go away!]
Cui Long, if the facial mask you gave me doesn't save my face,
I'll kill you!
- Who is it?
- It's me, Shen Jia Zhen.
I'm coming.
What's the matter?
I'm having my period, so my stomach hurts.
Women were born to suffer.
Hurry! Quickly get up. Quickly get up.
Quickly go to the sofa to lie down.
Go on! Go on!
Grandma.
I have medicine in my briefcase.
- Where is your briefcase?
- Over there.
I'll get it for you.
Is this it?
No, it isn't this one.
It's this one.
This isn't a pain killer.
It's okay. I always take this.
If you take a lot of this medicine, you won't be able to have kids.
Why are you messing around?
Don't have children?
Does Ungrateful Child know?
No, he doesn't.
You don't have to have a baby with him.
But you'll have your own child eventually, won't you?
If you mistreat your body right now,
you'll be the one suffering later.
Just endure the pain.
You have to stop taking the medicine.
[Yao Yao, I come late]
Brother, thank you very much!
Have another sip, Brother.
- No, I've drank too much.
- Brother. Brother, drink some more!
- I can't anymore.
- Take another sip! I need to thank you.
Brother! Brother, stop sleeping!
Drink some! If you're dizzy, who will I drink it with?
- If you can't, then I will.
- Drink slowly.
- He can't drink anymore!
I have to thank my brother.
Drink some!
Come, Fang Wei!
Everyone, let's drink together!
Drink up! Come on!
- Get up.
- Say no more.
You'd drink it all in one go if we were good friends.
Cheers.
Bei Yao Yao, I'm not here to see you.
I'm here to deliver the drone.
I know.
Sounds good.
I also don't think you're here because of me.
You posted it onto our WeChat Moments.
If you didn't want me to come, you could have blocked me.
Fine!
- Slow down.
- Wait!
- Hi.
- Hey.
Bei Yao Yao, I'm the only one who can see your WeChat Moments, am I not?
Everyone can see it.
But the one who was able to get here, is still really only you.
Just now, it's your words!
I think my coming here was worth it.
- I'll give you a toast.
- Come on! Have a drink!
You're overthinking, aren't you?
Let me tell you the truth!
I don't want to date.
- Give me a reason!
- I don't trust you.
Then whom do you trust?
Work!
So are you planning to spend the rest of your life with work?
Cui Long, let me tell you.
I've been hurt by someone before.
I've hurt someone else, too.
It was ruthless.
Bei Yao Yao, let me also tell you something.
I don't know about your past, and you don't have to talk harshly.
I have only one request.
Give me some more time!
Okay. I'm leaving now.
You just said to give you some time.
How long is it then?
♫  Was it joy or sadness?  ♫
♫  It boomerangs in my heart  ♫
♫  Everything about you  ♫
♫  Is the same as when I met you  ♫
♫  Everyone says love is just a dream  ♫
♫  But after meeting you  ♫
♫  I believe in this dream  ♫
Must you drive all night just to deliver the drone?
Don't you know what express delivery is?
Drive safely! No matter how late it is, tell me when you get home.
♫  From those who are too crazy  ♫
Yes!
♫  I want to ask the wind how far it will blow  ♫
♪  Today is a good day  ♪
♪  Whatever you want can be done  ♪
❝ One Half ❞ by Mo Fei Ding Lu
♫  The sun has only shone halfway  ♫
♫  The freckles on my face are bright and dark  ♫
♫  Oh...  ♫
♫  Who sung the song halfway through  ♫
♫  Leaving behind the roars of the chorus in an empty room  ♫
♫  I...  ♫
♫  Slowly tidied up the embarrassment of the dispersing crowd  ♫
♫  Who would abruptly break off the lingering care of the past?  ♫
♫  You deserved it, someone said  ♫
♫  It would be for the best that the story stays unfinished  ♫
♫  Those words were spoken halfway  ♫
♫  When those few words reached the tip of the tongue  ♫
♫  It would take several years to accept  ♫
♫  Whose heart is closed midway from now on  ♫
♫  Locking up all the endless insomnia in the past?  ♫
♫  Some words are only spoken halfway  ♫
♫  To adjust the emotional intensity afterwards  ♫
♫  Just air-dry it slowly with time  ♫
♫  Whose heart will miss a half from now on  ♫
♫  Just let it totally submerge  ♫
♫  My remaining dimness  ♫
♫  The other half  ♫