❝ Wild Soul ❞
Lyricist: Fang Jie - Composer: Tian Zuan Fang Xiong - Singer: Zhang Liao
♫  Ah, ah, the story starts  ♫
♫  I am a bad boy  ♫
♫  Oh, oh, the storyline is pretty good  ♫
♫  Ah, ah, the story starts  ♫
♫  I am a bad boy  ♫
♫  Oh, oh, the storyline is pretty good  ♫
♫  Tell me why, tell me why  ♫
♫  The ending can't be re-done  ♫
♫  Fate can't be changed?  ♫
♫  This waiting in the afternoon  ♫
[Win The Future]
♫ Will be what I expect ♫
♫  This waiting in the afternoon  ♫
[Episode 12]
Who grills meat like this?
I'm hungry! If you grill it one at a time, how long will it take before it's ready?
- Even if you're hungry, you still need to wait until everyone gets here.
- Everyone?
Ye Chao Dong skipped out because he doesn't drink.
You aren't on good terms with Xiao Yun.
Old Lei said that he was busy and would be here later.
Fang Wei is probably scared that he would've to pay the bill.
He joined the team after I resigned.
The new replaces the old. How meaningless!
That rhymes pretty well.
Give Fang Wei a call and ask him where he is.
What's the rush?
You should appreciate our time together.
If you really resign, then we won't be able to see each other even if we want to.
Are you that eager to see me leave?
I'm afraid that you'll regret it.
How much did you drink to be like this?
How much did she drink?
Come! Let me show you guys something.
Have the Marketing, Sales, and Public Relations departments come up with a layoff plan as soon as possible.
Regarding the redundant staff, our Sales department already has a preliminary layoff plan.
Then I have to say this.
As long as Jieke is still operating,
not a single employee in the Sales department can be laid off.
Director Zhou, you should clearly know that
what determines if a business thrives or dies, isn't skill or talent, but cash flow.
How much will be saved by laying off a few sales department employees?
How much?
I, Zhou Rui, will give my annual income and bonus this year to take care of these people.
I only have one request.
Not one person in the sales department can be cut.
Xie Yi!
Come, come! You handed in your resignation for nothing.
It's for nothing!
Right now, you still have a chance to change your mind.
I don't regret it.
I'll never regret it.
I won't hide it from you guys.
I also handed in my resignation letter.
Old Lei, no...
Why did you do that?
To be honest,
I never thought I'd last in Sales into the Twenty-First Century.
I've never been a great salesperson.
I can't compare to Chao Dong's sales performance.
I'm not as young as Xie Yi.
I'm not as capable as Fang Wei, either.
Young Long, don't look at me! I wasn't going to compare myself to you.
In addition, my proposals aren't as good as Xiao Yun's.
I'm only still here today because President Chen and I are old friends.
To put it bluntly,
the waves wash away the sand, just as times've changed.
I can't do it anymore; I really can't keep up.
- You don't have to feel sorry for me.
- This cup of wine is to toast you, Old Lei. Cheers!
- Thanks!
- Old Lei.
- It's a toast to Director Zhou, too.
- All right.
I...
have a toast to myself.
Stop acting up!
Take it easy. Easy!
Don't say anything!
What are you doing here?
Do you have amnesia?
I had a very long dream.
Me, too! I dreamt of you.
Can you not be so vulgar?
I'm being serious.
I dreamt that we were bidding in the O&T negotiation room.
We took turns bidding and drove the price lower and lower.
From tens of millions to just a few million. Then—
Help me call the nurse.
It isn't empty yet, why should we call the nurse?
- I told you to call the nurse, then just call.
- Tell me what you need.
I can help you.
I want to go to the bathroom.
I... I...
I'll go with you.
Let's go!
In a minute! I'm dizzy.
Lend me a hand!
What are you doing here?
Didn't you tell me to come?
When did I tell you to come?
You told Xiao Le that you were in Saihanba.
Isn't that you trying to tell me indirectly?
Then you posted a photo with the IV drip, isn't that got your location?
I told Xiao Long that I was in Saihanba
because I was worried the company might need me for something.
I sent her a photo because I really thought that I was going to die last night.
Really? You felt that you were dying yesterday.
Then what are you doing here?
I'm going home.
- We're here.
- Ma'am.
- Is there anywhere to hang the IV drip in there?
- No.
Go ahead! I'll hold it for you outside of the door.
Go on!
- Don't get too close to me.
- I can't hear you!
I hear nothing.
- Don't get too close.
- Okay. I got it.
Don't get too close. Got it!
[Female Toilet]
Excuse me!
Are there shared portable power bank chargers here?
- What did you say?
- Shared portable bank chargers.
No.
What a shabby place!
[Jieke Company]
Where are you?
After you've rested, reply to me.
Let me borrow your shoulder to lean on.
DIdn't I come to let you lean on me?
I bet you couldn't imagine
the two of us would be so miserable now.
Miserable?
Xiao Le is such a traitor.
Shouldn't we thank Xiao Le?
Hello!
Did you want to borrow my charger just then?
- Yes, yes, yes.
- This is mine; I'll let you borrow it.
- Thank you so much.
- You're welcome!
It has only one port, do you want to charge it or should I?
I already powered off my phone, so I don't need to charge.
I'll charge it then.
Take it.
Then... Then I'll take back my shoulder and return it to you in a little bit.
Hello! You are really rushing.
Director Zhou,
where did you go?
President Chen is going crazy looking for you.
It's fine! Let him stay crazy for a while.
How is the company?
Director Wei called everyone into a meeting.
I don't know why, but he didn't ask for me.
Then you can just look for clients by yourself.
You can't expect others to always arrange work for you, can you?
Without your guidance,
I don't even know how to open my mouth.
I'll show you a good way.
Go to a square where there are a lot of people.
Ask for ¥1 from everyone.
Once you've gathered ¥100,
it'll be mission accomplished.
However, I'll remind you! No matter what method you use, it cannot be illegal.
Then wouldn't I be a beggar?
You've only one chance to ask for help.
No need! Wouldn't that be just ¥100?
I'll definitely complete the mission and surpass the quota.
I'm watching you boast.
Zhou Rui.
Director Zhou.
what exactly are you doing?
Can you reveal a little?
What do you want to know?
You suddenly got out of touch.
- Everyone feels lost.
- Zhou Rui, I want to go back.
I'm afraid Director Wei will take advantage, you know?
- Okay. I'm hanging up.
- Don't force me to search for you!
- You know my skills.
- You dare?
Come on! I have another call.
Hello, President Li! President Li.
My cellphone? My cellphone's battery was out.
I've already given your account to Wei Yan.
His salesperson will contact you.
I'm keeping an eye on it for you. Don't worry!
Hello, President Huang!
Of course, we'll take care of your company's matter.
I'll let you know when it's done.
I'll contact you when I get back.
Yes, yes, yes. It's because my cellphone was out... out... of battery.
No power left.
Okay, okay, okay.
[Jieke Company]
Morning!
Old Lei!
- Old Lei! Old Lei!
- Don't shout!
- He resigned.
-His things are still here.
You must be joking.
Fang Wei, what are you doing?
He's really gone.
Even his tea set is gone.
When Old Lei isn't here,
it really feels like we lost something.
Why didn't he think it through?
Just to endure two more years, then he'd be able to retire.
- Two years go back quickly.
- No more talking, okay?
I think he actually thought it through.
Now, he's resigned, he gets to be free.
He's gone?
It isn't a workplace without people coming in and out.
Did your father teach you that?
What's wrong with that?
[Jieke Company]
Xie Yi, I...
I want to explain a little to you.
The person you need to explain to is Old Lei.
Do you believe that I'll drag you across the floor?
Director Zhou isn't here, so Director Wei said,
I should lead this meeting regarding the matter of payments.
Stop messing around!
Everyone is here?
Yes. Everyone is here.
Think about who hasn't made their payments yet.
Old Lei should've some.
Previously, he was working on a health-related project.
It's for that difficult President Lu.
With the current situation, I don't know who will take care of the project.
Introduce the project's detailed content.
Okay.
Sheng Kang is the leader in Beijing's health industries.
At the end of last year, Old Lei and Sheng Kang's President Lu agreed on a coordination agreement and signed it.
The contract is for... for...
It was for... twenty four million.
Currently, the project is complete, but they still owe us nine million.
- What's up with the delay?
- I've met with President Lu only once.
However, I heard from Old Lei that President Lu is very strange.
It seems that she's difficult to deal with and rarely shows her face.
However, I heard that she spends most of her time at the beauty parlor.
What should we do then? Will you follow up with her?
Old Lei only said that he's leaving the client with me.
He didn't say for me to go after the payment.
A part of your responsibility as a salesperson is to make sure you get your payments.
If you don't think you can handle this, hand your project over to someone else.
This Sales performance is dependent on a competent team member.
How can this be? This is what Old Lei handed over to me.
That's why I asked you to follow up.
I can go with you.
That won't be necessary.
All right! Who else?
He has one.
Tell me about it!
Brother Dong! Brother Dong, I really do regard her as a friend.
- I want to help her, but—
- We don't have friends in the workplace.
Follow up on your own clients.
Director Zhou won't give you a second chance.
Xiao Yun, I don't know what to tell you.
Do you know who is the most miserable after a battle?
- Those who die.
- No.
It's those who got abandoned.
Put it on my card.
- Hello, President Lu!
You are...
I'm Jieke's Xiao Yun.
Take it to the car for me after you wrap it.
President Lu, let's have a chat over coffee if you're free.
Next time!
She ran when she heard Jieke.
She keeps evading her debts.
Hello! I don't want my flowers anymore.
Beauty, can you lend me one yuan?
I want to buy a bottle of water, and then, I'll transfer the money to you after I add your WeChat.
You can transfer me the money through WeChat but can't buy the water with it?
Bro! Bro! Bro, can you lend me one yuan?
I made a bet with someone and just need one more yuan.
You're losing!
You...
Sis., I just need one more yuan to buy a hamburger.
Can you lend me it?
Scammer!
I just got scammed out of ten yuan.
Scammers are resorting to scamming even one yuan now.
Do you have one yuan in a coin?
My bike chain broke, soI need to tighten it.
There are so many bikes up there, isn't it just as good to switch yours for another one?
You're so inflexible.
Little friend.
Do you have one yuan?
No.
How did you buy your lollipop then?
Do you want some?
You can enjoy it yourself.
- All right, let go of me.
- Wait!
What are you doing?
It's my first time meeting your parents.
I'm embarrassed to have come empty-handed.
I have to straighten myself out.
Who said you were meeting them?
You can just drop me off here.
I thank you. See you in Beijing!
Hello, Auntie and Uncle!
What are you doing?
Jia Jia, why did you come back on your own?
Didn't your dad go to pick you up?
Who is this?
Nice to meet you, Auntie!
Auntie, do you have potatoes at home?
Yes.
- I'll look for it myself.
- What is he doing?
Auntie, I found it.
Ignore him, Mom!
If you put this on where the needle was, it won't swell up.
Don't you believe me?
Do you believe me?
It's nice.
It's kind of cool.
Have you eaten yet?
- What do you want to eat? I'll prepare it for you.
- Okay. Thank you, Auntie.
- Mom, he already ate.
When did I eat? I haven't eaten yet.
You've already eaten.
I haven't eaten.
I said you already ate, then you've eaten.
Fine! I ate. I already ate.
I won't eat. I won't eat at all.
What are you doing?
Jia Jia's friend, you...
- Auntie.
- What's your name?
J-Just call me Zhou Rui.
Yes. It's the Zhou from Zhou Gong,
(TN: Also known as Duke of Zhou)
and Rui from sharp.
(TN: Pinyin for sharp is "rui li")
It's a good name.
Not even the sharpest of knives can hurt the Duke of Zhou.
It's just a dream, isn't it?
Great description!
Have a seat!
Jia Jia, come with me for a second.
Why are you treating this like it's your home?
It's the most basic quality a salesperson should have.
Sit here!
Talk!
Talk about what?
How long have you been with Zhou Gong Rui?
What did you call him?
We aren't together.
I'm serious.
We really aren't.
They firmly believe that tofu skin
is exactly the great inventors of tofu.
Why did you bring him home if you aren't together?
He stayed with you the entire night at the hospital, didn't he?
He even knows to use potatoes to stop the swelling.
You won't tell me the truth, will you?
I'll ask him later, then.
Mom, there's really nothing going on between us.
We can't even be considered colleagues.
We just work in the same industry.
Now that your dad isn't here,
tell me before your dad comes home.
What exactly is going on?
Why does everything about you seem wrong this time you come home?
It's probably because it's been a while since I've come home.
Everything feels strange.
Fine! You don't want to tell me, do you?
Then, does Zhou Gong Rui know about what problem you're hiding?
I didn't tell him anything.
If there really was something wrong, I would've told you before I told him.
Mom, don't try to get any information from me.
We really aren't together.
He's already here, we can't just kick him out.
Where is he going to stay?
In the storage room.
It has long been part of the Chinese history
and ancestors in the countryside, too.
Who is that?
President Lin?
President Lin, you still haven't leave yet?
It still isn't that late yet.
Why is everyone in the Sales department gone already?
Hasn't the Sales department been always like this? They never stayed in the office during work hours.
Besides, their boss, Director Luo, hasn't been here in days.
I'm telling you, Bian Hai Tao!
Stop gossiping about them to me.
Should I ask them all to come back?
What then? Pay them overtime?
[Wei Yan]
- Hello?
- President Lin.
There's some bad news.
The bank has approved Jieke's loan.
All right. I got it.
Hello? Did you find him?
Keep going! Continue to look!
Can you stop calling?
Your apprentice eloped and can't be found.
What good is it to keep on calling?
Who did he elope with?
Don't pretend you don't know!
Which girl? I really don't know.
Don't be so curious!
Just consider giving him some time off.
Zhou Rui has been working for you day and night since he came.
Give him a break! Come on.
President Chen.
- Sister Wei.
- Old Lei.
You haven't been here in so long.
It's full of elites in here, so I dare not come.
- Are you okay with this?
- Yes.
Bring us another glass!
Have you completed the resignation formalities?
I completed it as you instructed.
- I can do it myself.
- Let me! Let me!
That's good! Thank you.
I can't get that rascal Zhou Rui
to come back, no matter what.
The board of directors are also pressuring me to fire someone.
I'm sorry to make you do this.
When Zhou Rui comes back, he'll help you get another position.
It just so happened that I wanted to take a break.
With just one sip, I know that this wine is for me to drink.
Sister Wei is still the same as always.
Here!
I got it!
Gong Rui, can you drink?
I...
I'm okay. Drink with my dad!
Zhou Gong Rui, I won't be drinking with you.
I just took some antibiotics.
Auntie and Uncle, thanks to both of you.
Thank you for your hospitality.
Welcome to Saihanba!
- Drink what you can.
- Okay.
Good! Good wine! Good wine!
A-Auntie, w-what is this?
Soba noodles!
Soba noodles?
It's made from buckwheat flour.
It's said that when he was still alive, Kangxi also ate this
(TN: The 3rd emperor of the Qing dynasty. His 61-year reign makes him the longest-reigning emperor of Chinese hisory.)
when he was hunting in the Mulan imperial hunting park.
- Isn't it delicious?
- Yes.
- Dad.
- It's tasty.
Zhou Gong Rui...
Zhou Gong Rui is from the south.
- His throat is too narrow to swallow this.
- Who said that? I can swallow this.
I like it. Really!
Do you eat raw garlic?
You lose half of the nutrients, if you don't eat buckwheat with garlic.
- Here!
- Okay.
Add some black vinegar.
This is black vinegar. This...
Uncle, here's a toast to you.
Have some food before you drink.
- There's also some grilled meat.
- Okay.
Here! Here! Here!
Gong Rui, do you like Baozipi?
(TN: the bread portion of steamed buns)
Sister, good to see you again.
Please, come inside.
Take it easy!
Miss, is this your first time here?
Yes. I want to look around.
I'm sorry, Miss! We're for members only, so you can't look around.
- How much is the membership?
- We have several tiers.
The basic is twenty nine thousand eight hundred.
- The higher one is thirty nine thousand eight hundred, and sixty nine—
- Hold on! Hold on! Hold on!
Mr. Long, I want to ask you a favor.
Accelerate! Just hit him!
I just don't believe that he won't get out of the way.
- Hit him!
- Come on.
- Come on!
- Accelerate!
Hit me! Come on!
Okay.
Brother-in-law!
It isn't like I'm getting an inheritance from you.
Why do you keep avoiding me?
- Open the door. Open it!
- Let him in!
You should've told me earlier that you were Young Master Cui's sister.
Young Master Cui's mother is one of our biggest customers.
Young Master Cui already told us on the phone
to take care of you because of your poor health.
My health is poor?
What's wrong with me?
I know that that you were diagnosed with a terminal illness at such a young age.
- I can understand how you feel, but please be at ease!
- Stupid Cui Long.
- Medical facilities nowadays are amazing.
- B*stard!
You have to believe in yourself.
Miss, which room is President Lu in?
- You are?
- I'm her assistant.
I have her phone and I want to hand it to her.
Okay. That's the room.
Our President Lu is always so forgetful.
She's getting older, so she's confused.
I don't have money!
It's just a mere fifty million.
A mere?
I just paid off your twenty-million debt.
- Mere?
- Really!
That was an accident.
Brother-in-law, help me one more time.
I'll definitely pay you back in full with interest.
Let's do this!
In addition to the twenty million from last time, it comes out to be seventy million.
I want to own fifty one percent of your company.
Let's do this, Brother-in-law!
I'll pay you the highest interest rate on private loans.
This... This... Forget the shares!
It's like you're trying to scam me of my money.
Are you addicted to losing money?
You win some, you lose some.
I'm losing money now to win later.
Isn't that what you always say?
Poor, but still strong, never giving up on your ambitions.
Don’t worry that no one would appreciate you! Just understand where you are heading to.
In this world, under the sky, who doesn’t know you?
Brother-in-law,
look at this!
[Fast Future Technology Cloud Computing Project Proposal]
You've even created a fake project proposal
to try to cheat me of my money.
Brother-in-law, this is cloud computing.
I'm telling you! As long as we succeed in this,
we'll be able to ring the bells in the near future.
Ring the bells? It will be ringing your death knell!
What century is this?
Brother-in-law, don't get so riled up!
Brother-in-law,
think about the fifty million.
If we were to convert the previous twenty million into shares,
it would be worth five percent at most.
Pull over!
- Get out!
- We aren't there yet.
Get out!
A man without foresight!
He doesn't even understand cloud computing,
but he calls himself an internet-guru.
It's hard to live up to a great reputation.
❝ One Half ❞ by Mo Fei Ding Lu
♫ The sun is only shining halfway  ♫
♫ The freckles on my face are bright and dark  ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫  Who sung the song halfway through  ♫
♫  Leaving behind the roars of the chorus in an empty room  ♫
♫  I...  ♫
♫  Slowly tidied up the embarrassment of the dispersing crowd  ♫
♫  Who would abruptly break off the lingering care of the past?  ♫
♫  You deserved it, someone said  ♫
♫  It would be for the best that the story stays unfinished  ♫
♫  Those words were spoken halfway  ♫
♫  When those few words reached the tip of the tongue  ♫
♫  It would take several years to accept  ♫
♫  Whose heart is closed midway from now on  ♫
♫  Locking up all the endless insomnia in the past?  ♫
♫  Some words are only spoken halfway  ♫
♫  To adjust the emotional intensity afterwards  ♫
♫  Just air-dry it slowly with time  ♫
♫  Whose heart will miss a half from now on  ♫
♫  Just let it totally submerge  ♫
♫  My remaining dimness  ♫
♫  The other half  ♫