❝ Wild Soul ❞
Lyricist: Fang Jie - Composer: Tian Zuan Fang Xiong - Singer: Zhang Liao
♫  Ah, ah, the story starts  ♫
♫  I am a bad boy
♫  Oh, oh, the storyline is pretty good  ♫
♫  I'm a bad boy  ♫
♫  Ah, ah, the story starts  ♫
♫  I am a bad boy
♫  Oh, oh, the storyline is pretty good  ♫
♫  I'm a bad boy  ♫
♫  Tell me why, tell me why  ♫
♫  The ending can't be re-done  ♫
♫  Fate can't be changed?  ♫
♫  This waiting in the afternoon  ♫
[Win the future]
♫  Will be what I expect  ♫
♫  This waiting in the afternoon  ♫
[Episode 3]
We'll need you to put in some great effort tonight.
- We need to re-do the bidding proposal.
- Director Zhou, we might be able to re-print it.
We really don't have enough time to re-do it.
Besides, Director Wei is the manager of the O&T bidding committee.
You were the one to burn the documents so we need his signature in order to re-do the proposal.
[Jieke Company]
Do you all think the same way?
All right. You may all leave.
- Engineer Liu.
- Director Luo.
I'm sorry! I'm late.
Here's the situation!
Before negotiating the price on this O&T project, I want an accurate
warehouse sorting efficiency rate guaranteed to be beyond ten thousand.
If we can't reach that, then we're overpromising.
Director Luo, let me put it this way.
If someone who does long-distance runs all the time, he runs a distance of five miles consistently.
Suddenly, at the same pace, he runs six miles, his heart and lungs should still be able to endure it.
I don't think that's considered overpromising.
It still doesn't mean that there are completely no risks, does it?
That's why we need to organize the test right away.
- All right! Go ahead and get ready for it.
- Sure.
- I'll work on the rundown.
- Got it.
Bro,
this is my first time seeing the morning sun this year.
Our test's results are better than Huikang's.
- You're lucky.
- What I want is a good result.
What do you want me to do?
Help me create a hypothetical test on the maximum limit for warehouse sorting.
If you need any reference data, ask the Technical Department.
All I need is the Wi-Fi password.
[Server Single Bin Sorting Efficiency]
[Server Performance Test Evaluation]
[Processor Performance]
[Temperature Is Too High]
Did you do this based on the standard sizes?
Of course, not.
There are various sizes and even irregular shapes.
I based it on the most difficult measurements.
Got it!
[Processor Performance]
[Temperature Is Too High]
[Server Messages]
[Processor Performance - Sorting Robot System - Cache System - Database]
10,063.
The Computer Room Processor is burned.
It'll mess up the robotic sorting system.
That's the end of the world.
[O&T Group]
[Huikang's Project Bidding Proposal]
[Technology] - [Price]
Go ahead and have it all.
Every time we bid on a project,
it's so annoying that we need to guess our rivals' moves.
If, they insist on working with the original data,
they'll definitely lose.
[Technology]
[Price]
You didn't go home?
I'm re-doing the O&T bidding proposal.
There are so many people outside, how can we be short-staffed?
First, they don't want to work with me.
Second, I don't want to use them, either.
Do you really think you have three heads and six arms?
Master, can I bring someone over from the East China Regional Office?
You can't! People in the East China Region have their own matters.
If I moved someone over and the project became their performance, how am I going to calculate it?
How would we calculate the commission?
Acutally, if our company's technology can score 90 points,
Huikang can only score 75 max.
I'm confident in using our technology, we'll be able to win this project.
However, if we need to win this project, we'll need to re-do the proposal.
You burned the proposal, didn't you?
Then you need to bear the consequences.
I really can't help you on this.
Master, then,
can you let me do this my way?
- Understood.
- President Du.
Sorry to trouble you.
President Chen, you're here.
Please take a seat!
This is the first time inviting you to dinner.
I also don't know what you like.
- Let the host make the decision.
- Okay.
This is also my first time having dinner with President Du.
I also don't know what kind of wine you like to drink.
I made the decision and brought you two bottles of Australian red wine.
You're here because of Zhou Rui, aren't you?
You actually already know all about it.
He was just transferred from the East China Region.
He's young and impulsive.
He always thinks outside the box.
I'm afraid he might trouble the clients and trouble you.
The day of the test, Jieke was indeed ahead of Huikang.
It's a fact that your company's technology is outstanding.
Jieke can go ahead and prepare the quote for pricing.
President Du, you're so open-minded.
It makes me even more worried.
President Chen, I'm going to toast you with tea instead of wine.
I hope you don't mind.
So how is it? When can I come over?
President Chen hasn't agreed.
It's just a bidding proposal.
It won't take up a lot of time.
We're done with the technical part.
You need to help me out with the price and look at every single word on the proposal.
- Every single word.
- No problem!
Now that you're here in Beijing, are you feeling a little lonely?
- Why are you here?
- I'm on vacation.
- Then let's get to work.
- Bring it on!
Let's go!
Director Zhou, are you looking for me?
I don't care what Director Wei asked you to do.
You're leading this O&T project.
So right now I need to know your attitude on this.
Not... not the attitude towards me,
but toward this project.
What kind of attitude can I have?
Option one, stay here.
We work together on the quote for the pricing.
Option two, go out the door and leave.
[Server Purchase]
- Is this the price we're offering?
- No.
A hundred sixty-eight million, I'm guessing.
This will be Huikang's first offer, but it's definitely not their final offer.
A hundred sixty-seven million,
will be their offer for the second round.
So one hundred sixty-five million should be Huikang's final offer.
Which means that we'll be chosen as long as we have a lower offer, doesn't it?
Then that depends on whether Director Luo will get too competitive or not.
Director Zhou, if both are competitive,
then both parties won't have any room for profit.
Yang Lu, help me calculate
how low can our final offer be.
O&T's final offer is a hundred and sixty-nine million.
Our first offer was a hundred and sixty-eight million.
Our final offer can't be lower than a hundred sixty-five million.
You're only giving me four million to negotiate with, how am I supposed to negotiate?
Only when we keep it above one hundred sixty-five million, can we ensure making a profit.
Here's why.
We've analyzed the other companies' possible profit and wiggle room and conservatively speaking—
I don't care about the other companies. Tell me Jieke's!
Jieke has high debt and high purchase costs.
- So their offer will be—
- Not necessarily!
Their technology score is higher than ours.
Even though they have a lot of debt, they don't have bad assets.
Therefore, their final offer might be close to ours.
In order to promise to make a profit, our final offer needs to be kept at a hundred and sixty six million.
I just want five million to be authorized.
Director Luo, the authorization you're requesting isn't something our marketing department can be responsible for.
What if I insist on having it?
Then you'll have to ask President Lin yourself, Director Luo.
I'm sorry, Director Luo! President Lin isn't here.
How about...
you talk to President Chen directly?
Keep the profit! It can't be any lower than this.
I've always been curious.
I heard that you've never lost a battle in the East China Region.
Is that true?
Of course, I have! If I've never lost, how do I win?
What's your opinion on winning and losing?
Depends on what you're fighting for.
Are you fighting for the clients or fighting the enemy?
So are you fighting for Du Heng or fighting Luo Jia?
I'm not sure yet.
Tonight at nine. My treat!
Busy.
You pick the place then.
No!
Give me a chance to apologize.
We'll see!
Meeting someone here?
How could you tell?
Eyes are the traitors to the soul.
♫  Oh, oh, the storyline is pretty good  ♫
♫  I am a bad boy
♫  I am a bad boy  ♫
♫  Ah, ah, waiting with patience  ♫
♫  Oh, oh, the helplessness of a stranded beast  ♫
♫  I am a bad boy  ♫
I locked you in a storage room.
It was my fault.
I'm making it up to you now.
I've written my final offer...
My final offer right now is in my palms.
We, as sales people, are gamblers.
Let's gamble! Left or right?
I never gamble.
Why would I gamble on things that I'm sure of?
I'm not joking with you.
If you don't pick one, you'll just miss your opportunity.
Five, four...
Your way of apologizing is very unusual.
Three...
Your gambling problem is pretty serious, isn't it?
Two...
I'm not picking.
One.
Look! I'm this kind of person that
when I asked you out,
I truly want to apologize to you.
For real!
It must be exhausting to redo the bidding document.
How did you find the time to ask me out?
How do you know that I'm redoing the bidding document?
If you're not redoing it, why did you burn it then?
I'm off.
Take my advice! Competing with low prices...
Is bad for the industry!
Ten points for you.
Get me another one!
Another one. Thanks!
I really underestimated your senselessness.
Director Luo.
If you need Zhou Rui's bidding price, I can get it for you.
I don't need it.
Zhou Rui had mercy on you and didn't go after you.
Compared to him, you're really lacking.
I also have... my own reasons.
Reasons?
It seems to me that over-promising
is still way worse than competing with low prices.
You made it your habit, haven't you?
Do something else! It's nearly impossible for you to keep making a living in sales.
Zhou Rui will never... will never make any offer that leaves no profit for his company.
As long as you have a price lower than his, he'll definitely give up.
I'll get Jieke's final offer before the bidding.
- You messed it up so quickly.
- Sister.
Have a seat!
It's worse than messing it up.
She didn't want to talk in the first place.
Luo Jia is the most unusual sales rep I've ever seen.
How unusual?
I'm worried that you'll lose badly.
Good question!
I'm talking about love.
Love?
None of us, sales people, are normal.
Sales people like her and I
only talk business, not love.
- Director Zhou.
- Could you do me a favor?
Go ahead! I can do a hundred favors for you.
Help me keep an eye on Luo Jia these days from a safe distance.
Go to see whom she's meeting with and photograph it. Can you do it?
Director Zhou, what do you mean?
- Is it difficult?
- It isn't difficult.
It's quite thrilling actually.
Send the pictures to me as soon as you take them.
Like a spy movie?
Only you and I know about this.
Understood.
Let me teach you something.
One of the most important skills of a salesperson is stalking.
Got it!
[Guohuo Bridge]
- Director Qian.
- Director Luo from Huikang, we meet again.
Yes. We meet again.
I wanted to meet with you because I want to confirm the efficiency of sorting the warehouse receipts.
Sure.
- Wait for me in the car.
- All right.
Are you on your way out soon?
I'll have a meeting later.
All right. I'll email the information to your cellphone first, please find time to read it.
I'll provide the detailed presentation after your meeting.
- Sure.
- Okay, I'll let you get back to your work.
- See you later, Director Luo.
- See you!
How childish!
Hello, Director Zhou.
President Chen.
Master.
Do you know this person?
Director Qian from the bidding evaluation committee.
What's his position there?
He has a technical background as well
and also the authority to speak.
Do you want to take him down?
Right now... It's too late to take anyone down.
However, let me give you the report! If Huikang's technical score exceeds 80 points for this,
I'm worried that it eventually have to be the lowest price.
Lead and do your best in times of crisis.
By the way, Wei Yan is back.
Haven't you two met?
I'll make an appointment after the conclusion of O&T's bidding.
Fang Wei!
No one found out that I went out, right?
Why is it never flowers every time?
Next time.
Come here. Come here. Come here.
I want this one.
What's going on?
When did our Administration Department start giving out benefits?
Administration Department?
The toilet rolls that your Administration Department issued last year,
I still haven't finished using.
I'm still starving.
What's there to wipe by giving us that many toilet rolls?
Is that so?
Then does this mean your Sales Department opened up the vaults?
Director Wei is back with gifts for everyone.
[Jieke Company]
This is for you.
Come in!
Director Zhou.
What's up?
Director Wei came back early.
I just came to tell you.
Why are you telling me this?
I thought you'd want to know.
You thought so?
Based on what?
I'm leaving then, Director Zhou.
- Director Wei.
- It's such a hot day, why are you drinking some kind of black tea?
Alright. I'll replace this with green tea.
It's still appropriate to retain you.
What I want are outstanding achievements.
Just like this Pixiu, it can only enter but not leave.
(TN: Pixiu - Chinese mythical beast used in geomancy)
I can transfer the O&T project to Zhou Rui.
Since you've moved him to Beiing,
I can unload my burdens to him at any time.
Let's talk about this again after O&T.
Director Wei, I heard you're back in Bejing to re-org the teams.
Then... Then, I...
You're from the Beijing region and still responsible for Beijing.
There won't be any changes for you, will there?
This isn't for you to worry about.
What's the progress on the O&T project?
Currently, it seems like Zhou Rui has revived this project.
However, the original plan has been subverted.
Go to the Sales Department and say hi to them.
Zhou Rui is here.
They're all facing problems with choosing sides.
Whether to follow the person or the project,
they're very clear about this.
- This—
- Besides, O&T isn't the only project you have.
- How's Fast's payment coming along?
- Fast?
Regarding this Fast project, I...
If you can't get it done, quickly get legal affairs to handle the contract immediately.
Don't wait until the chickens have flown the coop and come out empty-handed.
I want to wait for awhile longer
because these two companies are both in logistics.
One is a city and the other is a village.
Actually, the projects of these two companies can complement each other.
We're doing business transactions, not charity.
I understand.
I caught half of a movie on my flight back.
It had a phrase that the meaning seemed to be,
"Whoever feeds you, he's your boss".
Director Wei,
I got it.
9pm at the same old place.
Not going.
I lied! I'll be there.
Director Qian, did you read the content of the email?
Yes, I did.
I know that, in the eyes of technical specialists,
our sorting of warehouse receipts isn't an obvious advantage.
However, I still want to contend for your critical vote.
Frankly speaking, I just want—
I understand.
However, you should know how General Tian Ji won the horse race.
Can I take this based on my understanding then, Director Qian?
Huikiang doesn't need to compete with our competitors on the same track.
Is that correct?
Based on industry rules, I can't make any comments.
[Job completion failed.]
[Please check toner cartridge.]
[Error. Please check cartridge toner.]
- Hello, Fang Wei.
- Director Zhou.
That one...
I don't know what's wrong with the company's printer that it isn't printing.
Is the ink cartridge or toner cartridge used up?
I'll be right there.
Director Zhou.
Why didn't you go home?
Even if I go home, I can't sleep.
[Select the function you want to use.]
[Start]
It's done.
Keep watch over this for me! I'm going out for a while.
Okay.
Bidding starts tomorrow morning, but you're still drinking such strong drinks?
I'm used to it.
All right, I'll keep you company.
It's better if you back out.
It's better than losing.
You first burned the proposal and then had your five minute speech.
Your impression score and exposure are already sufficient.
You can't save Jieke.
Do you know that Iron Man can't save the world every time,
but he still won't give up.
You must've signed a non-compete agreement.
Take a half year sabbatical to enjoy life and travel the world.
When you come back, I'll let you have my office.
Did Boss Lin want you to convince me?
He doesn't know we're meeting.
I understand now.
You're trying to bribe me, get me to back out.
- It means you have a guilty conscience.
- Bribe you?
That sounds so horrible.
Wang Yi Nan wanted to tell me your lowest price but I refused.
Tomorrow, I'll honestly win O&T.
See you tomorrow.
- Where are you?
- I just got to the hotel.
We need to revise the bid.
The bidding starts tomorrow morning; do we have enough time?
We must because Luo Jia has met Wang Yi Nan.
- What did he say?
- I don't know.
Regardless, they've met. Wang Yinan has been with me for so long.
He knows my bidding strategy.
- What do you need me to do?
- Base on the existing quotes,
make two copies and then create two more quotes.
- Quote higher or lower?
- Lower.
Make it lower by half a million.
That's one hundred sixty five million.
Is that the profit sacrifice you were talking about?
We must guarantee fifteen percent profit and that's my bottom line.
Okay, I'll send you an e-mail when it's done.
[Prohibit Climbing]
Zhou Rui would never... would never make a deal that loses money.
As long as you go below the reserve price, he'll definitely give up.
Fang Wei, Fang Wei.
Wake up. Wash up.
- Bring something for breakfast.
- Okay.
I'm going to go through everything in my head one more time.
Oh right! You drive me today.
- Am I not following Luo Jia anymore?
- It's over.
- Alright.
- If we win today,
I'll know
there's still hope for you.
Really?
Actually, I'm even willing to work in the sales department.
[O&T Group]
[Oriental & Technology]
Hello everyone! I'm Luo Jia from Huikang Co.
Hello everyone! Hello President Du.
I'm Zhou Rui from Jieke.
[Bid Documents]
[II. List of Bid Opening]
[Bidder: Huikang Co.] - [Project: O&T Co. Server Purchase Bid]
[Purchase Items] - [Bidding Quotes]
[Bidder: Huikang Co.]
[O&T Co. Server Purchase Total] - [¥ 168,000,000]
[Bidder: Jieke Co.]
[Purchase Items] - [Bidding Quotes]
[O&T Co. Server Purchase Total] - [¥ 168,000,000]
Everyone, Jieke and Huikang's bottom lines
are the same.
Everyone, please give your thoughts.
Huikang company is a leading hardware manufacturer.
They have a high market share so their cost is well controlled.
As for Jieke, only their R&D costs are high
which is why they can set a low bid price like Huikang's.
It'll definitely reduce operation and maintenance in the future.
Therefore, personally, I prefer Huikang.
Both companies are different.
Huikang wants to manufacture faster.
So they depend on CPU processing power for speed.
But Jieke seeks stability.
Their advantage is in their design and software.
Huikang's advantage is that they can quickly meet the market demands.
So that everyone is able to see and buy it,
but they may not be able
to continue this trend in the future.
If both items have about the same technical specifications,
then the price is the deciding factor.
The safety of the product should be the deciding factor.
For person as bored as you, of course you'd come up with something equally boring.
I really do like to do super boring things.
- Like what?
- Like... Analyzing your lowest bid price.
Any results?
Director Luo,
if an always victorious general like you loses to a newcomer nobody like me,
then you'll probably be extremely ashamed, won't you?
Have you always been so confident?
Instruct Jieke and Huikang to submit second quotes.
The rest are out of the game.
I think you...
You probably know Jieke's quote, don't you?
Is this hard?
But Director Luo, I believe you won't have just one plan, will you?
Price Reduction.
Since we already know each other's bottom line,
then let's just be natural.
Sure.
President Du would like to invite you both to go to the small conference room.
❝ One Half ❞ by Mo Fei Ding Lu
♫  The sun is only shining halfway  ♫
♫  The freckles on my face are bright and dark  ♫
♫  Oh...  ♫
♫  Who sung the song halfway through  ♫
♫  Leaving behind the roars of the chorus in an empty room  ♫
♫  I...  ♫
♫  Slowly tidied up the embarrassment of the dispersing crowd  ♫
♫  Who would abruptly break off the lingering care of the past?  ♫
♫  You deserved it, someone said  ♫
♫  It's for the best that the story stays unfinished  ♫
♫  Those words were spoken halfway  ♫
♫  When those few words reached the tip of the tongue  ♫
♫  It would take several years to accept  ♫
♫  Whose heart is closed midway from now on  ♫
♫  Locking up all the past rainy nights of being restless  ♫
♫  Some words are only spoken halfway  ♫
♫  To adjust the emotional intensity afterwards  ♫
♫  Just air-dry it slowly with time  ♫
♫  Whose heart will miss a half from now on  ♫
♫  Just let it totally submerge  ♫
♫  My remaining dimness  ♫
♫  The other half  ♫