How is my condition in your opinion?
It's too late now.
Late?
What do you mean?
What do you mean late?
Are you saying she has no chance
even with surgery?
It's because…
Chairman Ju already came by.
She means she's already booked.
It doesn't mean you have no chance.
What a relief.
-And here, I thought… My goodness.
-This is great.
Chairman Ju? Then…
No, it wasn't me.
Someone that great
wouldn't have just inquired with me.
Please don't get me wrong.
Are you sure?
What a shame. Is the location that bad?
Is it in a different place?
It's near the left collarbone.
And the angiostenosis is too severe.
If we don't stop
the blockage of blood flow in time,
-it would cause serious brain damage.
-That's right.
What? Brain damage?
No.
Dr. Rachel, please help me.
I'm sorry. I have to go.
Doctor, no!
-Don't go. Please.
-Goddamn it!
Doctor!
-What are you doing?
-Geez!
-Don't touch her!
-Let go!
-Let her go!
-Move!
-Doctor!
-Let her go!
Please don't go, Doctor!
-Please, I'm begging you.
-Damn, that hurts.
Doctor, please.
Hey, has Chairman Ju
transferred the money yet?
Chairman Ju.
He promised to deposit
$2 million by 3:00 p.m.
Two million dollars is 2.8 billion won.
For just one surgery?
By 3:00 p.m.?
Chairman Ju's life is worth $2 million?
Then, how much is my life worth?
Shall we get going?
-Sure.
-Okay.
Seon-mi.
I'll pay you $2.5 million!
Great thinking.
Your life comes first. Money isn't--
Please do my surgery!
Please.
I'll wire you the money.
Once the money's deposited,
we're taking off!
By the way, where are we going?
The Philippines!
What? No, not the Philippines!
I hate the Philippines!
No, I have trauma from it!
No, not the Philippines!
Then, how about Boracay?
Boracay sounds good!
Boracay? Boracay!
I like Boracay.
We don't need to tell him that Boracay
is part of the Philippines, do we?
Of course not.
DEPOSIT RECEIVED FROM LEE SEON-MI
It's here!
Nice!
Am I reading this right?
How many zeros are there? One, two, three…
-Just 100 million?
-This is 334 million won.
It's missing one zero.
EPISODE 6
We're a little short on capital
to immediately have cash on hand.
We sent 10% first as a deposit.
I'll pay you the rest after surgery--
That's not what you said yesterday.
It's due to construction on our branch.
Our money is tied to that.
I…
will not do the surgery.
No, wait…
Return the deposit.
What?
What? But…
What if I'd said that?
Goodness.
In return, if the surgery goes well,
we'll pay you 10% extra.
Was three billion won too much?
Damn, I thought we almost had it.
I saw this coming.
What do you mean?
We might as well do the surgery.
How can we perform surgery
on someone who's not even ill?
It's easier because she's not ill.
All we have to do is not kill her.
-Are you crazy?
Mom, are you crazy?
How can you make such a deal
in this situation?
We don't even know
if the surgery will be successful or not.
How can we send
that much money all at once?
Gosh, I can't believe you.
We'll get a call.
No.
This is wrong, Mom!
We can't just keep waiting like this.
I'll call Professor Yu now.
COORDINATOR MA
Let's ask…
-Hello?
-Hi, this is Coordinator Ma.
Rachel has decided to do the surgery.
Okay, thank you.
See that?
See that? I told you.
You're really unbelievable.
This is my team from Boston.
This is Daniel,
who I've been working with for ten years.
Sandy.
Edmund.
Patrick.
And this is our nurse, Abigail.
They're the best specialists.
You can count on them.
Okay.
Now that I'm seeing them in person,
I feel relieved.
I'll leave it all in your hands, Doctor.
All right. Shall we go?
It'll go well, right?
Of course. Don't worry.
Actually, Rachel is very sensitive.
I see.
The contract doesn't allow
for observing in person,
so we should go now.
Right. Let's go.
RESTRICTED AREA
You should go on ahead.
-Okay, I will.
-Thanks.
Has the surgery…
Are you out of money?
Do you regret it now
after giving it some thought?
You're already too late, you punk.
When I went to ask you in person,
that was the last chance of your life.
Did you think I wouldn't be able
to do anything without you?
You sure about that?
What if I wasn't?
As if you could do anything
with this damn hand.
Hey, get out of my sight.
You disgust me.
JAEKYEONG HOSPITAL
The surgery has now begun.
I hope she gets through it.
Don't worry.
She's a strong woman,
so she'll get through it fine.
Okay, then!
-Now, what do we do?
-What else?
I don't know what that means, but sure.
Okay.
Wait, what's wrong with the screen?
-Call the control room.
-Yes, sir.
Hurry!
-Yes, Dr. Jo.
-Wait.
Let me try.
I worked in maintenance in the past.
-You should've checked this in advance!
-I'm sorry, sir.
THE VIDEO CANNOT BE PLAYED
There it is.
My apologies.
What on earth?
They haven't even made a cut yet?
Hurry up and do something.
He noticed you haven't cut her yet.
Wait.
How does he know we didn't even cut…
Damn it. Hey, gather around.
Huddle up. Hey! Quickly!
Are we being filmed right now?
I think we're being filmed.
What do we do?
Damn it!
What do we do? We have to do something.
-What do we do?
-Wait, please be quiet!
Calm down for a second.
What's with you?
First, make the incision with the scalpel.
Next, open the incision
and check her aorta.
Cut it and stitch the ends back together.
Isn't that easy?
What are you… What on earth are you doing?
We might as well do the surgery.
All we have to do is not kill her.
I'll keep her alive.
You're not serious, are you?
I have the start and end
of this surgery all pictured in my head.
Okay, Yi-rang.
I know you're great.
I've always known you were smart.
I acknowledge that you're amazing.
But this is a whole different issue.
A person's life is on the line!
Do you get it?
Well, that's true.
-So…
-Yeah?
We should still open her up.
Only that will prove we performed surgery.
You think that makes sense?
All right. Are you guys ready?
What do you mean "Yeah"?
-Scalpel.
-What?
Don't do this, Yi-rang. Seriously.
You really don't have
any faith in me, do you?
Come on, Yi-rang.
Let's begin.
She actually did it!
Blood! She's bleeding!
They're beginning now.
Mom, please.
Damn it.
Prepare the artificial blood vessel.
She's as amazing as everyone says.
How is she so good at that?
Why is she so good at this?
All right, my hands are getting
a feel for this.
We've controlled the bleeding
and we'll close her up.
My gosh!
Poor Chairman Lee!
Damn it.
Suction. Closer.
Inject epinephrine every three minutes.
Up the charge to 30 joules.
Please.
I'll go get someone!
Mom!
My poor mom! Mom!
Hey, what's going on? What is it?
-Tell me. What's the matter?
-I…
Mom…
My gosh. What do we do?
-Somebody come in!
-Mom!
Mom! No!
"Fuck" isn't the answer.
The doctor's here!
Doctor.
Doctor, do something!
It's chaos in here.
Come on.
Everyone, everything's okay now.
Doctors, the doctor is here! Okay?
Now, we just need to wait calmly.
Yes.
And we have one more doctor!
This is even better! We're okay now.
I can't do it.
What?
Gwang-sik.
Please save my mom.
Look, I didn't mean what I said earlier.
I was upset at you,
so I just said it out of anger.
I'm really sorry.
I shouldn't have done that to you.
I hid behind my mom and ruined everything.
So, just vent all your anger on me.
But please save my mom.
Gwang-sik!
We're doctors.
If something happens to my mom…
If we can't save her while we can…
I won't be able to carry on. Gwang-sik.
Didn't I tell you the same thing before?
Seong-woo, we're doctors.
If something happens to her,
you think we'll be able
to continue with our careers?
Stop whining, you idiot.
Stop whining.
Mom!
Hey, you.
Unless you're going to grab a scalpel,
get lost.
But…
NO SIGNAL
Hey, he's a doctor!
Why would you let a doctor go?
Why let him go, you fool?
What are we going to do now?
Someone's dying!
-We're all doomed…
-All done!
-Let's pack it in!
-Pack it in!
What do you mean "pack it in"? Why?
She's still open!
Good job, everyone!
Well done!
-Thank you.
-Good job.
-"Good job"?
-Go, go.
-Thank you!
Let's go!
James, what is going…
No, James! Don't!
-No! Don't!
-Attention, please.
What is that?
Doesn't it look so realistic?
It's made of silicon and fiberglass.
It looks so real.
Look at this. You have to see it.
The heart is even pounding inside.
This is the heart.
You made all of that?
Even though I knew it was fake,
I was so surprised.
Everything here is a prop
from a film set.
What would we do
without Mr. Mustache?
I know.
You know the medical drama I always watch?
We took everything from there.
Why was I left in the dark again?
Wait.
Why do you have to take things so far?
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth.
She has to pay
for what she did to Jae-hee.
Then, was Dr. Im Gwang-sik…
Well…
He seemed to be wavering, so I went
to make sure he didn't change his mind.
Because what if he suddenly appears
and grabs a scalpel? So…
Oh no. We ran out of alcohol.
Why do I have to listen to you?
We can't let other children
end up like Jae-hee.
What am I supposed to do then?
Jo Seong-woo will soon visit you.
When he does…
Squeeze some ketchup on your finger
and wrap this around it.
Simple, right?
All right.
But on one condition.
He said, "On one condition."
Then, he suddenly asked me
if he could enter the operating room.
He said he wanted to
get payback on Jo Seong-woo
for all he had done to him.
That means
Dr. Im Gwang-sik also knew
this surgery was fake.
Obviously.
Now, Jo Seong-woo knows
how Jae-hee's mom felt.
Exactly.
But why was I the only one
who didn't know?
Why only me?
What?
Because you doubted me last time.
When did I…
Doctor, my foot.
Anyone can disinfect wounds.
She probably just read about it
from a few books.
Hey, that's…
Wait, that's…
Because of that one single comment?
You're such a pure soul,
which is why it's so fun to mess with you.
Let's go.
Bye.
You brats. Wait for me.
Where do you think you're going?
-Clean everything up before you go.
-What?
No.
I can't do this.
Guys?
What the heck?
Hey, Yi-rang!
Hey!
COORDINATOR MA
Why did he send me…
WE'VE CONFIRMED THE DEPOSIT
But how is that…
The number you have dialed does not exist.
No way…
Mom!
What? What's the matter?
-Seong-woo.
-Yes?
Did you send the money?
No, right?
Did you send the money or not? No, right?
-I did…
-You did?
You idiot!
Oh no, you idiot! Look at this!
It was all a scam!
Those bastards
didn't operate and faked it!
What am I going to do?
Hey, call the police.
Call the police right now.
What's that?
This picture… Mom, what…
So you're okay?
You crazy bastard.
Call the police now. Coordinator Ma…
Call the police.
Coordinator Ma…
Come on! Call the police!
What am I going to do?
Coordinator Ma!
Coordinator Ma, please!
I said call the police, you idiot!
The number you have dialed does not exist.
Please check and dial again.
Those bastards scammed us!
No! What am I going to do?
My money!
-Mom, then are you…
-I know!
Hey, go check
the security cameras right now.
Does that mean you're not sick?
Mom, you're okay!
You crazy bastard.
You damn moron.
That's what matters to you?
Do you know how much it was?
You crazy bastard!
Do you know how much money it was?
I have to check the security cameras
before they run away!
Mom!
How long have you been performing
ghost surgeries for?
How many other ghost surgeries
have you done?
I've been performing ghost surgeries
for Director Jo Seong-woo.
However, regardless of the surgery,
my goal was to save people.
That's what mattered to me the most.
I apologize.
According to one insider
during today's press conference…
So that's how it came to an end.
Look at how many cameras there are.
He was always hidden behind Jo Seong-woo,
and now, he's finally in the spotlight.
It was a wrong
he just had to right as a doctor.
Let's go.
There used to be a convenience store
over there, but now it's a cafe.
How do you know this place so well?
I was hospitalized here for a long time
when I was a kid.
Right. Did you prepare what I asked?
Jae-hee!
How have you been?
Here, this is for you.
-Ta-da!
What is all this?
Jae-hee, remember what I promised you?
Isn't this a bit too much?
Actually, this isn't from me.
It's from Yi-rang.
Say thank you.
I've been awake for a while.
What took you so long to visit?
While you were asleep,
we had a lot to deal with.
-Jae-hee, do you want to try it?
-Shall we?
-Wow!
-Keep going to the right.
-Wait, no…
-To the left.
-Let's try it again.
-That was so close.
Okay! You got it.
Now, press it.
-You did it!
-Yeah!
Let's take it out.
Want to give it another go?
Do you want to play again?
MARCH 28, 2000
Yi-rang, it's time.
You have to go to the birthday party.
James, what comes to your mind
when you look at this painting?
Are you calling me that again?
I'm not James. I'm Seo In-jae.
If you say Seo In-jae backwards,
it's Jae-in Seo.
It sounds like James.
Oh, is that so?
Then, I'll say Yun Yi-rang backwards
and call you Rang-yi Yun.
Rang-yi Yun?
It sounds nice.
"Waves on the Edge."
Is it a waterfall
flowing from top to bottom?
Just thinking about it
feels refreshing.
No, this is an explosion.
An explosion? But it's blue.
It looks like a water stream,
but it's not flowing down.
It's splashing upward
due to strong pressure.
After hearing that,
I think you have a point.
Whether it's good or evil,
or light or dark,
it may ambiguous on the outside.
But if you look closely,
everything is clear.
Isn't that interesting?
No, it's not interesting.
You might find it interesting
because you're a prodigy,
but I hate anything
ambiguous and philosophical.
No, this is science.
-Do you want to see it?
-No, I'm good.
I said I'm good. Yi-rang?
Where are you going in those nice shoes?
Yi-rang!
Yi-rang.
You'll be late for your birthday party.
We have to hurry.
Yi-rang.
Yi-rang!
Yi-rang…
We're going to be late for the party.
We have to go now.
Put this in and it's done!
-What's that?
-A volcanic explosion experiment.
Mix liquid soap and hydrogen peroxide.
Lastly, if you drop in potassium iodide,
it'll start to bubble and boom!
Boom? That's too dangerous.
-We have to go. Come on.
-No, wait! Wait…
Watch out!
It won't actually blow up.
Geez, stop fooling around.
You little…
That was a first!
This is amazing!
What's so amazing?
-That was dangerous.
-Miss Yi-rang.
Shall we go now?
Thank you.
Hey, Yi-rang!
Yi-rang!
-Yi-rang.
Yi-rang, look at Mommy.
The center square is all clear.
Seo In-jae.
Yes, sir.
I'm going to drop off the VIPs
after the party.
You're in charge in the meantime.
Yes, sir.
Yi-rang!
Ladies and gentlemen.
First, we'd like to thank you on behalf
of Yi-rang and Yi-rang's parents,
for taking the time to come here
and celebrate Yi-rang's tenth birthday.
One seat is vacant. I'll check.
-Now, let's welcome the birthday girl.
-Something wrong?
Let's welcome Princess Yi-rang,
by singing Happy Birthday…
-Where did the kid next to you go?
-There was nobody here.
Princess Yi-rang!
Where's the kid next to you?
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Yi-rang
Just a second.
Wait, that's not Yi-rang!
-Really?
-She's not Yi-rang?
Where's Yi-rang?
Yi-rang wanted to switch dresses…
Where?
In the restroom.
What happened?
Yi-rang is gone.
-Yi-rang!
Yi-rang!
You three, check over there.
You three, that way.
-Yi-rang!
Yi-rang!
Yi-rang, where are you?
She's gone. I'm sorry.
Honey!
-Honey, are you okay?
-Yi-rang!
Yi-rang!
Bring three billion in cash
and wait at Tongjin Development
near Exit 1 of Yuhyeon Station.
Then, I'll tell you where to meet.
TONGJIN DEVELOPMENT
I think we've been fooled again.
I know. How many times has it been?
It's been four times already.
Do you think he's noticed
we're tailing him?
Then, things will get complicated.
INVESTIGATION HEADQUARTERS
AT RINE CHAIRMAN'S HOUSE
Not at home either.
How did it go?
The number was routed to prevent tracking,
and he's going around in circles,
wasting our time on purpose.
He didn't want to make this
an easy deal from the start.
Something's off.
If he was just testing to see
whether we'd tail him,
he should've made another deal right away.
But why hasn't he still?
You think it's motivated by a grudge?
I'm not sure.
Anyway, we'll have to wait
for him to call again.
What about the security cameras
around the theme park?
We checked everything.
But for some reason,
we couldn't find anything.
-Who's that?
-He used to be our chief's senior officer.
No wonder why he seems so fierce.
36 HOURS SINCE THE INCIDENT
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Yi-rang
She disappeared without a trace.
What did I miss?
She wasn't waving at me.
Then, who was she waving at?
The theme of the party
was Alice in Wonderland.
There was nothing strange about it.
Don't get caught
until you blow out the candles.
Okay.
Blow out the birthday candles,
and when you take off the mask,
say "Surprise."
That sounds really fun!
What are you going to do in the meantime?
There's something I have to do
without anyone knowing.
What did she have to do
without anyone knowing?
Yes, sir.
I followed Yi-rang's friend,
who switched dresses with Yi-rang.
Yi-rang!
And Yi-rang…
The rabbits were playing
a game with Yi-rang.
A circle and a square.
The hot-air balloon.
There should be shapes
like circles, triangles, and squares.
But there's nothing.
Hurry up and look.
I'm dead if Chief finds out.
People don't die that easily.
You haven't starved to death either
thanks to me.
Fine, you're right.
I stayed at your gosiwon
and sponged off you, okay?
Do you really have to use that against me?
It's so unfair.
I fed you, sheltered you,
and turned you into a detective, you brat.
Geez.
Hello? Yes, sir.
Oh, I just stepped out to buy something.
It was in the picture, but not anymore.
A triangle and a half circle.
The pirate ship?
A square and a circle.
A circle and a cylinder.
The drop tower ride.
There it is.
A circle and a triangle?
A circle and a triangle.
I think there were more here.
An inverted triangle.
I found it.
Yi-rang was made
to get in the truck on her own.
Who on earth would do this?
I need a trophy to celebrate
my perfect victory.
This is boring. I want to go home now.
Is it because you keep losing?
People say you have an IQ of 167,
and you take after your dad,
so you hate to lose.
Thus, Rine Group will soon become
the biggest conglomerate in the world.
Is that why you kidnapped me?
No.
Then why?
Why do you want to know?
All you have to do is have fun.
Then…
everything will be over.
2 DAYS SINCE THE INCIDENT
How long have you been here for?
Hasn't it been suffocating here?
Do you think Mom is doing okay?
Seriously, can you believe
they still haven't found me yet?
What if I can never go back home?
I'm scared.
There must be a way to get out of here.
Do you remember this T-shirt?
Yes, of course.
Did you produce it?
No, I thought Rine
requested it to be made.
Thank you for calling IamJamJam.
I even got a call that he wanted
the rabbits to wear those T-shirts.
Were there any other requests?
I was asked to put weird shapes
here and there on the rides.
I think he said it was a surprise event.
He said kids would love it.
He asked me earnestly
to keep it a secret.
Kids would love it?
Judging from the situation,
the culprit's an acquaintance.
Could I see the security camera footage
from the hallway?
The security camera in the hallway
has been out of order for a long time.
There's one outside the building.
The manager said
the cops took the security camera footage
near the hot-air balloon.
But it's not in the investigation data.
What? There's no security camera footage?
Nope.
And no security cameras outside captured
the ice cream truck you mentioned.
For someone to completely erase
the traces like this,
could it be…
Yi-rang left on her own?
The culprit was playing
a game with Yi-rang.
He used a trick to leave without a trace.
Anything else you've found?
The security camera footage is gone.
The security camera footage is gone?
I think the culprit had an inside man
within the police.
I'll report it to the chairman.
Don't tell anyone about it for now.
-But--
-You know what I mean, right?
Yes, sir.
3 DAYS SINCE THE INCIDENT
Go.
Hide tight
I can see your hair
I mean, is this really necessary?
Hide tight, I can see your hair
Found you.
I think we need to switch it
to an open investigation.
Are you the one who showed him
the security camera footage?
What? No.
Chief, why would you say that?
I heard you've been meeting
with the bodyguard often.
What do you mean "meeting"?
We're friends,
so we've only said hi a few times.
Is that so?
Chief, you need to see this.
Breaking news.
The only daughter of Yun Tae-ho,
business tycoon and CEO of Rine Group,
has been kidnapped.
Investigating authorities revealed today
they will switch
to a public investigation
after having conducted it confidentially.
Goddamn it.
Switching to an public investigation
without any word?
Are they serious right now?
The decision by police
and investigating authorities…
Hey, turn that off!
MOM-AND-POP
CONVENIENCE STORE
This is the last road connected
to the outer roads around the theme park.
Then, there should've been
traces left behind.
Good day, ma'am.
I'm from the police.
Could I check your CCTV?
When are you going to stop bothering me?
So they've been here already.
I wonder who it was.
By any chance, does the one
who took the security footage look--
A ton of people have come by here.
How am I supposed to remember all that?
Right?
Of course.
How much is this?
Going straight out from Any World…
How can I be eating bread right now?
Yi-rang must be suffering
so much right now.
GYEAN-DONG
WILD BIRDS IN THIS AREA
That could have caught something.
-Hello.
I'm from the police.
Could I see what was caught on camera?
It's migratory bird season,
so it's been here for days.
It could've caught something.
Can you go back?
Wait, stop.
One second.
It's already been five days
since Chairman Yun Tae-ho's only daughter
was kidnapped.
However, the victim's whereabouts
are still unknown.
It's me.
We're getting rid of the girl tonight.
Really?
Okay. See you soon.
Who was that call from?
It's my wife.
My child must've gotten
into trouble again.
Did you get all the data?
The security camera footage and all?
Yes, I'm sure my guys got them.
I'll see you later then.
Right. Bye.
Don't be a hassle. Just eat it, okay?
How long do I have to do this for?
I'm so sick of it.
Hey, mister.
I'm really bored too. Let's play cards.
I have something to report.
I won this time, right?
It's flush for me.
Damn it.
Let's play one more time.
Hey, you think you can win?
She really is a genius.
Let's play one more time.
Sure. But if I win again,
we'll play the game I want.
I got it this time.
It's full house.
Damn it!
Let's play the game I want now.
Hide-and-seek.
Count to 30 slowly.
I'm going to hide.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight,
nine, ten, eleven, twelve,
thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen,
seventeen, eighteen…
Here I come.
Hide tight, I can see your hair
POTASSIUM IODIDE
Found you.
Where's the kid?
Inside.
We're wrapping things up here tonight.
Five, four,
three, two, one.
Hurry and check the kid's room!
Yi-rang.
Damn it.
Hang in there. I'll save you soon.
Just a bit more. I can go home now.
James!
Yi-rang, run!
Yi-rang!
MYUNG GU-HO
BORN IN 1997, AGE 5 AT THE TIME
DOUBLE ABDUCTION?
MYUNG JIN-SU
BORN IN 1965, INFORMANT
LEE SEONG-MIN
Hide tight
I can see your hair
Thanks to everyone
who supported Mystique…
This is unfair!
Gil Beauty is the queen of power trips
and the queen of lawsuits.
Your appearance is also your talent.
It's 32.57?
What a pig.
Okay, the operation will begin.
This was stuck deep inside.
Mom!
Son.
We'll lure in Gil Beauty in a way
that is mysterious, secretive,
and thus more attractive.