=Lost You Forever S1=
=Episode 35=
Are you never going to see anyone?
- You're someone.
Xinyue, they have things to discuss.
Let's hang out somewhere else.
- Alright.
- Let's go.
Chief Lirong, this way.
(Lirong Chang)
I am Chief
Lirong Chang.
May Your Highness be well.
I've heard so much about you.
I finally have a chance to meet you
thanks to Jing.
Your Highness, our Lirong Family
has always been
suppressed by other clans.
We are running
the lowly business to make ends meet.
It's a disgrace to our ancestors.
Your Highness, please guide us
back to our glory.
I truly admire you for planning
for your clan.
I will do my best
to make your wish come true.
Thank you.
We are willing to offer you
our fiercest warriors
and 500,000 jade and silk every year
to assist Your Highness.
Please get up.
I will never
forget
your help.
We're brothers from now on.
I haven't seen my father
since I came back.
He's been waiting.
I've told Xuan that
I'm going back
to see my father in Haoling.
I can't go with you.
A letter came from Qingqiu.
Grandmother is not so well.
I haven't figured out
what to do about your grandmother.
But there are many medical books
and remedies in the palace
of Haoling.
I'll check
if anything can be helpful.
Xiaoyao.
Thank you.
I may not be able to help.
It's too early for that.
It's the intention that matters.
(Tushan Mansion)
What did you say?
Tushan Jing likes
the Great Princess of Haoling.
No way.
Why would the Great Princess like him?
He hooked up with the Great Princess.
No wonder he won't marry you.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
I'm just saying.
Father.
I'm back.
It's so good to see you.
You've lost some weight.
You are back.
Not missing any limbs, huh?
Your 10,000-year Water Chalcedony
would have healed me
anyway.
That's just the leftover food
of my spirit beasts.
I see.
Anyway, you're breeding them.
So, thank you.
You!
A princess
almost got killed by the bullies.
So useless.
If it's up to me, you should
stay on Wushen Mountain.
Father will make sure
that nobody bullies you.
Nian is right.
Stay at Wushen Mountain for a while.
Alright.
I'll do as you say.
Your Highness.
Found any clues?
I found a Chi Chen Village in Baili
where Chi Chen supposedly
lived with his wife.
Chi Chen had a wife?
Yes.
The locals are highly alert.
They stopped talking
almost instantly.
I sneaked inside and saw
the portrait of Chi Chen.
He had lived there for sure.
But there was no portrait of his wife.
I only know that
she went by Xiling Witch.
Xiling Witch?
Alright.
You may leave.
I take my leave.
(Xiling Witch?)
(Did Auntie and Chi Chen truly...)
Sang, go to Xiyan Town in secret.
Go to Xiyan Town in secret?
I have a letter for General Yinglong.
No one shall read it,
not even you.
Rest assured.
I'll kill whoever reads it,
including me.
You.
- Your Lordship.
- Give it to Supervisor Liu.
Okay.
(Daming Hall)
Cang Xuan.
What's up?
Xinyue.
Are you alright?
Yes.
I'm just so happy
for you.
You have developed strength.
Once the Daming Hall is built,
you'll have fame.
Cang Xuan.
You're finally making it
after so many years.
All thanks to you and Fenglong.
I proceed and retreat
alongside you.
I'll keep you company
no matter what you do
until you get everything you want.
Miss.
It's too tiring to copy
all these in person.
Why don't you get some help?
These are the records of how
the former kings
ruled the Central Plains.
How can I let others copy them?
Cang Xuan has great ambition.
Of course, I have to help.
Once I offer him this as a gift,
it will be much easier
for him to gain control
and rule over
the Central Plains.
Your gift for His Highness
not only showed
your love and loyalty,
but also your consideration.
I bet His Highness
will be so happy to get it.
A gift has to be pleasing
to the recipient.
Cang Xuan
deserves such an effort.
And
there are things
no one can offer him except me.
What is it, Miss Fangfeng?
Jing.
Are you really
canceling the engagement?
Miss Fangfeng.
I have
made myself clear.
Please contain yourself.
I've served the Tushan Family for years,
but you never appreciated it.
Since you're so determined,
I won't displease you.
I'll quit
for you two.
Thank you.
Miss Fangfeng.
I'll pay you back.
Grandmother.
Miss Fangfeng agreed
to cancel the engagement.
She agreed?
No way.
She knew that
I'm in love with someone else.
So she decided
to find her true love.
Grand Madam, bad news.
Miss Fangfeng committed suicide.
Thankfully, I found her in time.
Otherwise...
How's Yiying?
The physicians came and said
that she would be fine.
But the poison damaged her
and she needs to rest and recover.
You've either
been gone or in a coma
for the past decades.
Yiying stayed by my side on your behalf.
She fed me medicine and did house chores
industriously without complaining.
What has she done to you?
Why do you want her dead?
Grandmother, I...
Grandmother.
Miss!
Don't blame it on Jing.
It's all my fault.
I don't deserve him.
I'm the one to blame.
Sweetheart.
The Tushan Family
didn't treat you right.
I failed to educate my grandson.
Grandmother.
The physicians say
you can't get emotional.
Please don't cry.
It's all my fault.
Since you realized your problem,
stay and take care of Yiying.
Help her recover.
What's wrong?
Do you want me
to redeem your sin for you
and take care of Yiying?
Grandmother, go back.
I will stay here.
Rest well.
Get Jing to serve you.
Don't go easy on him.
Miss.
Xuanzhou.
Stay here and take care of her.
Miss Fangfeng.
I'll be outside.
Call me if you need me.
Grandmother, why didn't you go to bed?
You barely recovered.
And Yiying is sick.
How can I fall asleep?
I might as well work on something.
So I made some soup.
Have some.
Leave the rest for Yiying.
Father.
Why are you staying up so late?
I want to ask you the same question.
You've been locking yourself
in your room to read medicinal books
these days.
Nian came to make a complaint.
Jing's grandmother is ill.
I'm looking for
a way to treat her.
But you can't focus
solely on someone else's senior.
My apologies.
(Daming Hall, Zijin Palace)
Look.
Prince Cang Xuan is quite impressive.
It's dull and complicated
to build the hall.
Not everyone
can remain so devoted
for 40 years.
Strange.
It's such an important event.
Where is Jing?
The propitious time has arrived.
Let the ceremony begin.
Blessed by
the almighty heaven,
the Daming Hall is completed.
I, Xiyan Cang Xuan,
lead the clans of the Central Plains
to pray for peace and safety.
What happened?
What should we do?
How did it collapse?
Father.
It seems that
Cang Xuan hasn't improved much.
You made him build a hall
but he made it collapse.
No wonder those clans
are impeaching him.
Father.
Although this incident may not be
Cang Xuan's fault.
But we should
look into it to appease
those clans.
Otherwise,
they won't recognize our authority.
What do you suggest?
Since the clans suspect
Cang Xuan of embezzlement,
I suggest
we send a commissar to look into it
and reveal the truth.
We may
clear Cang Xuan's name if he's wronged.
Proceed.
Father, you're truly wise.
The Fan and Zheng families kept
spreading rumors,
which convinced the clans
that Cang Xuan embezzled money.
Chenrong Yi wanted to reconcile them,
but seeing everyone enraged,
he agreed to report
to the King of Xiyan.
Chenrong Yi always prioritizes
the peace and harmony
of the Central Plains.
Cang Xuan became the target.
He wouldn't displease the clans
to protect Cang Xuan.
The King of Xiyan has accepted
Deyan's advice
and sent a commissar
to look into this incident.
The King of Xiyan wants to show
that he won't favor Cang Xuan.
So this time,
Cang Xuan has to count on himself.
If Cang Xuan
fails to steer through this,
his well-established power
in Central Plains
will be ruined.
If Cang Xuan gets
kicked out of the Central Plains,
he has to return to Xiyan Town.
But his two uncles
won't give him another chance.
The path to the throne
is paved by blood and bodies.
Cang Xuan chose this path.
So he must have been
well-prepared.
Master,
are you really letting him be?
I've taught him
everything I could teach him.
Princess.
Jintian Valley's forging master is here.
You're the one
who wants the bow and arrows?
You have little spirit power
and expect to kill people?
Chief was right.
It's truly challenging.
When I first saw you,
I also doubted
that you were
the forging master my father invited.
I'm Jintian Xingchen,
the most talented forging master
in the Jintian Family.
If the clan chief hadn't told me
how challenging it was,
I wouldn't do it even for
His Majesty.
I'm counting on you.
How come
your hands are even rougher
than mine?
I practice archery to kill people.
How do I succeed without hard work?
I thought
you wanted a weapon for fun.
It looks like I was wrong.
Do you have any requirements
on the shape, color,
or auxiliary functions?
There's only one.
It should be deadly.
You're quite an expert.
Weapons are meant
for killing people.
Those who ask for fancy stuff
are amateurs.
I do have a weapon for you.
What is it?
You're so lucky.
It's unbelievable.
You don't know
what rare materials I used for it.
There are merfolk's bones,
siren's organs, tortoise blood,
undersea bamboo, star sand,
and epic moonstone.
Those are all rare treasures.
Even His Majesty
can't easily gather those.
I wonder how that person
gathered all those materials.
It's such a legendary weapon.
Why is it unwanted?
Are you here for the weapon?
Just a second.
Here you go.
How about it?
Do you like it?
This is my best piece of work.
I don't want it anymore.
What?
You don't want it?
I can't use it anyway.
It serves no purpose.
You already wasted my materials.
You can't force me to buy it.
No matter why he didn't want it,
it wasn't because I did a bad job.
Look.
This is the bow.
What a nice bow.
Of course.
This is the best
piece of work in my life.
But...
But what?
The bow
needs to be tamed.
It has a special requirement.
How special?
It needs the blood
of the nine-headed demon.
The only known nine-headed demon
throughout Dahuang
is that guy called
Xiang Liu with Nine Lives.
I heard he's really eccentric
and difficult.
No wonder nobody wants this bow.
Well, the rare materials won't work
without the blood
of that demon.
But you're the Princess of Haoling.
Your father is the king.
You'll find a way.
This is truly a legendary bow.
I promise
you won't regret getting it.
This bow
is mine.
Your Highness.
I found the cause of the collapse.
The bucket arch broke.
They are crisscrossed and layered
upon each other
to share the burden of the beam
on the columns
and support the eaves.
If the bucket arch breaks,
the roof collapses first
and pulls the walls and columns.
That's similar to what happened.
But our bucket arch
was made from Kunwood,
which was solid.
How did it break?
I found white ants
under the broken bucket arch.
I thought they were common ants.
But the experts said that
those ants were bred
by chalcedony from Mount Jade
and could eat Kunwood.
Someone must have
placed them there
to eat the wood.
I have found the suspect
and ordered an arrest.
Your Highness.
Your Lordship. I went to arrest
the carpenter Peng Shan.
But he had committed suicide at home.
We lost our key witness.
I wasn't fast enough.
Your Highness.
The commissar has arrived at Zhiyi.
Who is it?
Yueliang.
It's him.
I came to the Central Plains
because a palace collapsed.
I didn't expect that
I'd be kicked out for the same reason.
The plan was to give these
copies of the historical records
to Prince Cang Xuan as a gift,
but the Daming Hall suddenly collapsed.
You didn't even have the chance
to give him these files you copied
and the letter you wrote.
(To Cang Xuan)
Miss.
Should I send them
to Prince Cang Xuan?
Miss.
Remember.
There were no gifts.
Yes.
Pack the medicinal material
and the spirit herb.
Take them to Chenrong Mountain
with us.
Why didn't you pack any jewelry,
but took all the rare medicinal material
from the palace?
You don't get it.
I need them to make medicine.
Since I need a favor,
I must offer some gifts.
Xuan is in deep trouble.
What's wrong?
The Daming Hall collapsed.
The King of Xiyan sent Xuan's archenemy
Yueliang to look into this.
Yueliang
will take a deadly strike now.
Shan Hu, Miao Pu.
Pack up.
We're going back.
Yes.
I'm coming with you.
May I?
I heard my father is choosing
a husband for you.
Don't you like any
of those young men?
They...
They're no match for Xuan.
Come.
Sit down.
I see you as my sister.
So I don't want you
to fall for Cang Xuan.
To be honest with you,
back in Xiyan Town,
although he was faking it,
it was a fact that he was popular
among women.
Moreover, he has
Chenrong Xinyue with him now.
I know.
Cang Xuan
never cares about romance.
If another woman falls in love with him
and can offer him
some assistance,
he won't mind it.
I'm afraid
he'll accept her.
If marrying a woman
can help him avoid conflicts
and save dozens or hundreds
of guards,
or even prevent a war,
what do you think he would do?
In fact, I don't like it, either.
But I wandered the world
for hundreds of years.
I was once an ordinary person.
I know
how precious it is to live in peace
and how fragile a common person is.
So
I fully support him.
Nian,
let Father find you
a good husband in Haoling.
Stop thinking about Cang Xuan.
I've been trying to forget him
for 40 years,
but I can't.
I've been thinking about it so much.
And I've made up my mind.
Even if he marries other women,
as long as he's sweet to me,
I won't mind it.
Can't you just toughen up?
You're a princess.
You don't need any man.
How come you can't live
without him?
You just...
You just feel heartbroken and that's it.
But
I'm not as good as you.
I can't live on
with a broken heart.
All I know
is that without Xuan,
there is no fun
in whatever I do.
I'd rather die.
Are you saying that you can't forget him
with all the years you have as a deity?
Sister.
Apart from Father and Mother,
only you can help me.
Sister.
Help me, please.
Your Highness.
General Yinglong told me
to bring it to you.
Your Highness, what did he say?
Your Highness.
Are you fine?
For Xiaoyao,
I must stay in the Central Plains.
I have to.
Jing.
Wake up.
Jing, are you fine now?
Where's Xiaoyao?
She went to visit her father
and hasn't returned.
Jing.
What exactly happened?
We've been looking for you.
But you were
hiding in Lirong Chang's casino
and getting drunk.
Why are you looking for me?
Go get changed.
Sorry.
I took extreme measures
to wake you up.
Brother,
I didn't expect that
we would
meet again under such a circumstance.
Please bear with me.
Your Highness,
we found the account books.
Nothing left?
Rest assured.
I searched everywhere in person.
There is nothing left.
Brother.
Don't blame me if I'm being careful.
First, this is an edict
issued by the king,
and I must be impartial.
Second,
I really want to clear your name.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
I will look into it thoroughly
and slowly
until I'm happy with the result.
Your Highness.
Are those account books fine?
Will they find out
about our secret army?
Tushan Jing cooked the book.
Yueliang won't find anything.
And the materials for the Daming Hall
are authentic
and of top quality.
It's impeccable.
But nothing can be a secret forever.
It's been decades.
Someone from those clans
may have noticed something.
If Grandfather decides to look into it,
our secret army
will be exposed one day.
Your Highness.
Princess is back.
♪All things are dim,
while only your eyes shine bright♪
♪I'll follow my heart
and go to chase the sun far away♪
♪Everything seems sad,
while only your brows raise in delight♪
- Xuan.
♪I'm waiting for you
to enjoy the scenery at night♪
♪You came with wind and rain,
while left with my four seasons♪
♪Without you,
even the best scenery is dull♪
♪It began like a tornado,
and went away leaving only dust♪
Xuan.
I misunderstood you
and took off.
Are you mad at me?
If I'm so easily
mad at you,
I'd be mad all the time.
♪Even the most beautiful world♪
It's cold. Get inside.
♪Is a mess♪
Why don't you stay on Wushen Mountain?
What if you catch a cold
on the way here?
We won't catch a cold
on the Wushen Mountain,
but we'll be worried sick.
Don't worry.
It's under investigation.
Did Grandfather send someone
to take over your job
and build the Daming Hall?
I don't know.
We're still waiting.
Shan Hu.
Send it to my father.
Yes.
(Xuan.)
(I will help you stay)
(in the Central Plains at all costs.)
Are you worried about His Highness?
You're afraid the clans here
will be severe on him
for this incident.
I am worried,
but I'm not afraid.
I've been in an existential crisis.
Cang Xuan and I
have seen the blood.
Everything is ready
to be sent
to the Central Plains anytime.
No rush.
Your Majesty.
Yueliang is searching
Chenrong Mountain.
Things are against Cang Xuan.
This is the path he chose.
He must walk it on his own.
No one can do it for him.
You must understand
that we're not trying to save him
but to boost his momentum.
To save him, we need to act fast.
But to boost his momentum,
we wait for the right moment.
What if
there is no momentum to boost
if we don't
save him now?
It's very likely.
But
this is the deadly dangerous
path to the throne.
What's wrong?
I gathered all the spirit herbs
and spiritual medicine
from the Haoling Palace
and made some fine poisons
for you.
Cut to the chase.
I got this bow
from the Jintian Family.
What do you think?
Not bad.
But I haven't tamed it,
so it's only unleashing
20 percent of its potential.
I need three drops of blood from you
to claim the weapon.
May I?
Why would I help you
for no reason at all?
I taught you archery so that
you won't ask for favors.
If you want something,
get it yourself.
I made it.
Thank you.
Just with words?
You took my blood.
Shouldn't you pay back
with your blood?
Master, here you are.
Keep it for now. Don't renege on that.
I dare not.
It's good enough
for you to have fun.
But if you want to kill people,
you can be more vicious.
It's meant to kill people.
I'm planning to apply poison to them.
Once shot,
no one survives.
Congratulations.
You've mastered archery.
I have?
With low spirit power,
this is the best you can do
with archery.
From now on,
♪You laugh eyes like stars♪
you don't have to learn from me.
What?
Are you reluctant to leave me?
♪Carved in my bones and heart♪
Thank you for teaching me archery.
♪Waiting for snow♪
♪Waiting for destiny's favor♪
♪Waiting for you a lifetime♪
It's the Fangfeng family's
exclusive skill.
I don't mind
teaching you.
I've told you before.
I teach you archery.
You play with me.
The only thing I lose
is just time.
And you pay back with time.
It's a fair trade.
♪In every corner of this earthly realm♪
You've calculated it so well
to not lose anything.
Did you
want to take advantage of me?
You have nine heads.
I can't take advantage of you.
I'm happy with a fair trade.
♪It's the way back. It's the way home♪
Good for you.
I have to go.
See you around.
♪It's loneliness♪
♪In every corner of this earthly realm♪
♪It's longing. It's self-pity♪
♪The tones of tenderness♪
♪It's muteness. It's imprisonment♪
♪Scenes unfurl within myself♪
♪It's the way back. It's the way home♪
♪Life is like dancing in the snow♪
♪It's the end♪
♪I offered up my prayers in this life♪
♪For forever accompanying you♪
♪I brewed eternal yearning in wines♪
♪Walking in the mortal with you♪
♪I offered up my prayers
in the next life♪
♪For our permanent love to continue♪
♪Let momentary sorrow and joy fly♪
♪Till the end of the world,
I'll hold you♪
♪The fate brought us to here♪
♪I almost forgot about
the first time I met you♪
♪The destiny brought us together♪
♪I would drink with you
in our limited life♪
♪Under a crescent moon,
I felt empty and emotional♪
♪Afraid I would lost you forever
with mixed feelings♪
♪Hope your eyes remain pure and warm
and our country splendid♪
♪I prefer mortal life,
enjoying abundant blossoms♪
♪Under a crescent moon,
I felt empty and emotional♪
♪Afraid I would lost you forever
with mixed feelings♪
♪Hope your eyes remain pure and warm
and our country splendid♪
♪I prefer mortal life,
enjoying abundant blossoms♪