=Lost You Forever S2=
=Episode 7=
Has Skinny ever disliked you?
Have you ever had regrets or grievances?
I'm not a prostitute,
and he's not my client.
Life can't always be sweet.
Sometimes, it's also bitter.
After I gave birth to two sons,
I almost split up with Skinny.
However,
Skinny begged me
and apologized.
So, I forgave him.
When I look back and think about it,
I feel lucky
that I didn't break up with him.
It seems time has ultimately proven
that your choice was not wrong.
In my life,
I've cried, laughed,
and tasted bitterness and sweetness.
It's been worth it.
But people can only see the choice
in front of them,
not in the future.
What if we make a choice right now
that makes us sad,
but we won't regret it in the future?
About this question,
I can't answer it.
Even those deities
who've lived for hundreds of years
can't answer it either.
Living a life is
like making a journey in the wilderness.
Nobody knows what lies ahead.
Perhaps it's smooth.
Or perhaps,
it's a bumpy road.
So,
everyone wants to find a companion
to support each other.
Life is full of challenges,
obstacles, and setbacks,
but we try to live our lives.
What if you choose
and trust the wrong person?
Young lady.
Just remember
that if you want something,
you must believe
that it exists.
If you refuse
to believe,
you won't give your heart.
If you don't even give your heart,
you won't
get what you want at all.
(If I don't believe)
(and give,)
(I won't get what I want.)
(Jing and I have come to this.)
(Could it be my fault?)
Tian'er.
You've done well.
Skinny must feel lucky
to marry a good wife.
Mu
and I are happy for you.
Who are you?
Xiaoliu.
This place hasn't changed.
Sadly, you and I
can no longer get along as we used to.
You are the Princess of Haoling.
I am a rebel general.
We live in different worlds.
No need to feel sad.
You're right.
We are from different worlds.
I've been missing for so long.
There must be an uproar out there.
You did this.
Yet the Fangfeng Family
has to take the blame.
Fangfeng Yiying will have to shield them
from this unexpected disaster.
She is Chief Tushan's wife.
So she will
get the Tushan Family involved.
You think I'm the one
who wants to ruin your wedding?
If it's not you, who then?
I have a deal to do with you.
I need you
to stop Fenglong's wedding with Xiaoyao.
In what capacity do you ask for my help?
Ye Shiqi?
Can he afford my help?
Ye Shiqi can't afford it,
but Tushan Jing can.
Tushan Jing?
Who is he to stop this wedding?
I pay for a service.
You get paid to do a job.
Since when do you care who I am
when doing business?
Help me stop this wedding.
From now on,
I will provide provisions
for the Chenrong Army every year.
This seal is the proof.
Money is a good thing.
You can hire others
to do what you dare not to do.
Chief Tushan.
That's very generous.
Will you take this deal or not?
I'll take it.
Why not?
You know,
I never turn down money.
Good.
I hope you can stop it
before the wedding.
Don't disturb others.
Minimize the harm.
I've taken the deal.
I decide how to finish this.
You needn't bother.
I don't need you to tell me what to do
or set the price.
I decide how you're going
to pay for my help.
My word is final.
I help you ruin the wedding,
and you provide the Chenrong Army
with army provisions
for 37 years.
Tushan Jing hired you to do that?
If you don't believe it,
you can ask Tushan Jing yourself.
By what right did he ruin my wedding?
What does he want?
I was hired to do a job.
What the employer thinks
is none of my concern.
I hate him.
When can I leave?
I've already got what I wanted.
You can leave
at any time.
Just a reminder,
the poisonous bug isn't removed.
If you reveal that I'm Fangfeng Bei,
I will give you a painful death.
You don't believe it?
If you don't want to die,
don't say anything you shouldn't.
Is this
why you won't remove the poisonous bug?
General Xiang Liu.
What a scheming one.
This is the kind of person I am.
You knew it.
Mr. Yu.
Yu Xin.
Watch your manners.
Miss.
Are you looking for me?
I want to see Tushan Jing.
Take me to Qingqiu.
Who do you think you are
to see Chief Tushan?
Tushan Jing will definitely see me.
If I'm lying,
you'll just make a trip in vain.
After all, I am in your hands.
You can punish me.
If I'm not lying,
but you refuse me,
you will make a big mistake.
You don't look like an ordinary lady.
I don't think you're lying.
I will accompany you to Qingqiu.
(Qingshui Town)
Miss.
After leaving Qingshui Town
and the snow abates,
we'll take a cloud carriage.
Okay.
(I'm afraid of loneliness.)
(If I can't find
enduring companionship,)
(a brief encounter is also good.)
(Fangfeng Bei,
who accompanied you briefly, has died.)
(You can now enjoy someone else's
enduring company.)
(Tushan Mansion)
She wants to see the Chief.
So you brought her here?
How could you act so rashly?
It is her.
Jing Ye.
Prin...
Princess?
This pill only relieves your heartache.
But it can't cure you.
Your heart is damaged.
Don't think or worry too much.
You need some quiet rest.
Okay.
I got it.
I know
you're worried about someone.
You can't stop worrying.
Chief.
The princess is here.
Jing Ye.
Get new clothes for me.
I smell of medicine.
How do I look?
You look much better.
The princess is weary from her trip.
I have arranged for a maid
to help the princess get bathed
and dressed.
It will take a while.
Chief, no rush.
Take your time.
No need to sweep it.
The princess likes the snow.
Your Majesty.
The princess hasn't returned.
The snow...
Xiaoyao will come back.
No matter where she is,
I will find her and bring her back.
Okay.
Keep the snow
until the princess returns.
This year's winter is unusually cold.
It's the same every year.
Every year around this time,
it snows frequently.
In previous years, with Xiaoyao around,
even when it snowed,
I didn't feel cold.
The princess loved the snow.
At Zhaoyun Peak,
whenever it snowed,
the princess would be happy.
It's always spring in Haoling.
Xiaoyao never saw snow before.
Naturally, she's happy
to see the snow.
Your Majesty used to do this
to please the princess.
You're drawing me.
It was easy to cheer her up
when she was a kid.
Her emotions always appeared
on her face.
If I pleased her,
she would be very happy.
(Forget it.)
(What can I do even if I ask him?)
(Even though Tushan Jing is behind it,)
(can I kill him?)
(It's just going to bother me.)
(I'd better leave.)
Thank you.
I came here
in a fit of anger because of Xiang Liu.
You know,
people tend to be impulsive
when they are angry.
When I'm impulsive,
I'll do something I don't want to.
Actually, I didn't intend to see you.
I just...
It's getting late.
There might be a blizzard.
You stay for the night.
Tomorrow morning, I'll send you
back to Chenrong Mountain.
It doesn't look like
it's going to snow again.
Look.
The weather wants you to stay.
Fine.
I'll go back to my room.
I'll use the front door.
(Since I'm here,)
(I might as well make things clear.)
- I...
You go first.
I have something to say.
I also have something to say.
I waited outside the Tushan Mansion
but I didn't see the princess.
But I saw a suspicious person.
Who?
Upon investigation,
that person is Yu Xin.
He talked with the guard
at the gate.
The carriage went straight
into the Tushan Mansion.
But I don't know
if there's anyone else in the carriage.
Yu Xin?
She's in the Tushan's.
Bring her back.
Yes.
So Xiaoyao has stayed
in Qingshui Town for a while.
No wonder I searched the entire Dahuang
and could not find her.
But why did Fangfeng Bei
take the princess to Qingshui Town?
Go to Qingshui Town to verify this.
If you can't find anything,
you can go to the Rejuvenation Hall.
Yes.
I haven't been able to sleep well
these years,
always tossing and turning,
thinking about the past.
I thought
you had completely let it go
and didn't care.
In those first few years,
I really resented you.
So whenever you appeared,
I deliberately acted
as if I didn't care.
But actually,
I've been secretly paying attention
to your reactions.
However, over these years,
my mindset has changed a lot.
The way I view things has also changed.
I increasingly feel
that blaming everything
on you
is actually not right.
Fangfeng Yiying tried
to assassinate Cang Xuan
many times, you know?
Once,
she shot through Cang Xuan's chest.
Well,
when facing you,
she's always been kind, polite,
and gentle.
But I have long known
that she is deep in thought
and ruthless.
I also know that you are soft-hearted
and feel guilty towards her.
She will definitely
use your temperament against you.
But,
I did nothing.
I thought I was clear-headed
and stood by.
I even
never reminded you.
Actually, we could have
easily solved the problem together.
However, I watched you struggle
and fall into the trap.
It's not like that.
It's all my fault.
Because of my childhood experiences,
I feel pessimistic
about human relationships.
And nothing is reliable.
I've never truly believed in you
because I don't dare to.
I've also never done anything for you.
Whenever something occurs,
I will be like,
look,
everything is going as I expected.
Human nature is unpredictable.
No one is reliable.
However,
there is a saying
that you reap
what you sow.
I got what I sowed.
Because of my distrust
and my self-righteousness,
I have lost the person I like.
Unfortunately,
some mistakes
can be corrected,
but some mistakes
can never be corrected.
Xiaoyao.
Don't cry.
It's not your fault.
I promised to give
and trust you first.
I should've protected you.
But I failed.
I am the one to blame.
Xiaoyao.
I would rather you don't care about me
and forget me.
I can't watch you
endure the same pain as me.
I don't want to care about you.
I want to forget you.
But why did you stop me from marrying?
Why did you stop me from moving on
and acting as if nothing has happened?
Before,
I apologized to you.
Now I take it back.
I do not regret it at all.
Xiang Liu used the most extreme methods
to stir up things in Dahuang,
but I'm very happy
that you didn't marry Fenglong.
You rogue.
I've always been a rogue.
I will return
to Chenrong Mountain tomorrow.
You don't need to see me off.
The mistake has been made.
Even if we regret it,
there is no going back.
Whether it's for you
or me,
from now on,
we should not meet again.
I've heard you out.
It's your turn to hear me out.
That's fair to me.
I have already...
Tushan Tian is not my son.
Mother.
Why doesn't Father come to see me?
I miss Father.
(Fangfeng Yiying)
How about I perform a magic trick
for you?
Great.
The butterfly plays with you, okay?
Mother.
Did you use magic
on Father?
Otherwise,
why does Father become mute
as soon as he sees you?
He never talks to you
or keeps me company.
Don't talk nonsense.
But it's the truth.
Time to sleep.
So, you suspect
that Tian is Tushan Hou's son.
Fearing the truth would come out,
they killed your sister-in-law.
Exactly.
Didn't you say you remembered nothing
about that night?
How can you be sure
that Fangfeng Yiying and you did not...
Fangfeng Yiying had Grandma drug me,
tipping me over the edge.
And I mistook her for you in a daze.
But Fangfeng Yiying didn't know
what you meant to me.
Precisely because it was you,
I definitely couldn't
take you in that case.
Even if I offered to sleep with you,
would you refuse me?
If you did that,
I'd only be more restrained.
it meant you trusted me.
I'd never betray your trust.
I'd give you the best of everything.
I'd only take you after marrying you.
Even though I can't
remember what happened that night,
I clearly remember
I was in Fangfeng Yiying's room.
I have always desired
to be with you openly.
How could I possibly
take you on another woman's bed?
I was delirious,
but I would never go
against my innermost desires.
I trust you.
Thank you for trusting me.
Hou.
You know Tushan Jing is now in Qingqiu.
Why do you want to meet with me?
If others see us,
our efforts will be in vain.
Hou.
I don't want
to live furtively anymore.
What do you want?
It was hard to kill Tushan Jing
when he hid in Zhiyi.
Now that he has returned to Qingqiu,
we can take the opportunity to kill him.
Tushan Jing
(Tushan Hou)
can't do without medicine.
Why make an unnecessary move?
I've sent someone to investigate it.
The dosage
of his medicine is increasing.
It means his heart condition
is getting more severe.
There's no need
for us to take action at all.
Alright.
Just be patient.
Don't alert him.
It's better to wait quietly.
Just watch Tushan Jing
live longer in pain.
So you've long suspected them.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I have no evidence.
If you've already forgotten me,
why should I say it and upset you?
Tonight,
I've learned you never forget me.
Things couldn't get any worse anyway.
So I tell you all.
How have you been these...
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
It's getting late.
Good night.
I have to go.
Jing.
Chief.
What exactly is the illness you have?
It's nothing serious.
I'll be fine after some rest.
How could this happen?
Decades ago,
Chief was utterly devastated
with a heart condition.
Over the years, for the sake of you,
he could neither sleep nor eat well.
His moods grew gloomier.
Over three months ago,
you even invited Chief
to your wedding banquet.
It made Chief get a serious illness,
and the heart condition worsened.
His lifespan has been affected.
- I'm afraid...
- Jing Ye.
Just leave.
I didn't mean to keep it from you.
Xiaoyao.
Don't cry.
Don't cry for me.
Take medicine
according to my prescription.
You mustn't use your spirit power.
Think and worry less.
Have some quiet rest.
Alright.
Chief's illness began over 40 years ago.
Now, he has old
and new diseases.
Your Highness' prescription is good.
But it requires long-term care.
A decade or two, I guess.
Your Highness, have you decided?
Do as the princess says.
Yes.
What's wrong?
Does your heart hurt again?
This is your medical fee.
Please accept it.
Chief.
The King of Xiyan
sends someone
to bring the princess back.
Your Highness.
I'm here by His Majesty's command
to escort you back to the palace.
If I accept this,
I'll promise to cure your illness.
I'll do what you say
and take care of myself.
In a few days,
I will go to Zhiyi.
Please continue treating me then.
If you didn't get the grains and fodder,
many brothers would die this winter.
I am the adviser of the Chenrong Army.
I'm doing what I should.
How did you
convince the Tushan Family
to lend a hand?
Just do it as the businessman does.
What business could make them take risks
to provide us
(Hong Jiang)
with grains and fodder for free?
The King of Xiyan might send people
to inspect Qingshui Town.
Tell our people to be cautious
lest we're exposed.
Why?
Could they find out
about the grain supply?
With Tushan Jing's capability,
I don't think he can't handle it well.
Then what happened?
If you don't want to say,
you surely have your reasons.
I won't ask you.
I will instruct soldiers
to act cautiously.
(Why not quit being a princess)
and rove the world with me?
Okay.
If you give up everything,
I will go with you.
Grandfather.
I am back.
You even had the nerve
to call off the wedding
in front of everyone.
I thought you were afraid of nothing.
Come out and talk.
Come out.
What exactly is going on
between you and Fangfeng Bei?
If he wants to marry you,
will he have no courage to meet us?
Fangfeng Bei is dead.
Are you sure Fangfeng Bei is dead?
I am sure.
Fangfeng Bei
will never appear again.
Fangfeng Bei died for me.
I don't want to talk
about him anymore.
In front of the crowds,
Fangfeng Bei and Xiaoyao left together.
Now Xiaoyao has come back,
but he is dead.
We owe an explanation to the people.
When my guards caught up with Xiaoyao,
Fangfeng Bei refused to release her.
To protect the princess,
the guards killed him
in an emergency.
Actually, it's good
that Fangfeng Bei was killed.
That's what the Chishui Family
and other people want.
It also helps appease Fenglong
and Chenrong Yi.
The Fangfeng Family doesn't dare
to complain
because of a baseborn son.
That's good.
You go back and rest.
I need to discuss some things
with Grandfather.
You may leave.
When you asked me
to persuade Xiang Liu to surrender,
did you already know
that Xiang Liu and Fangfeng Bei
were the same person?
It was just my speculation before.
I only found it out today.
If it had not been
for Chi Chen back then,
Auntie wouldn't have...
Xiang Liu is really too arrogant.
How dare he see Xiaoyao again.
♪Looking back on my old days♪
♪I was unruffled
with no sorrow and soreness♪
♪In my chaotic life,
I failed to meet your gaze♪
♪Only emptiness remained♪
♪Enduring all things in my life♪
♪I valued all but indifferent
to wealth and fame♪
♪Basking in the sun,
I couldn't feel your sunlight♪
♪All I feel is a painful heat wave♪
♪All things are dim,
while only your eyes shine bright♪
♪I'll follow my heart
and go to chase the sun far away♪
♪Everything seems sad,
while only your brows raise in delight♪
♪I'm waiting for you
to enjoy the scenery at night♪
♪You came with wind and rain,
while left with my four seasons♪
♪All is bleak without you♪
♪It began like a tornado,
and went away leaving only dust♪
♪Without you,
even the most beautiful world is a mess♪