=Lost You Forever S2=
=Episode 16=
Marrying Nian
will make you a bit happier.
After all, you watched her grow up.
In your heart,
she must be different from
those women from the Zijin Peak.
Nian is different from them.
But it doesn't mean
I want to marry her.
Your marriage to Nian would quell
the strife between our two kingdoms.
Moreover, Nian is sincere.
And you know she likes you
more than any other women.
Have you ever considered
what I truly feel?
You've only ever thought about Nian.
Nian wants to marry me.
You think
that I already have
so many women,
so one more woman
doesn't really matter, right?
What are you talking about?
I just think
if you could previously marry
those women to win over those clans,
why can't you marry Nian?
Is she in any way inferior to them?
Why are you looking at me?
Back then,
when you married Chenrong Xinyue,
you were all elated.
What's wrong with marrying Nian now?
Why so reluctant?
When was I ever elated?
Did you see that?
Tell me
how I was ever elated.
I didn't see it with my own eyes,
but back in the day,
when you married Chenrong Xinyue,
the people of Haoling all discussed it.
So many people
saw you in high spirits.
Xiaoyao,
anyone can say so, but you...
How could you?
Cang Xuan,
just be drunk
in front of all the guests from Dahuang
and the officials from both kingdoms
tomorrow.
Xiling Jiuyao, let me tell you.
I felt very sad
every time I got married,
especially when I married
Chenrong Xinyue.
I even hate myself
and hate you too.
If you are drunk again,
I will hit you.
I'm serious.
I don't want any of those women.
I just want...
Cang Xuan,
what is wrong with you?
Before,
I could always tell
what you were thinking.
But this time, I have no idea at all.
I admit
I did only think about Nian.
I didn't consider you.
Because in my heart,
I feel
you care more about the whole world
and the political landscape,
and care less about other things.
Which of these two pendants
do you prefer?
Whichever.
Then at the wedding ceremony tomorrow,
which color of lipstick
do you want to apply?
Vermilion,
silvery red,
scarlet,
rose red,
begonia red
or peach red?
Whichever.
Why do you
always reply "whichever"?
My dream has come true.
I'm happy.
- Congratulations.
I've never seen a bride like you.
Then what do you think a bride
should be like?
If one day,
I can marry Cang Xuan,
I will definitely be nervous.
I'll also be a bit scared
that I'm not pretty enough.
From accessories to the color of rouge,
I will pick everything personally.
I will look forward
to my future with him.
Nian,
are you happy?
I used to think
if one day,
I could marry Cang Xuan,
I would surely be overjoyed.
But now my dream has come true,
and I am not as happy as I had imagined.
If you have regrets,
I will issue an edict at once
to cancel tomorrow's wedding.
Now all the people of Dahuang know
that I will be married
to the King of Xiyan tomorrow.
The Four Great Clans,
Haoling's four tribes,
the clans of the Central Plains,
and the old clans of Xiyan
all gather at Wushen Mountain.
The wedding
can't be canceled casually.
I am the King of Haoling.
So I have the final say.
You just consider
whether you want to marry or not.
Leave the rest to me.
Kings should keep their word.
Aren't you afraid of
being ridiculed by the people?
Compared to your lifelong happiness,
the people's scorn
is nothing.
All the clans gather at Wushen Mountain.
It is just good.
Presumably, each clan has sent out
their most outstanding offsprings.
Among them are certainly
many outstanding young men.
You can choose an ideal husband
among them.
It is not
just mine and Cang Xuan's wedding.
It also concerns the peace
of the Dahuang.
Father,
if you cancel it
and change the groom casually,
aren't you afraid of causing
chaos in Dahuang?
So what?
I was able to quell
the Five Princes Rebellion back then,
so I am not afraid now.
Father,
you are the best father.
Nian,
Cang Xuan is an emperor.
He...
I know.
He doesn't like me,
but I like him.
Marrying him
isn't as happy
as I thought it would be,
but I know
if I don't marry him,
I'll never be happy in my life.
Nian.
Father,
don't worry.
I'm not what I used to be anymore.
I still like Cang Xuan,
but he's not everything
to me anymore.
I'm not the most important to him.
Similarly,
he's not the most important to me.
If I have to choose between him
and you,
I will choose you.
If I have to choose between our people
and him,
I will choose our people.
If that's the case,
don't marry Cang Xuan.
Father,
I know well
Cang Xuan doesn't want to marry me,
but I insist on marrying him.
Because between his happiness
and mine,
I choose to make him unhappy
and make myself happy.
Father,
I've grown up.
I promise
I will take good care of myself.
If you really don't want
the wedding tomorrow,
we'll find a way to cancel it.
How do we do it?
Tomorrow's wedding
is already known to all the people.
Millions of troops
are guarding the border
between the two kingdoms.
One careless move
could lead to great chaos.
I haven't thought it through yet.
But
whatever you don't want to do,
I will support you.
Let's figure out a way together.
There must be a way to cancel it.
Aren't you afraid of danger?
No.
Since we were little,
we've never had a peaceful day.
What number is this?
Six.
Are you messing with me?
Tomorrow,
all the people will see
the King of Xiyan joyfully
marry the Princess of Haoling.
Cang Xuan.
I was drunk just now.
Now I am sober.
Things have come to this.
Marrying one more woman
makes no difference.
Are you really willing?
Yes.
You said just now that you wanted...
What do you want?
As long as it's something I can do,
I will help you achieve it.
I want...
What do you want?
I want us both to be safe and sound.
Cang Xuan,
you are the King of Xiyan now.
In the future,
you'll be the master of Dahuang.
No one will hurt you again.
Nor will anyone hurt me anymore.
Right.
We have already reached the summit.
♪Looking back on my old days♪
As usual.
Don't congratulate me.
Don't give me gifts.
And don't show up
at the wedding tomorrow.
Alright.
I'm not giving a gift.
Nor will I attend.
♪Enduring all things in my life♪
On Wushen Mountain, you and Auntie
loved the Yiqing Garden most.
I will build you an identical garden
on Chenrong Mountain.
You don't have to.
Jing told me in Qingqiu,
he would build me a Yiqing Garden.
♪All things are dim♪
♪While only your eyes shine bright♪
♪I'll follow my heart
and go to chase the sun far away♪
♪Everything seems sad♪
Why have these fish
suddenly all run away?
The fish from Wushen Mountain
don't like me being here.
Xuan,
just a few fish.
You've conquered Chenrong Mountain.
Wushen Mountain is no challenge for you.
Will you accompany me?
Of course.
I will.
♪Without you♪
♪Even the most beautiful world♪
(Cheng'en Palace, Haoling)
♪Is a mess♪
(Sunlight Hall)
With wonderful music,
the phoenix arrives in splendor.
♪I climbed mountains♪
♪And crossed rivers♪
♪But I couldn't walk out
of life and death♪
♪I lived through gatherings♪
♪And parting♪
♪But I couldn't walk out
of sorrows and joys♪
♪I lived through spring♪
♪And summer♪
♪But I couldn't walk out
of the memories♪
♪But I couldn't walk out♪
♪Of the memories♪
Cang Xuan.
♪You are in my mind♪
♪But not hold my hand♪
♪You were here yesterday♪
♪But you are not here tomorrow♪
♪You appear in the rain♪
♪But disappear in the water♪
Vast mountains and rivers.
May the couple be together forever.
May the couple be blessed
with many thriving children.
♪You have dark hair♪
♪You appear at the foot of the mountain♪
♪Not on a cloud♪
What is gained
cannot compensate for what is lost.
You're being foolish again?
I thought it was an illusion.
I thought you were fake.
But how come you are here?
I came because I wanted to.
Do you know what day it is today?
The King of Xiyan
is marrying the Princess of Haoling.
Do you know
how many guards are stationed
on Wushen Mountain?
I know the King of Xiyan
is getting married.
That's why I came here.
You don't seem like someone
who likes to join the crowd.
If it were just a wedding,
I naturally wouldn't be interested
in joining the crowd.
What do you mean?
The King of Haoling is a wise ruler.
He couldn't possibly be aware
of the danger of leaving
the throne empty
and still delay appointing an heir,
unless he has his own plan.
Now, the King of Haoling
has his only daughter
marry the King of Xiyan.
And he is also the master
of the King of Xiyan.
Could it be...
What?
Could it be that he wants
to give the Haoling
as a dowry to Xiyan Cang Xuan?
How could that be possible?
No wonder you are a nine-headed demon.
Your jokes are more ridiculous
than those of others.
It seems I guessed right.
Nine heads do think better than one.
Xuan has inherited
our grandfather's ambition
to unify Dahuang.
After subduing Haoling,
he will then send troops
to attack Hong Jiang.
I thought the war
between Haoling and Xiyan
would be hard to end in a few decades.
I didn't expect
Dahuang would be unified so quickly.
Do you still
continue following Hong Jiang?
The world is vast
and boundless.
Don't you really
want
to do anything else?
The world is vast
and boundless.
Right.
You are a nine-headed demon.
Do you want to be bound by fate?
Have you not considered making
a different choice?
Are you worried about me?
I know
you just see me
as an object of trade.
But I see you
as a friend.
Friendship
cannot be seen or touched.
I don't think I can rely on it.
If Xiyan Cang Xuan knows
we both have a poisonous bug
in our hearts
and our lives are connected,
will he kill me?
You are my pawn
to control the King of Xiyan.
You knew
what this poisonous bug was all along.
Right?
Right, so what?
Since you could help Cang Xuan transfer
the poisonous bug to yourself,
you surely know the method to remove it.
Take a guess.
If I die,
will you still be alive?
Other way around.
If I die,
will you still be alive?
You can use the poisonous bug
as leverage against Cang Xuan.
Aren't you afraid
I would use the poisonous bug
to scheme against you?
Scheme against me?
I'm looking forward to it.
Xiang Liu,
what exactly do you want?
Make yourself clear.
Xiaoyao.
The wedding is over?
Yes.
Xuan.
Is everything going well with him?
Yes.
What are you worried about?
Nothing.
I was just taking a walk by the sea,
and Xiang Liu suddenly appeared.
I was just asking him
about removing the poisonous bug.
Does Xiang Liu have a way?
I guess he does.
Otherwise,
knowing it would
make our lives connected,
he wouldn't put the poisonous bug
inside him willingly.
But
he didn't tell me.
The poisonous bug bothers me
until it's removed.
Xiang Liu is known as "Nine Lives"
with exceptional spirit power.
Between him and me,
I'm more vulnerable.
If there's any worry,
he should worry
that I might drag him down.
I misspoke.
I am hard
to kill
and sure to live a long life
and become an old woman.
Don't worry.
I've been studying
medicine and compiling
medical books recently.
Since Xiang Liu can remove
the poisonous bug,
I can certainly do it too.
It's just that I need some time.
You're right.
We will definitely find a way.
This place.
Have we been here before?
Chief Tushan,
it was here
where I offered my first kiss,
and you rejected it.
It was my fault for not knowing
what I was missing.
Now that you know it,
don't miss the opportunity anymore.
This time,
you can't dodge.
it is you who can't dodge.
Since ascending to the throne
in my prime,
it has been hundreds of years.
And now I'm in my twilight years.
My body and spirit ail.
Still, state affairs are burdensome.
I am well aware
that I cannot sustain it.
Holding the throne in vain
isn't good for the kingdom.
I fear I would dishonor my ancestors
and disappoint the people.
Now there is a ruler who is wise
and capable.
I've decided to cede the throne to him.
I wonder
which member of the royal family
you have in mind.
Not from the Haoling royal family.
It is
Xiyan Cang Xuan.
Your Majesty.
Absolutely not!
Xiyan Cang Xuan is the king
of the Xiyan Kingdom.
If you cede the throne to him,
would it not be
like giving the great lands of Haoling
straight to him?
Please think again
and take it back.
- Please think again
- and take it back.
The lands were once one.
Your Majesty, you prioritize peace
and the well-being of all people,
and abdicate the throne
to unify the lands.
Your generosity
is beyond ordinary people.
My subordinates and I
will abide by your command.
I will abide by your command.
Good.
Qinglong,
Xihe, do you two squads
have any objections?
We Qinglong Squad
will abide by your command.
We Xihe Squad
- Your Majesty, please don't.
- Please don't.
Issue the edict.
Here's His Majesty's decree.
I understand the rulership
is not a personal possession
but is earned through virtue.
Heaven and people
all demand the wise
and the capable to be selected,
which is a principle embraced by all.
The position isn't for one
to possess alone.
Cang Xuan of Xiyan
(Father cede the throne to me.)
is sagacious
(I'll try to be a good ruler and not let you down.)
and outstanding.
Today, I retire to another palace
and cede the throne to him.
That's all.
You and His Majesty have unified Dahuang
without waging war
or disturbing the people.
It is truly a joyous
and congratulatory event.
It is too early
to be happy now.
Cang Xuan
has only nominally unified Haoling.
The Haoling tribes
will not be sincerely convinced.
It is heard
that the court officials opposing
Cang Xuan's succession
are not in the minority.
Although
all have been suppressed by the might
of the King of Haoling,
they will surely obstruct at every turn.
It is not easy for Cang Xuan
to fully control Haoling.
You don't need to worry.
With His Majesty's wisdom and ability,
he will certainly make
the Haoling court officials convinced.
Right.
I believe that Cang Xuan can achieve it.
After all, I have spent centuries
but still failed to make the clans
of the Central Plains
truly submit to me.
Cang Xuan, however,
accomplished it in less than a century.
(Since Xiyan Cang Xuan
succeeded to the throne,)
(he has governed with diligence)
(and love for the people.)
(Regarding Ru Shou, Qin Mang and others)
(who supported his succession,
he saw them as his right-hand men)
(and entrusted them
with important tasks.)
(Towards the good officials
who opposed his succession,)
(he treated them with courtesy)
(and accepted their criticism.)
(As for the treacherous ones)
(who profited from chaos,)
(he suppressed them)
(forcefully.)
(The turmoil over the throne
gradually subsided.)
(Under the rule of Xiyan Cang Xuan,)
(the order has been restored
and the governance has been upright.)
(Haoling has prospered.)
(All are convinced.)
(Now,)
(Haoling)
(and Xiyan)
(are truly united.)
(Xiyan Cang Xuan is honored)
(as the Lord of Dahuang.)
How is Father?
No serious issues.
But if he wants to fully recover,
he still needs to recuperate.
Father, you've worked hard.
Cang Xuan,
I want to ask you for something.
No matter what it is,
as long as you want it,
just take it.
I want Xiyan Mountain.
Father,
there's no need for that.
Father, why do you want that?
Now, the situation is settled.
I want to leave Wushen Mountain
and move to Xiyan Mountain.
Why?
Father does not want
two rulers in one kingdom,
and he is intent on crushing
all the officials' hopes,
and making everyone acknowledge
only Cang Xuan as the king.
There is also a personal reason.
Xiyan Mountain
is the birthplace
of the Xiyan royal family.
It's of extraordinary significance
to the Xiyan Kingdom.
Becoming the master
is to show the world
my status is the same
as the Great Emperor's
and Haoling is not a submission.
Father,
there's really no need for that.
The climate of Wushen Mountain
and Xiyan Mountain
is entirely different.
You may not be able to adapt.
The climate of Chenrong Mountain
and Xiyan Mountain
is also entirely different.
Isn't your grandfather
also living well there?
I've heard
he's must better
than when he was at Xiyan Mountain.
Father,
how can you bear
to leave Wushen Mountain?
On Wushen Mountain,
the only one I can't bear to part with
is you.
I am tired.
I want to change my way of life
and don't want to stay
in this palace anymore.
Your mother will stay to accompany you.
Even when Cang Xuan is not around,
you are not alone.
Cang Xuan,
are you willing
to give Xiyan Mountain to me?
Of course I am willing.
But Father,
please recover fully before you leave.
If I stay here,
even if I do not want
to deal with something,
it will still reach my ears
and prevent me from resting in peace.
If possible,
I want to leave soon.
Father,
let me accompany you back
to Xiyan Mountain.
It's a good opportunity
to help you recuperate.
With you accompanying Father back,
I will be much more at ease.
Rest assured.
I will definitely arrange it
as soon as possible.
(Sunlight Hall)
You're a good king.
In my lifetime,
I am not a good son,
a good brother, a good friend
or a good husband.
But I am indeed
a good king.
You're a good father.
You're the best father to Nian and me.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
What are you here for?
Are you still angry
about the matter
of the Queen of Haoling?
It was my fault for not informing you
in advance.
I've come specially to apologize.
To apologize?
You did a lot
to help His Majesty marry
the Princess of Haoling.
Now, your fame
in the court is resounding.
I can't afford
your apology.
Your Majesty,
the marriage alliance between the two
royal families of Xiyan and Haoling
has averted a war
between the two kingdoms
that may last for decades
or even hundreds of years.
The people will all be grateful to you.
Enough!
Save your principles
for the court session.
I am not your peer or subordinate.
I am
your sister of the same mother.
Xinyue,
I'm doing this for your good.
The Queen of Haoling lives
at Wushen Mountain.
You can't see her at all.
She has no impact on your status.
For my good?
You and father,
for what you call the clan's interest,
for your own high positions,
have sacrificed me once again.
Putting on airs.
Utterly hypocritical.
Just scold me
if you want.
Don't bring Father into this.
I warned you about this from the start
His Majesty carried
the whole world in his mind.
If you wanted a devoted husband,
don't marry His Majesty.
This was your own choice.
It wasn't me or Father
who forced you to become the queen.
Without me and father,
would someone willful and selfish
like you secure your position?
Get out of my sight!
I will no longer need
your concern in the future.
(Base Camp of Chenrong Army)
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Mr. Xiang.
Starting today,
add an extra portion
of meat to everyone.
You've gathered more provisions.
Let me say thank you
on behalf of everyone.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Tell me.
Does our perseverance make sense?
No matter the obstacles,
I shall go forth.
♪Looking back on my old days♪
♪I was unruffled
with no sorrow and soreness♪
♪In my chaotic life,
I failed to meet your gaze♪
♪Only emptiness remained♪
♪Enduring all things in my life♪
♪I valued all but indifferent
to wealth and fame♪
♪Basking in the sun,
I couldn't feel your sunlight♪
♪All I feel is a painful heat wave♪
♪All things are dim,
while only your eyes shine bright♪
♪I'll follow my heart
and go to chase the sun far away♪
♪Everything seems sad,
while only your brows raise in delight♪
♪I'm waiting for you
to enjoy the scenery at night♪
♪You came with wind and rain,
while left with my four seasons♪
♪All is bleak without you♪
♪It began like a tornado,
and went away leaving only dust♪
♪Without you,
even the most beautiful world is a mess♪