=Lost You Forever S2=
=Episode 6=
You
saved me.
So,
I'm your servant.
Please name me.
Beggar.
Starting today,
your name is Ye Shiqi.
♪Let momentary sorrow and joy fly♪
♪I'll hold you
till the end of the world♪
Give Tushan Jing 15 years.
And 15 years later,
Ye Shiqi will be back to you.
Last night,
a man forced me to kiss him.
But now I only want to kiss you.
Your kiss
is sweet.
Because you are sweet.
Jing.
Do you really see me
as important as your life?
You are
more important than my life.
♪Joys and sorrows are mixed♪
♪The wind and rain beat down on me♪
♪My eyes are wet♪
♪The view is splendid♪
Xiaoyao.
♪But I prefer the worldly life♪
♪That's our destiny♪
Flowers bloom together.
I'll be with you forever.
♪The destiny brought us together♪
Flowers bloom together.
I'll be with you forever.
♪A new moon sets♪
♪Joys and sorrows are mixed♪
♪The wind and rain beat down on me♪
♪My eyes are wet♪
Xiaoyao.
It's almost time.
Let's go inside.
♪But I♪
♪Prefer the worldly life♪
Okay.
The auspicious time has arrived.
It's time to perform the ceremony.
Bow to heaven and earth.
Bow to the elders.
- Xiaoyao.
Xiaoyao.
Don't marry him.
Guards.
Get this rascal
out of here.
Fangfeng Bei.
There are honored guests present.
I don't want to disturb them.
Before you do anything,
think of your family and clansmen first.
Xiaoyao.
Don't marry him.
What do you want to do?
Don't marry Chishui Fenglong.
You are now telling me not to marry him?
The ceremony is still not completed.
You can choose not to marry.
Leave immediately.
Do not appear
in front of me again.
Ignore him. Let's continue.
I don't want
to miss the auspicious time.
Okay.
Bow to the elders.
Xiaoyao.
Do you still remember the oath
you once swore?
I swear
if Xiang Liu helps me
remove the poisonous bug from Xuan,
I will do one thing for him.
What if you break this oath?
I will die
miserably.
Forget it.
You're a petty man.
So you won't be satisfied with it.
Tell me.
What oath do you want me to swear?
If you break the oath,
all your pleasures
will turn into pain,
and all your happiness
will turn into sorrow.
Xiaoyao.
What do you want?
I want you to leave with me now.
Even if you try to destroy me,
why do you do it
in the most insulting way?
You don't need to ask the reason.
You just need to do as I say.
Come with me.
Immediately.
Right away.
Xiaoyao.
It's time for the ceremony.
You owe me.
I swear
if I break this oath,
all my pleasures
will turn into pain,
and all my happiness
will turn into sorrow.
Xiaoyao.
Don't.
I'm sorry.
Today,
I cannot marry you.
I'm sorry.
What?
She's not marrying him?
You'd rather leave with him
than marry me.
In your heart,
I, Chishui Fenglong,
am not better
than an idler?
It's not like that.
I...
Come with me immediately.
I am sorry.
I cannot marry you today.
I don't expect your forgiveness.
No matter how you punish me
in the future,
I will bear it.
Let her leave.
I said let her go.
Do not stop her.
Wait.
Xiaoyao.
Everyone.
The food and drink are ready.
You have all come from afar.
Please enjoy the food and drink
before leaving.
Your Lordship.
Chief Chishui.
After I return
and report this to His Majesty,
we'll give the Chishui Family
and the Chenrong Family an explanation.
Ru Shou, please.
It's urgent.
There's big trouble.
Your Majesty.
The princess ran away from the wedding.
What did you say?
In the middle of the wedding ceremony,
the princess suddenly
left Chief Chishui and ran away.
It has been widely discussed in Dahuang.
She ran away?
The Chishui Clan has lost face.
Good.
That's good.
She should run away.
His Majesty
is definitely mad.
What did you say?
Xiaoyao dumped my brother
and left with Fangfeng Bei?
And even in front of all the guests
of Dahuang?
Yes, Your Majesty.
She ran away from her wedding.
How dare she?
Please calm your anger.
She has made the Chenrong Family
and the Chishui Family lose face.
She won't end up well.
Her reputation will be ruined,
and she will die alone.
The rites and laws
of Haoling are strict.
There's no place for her.
She has to hide
in the Chenrong Mountain
and spend the rest of her life
by relying on your support.
She has to stay
in the Chenrong Mountain for a lifetime?
Yes.
No man
will marry her.
And she will die alone.
Only His Majesty
will provide her with a place to stay
for the sake of their
childhood friendship.
Your Majesty.
Haoling Jiuyao.
Why did you run away from your wedding?
Why?
This is Qingshui Town.
We will stay here for a while.
I have
ruined your wedding
with Chishui Fenglong.
Will you hate me?
Whether I hate you or not,
does it matter now?
After all, I owe you.
When you ask me to repay,
I must repay it.
It's good that you understand.
When did you know
I was to be married?
Before you left Haoling.
You had enough time
to stop this wedding.
But you did it at the wedding
and took me away,
making Chenrong and Chishui Family
hold a grudge against me.
Why do you treat me this way?
You dishonored Haoling
and ruined my reputation.
I will be despised
by everyone in Dahuang.
Forget it.
It happened.
What else can I do?
Perhaps,
I was just born unlucky.
I'm tired.
You get out.
Grandfather.
I'm going to issue a decree
to give Luoshui to the Chishui Family
as compensation.
Such a generous reward.
The engagement will be canceled?
(Apology Letter)
That's fine.
When issuing the decree,
you give my apology letter
to them as well.
Yes, Grandfather.
Your Majesty.
After the princess left
with Fangfeng Bei,
she vanished.
Vanished?
Double the search people.
Look for the princess
all over Dahuang.
Jun Yi.
You go to the Fangfeng's place
and inquire about Fangfeng Bei's news.
- Yes.
Where on earth
has he taken Xiaoyao?
You needn't worry too much.
Xiaoyao was stranded in Dahuang
and lived alone
at a young age.
She knows how to protect herself.
In the current chaotic situation,
her disappearance isn't a bad thing.
You're right.
Sang.
You tell Jin Xuan
to have her spies
suspend their current tasks
and spare no effort
to look for the princess.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
At the wedding,
the princess ran away.
It has never happened.
It has not only offended the Chishui
and Chenrong clans
but also disgraced Haoling.
I implore Your Majesty
to severely punish the Great Princess.
Your Majesty.
Fangfeng Bei abducted the princess,
damaging the reputation
of Haoling royal family.
I earnestly request Your Majesty
to issue a decree
to arrest Fangfeng Bei
and sentence him to death.
- Please severely punish Great Princess
- and sentence Fangfeng Bei to death.
Qin Mang.
Send a metallurgist
from the Jintian Family
to Chishui.
On my behalf,
offer apologies
to Chenrong Yi and Mrs. Chishui
and cancel the engagement.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Now, everyone is talking
about the princess's escape
from the wedding.
A decision must be made promptly
to calm the situation.
Are you suggesting me
to kill my daughter
because of others' gossip?
Your Majesty.
Fangfeng Bei is lowly
and dissolute.
He is already of ill repute.
Abducting the princess
is a capital crime.
In my view...
In my view,
Chishui Fenglong is unromantic
and dull.
On the contrary,
Fangfeng Bei is lively,
bold, and interesting.
Since he dared
to take the princess away,
just let him
marry the princess.
What if Fangfeng Bei refuses
to marry her?
If so, let him
marry into royal family.
Let him make a choice.
After all,
Haoling is a nation of etiquette.
Moreover, Your Majesty is reasonable.
Permission granted.
Fangfeng Bei
ruined Chief Chishui's wedding
and took away the Princess of Haoling.
What will you have him do?
He has made such a grave mistake,
so he must pay for it with his life.
Fangfeng Bei
is dead?
Didn't he tell you?
It was just companionship
and merely a game.
Now that the game is over,
he should die.
An insignificant lowly man.
His death means nothing.
No need to be sad.
Did you take this game seriously
and open your heart to him?
Yes.
I took it seriously,
because Fangfeng Bei is not like you.
You have the power of Nine-Headed Demon,
but you have no feelings.
Fangfeng Bei
is a lowly man with average ability,
but he taught me archery,
played with me,
and shared delicious food with me.
He brought joy to others.
It's natural to feel sad
for such a friend.
Don't worry.
When someone like you dies,
I won't shed a single tear.
Don't flatter yourself.
I've never had any feelings for you.
So I don't worry at all.
Right.
We have no feelings
for each other.
That's for the best.
♪Breaking the riddle of fate♪
♪People are drifting
from place to place♪
♪Destiny of love is going on♪
♪It's hard to run away from it♪
♪I keep out of the world♪
♪Lowering my head to observe the heart♪
♪I'm here for you♪
♪My heart is connected to you♪
♪Under the moon♪
♪You're full of my memory♪
♪You look obstinate and unruly♪
♪Whenever I'm alone♪
♪I'll miss you and only think about you♪
♪I'm willing to spend the rest
of my life with you♪
(Tushan Mansion)
Chief, it's time
to take the medicine.
Put it here.
I'll take it later.
Hu Zhen said
that your health was seriously weakened.
You can't worry too much.
You must take more rest.
Can't you order us
to do it?
You don't have to exhaust yourself.
It will be done very soon.
We can
handle business.
Let Hu Zhen take care of it.
Please take the medicine first.
(Prepare the Chenrong Army's food
and winter clothing within ten days.)
The Chenrong Army?
Previously, the Central Plains clans
were against the King of Xiyan,
so they socialized
with the Chenrong Army
and secretly supported them.
But now, His Majesty
is supported
by the Central Plains clans.
Even the Central Plains clans
have stopped providing assistance.
Why do you get yourself involved?
What if His Majesty
discovers it?
Therefore,
I must do this on my own.
Only then can the plan be flawless.
One person alone
cannot save the situation.
Now everyone is avoiding them.
Relying solely on themselves,
they even cannot buy food and supplies.
Only you are willing
to take the risk to provide support.
I'm not qualified to support others.
Winter is around the corner.
There is a lack of clothing
and food in the mountains.
They will have a hard time.
I really don't know what they are after.
(Loyalty and Righteousness)
Then what are you after?
You've lived
in Qingshui Town for decades.
Don't you plan
to go out for a stroll?
I'm not interested.
The streets are still the same,
but the people have changed.
In that case,
it's better not to see them.
So I won't feel sad.
This is strong liquor
that was specially made.
One cup of it can get you drunk.
No matter how strong it is,
it cannot drown all my sorrows.
Xiang Liu.
You really
are a heartless nine-headed demon.
An ungrateful demon.
You knew me well
from the very beginning.
Since you dare to deal with the demon,
you should have the guts
to bear the consequences.
Yes, indeed.
Our dealings have always been fair.
Even if I could decide again,
I would still transfer the poisonous bug
in your body.
It's all my fault.
Are you willing
to marry Chishui Fenglong?
Why did I agree to marry him if not?
Xiaoyao.
Look into my eyes.
Are you willing
to marry Chishui Fenglong?
No, I'm not.
Are you willing to marry Tushan Jing?
Are you willing
to marry Ye Shiqi?
Yes, I am.
Who do you want to spend your life with?
Tell me.
Who do you most wish
to spend your life with?
It hurts.
Tell me.
I won't ask anymore.
No more questions.
Why?
Because...
Have a good sleep.
After you wake up,
you will forget what just happened.
The liquor can't make me feel better.
It only causes headaches.
Great-grandmother.
Look at the snowman I made.
Great-grandmother, look.
Okay. They are all good!
Come on. Chase me.
Stop.
Did you hear me?
Come here.
You're going to get a hit.
You hurt my waist.
Young lady.
You're the new neighbor
who just moved in, aren't you?
Come.
Sit here.
Have a chat with me.
Tian'er.
You...
How do you know my name?
Ever since
Skinny passed away,
I have not heard that name for so long.
I heard of your name
from the elderly in town before.
They must be
gossiping about me.
I was a prostitute,
unworthy of a good life.
But I spent a lifetime with Skinny
and have had
four sons
and one daughter.
Now I have ten grandsons,
eight granddaughters,
and three great-grandsons.
What about Mu,
Chuntao,
and Pimply?
They passed away.
All of them.
I'm the only one who's alive.
Did Mu live a good life
before he passed away?
Yes.
Mu
had no children,
but
Skinny and Pimply
treated him as their father,
Chuntao
and I
are good daughters-in-law.
When Mu passed away,
he had no regrets.
But he
always thought about Xiaoliu.
Luckily,
Shiqi came back.
Shiqi
spoke privately to Mu.
Well,
I don't know what they talked about.
Anyway,
Mu finally felt relieved
and passed away peacefully.
Shiqi?
Yeah.
Shiqi.
Well,
he used to work at Rejuvenation Hall.
Afterwards,
although he left Qingshui Town,
he would come back to visit us
every few years.
He's like our family.
Just like family.
You're still in the mood to read?
Do you know the Great Princess
of Haoling is missing?
Both Their Majesties looked for her
all over Dahuang but failed to find her.
I'm talking to you.
Your beloved one has gone missing.
She's missing.
Even Their Majesties can't find her.
What do you think I can do?
That's true.
There is nothing you can do.
No.
It's weird.
You look too calm.
This is not you.
How's Fenglong doing?
What do you think?
At the wedding,
his bride ran off with an impudent man.
Nobody can take it,
let alone Fenglong,
who has a smooth life.
He must
feel heartbroken.
You go and console him.
I'm a man.
I can't console a man.
You can do it as the man does.
You mean
I can be his punching bag
to vent his anger?
Are you crazy?
This is what I've gained
from years of doing business.
Come on. You don't have to.
Cheer Fenglong up, right?
I was going to do it anyway.
I'll take him around to clear his mind
and be his sparring partner.
Rest assured, I can do it.
I remember
I haven't raised your casino's rent
for many years.
Understood.
I'll go to Chishui right now.
Fangfeng Bei took away your beloved one.
Fangfeng Bei, remember?
Don't you go to that place
to look for her?
I'm off.
You want me to go look for her?
You fear if I don't look for her,
she'll be with someone else?
Many years ago,
all I wanted was to be with her.
So I took advantage of her soft heart.
Between Xiang Liu and me,
I didn't give her the chance to choose.
But I failed to make her happy.
Now I'm giving her the chance to choose.
That's what I owe her.
♪Looking back on my old days♪
♪I was unruffled
with no sorrow and soreness♪
♪In my chaotic life,
I failed to meet your gaze♪
♪Only emptiness remained♪
♪Enduring all things in my life♪
♪I valued all but indifferent
to wealth and fame♪
♪Basking in the sun,
I couldn't feel your sunlight♪
♪All I feel is a painful heat wave♪
♪All things are dim,
while only your eyes shine bright♪
♪I'll follow my heart
and go to chase the sun far away♪
♪Everything seems sad,
while only your brows raise in delight♪
♪I'm waiting for you
to enjoy the scenery at night♪
♪You came with wind and rain,
while left with my four seasons♪
♪All is bleak without you♪
♪It began like a tornado,
and went away leaving only dust♪
♪Without you,
even the most beautiful world is a mess♪