=Lost You Forever S1=
=Episode 7=
Sorry about that.
Goodbye and take care.
I was in a hurry, so I forgot the gift.
I'll have Sang deliver it later.
Mr. Xuan, you could save the courtesy.
It's nothing.
I am annoyed every time I see you.
If it weren't for my brother,
I would order to lash you.
If it weren't for your brother,
I would slap you.
Mr. Xuan, is there anything else?
Where's Ye Shiqi?
He's always with you, but he's not here.
I asked him
to cook more dishes in the kitchen.
He must be busy now.
Alright, I'll take my leave.
Take care.
Back in the spring six years ago,
you were lying in that bush.
It's been over six years.
You left the banquet abruptly just now,
so Xuan is suspicious of you.
He's sure to start investigating you.
Actually, you and Nian
are the same type of person.
Looking down from on high,
and overlooking all living beings.
But when I see Nian in that state,
I really want to slap her.
But when I see you, I...
What do you want?
I want to pull you down to earth.
Don't wipe it.
Come here.
He's not going anywhere.
Say what you want right here.
Are you coming over by yourself,
or you want me to come to you?
I...
Xiaoliu,
step back.
We're all friends here.
We're all friends.
You must know there's a happy event
at Rejuvenation Hall today,
so you brought a gift, right?
Shiqi.
Get on.
Alright.
Xiaoliu.
Don't worry, Shiqi. I'm fine.
You go home. I'll be back soon.
Go home.
I'm coming.
Go home, Shiqi.
Go home.
Chubby!
Chubby, you crazy bird, stop it.
Are you in a bad mood today?
Don't think I don't know.
You must be upset.
Whenever you're upset,
you would torment me for fun.
That crazy bird nearly got me killed.
Why is your spirit power so low?
I practiced hard.
Originally, my spirit power was not low
but rather high among my peers.
It's all because of that stupid fox.
In case my spirit power
didn't go in vain,
he used medicine to disable me,
which made my spirit power
go into my vessels little by little,
making it easier for him to eat me.
I heard that
the pain of dispersing one's power
is like bones being drilled
and marrow extracted.
It seems that my forty lashes
were too light for you.
I'll have to find other torture tools.
Do you think it gets smoother
the more you practice, like singing?
It's precisely because
I suffered so much back then
that I'm really afraid of pain now,
more than most people.
How did you endure
those thirty years in the cage?
In the beginning,
I fought against the fox.
I always provoked him.
But later, I got scared
after being tortured,
so I didn't dare to do that anymore.
In the end,
I stayed silent and uncooperative,
even trying to end my own life.
Even someone like you would seek death?
Yes.
But I never managed to die.
Later on,
I went from wanting to kill myself
to wanting to kill him.
Our mentality is really strange.
You can tell whether
you're happy or not,
or painful or not
by comparing yourself with others.
Do you need me to
delve deeper into my miserable past?
I could exaggerate it a bit.
I'm sure you would think
there would be no other miseries.
You look quite different tonight.
Did something unpleasant happen?
You lived by the water
when you were a child?
(Gourd Lake)
So beautiful.
Life is precious
as long as we can enjoy such views.
Even the rarest scenery would become
dull if being seen too much.
It will only be meaningful
if there's someone by my side.
Sceneries are dead.
Only meanings from people
will bring them alive.
Why are you in a bad mood?
The Central Plains are now stable.
The King of Xiyan will
eventually round up Hong Jiang.
The trend of the world is irreversible.
It's not something
an individual can stop.
Actually, you're just a demon,
a despised nine-headed demon.
For the arrogant deities in Chenrong,
you're probably less than nothing
in their eyes.
Why are you worrying about Chenrong?
What can you gain
from following Hong Jiang?
In your view, what should I do?
If you like power, you might as well
defect from Hong Jiang
to the King of Xiyan.
I was wrong.
It's okay. I'm thick-skinned.
Xiaoliu!
Are you alright?
A bowl of hot soup goes down,
and all my internal organs
are comfortable now.
You shouldn't spoil me like this.
What if I get used to your care,
but then you leave?
What should I do then?
I won't leave.
People who make promises are countless,
but those who keep them
are hard to find.
Sleep tight.
Just ignore Xiang Liu.
I'll deal with him in the future.
Don't worry. I've already
thought of a way to deal with him.
(Chenrong Army Base Camp)
Mr. Xiang.
Somebody!
Another one fainted.
Quick, send him away.
What's going on?
Mr. Xiang,
recently in the camp,
many people got sick from malaria.
Why is there a carriage?
Xiaoliu, come up. Let's have a look.
The young lady from a big family
is pretty indeed.
(Yu Mansion)
Xiaoliu, isn't that Mr. Yu?
Yes, it's him.
Xiaoliu, I'm not mistaken, am I?
The half king of Qingshui Town,
Mr. Yu, also has to salute this lady.
The entire West River Street,
including your pharmacy and my restaurant,
belongs to Mr. Yu.
You're not mistaken.
It seems we have an honored guest
in Qingshui Town.
Skinny.
Have you remembered the rhymes
I taught you to distinguish herbs?
Yes.
I'll give you a test.
Okay.
Shiqi.
Go ahead.
What is this?
White peony root.
Xiaoliu, why did you hit me?
Just hitting your pig-like head.
White peony root? You idiot.
Largehead atractylode for the spleen and qi,
and white peony root for blood and menstruation.
Why can't you remember?
Shiqi has already
distinguished all the herbs
within less than six months.
And you? It's been so many years,
and you still can't remember.
It's been years,
You just can't remember, right?
Xiaoliu.
Drink some water.
Let me check.
Skinny,
if I teach you again, can you remember?
Largehead atractylode is for blood
and menstruation,
eliminating dampness and diuresis,
arresting sweating
and preventing miscarriage.
Remember?
Can you remember?
Are you able to remember?
Something's wrong!
What happened?
I-I heard
Mr. Yu wants to take back the shops
near the river for other uses.
Our Rejuvenation Hall is by the river,
so it will also be taken back.
What should we do, Xiaoliu?
When we rented this place,
it was just a wasteland.
Xiaoliu and I
put in so much effort
to make it what it is now.
Even if Yu Xin
is half king of Qingshui Town,
he shouldn't be so overbearing.
Taking it back at will?
I like being near the water.
I don't want to move.
It seems it's time to meet
the king of Qingshui Town.
I'll go with you.
Okay.
(Yu Mansion)
Mr. Yu.
Save the courtesy.
Just speak up.
I heard you wanted to take back
the shops by the river.
That's right.
It includes Rejuvenation Hall.
You intend to rent it out again
after taking it back, right?
Whomever you rent to is the same.
Why not continue renting to us?
Regarding the rent, it's negotiable.
We can pay more.
(Mr. Yu)
Let alone for this one shop,
even the rent for all the shops
on the entire street
is nothing.
Can't we negotiate?
After you take it back,
you can't just leave it idle.
It needs to be used.
You've been in Qingshui Town
for over twenty years, right?
To be honest,
I'm just a servant,
merely running errands.
My master is extremely wealthy.
Let alone for this one shop,
even if the entire Qingshui Town is idle,
it won't have any harm.
I have to go.
I won't keep you any longer.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Miss Jing Ye.
Stop!
Master.
They all say you're dead,
but we don't believe it.
It's been ten years.
Heaven has pity on us.
I finally found you.
Why don't you talk, Master?
I am Jing Ye.
Did you forget?
And Lan Xiang.
You once joked that our names
together sound like
"the fragrance of
an orchid in the night."
Yu Xin, send a message to the Madam now.
Tell her we've found the junior master.
Yes.
Master,
have you even forgotten the Madam?
Take your time with
your family affairs. I will leave first.
Master.
Xiaoliu, time to eat.
Xiaoliu, did Mr. Yu agree to
let us continue renting here?
I can't eat anymore.
I can't have it, either.
I've been living here
for more than twenty years.
I can't bear to leave.
Don't worry. We can rent
for as long as we want.
Even if we don't pay the rent,
no one dares to take it back.
Really? You convinced Mr. Yu?
Kind of.
Thank God.
That's great. Let's eat.
Come on. Let's eat.
Mu, don't worry.
I will definitely
stay with you all the time
and take care of you until you die.
You have a short life.
I'm sure I can accompany you to death.
I won't let you be lonely and helpless,
but I don't know
who will be with me when I die.
Bad boy, you're talking nonsense again.
Where's Shiqi, Xiaoliu?
Why hasn't Shiqi come back yet?
He's not coming back.
We don't need to
prepare meals for him anymore.
He's not coming back? Where did he go?
He's staying in Mr. Yu house.
Really?
He's working for Mr. Yu now?
Mr. Yu is the one
who pays the most in Qingshui Town.
If Shiqi can live a decent life there,
we will benefit too.
So many good things happened today.
Let's add dishes to celebrate tonight.
Okay, I'll go buy groceries later.
I'll go buy the wine.
Enjoy the meal.
I'm full.
Why are you still wearing this?
Your clothes are scented?
I don't like the smell.
From now on, no more scent.
You should go home now,
in case your family worry.
I...
I still want to be Ye Shiqi.
There is no Ye Shiqi in this world.
My Lord, I've known Ye Shiqi's identity.
(Upon investigation, Ye Shiqi is Tushan Jing,
second son of Tushan Family)
It's him.
Xiaoliu, let me do it.
Thank you.
What for? It's my duty.
Xiaoliu, were you waiting for someone?
No.
I must have seen it wrong.
When you turned your head and saw me,
you seemed a little disappointed.
So I thought
you were waiting for someone.
Xiaoliu, why don't you go home first?
I'll finish washing soon.
Are you used to living here these days?
Ever since I came to Rejuvenation Hall,
I've felt settled like never before.
I can sleep till daybreak.
Xiaoliu,
thank you for helping me and Skinny
to get together and for giving me a family.
Aren't you worried about the future at all?
Rather than regret in the future,
you'd better stay away now.
As long as your heart
becomes cold and hard,
the pain will be less.
Once the heart becomes hard and cold,
it can indeed block out pain,
but it will also block out joy.
What's wrong, Xiaoliu?
Your words inspired me.
Thank you, Tian'er.
You're welcome.
I can't feel his pulse. He's dying.
Mr. Xiang, malaria is toxic
and hard to prevent.
The number of patients
is increasing day by day.
We urgently need
a large amount of medicinal materials,
but...
I will figure it out.
List out the needed medicinal materials.
Yes, I will write it down immediately.
There's no scent on your clothes.
You don't like it.
The herbal medicine made by me. Wear it.
What? Don't you like it?
Never mind.
You can keep using the scent.
How many maids did you have before?
Two.
How much money do you actually have?
I...
I haven't counted.
Did your previous issue happen
because of money?
Yes.
Does Jing Ye look better or Lan Xiang?
Do you still remember the herbs
I told you about before?
I do.
Those herbs seem ordinary,
but by adding a little thing,
you can take down
either deities or demons.
You're not that nine-headed demon.
You don't have nine lives.
Don't eat things randomly.
Okay.
So does Lan Xiang
look better or Jing Ye?
The intimate people
would be the most unreliable.
Look out for yourself.
Okay.
Don't take action,
enduring and pretending to be dumb.
Or if you have to,
do it decisively and completely.
Never be soft-hearted.
If you really can't beat them down,
you can come back
and help me grow medicine.
Anyway, you won't starve.
Okay.
My Lord,
many people in Chenrong Army
got sick from malaria and lack medicine.
Xiang Liu is trying
to gather medicinal materials.
If he can't control the disease,
it will inevitably
lower the army's morale.
It is the time
to force the Chenrong Army to surrender.
Pass the order.
Buy up the main medicines
Xiang Liu needs,
so they have no medicine to use.
When they have nowhere to go,
take the opportunity
to lure them to surrender.
Yes.
However...
Tell me.
My Lord,
the men of the Fifth and Seventh Kings
have been active lately.
If we act now,
I'm afraid the credit
will be taken by your uncles,
which will benefit them but not you.
If they can surrender earlier,
the world can be peaceful sooner.
How can I give up for personal gain?
Even if I want the throne, I can't leave
the interests of the people behind.
I am impressed
that you care for the entire world.
Go. Be cautious.
Yes.
As you all know,
there are three royal families
and four noble families in Dahuang.
Today, I want to talk about
one of the four noble families,
the richest family in Dahuang,
the Tushan Family.
The Tushan Family are descendants
of the nine-tailed deity fox.
They have been running businesses
for generations.
Their businesses
are throughout the entire Dahuang.
The Qingqiu Hill
where the Tushan Family live
is built with jade tiles
and gold bricks,
as well as various exotic animals
and monsters in the garden.
Although the Family is not a royal one,
it is like a royal family.
Their offspring are continuous,
and their influence is deeply rooted.
Even the two emperors
have to show them some respect.
Don't be envious, everyone.
After all, wealth
is like a wisp of smoke.
Anyway, you can't wish for it
if Heaven doesn't bestow it to you.
Xiaoliu, come sit here.
Mr. Xuan.
Thanks.
The Tushan Family is large
and has a big business,
but their descendants are not many now.
This generation's direct line
only has a pair of brothers.
Known as Master Qingqiu,
the junior master of the Tushan Family
is intelligent, handsome,
and proficient in zither, chess,
calligraphy and painting.
Not only is he elegant and witty,
but he is also good at
running businesses.
So all the girls in Dahuang
call Master Qingqiu
the man of their dreams.
Xiaoliu.
You didn't recognize him in new clothes?
This roasted ginkgo seed
is really delicious,
but it's a bit troublesome to peel.
Try it.
- Having this.
- (The junior master of the Tushan Family)
is not only accomplished
in both literature and martial arts,
but his tactics
are also quite remarkable.
So much so that
in Qingqiu Hill and even Dahuang,
everyone only knows the junior master,
but not the senior master.
As the saying goes,
from the same family
but with different destinies.
Sit, please sit.
What are you waiting for? Sit.
Master Qingqiu
is famous all over the world.
He might be the next leader
of the Tushan Family.
Across the whole world,
the number of young ladies
from prominent families
who want to marry him
is simply countless.
The Lady of Tushan
had been selecting for a long time,
and finally decided on
Miss Fangfeng for the junior master.
Miss Fangfeng
traveled around with her father
and brothers since she was a child.
She is unlike ordinary girls.
Not only was she born
as beautiful as a blooming flower,
but she also
has excellent archery skills.
Unfortunately,
during the wedding preparation,
the junior master was seriously ill.
The wedding had to be canceled.
The lovers failed to get married.
Over these years,
the junior master
has been healing in seclusion.
The power of the family
has changed hands to the senior master.
This is exactly the turning of fate
and the unpredictability of destiny.
Once the trend changes,
fortune is beyond one's control.
What's your name?
Next time we meet,
it wouldn't be appropriate
to pretend not to know you.
But even if you lent me
ten times the courage,
I wouldn't dare to call you Shiqi.
Even if you don't mind,
your wife would shoot me with an arrow.
Even if you don't tell me, I'll hear it
from someone else sooner or later.
Tushan Jing.
How do you write it?
What's the name
of your soon-to-be bride?
Six years.
I've taken you in for six years.
You exempt me from six years of rent.
From now on, we owe each other nothing.
Master Qingqiu?
I'll have to call you that
from now on, right?
Look, Xiaoliu saved you,
but you didn't even
reveal your true identity to him.
No wonder Xiaoliu is angry.
Wait until Xiaoliu calms down
and then sincerely apologize to him.
I'll take my leave.
♪Looking back on my old days♪
♪I was unruffled
with no sorrow and soreness♪
♪In my chaotic life,
I failed to meet your gaze♪
♪Only emptiness remained♪
♪Enduring all things in my life♪
♪I valued all but indifferent
to wealth and fame♪
♪Basking in the sun,
I couldn't feel your sunlight♪
♪Only heatwaves retained♪
♪All things are dim,
while only your eyes shine bright♪
♪I'll follow my heart
and go to chase the sun far away♪
♪Everything seems sad,
while only your brows raise in delight♪
♪I'm waiting for you
to enjoy the scenery at night♪
♪You came with wind and rain,
while left with my four seasons♪
♪Without you,
even the best scenery is dull♪
♪It began like a tornado,
and went away leaving only dust♪
♪Without you,
even the most beautiful world is a mess♪