=Lost You Forever S1=
=Episode 5=
Actually, I prefer to eat mortals.
Someone like you is just enough
for each of my heads to take a bite.
You have little spirit power,
but your body is a treasure.
You...
You really
eat people?
Dare to talk nonsense now?
No,
no,
no.
Do you want me to come over?
No,
no.
Xiaoliu.
I'm leaving.
Xiaoliu, are you...?
Bad bird,
you wait and see!
You're still up?
It's so late.
Go to sleep early
and take care of your body.
The secret report said you wanted
to see me about something important.
What exactly is so urgent?
Xiang Liu?
Are you looking for him?
Who sent you?
Catch him alive.
Xiaoliu, come quickly.
Shiqi has been busy all morning,
making all your favorite dishes.
Thank you for your hard work.
Let's eat.
These are all your favorites.
Eat more.
Thank you, Xiaoliu.
Where's Mu?
He still refuses to go out?
Xiaoliu, let's go and smash the winery
of that wretched man and woman.
With your strength,
you're going to smash their winery?
You'd be thrown out
before you reach the door.
I don't care.
Anyway, I can't put up with this.
This matter can't be left like this.
In this world, as long as you are alive,
you must swallow your anger
even if it's not fair.
You must concede
even if you are unwilling.
Let me tell you.
Even those princes
and princesses live the same way.
It sounds like you're telling the truth.
You're not them.
How do you know how they live?
You brat. I ought to teach you a lesson.
Is it right?
Xiaoliu,
I heard what you said.
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
Master,
the worker from Mr. Yu's store said
this stuff was transported from Haoling.
It's very valuable.
In the future, one basket can exchange
for ten bottles of your tiger penis wine.
Okay. Go on with your work.
Xiaoliu, your visit graces our humble shop.
Sorry for the lack of reception.
What would you like?
Give me a pot
of your sweet wine here.
Alright.
Osmanthus wine.
It's sweet and smooth.
This is so sour.
Are you selling vinegar?
Forget it.
Give me a pot of
the strongest wine you have here.
Superior Shao Dao Zi.
Xiaoliu, have a taste.
This is your strongest wine?
It's diluted, isn't it?
It's so bland.
You're deliberately making trouble.
If you're still not satisfied,
I'll get you another drink.
I see you sell
something called tiger penis wine.
The one they're drinking.
Get me a jug of that to taste.
The taste of this wine is off.
I deal with a variety
of medicinal herbs year-round,
and I can tell
authenticity just by smell.
If someone drinks your tiger penis wine,
far from showing their masculinity,
I'm afraid they'd never
have an erection again.
Sir, don't listen to his nonsense.
Please don't go.
Sir.
Master,
the lady said she
has no appetite and cannot eat.
Take it to Nian.
These lychees are quite fresh.
Let me try.
Xiaoliu, my sister has been having
a poor appetite lately,
so I specially found
some fruits she likes for her.
Xiaoliu, please stop teasing me.
You really spoil your sister.
I'm sorry for the offense last time.
I apologize to you.
Let your sister apologize to Mu.
My sister is stubborn.
I'll apologize to Mu instead.
What a good brother,
willing to bend his head
rather than letting his sister suffer.
As her elder brother,
I should take responsibility.
I heard the mulberry wine here
is very good.
Mulberry wine is
the signature wine of our shop.
Isn't it because
your sister loves this wine
that you can make it so well?
Send a few jars of
the best mulberry wine
to the Rejuvenation Hall
and apologize to Mu.
If Mu accepts it,
from then on,
I won't come to your shop
to taste wine anymore.
Let's go.
Alright, let's go.
Where is Mr. Xuan going
with so much wine?
It's for the Rejuvenation Hall,
and he is going to apologize to Mu.
My sister offended you the other day.
I apologize on her behalf
with the wine.
Alright.
Isn't the wine for me?
What's the meaning
of you drinking it all yourself?
You're indeed generous, Mr. Xuan.
Today,
I accept you as my brother.
My brother's sister is my sister.
Being embarrassed
by my own sister is nothing.
Let's forget about this.
No one needs to mention it anymore.
How can we not drink
when we do such a big thing
as acknowledging a brother?
Come on.
Let's drink together.
Today we won't go home
until we're drunk.
Cheers.
This guy is quite a character.
He's capable of humbling
himself to coax his sister
and also shows manly spirit
when forming brotherhood with others.
Are you really not drinking anymore?
I should
go back.
Then the two of us
will drink again next time.
Alright.
We'll drink next time.
I'll keep the wine.
I'm leaving.
Master, watch your step.
Watch out.
Slow down.
There's no one to assist me.
You had a good time,
but now I'm left to deal with the mess.
Let me do it. You rest.
I dare not.
Today it's my turn to wash dishes.
How can I let you help me?
Are you still angry?
Angry?
What's there to be angry about?
Mu already buddies up with him.
Why should I still be angry with him?
You're angry with me.
You don't talk to me.
I talk to you every day.
Aren't I
talking to you right now?
I want to hear you talk as before.
As before?
What's the difference
between before and now?
Aren't I treating you
the same as Pimply and Skinny?
Xiaoliu,
I'm sorry.
Master, be careful.
Are you alright?
With your status,
why stoop down
to apologize to a commoner?
Qingshui Town is full of hidden talents.
An unknown physician like Wen Xiaoliu
actually managed
to use poison to defeat Haitang.
Who knows how many other methods he has?
If we were to really confront him,
it would only lead to more trouble
such as his snooping and poisoning.
We have important things to do,
best not to complicate matters.
With the princess around,
how can there be no trouble?
Nian is just bored,
looking for some fun.
It's no big deal.
Why hasn't Jun Yi come back yet?
Not yet.
Did something happen?
Abracadabra.
I hope the Nine-Headed Demon
chokes to death while eating,
drowns while drinking
and falls to death while walking.
I didn't curse you.
You just cursed me?
No.
Don't hit my face.
Are you scared?
Yes.
Lying again.
That day by the lake,
you already knew the secret of my body.
I originally thought
you would eat me
to increase your spirit power,
but I didn't expect you to show mercy.
You just drank
a few mouthfuls of my blood.
Naturally, I'm not afraid.
Now I only drink
a few mouthfuls of your blood.
Who knows which winter
I will use your flesh as a tonic
to nourish myself?
I'm completely yours now.
You can do whatever you want.
Lying again.
You're hurt?
Who is the person
that is so capable to hurt you?
You're sleeping on my bed.
Where should I sleep?
Xiang Liu.
Nine-Headed Demon.
What should I draw for you?
When healing your wounds
with internal energy,
you can't lose focus.
A minor mistake
will lead to more injury.
A serious one will
destroy all your spirit power,
and your consciousness will be confused.
How the tables have turned on you!
Focus on healing.
Don't be disturbed by me.
These two strands of hair.
Bad.
Too ugly.
What should I draw for you?
Let me draw a turtle for you.
No, not a turtle.
I got it.
You look great!
Let me show you.
Do you look great?
Don't be angry.
Let me count.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight, nine.
I'm still very curious.
What do your nine heads
look like?
When will you
let me see your true form?
I will eat you.
Want to eat me?
No problem with that.
As long as you don't
mind me being dirty,
you can eat me.
Come on. There you go.
Looks like you're almost done.
Then I'll leave now.
I will disappear for a few days.
During these days, don't look for me.
When you start to appreciate
the goodness I have shown you,
I'll come back.
Shiqi,
come.
Xiaoliu.
Come here.
Xiang Liu is a bit tired.
He's sleeping in the room.
You keep an eye on this door.
Don't let anyone in.
After Xiang Liu wakes up,
he will leave naturally.
I have something to do,
so I'll leave now.
Tell Mu not to look for me.
This place is really nice.
Safe and sound,
with good wine to accompany.
However smart
Xiang Liu is,
he will never guess that I hide here.
I am really amazing.
It's my uselessness.
Although Xiang Liu
was injured this time,
the helpers I brought
were all killed by him.
Only I escaped.
I'm worried that
it has exposed our tracks.
If Xiang Liu investigates,
it will threaten your safety.
Xiang Liu is indeed a dangerous person.
Since he can't be used by me,
we have to strike first.
Take advantage of his severe injury
and immediately dispatch
people to find him.
We must fully remove
the threat to avoid trouble later.
Yes. I will obey the order.
(The Nine-Headed Demon's life)
(is really valuable.)
(There are his enemies everywhere.)
(Will he escape safely)
(this time?)
Your Lordship, a spy once found traces
of a white eagle nearby.
Xiang Liu is likely to hide here.
Listen to me.
Search carefully house by house.
Don't miss any clues.
- Yes.
Didn't you just change the bedding
for Xiaoliu yesterday?
Why are you changing it again?
Fussy man.
Pointless fussing.
Remember to close the door.
Be careful. It's hot.
Mr. Xuan,
I am really sorry.
I'm starving,
and I followed the aroma and came in.
I'm hungry, too.
A chance meeting
is better than a planned one.
How about having a meal with me?
Okay, yes.
This is freshly brewed wine,
just taken out of the wine cellar.
Have a taste.
Thank you, Mr. Xuan.
(Does he discover)
(that I was hiding in his wine cellar?)
(Is he planning to
poison me to silence me?)
Mr. Xuan,
what are you planning to do?
Steamed chicken.
Taste it.
Great cooking.
Are these dishes all made by Nian?
She only knows how to eat food
and doesn't know how to cook.
Unexpectedly,
you can both make wine and cook.
Nian is really fortunate.
She calls me brother.
Isn't it natural for me
to take care of her?
How come I haven't seen her lately?
You want to see her?
No.
I was just asking.
I had her embroider something for me,
and she's been doing it
in the room recently.
No wonder she hasn't been out
causing trouble.
Nothing.
I mean, Mr. Xuan, you really are
great at teaching your sister.
If Nian makes more offenses
in the future,
Xiaoliu, could you please be
a bit lenient considering she's a girl?
(In the future?)
(He said "future".)
(So he's not going to kill me today?)
No problem.
Rest assured.
The next time I see her,
I will definitely accommodate her.
Thank you for your generosity.
You're really a good brother.
Being your sister is really fortunate.
Actually, I'm not a good brother.
Mr. Xuan,
I toast you.
Thank you for your hospitality today.
It's getting late,
so I'll take my leave now
and let you be.
Feel free to visit in the future.
Don't worry,
I'm very familiar with this place.
No need to see me out.
I was wrong.
I was really wrong.
I won't do it again.
Aren't I back now?
My body and I are both yours now.
I promise
I will clean myself up
thoroughly from now on,
and you can come and eat me anytime.
Please forgive me this time,
okay?
Just this once.
Why is it you?
Why are you in my room?
I'm sorry.
I let you down.
That's not what I meant.
I mistook you for someone else.
I'm sorry for my harsh tone just now.
Don't take it to heart.
You can come into my room.
It's my fault.
Want to eat me?
It's fine with me.
As long as you don't
mind me being dirty.
Come on. There you go.
Wen Xiaoliu,
we'll settle this account slowly.
We have all the time in the world.
My Lord, we received a message
from the Chenrong Army's remnants.
Xiang Liu has somehow healed his wounds.
This quickly?
Shall we attempt another assassination?
We've missed
the best opportunity to kill him.
For now, let's hold our forces.
Instruct our insiders to be careful
and not to arouse his suspicions.
Yes, I understand.
Why did you bring a pig's head home?
What if it scares the lady?
Haitang, take the pig's head
to the kitchen.
Don't let Nian see it.
Yes.
I just learned from Butcher Gao
that Wen Xiaoliu has been
in this town for decades,
even longer than Butcher Gao.
Mu is a deserter from Xiyan
who refused to fight.
Skinny and Pimply are orphans
he and Wen Xiaoliu picked up.
Wen Xiaoliu is timid and greedy
on normal days,
but he is gentle
and gets along well with his neighbors.
He hasn't committed any major crimes.
It sounds like
there's nothing suspicious.
He is simply an ordinary physician.
(Wen Xiaoliu)
Look at me.
You look like just a wine seller.
Flawless.
Yes, flawless.
It's highly likely
he's hiding something deep.
Have Jun Yi investigate further.
That makes sense.
Perhaps, Wen Xiaoliu is like you.
He is not what he seems.
Skinny.
What's up, Xiaoliu?
Has the wisteria at the foot
of the mountain bloomed yet?
I'm busy working.
I don't have the time
to care about wildflowers or grass.
The flowers have bloomed.
Why are you asking, Xiaoliu?
Nothing. Just asking.
Go back to work.
Xiaoliu, eat it while it's hot.
Wisteria flower egg pancake.
You made this?
Ye Shiqi,
you always know
what I'm thinking, don't you?
But now,
I don't want to eat this pancake.
There won't be a second time.
What did you say?
No matter what happens,
I will never let you
be unable to find me
when you need someone to lean on,
never again.
Xiaoliu.
Hurry.
Come with me to see.
See what?
You'll know when you see it.
Hurry.
Let's go together.
♪Looking back on my old days♪
♪I was unruffled
with no sorrow and soreness♪
♪In my chaotic life,
I failed to meet your gaze♪
♪Only emptiness remained♪
♪Enduring all things in my life♪
♪I valued all but indifferent
to wealth and fame♪
♪Basking in the sun,
I couldn't feel your sunlight♪
♪Only heatwaves retained♪
♪All things are dim,
while only your eyes shine bright♪
♪I'll follow my heart
and go to chase the sun far away♪
♪Everything seems sad,
while only your brows raise in delight♪
♪I'm waiting for you
to enjoy the scenery at night♪
♪You came with wind and rain,
while left with my four seasons♪
♪Without you,
even the best scenery is dull♪
♪It began like a tornado,
and went away leaving only dust♪
♪Without you,
even the most beautiful world is a mess♪