=Lost You Forever S2=
=Episode 1=
(Previously)
Seven bunny babies.
The mother and the kids are fine.
Whoever can't have a baby
(Rejuvenation Hall)
come to my Rejuvenation Hall
and look for me, Wen Xiaoliu.
It's been 300 years.
Cang Xuan, swing higher.
Higher.
Alright.
I've traveled through Dahuang
and searched everywhere
in Haoling and Xiyan,
but I have no news of her.
Xiaoyao must think
that her brother is useless, right?
Beggar.
Starting today,
you'll be Ye Shiqi.
A physician from Qingshui Town
could be so powerful.
Do you have wives
or concubines who are infertile?
Who
are you exactly?
I am just an abandoned person.
Mother.
When you miss me,
take it out and look at it.
I couldn't protect myself,
had no one to rely on,
and had nowhere to go.
Get the most experienced interrogator.
Just leave Wen Xiaoliu alive.
I swear.
- We stand by each other.
- Forever and ever.
- We shall trust
- and look after each other.
- Never go back on my word.
Cang Xuan.
You are descendants of great families.
Why did you come
and suffer in Qingshui Town?
For my sister.
I will bring you back
from Mount Jade as soon as possible.
Xiaoyao.
Six years.
I've taken you in for six years.
You exempt me from six years of rent.
From now on,
we owe each other nothing.
Even the rarest scenery would
be dull if it was seen too often.
It will only be meaningful
if someone is with me.
Life is precious as long as we can
enjoy such views.
The love poisonous bug
not only wants your life
but also your heart.
You may have nine lives,
but you only
have one heart.
Once you give your heart,
you can never take it back.
Cang Xuan.
Now that you're back,
I'm not alone anymore.
I decided to be the Princess of Haoling.
Since you chose
to return to Xiyan Mountain,
despite
the trials and tribulations ahead,
I'll help you fulfill your dreams
by your side.
Cang Xuan.
Let's
go home together.
What if I fall in love with you
at first sight?
I want you to remember me.
Fang
Feng
Bei.
Remember.
Don't move!
Xiaoyao, move away!
You cannot die.
We're still alive.
Why not quit being a princess
and wander around with me?
Alright.
If you give up everything,
I'll go with you.
I'm afraid of men
like you and my father.
Because in your hearts,
there is always
something more important
than your women.
We are not suitable to be husbands.
In my lifetime,
I hope to see
a real prosperous empire
that leaves a grand legacy
throughout history.
In 15 years,
don't open up your heart to another man.
Even if I'm not Tushan Jing,
I can still be Ye Shiqi.
The one with nothing?
Yes.
When I saved him,
he had nothing.
So I don't mind
if he becomes nothing again.
Don't break her heart.
If that day really comes,
kill me.
Miss Fangfeng.
You're pregnant.
I don't hate you.
But between you and me,
the relationship ends here.
We are strangers now.
Xiaoyao.
No matter what the future holds,
I will always stay by your side.
When you escaped from the death arena,
if it'd been me who saved you,
how great that would be.
Xiaoyao.
Let's get married.
Do you want to marry him?
He
swore that he would be good to me
and only have one wife
for his entire life.
Actually, that's all
a woman wants.
(Previously)
(Daming Hall, Zijin Palace)
After all these years,
we finally
get to drink so carefree.
Taking over by force
was an obvious shortcut.
Yet you choose not to make a move.
Were you certain that Grandfather
would choose you?
Of course not.
I knew
(Xiyan Cang Xuan)
if Grandfather
made Deyan the Crown Prince,
I would face
worse consequences
if I made a move then.
But I took a bet.
(Haoling Jiuyao)
I bet that Grandfather knew
what I wanted Xiyan to be like.
But what if he didn't?
There are many paths.
But there's only one throne.
Even if I'm bathed in blood
with my life at risk,
I have to go for it.
You and Grandfather
really know each other.
He bet you wouldn't stage a coup.
You bet he would pass the throne to you.
This time,
both of you won.
I am very grateful
not just because he gave me the throne.
I'm grateful because
he knows what kind of king I want to be.
Take it back.
I was moved by what you told me
last night.
But this Ruomu flower
was given to you
by Fourth Aunt before she passed away.
She wanted you
to give it to the girl you love.
I dare not accept it.
You'd better keep it.
Xiaoyao, I...
I...
What?
Since when do we keep secrets?
I...
I am very...
Grateful to you.
We are in it together.
You're grateful?
Do you want a beating?
Your wish has finally been fulfilled.
Why do I feel that
you're not so happy?
Yeah.
I find it strange too.
We have obviously
reached the top.
Yet I don't feel so happy.
It feels like there's a long way to go.
The burden we shoulder
hasn't been removed.
It has grown even heavier.
Yeah.
You are the King of Xiyan now,
the ruler of a nation.
You are not just Cang Xuan anymore.
The burden you carry
is surely heavier now.
I only want to protect my family
and not be powerless when faced with
life and death.
That's why I wanted
to be the King of Xiyan.
♪All is bleak without you♪
♪It began like a tornado♪
I know.
♪And went away leaving only dust♪
♪Without you♪
♪Even the most beautiful world♪
♪Is a mess♪
(Chenrong Mansion, Zhiyi City)
Miss.
Check and see if
you like these fabrics.
His Majesty has been enthroned.
(Chenrong Xinyue)
You will soon become
the Queen of Xiyan.
So I'm thinking,
we should have the weavers
make some new clothes
that fit your status
to not be
in a rush when the time comes.
You are very thoughtful.
It's my job to be considerate
to you, Miss.
Have you sent the gifts
to Chenrong Mountain as I told you to?
Did His Majesty reply?
The gifts have arrived.
But His Majesty hasn't replied.
His Majesty must be occupied
by the state affairs.
He will want to see me
once he's done.
You're right, Miss.
It must be so.
Let me write him another letter.
I'm worried that he will be
neglecting his health.
Haitang.
Pack all those
spiritual medicines here.
I'll take them
as gifts to Xuan.
Understood.
Nian.
Father.
Are you going to
empty my storeroom?
(Haoling Yi)
How can I empty the storeroom
of the wealthiest man in the world?
I even think
(King of Haoling, Ru Shou)
it's not enough.
Why don't you
add a few more things
as my gifts to Xuan
to congratulate him?
Alright.
I'll hand-pick them.
Step aside.
She's even packing nuts for him.
A grown girl is bound to leave home.
I mean,
time has changed.
Cang Xuan is now the King of Xiyan.
If the Second Princess
runs off there,
people may have opinions.
Let her be.
With Xiaoyao there,
nothing can go wrong.
That's right, Your Majesty.
It's not your problem if the princess
goes to Chenrong Mountain.
It's someone else's problem.
How many days has it been
since we sent the letter?
It's been
seven days.
And His Majesty hasn't replied?
No.
Miss Shen
is truly blessed.
Everyone thought that
her marriage to His Majesty
was a mistake.
But His Majesty ascended the throne
and became the King of Xiyan.
Just for the sake of
all the hardships they've been through,
Miss Shen could
become the Queen of Xiyan.
Stop calling her "Miss Shen".
Now,
she is the consort of the King.
Even Miss Xinyue has to pay respects
and greet her accordingly.
Who allowed you to gossip here?
Miss.
Go away.
- Yes.
Miss.
His Majesty needs
a queen by his side.
All the major clans of Xiyan,
let alone the ones
in the Central Plains,
intend to send someone to His Majesty.
You should make plans early.
Which lady from any major clan
can be more distinguished
than me?
Those women are not worth concern.
But what about the Princess
from Wushen Mountain
who clings to His Majesty?
Haoling Yi.
(Following His Majesty's sacred decree,)
(the populations and land ownership)
(throughout the Central Plains)
have been fully tallied
and documented.
Please take a look.
(Xiyan Deyan, Xiyan Yuyang)
Your Majesty,
(Chief of Huhe)
I have something to report.
Speak.
You've stayed in the Central Plains
since your ascension.
(Chishui Fenglong, Chenrong Yi)
This place may be prosperous,
but Xiyan Town is the capital.
Your Majesty,
please return to Xiyan Town.
Seconded.
- Please return to Xiyan Town.
(Chief of Shangyang)
Your Majesty,
Xiyan Town is the capital of Xiyan.
But your decrees are sent
from Chenrong Mountain
after your enthronement.
It's inappropriate to go on like this.
Your Majesty,
please relocate the capital to Zhiyi.
Your Majesty.
Please don't.
Xiyan Town has been the capital
since the founding of Xiyan.
How can we just move the capital?
Xiyan boasts
a vast territory,
abundant supplies,
and countless talents.
Yet Xiyan Town
is located in the northwest,
surrounded by mountains.
With poor transportation
of supplies and talent,
it can't function
as the capital city.
Xiyan Town is the foundation
of our entire nation.
Moving to Zhiyi
is disrespectful to our ancestors.
Zhiyi is situated
in the heartland of Dahuang
with access to all directions.
Relocating the capital to Zhiyi
will give us access
to supplies and talents.
It will be a policy
that boosts prosperity
and ensures long-term governance.
The Central Plains
are not our native land, after all.
are within our territory.
How can you say
they are not our native land?
Say no more.
Relocating the capital
is of great importance
and requires proper discussion.
Your Majesty.
Lady Shen invites you over
to have lunch with her.
Miss Chenrong is here,
visiting Lady Shen.
I have some court affairs
to discuss with Grandfather.
I won't go to Lady Shen today.
(Shen Shuhui)
Nice tea.
It's a tribute
from the Beijiang Clan,
allegedly exclusive
to the Xiyan royal family.
It's my first time having it.
If you like it,
I will have the maid pack some
for you to take home.
No need.
I was just indulging in something new.
I might forget it if I take it home.
Naughty girl.
Has His Majesty arrived?
His Majesty went to the Great Emperor.
He won't come over today.
Have some tea.
Grandpa.
Give me one more chance.
No, no.
I've given you three chances.
One last time.
I promise it's the last time.
Deal.
(Great Emperor of Xiyan)
No regrets once you've made a move.
No, no, I haven't moved.
Have you decided?
Why don't you enter, Your Majesty?
This is why I'm guarding the world.
Only by seeing that
can I continue forward with conviction.
Why don't you just walk in?
You sound like
you're jumping into a pit of fire.
Xuan.
Good to see you, Nian.
I haven't settled scores with you.
Both you and her
underestimated me
and drove me away.
Am I that unreliable?
Of course not.
You're the most reliable.
Except when you cheat.
Grandpa.
Xuan is bullying me.
Will you help me or him?
I'll help whoever calls me sister.
Sister.
Sister...
Alright.
I'll help you, alright?
Why did you come at this hour?
Did something come up?
Yes.
Grandfather.
I am planning
to take someone from
the Shangyang Clan as my consort.
Xiaoyao.
I...
I don't mean to take a consort.
I want to avoid warfare.
Of course, I know.
Grandfather passed the throne to you.
Naturally, you can't let him down.
To convince the old clans of Xiyan
to relocate the capital
and give up on the Fifth King,
bonding and reasoning
with them is not enough.
You have to benefit them.
Don't congratulate me.
Understand?
I know.
Go back.
Xuan.
I feel that
you're a bit upset.
Should I accompany you for a walk?
I have a pile of work to do.
How can I afford to be upset?
Be at ease and go back.
Okay.
Then I'll go back.
♪You appear at the end of the river♪
♪But disappear as clouds rise♪
♪You appear when I look up♪
♪But disappear as I lower my head♪
♪You appear in the snow♪
♪But disappear as flowers bloom♪
♪You appear as the smoke rises♪
♪You disappear in the light♪
♪You disappear♪
♪In the light♪
What are you doing?
I'm going to find Cang Xuan.
Nian.
Why do you want to find him?
Grandpa.
I like Xuan.
I want to marry him.
Grandpa.
Will you make him marry me, please?
Nian.
You're free to drink.
But don't act crazy.
Nian.
I really like him.
Grandpa.
Grandpa, can you help me, please?
Fine.
I will help you.
Really?
Grandpa, you've agreed?
I never go back on my word.
Would you stop it?
That's enough.
Nian.
That's great.
Grandpa finally said yes.
Finally...
I can marry Cang Xuan.
Grandfather.
How can you lie to her?
She will believe it.
Nian is a sweet little girl,
innocent, unruly, pure, and clever.
She doesn't have
those complicated schemes.
You should
really learn from her.
Be more willful
and more unrestrained.
I can't be willful or unrestrained
because of you and Cang Xuan.
What do you mean by that?
If I say I want to
hang out with Xiang Liu,
would you agree?
No.
Cang Xuan is bound to have
a decisive battle with him.
You hold different stances.
You see,
my bloodline makes it impossible
for me to do as I please.
So,
why should I lie to myself?
Nian.
Why is Your Majesty in a bad mood?
I once thought
the moment I turned Zijin Peak
into Zhaoyun Peak,
I could return to the past.
But even if I plant phoenix trees
all over Chenrong Mountain,
what then?
One wrong step
leads to a wrong path.
I don't think I have any chances now.
Which step was wrong?
I have no idea, either.
All along the way,
it seemed like every step
was the only choice.
But it just turned out
to be wrong.
Even if there are mistakes,
it doesn't matter.
Withered trees can thrive again.
Let alone people.
Where there's a will,
there's a way, for sure.
Is there really a way?
Of course.
There is nothing you can't do,
Your Majesty.
Let's hope you're right.
Relocating the capital
will surely
shake the foundation of Xiyan.
It absolutely can't be done.
His Majesty hasn't expressed an opinion,
but he seems attempted.
Please come forward to stop him.
I'm afraid His Majesty
won't listen to me.
Only you can persuade him.
Father.
I don't have the power
to rule the court anymore.
Great Emperor.
It's time for medicine.
You two may leave.
Please take care of yourself.
I take my leave.
Why did you stop me just now?
Cang Xuan has been
establishing his power in court.
If Father doesn't stop him,
then he will
surely relocate the capital
despite our opposition.
Father no longer has the power.
We are unable to stop Cang Xuan now.
However,
it may not be bad
if he insists on relocating the capital.
Why is that?
Such an act
will surely offend the majority
of the old clans who are against it.
The more opposition he gets,
the better for us.
That's right.
They won't change the capital city.
Then,
it's time to change the king.
Grandfather,
what do you think
about relocating the capital?
What I think doesn't matter.
What matters is what Cang Xuan will do.
Relocating capital has always met with
great resistance in history.
If not handled carefully,
the ministers may turn against the king
and stir up trouble.
It may even lead to
something like
the Five Princes Rebellion
back in Haoling.
(The Shangyang lady
has recorded merits.)
(Attired in fine garments,)
(she is gentle and compliant,)
(wise and intelligent.)
(Possessing a graceful presence,)
(she is known for her kind nature.)
(She is hereby titled a consort.)
(I hope she remains
sincere, filial, humble,)
(respectful and frugal.)
(The head of the Shangyang Clan
has been loyal and upright.)
(He has been grateful,)
(dignified, and righteous)
(while safeguarding the nation.)
(Such a man deserves appreciation.)
(I hereby bestow him with)
(the Qingyao Mountain as a reward.)
"Possessing a graceful presence,
she is known for her kind nature."
Miss.
The phrases in the decree
are always exaggerated and polished.
Please don't take it too seriously.
Miss.
Why don't you play the zither?
No one is here to listen to it.
What's the point of playing it?
Back then, we played
the zither and flute together
throughout the night.
But now,
it's hard to just meet each other.
Maybe
we can ask the young master to help.
Times have changed.
My brother can advise on state matters,
but not on His Majesty's
personal affairs.
Then,
let's get Madam here.
My mother may be Madam Chenrong.
But she resides in Chishui
and has no idea what's happening here.
She can't be of much help.
So what can we do?
My brother and my mother can't help.
But I have
a sister-in-law on Chenrong Mountain.
(Chenrong Mansion)
This house of yours
has been repaired just fine.
Your Highness, if you like it,
stay here with Xiaoyao
for some days.
I have no sisters.
I'm so lonely here.
Indeed.
We're not like those men
who at least have jobs to do.
We have too much free time.
It really is boring without company.
Xiaoyao.
I heard from my brother
that His Majesty has been distressed
because of the capital relocation.
It's a pity that I can't help at all.
It's okay.
It's the thought that counts.
Cang Xuan will understand.
What's the point of that?
He keeps everything to himself.
He never appreciates it
even if we want to help.
That's right.
It's all his fault.
I'll give him a scolding.
- It's not his fault!
Forget it.
Let's not talk about it.
The weather is so nice.
Let's go out for a stroll.
Good idea.
I haven't been out
for a long while.
Okay.
Let's check out the fabrics.
Thank you.
(Tushan Jing)
The nard is spilled. Let it be.
I'll have them repack some for you.
No need.
Thank you, Chief Tushan.
Come take a look.
Fresh out of the pot.
Braised chicken feet.
Braised duck necks.
Braised duck feet.
Come have a look.
Fresh out of the pot.
Braised chicken feet.
Braised duck necks.
Braised duck feet.
Don't miss out as you pass by!
Come take a look!
Please take a look.
Would you like some
to go with your drink?
Miss.
No need.
What will you bet on?
I don't believe it. I'll bet on...
Big.
I follow your bet.
Small.
- Small.
(Lirong Chang)
This lady bets quite boldly.
I run a small business.
You must compensate me.
Alright.
Impressive!
You are truly marvelous.
Don't tell me
she's the girl you like.
I must take a closer look.
The woman who can enthrall my buddy
must be extraordinary.
You are truly marvelous.
What's the point of these trifles?
If we play,
let's play big.
Who dares to play with me?
Why don't you
have a round with her?
Carry her home if you win the bet.
Buddy,
if you don't go out now,
you may lose your love to someone else.
Let's bet on
something new.
(Fangfeng Bei)
I dare you.
- Bet with him!
Why not?
Big or small.
The loser
must answer a question
without lying.
That's new.
Okay.
Let's bet.
Sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Who
do you like?
What kind of question is that?
What a lousy question.
Next one.
I'll ask whatever I want.
Just answer truthfully.
You lose if you don't answer.
Fine, then.
The person I like...
Is the one I want to spend my life with.
Who do you want to spend your life with?
That's another question.
Let's talk if you win.
She won.
It's my turn.
If you were given another chance,
would you still choose this path?
Yes.
Why?
Because I met someone
very important along the way.
If I had chosen a different path,
I might not have met that person.
You are quite loyal
to your foster father.
This is not fun.
I'm done.
Don't go.
Your money?
Who says she doesn't want the money?
Put all her money into my account.
On what ground?
You're wearing the wrong color
today.
It's not a good omen.
Why were you
gambling alone?
Where is your future husband,
the pride of the day?
You know I'm engaged?
Chief Chishui is engaged
to the Princess of Haoling.
It's hard not to know.
I forgot to congratulate you.
Congratulations.
Don't you have
anything else
to say to me?
What should I say?
Nothing.
There are two things
I'd like to discuss with you.
Go ahead.
The first thing.
I can still make pills
for you right now.
But after I get married,
I won't be able to anymore.
And the second thing?
I want to remove the poisonous bug.
It keeps causing you trouble.
Last time,
you were tired of it.
When you have time,
we'll go to Baili
to remove the poisonous bug.
Rest assured.
After that,
I will still keep my promise
to you.
Alright.
When I have time.
I'll deliver the pills to you
every three months.
I have to go.
♪Looking back on my old days♪
♪I was unruffled
with no sorrow and soreness♪
♪In my chaotic life,
I failed to meet your gaze♪
♪Only emptiness remained♪
♪Enduring all things in my life♪
♪I valued all but indifferent
to wealth and fame♪
♪Basking in the sun,
I couldn't feel your sunlight♪
♪All I feel is a painful heat wave♪
♪All things are dim,
while only your eyes shine bright♪
♪I'll follow my heart
and go to chase the sun far away♪
♪Everything seems sad,
while only your brows raise in delight♪
♪I'm waiting for you
to enjoy the scenery at night♪
♪You came with wind and rain,
while left with my four seasons♪
♪All is bleak without you♪
♪It began like a tornado,
and went away leaving only dust♪
♪Without you,
even the most beautiful world is a mess♪