[Royal Feast]
[Episode 26]
I think
that she should be conferred the title
of the Crown Prince's Concubine
so that
she can accompany Zhanji forever
and assist him.
Father,
if you think highly of her,
let her stay in the Imperial Food Service
to cook for you without any distraction.
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty said
that the child looked familiar.
She was chosen by the Late Emperor
to be the Great Imperial Grandson's Concubine
for Zhanji.
Of course, she looks familiar.
So, it is her.
Mother.
You promised me.
Your Majesty finally remembered.
Actually,
I should have informed Your Majesty earlier.
However, this child is very stubborn.
So, I sent her
to the Imperial Food Service
to temper her.
By a strange twist of fate,
I nearly ruined her.
Your Majesty.
Observe courtesy in the royal presence.
I have enough people to serve me.
You should let me
choose who I want.
Moreover,
I don't like her.
Zhanji,
the Late Emperor always loved you.
You never disobeyed
his orders.
The Late Emperor
couldn't be wrong.
Alright.
Well said.
This is a match made in heaven.
No wonder
she looked familiar.
Since it was a match chosen by the Late Emperor,
we should
choose an auspicious date
to bestow the title on her.
Yes.
No, Father.
I feel a tightness in my chest
after talking so much.
Leave.
Father.
Your Majesty.
You have a disharmony in the body.
I'll worry about you
if I go back now.
Let me take care of you.
Congratulations.
You may leave.
Mother,
you promised
that you wouldn't bring this up again.
Why did you rake up the past?
Honestly, do you dislike her?
Should I pick a flower
simply because I like it?
Why can't I leave it in the garden
to bloom freely?
You tried your best to procrastinate
because you want to protect her.
However, we both know
that in the imperial family,
she was already chosen for the title.
It's just a matter of time.
You saw it with your own eyes.
Your father's health is deteriorating.
Yet, he still worries about you.
Do you have the heart
to reject his good intention?
Permit me to leave.
Since small, he doesn't have to
say what he wants.
If he
takes a look at something,
and people will kneel and present it at his feet.
Everything under heaven
is his to take,
not just one flower,
but
the whole garden.
I'd never
heard him talk like this.
Send a secret letter to inform Le'an Prefecture
about what happened in the palace today.
Yes.
Leave us first.
I've done what you told me
to do.
His Majesty is having a relapse.
This is a great crime
punishable by nine kinship exterminations.
If His Majesty falls seriously ill
and news of the Crown Prince's disaffection
reaches Le'an Prefecture,
what do you think
the ambitious Prince of Han
will do?
Are you plotting a rebellion?
Wrong.
The Prince of Han is plotting one.
What does that
have to do with you?
What?
Are you scared?
In the Forbidden City,
the only person who cared about me
was gone.
I don't care about
any subversion.
However, I don't understand this.
You are in a high position despite your age,
and His Majesty
trusts and relies on you.
What more do you want?
You mean,
I should spend my life being the Emperor's lackey
and be ordered around at will?
Zhu Zhanji might not be able
to take this.
Here.
Noodles.
Yin Ziping.
I heard that dumplings and noodles
are offered before and after
going onto the bridal sedan chair.
I'd never heard about
eating noodles before getting married.
Can't bear to part?
A bit.
Zijin.
My mother said
that music, weiqi, calligraphy, painting,
needlework, and cooking were tools.
All tools are dispensable.
Is there anything that we shouldn't part with?
The Avataṃsaka Sutra says
that those who remember their initial resolve
in the past, present, and future
will be protected by Buddha.
My mother said
that I must adhere to my initial resolve.
I don't understand.
I know.
Ziping,
a fortuneteller told me
that I'd be
the Great Imperial Grandson's Consort.
It was heaven's will.
Later, he said
that someone else would be the consort
and I didn't have such great blessings.
I don't care,
but I refuse to give in.
Even if fate repeatedly taunt me,
I will still challenge fate.
Moreover,
China is a big country and has many talents.
I am not indispensable in the kitchen.
A cook tosses with her hand
and takes charge in the kitchen.
My right hand is not good anymore.
I'll go where I'm needed
and do what I do best.
Are you still thinking about Consort Zhuang?
Don't think about it or touch it.
That's the ancestral system.
Who says the system can't be changed?
You are
an insignificant Crown Prince's Concubine.
Who said that I'd be a concubine
forever?
You!
Ziping,
someone won't let me hide
or dodge.
Well then,
I will not hide or dodge.
Even the families of rebellious ministers
could be released.
Is there anything
that one cannot achieve under heaven?
Hold it.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, don't worry.
The wound
will heal after you rest
for seven or eight days.
Sheng Yin,
His Majesty has a relapse.
His condition is serious.
Tomorrow,
go to the Qianqing Palace with me
and diagnose him.
This...
Leave us.
Yes.
Your Highness,
I won't be able to do anything.
His Majesty hates me intensely.
He will never let me
treat him.
His Majesty
will not hold grudges against you
for treating my mother before.
It's not just that.
I...
I got drunk once
and joked with my colleagues.
I don't know how,
but His Majesty
heard about it in the Eastern Palace.
My father is magnanimous and gentle.
He is rarely angry with his officials.
What did you say
to make my father hate you to this day?
For a physician,
diagnosing by looking is more important than
smelling, listening, and feeling the pulse.
By looking at a patient,
I can tell about his internal organs
and his illness.
Don't worry.
You can tell me.
His Majesty
doesn't have the look of longevity.
Presumptuous!
Your Highness,
it's getting late. You should sleep.
Get out.
Leave us first.
His Majesty refuses to see me.
I do not know
what I've done wrong.
Aren't you
good at giving advice?
Why are you so quiet now?
Your Highness.
This isn't
the time to worry about His Majesty's favor.
A disaster
is approaching.
You mean...
It's impossible.
His Majesty is in his prime
and is deeply blessed.
He'll be back to normal soon.
Your Highness,
how are His Majesty's complexion and gait today
compared to before?
Safety can become a danger,
and blessings, misfortune.
You are smart.
Must I remind you?
I wish His Majesty a speedy recovery
so that he can comfort Your Highness.
If not,
Your Highness
should take precautions early.
Kneel.
First bow.
Rise.
Second bow.
Third bow.
Rise.
Fourth bow.
Stand up.
Crown Prince's Concubine,
this is against etiquette.
The Crown Prince personally sent you back.
He doesn't want you to feel insulted.
Mother thinks the people in my palace are clumsy,
and especially gave you these people
to take care of your daily needs.
These brocades, hairpieces, and bracelets
are my gifts.
Please accept them.
I thank the Crown Princess for your kindness.
You are now in the Eastern Palace
and therefore we are sisters.
You don't have to be so courteous.
You must be tired from the greeting ceremony.
Go back and rest early.
Take good care
of the Crown Prince's Concubine.
Yes.
[Xingyun Cottage]
Your Highness.
I'm not deaf.
Your Highness,
the Crown Prince's Concubine
is waiting for you in the hall at this moment.
Your Highness.
What is it?
Your Highness, where are you going?
The Crown Prince's Concubine is still waiting.
Has your injury healed?
I have been lying down for too long.
My arms have become weak.
If I don't get up and about,
I won't be able to draw the bow anymore.
Why is Your Highness here?
Good wine!
Officer You is drinking alone under the moon.
Too bad that the bright moon
doesn't know how to drink.
Let me
be your drinking buddy.
Your Highness, you cannot drink.
Your injury hasn't healed.
People say Shaojiu is a strong liquor
and one shouldn't drink too much.
You should drink Shaoxing rice wine
if you're alone.
However,
it is rare to meet like-minded people.
I like it.
Your Highness.
You can't get drunk tonight.
My courtesy name is Yunzhou.
Great.
Yunzhou.
At the Lantern Festival Banquet,
you displayed exceptional martial arts skills.
Let's have a friendly match.
Your Highness.
I won't dare.
Your Highness, be careful.
Again.
I have read your memorials.
How dare you?
Your Highness.
Your old wound has reopened again.
What should I do?
I was rude.
Your Highness, please forgive me.
It was just a friendly match.
Swords have no eyes.
How can I blame you?
Stand up.
Your Highness is magnanimous.
I am forever grateful.
Didn't you say...
I said I read
your memorials.
Since taking office,
you've submitted countless memorials
to my grandfather and His Majesty
about salt administration,
water transport of tribute grain,
tax law,
sea ​​defense,
and military affairs.
Every word was precious
and drove straight to the point.
Unfortunately,
these memorials
were thrown aside
and weren't taken seriously.
We are two patients
who couldn't fight to our hearts' content.
When your injury heals,
we'll fight again.
Yes.
Sir,
you are also injured.
Are you alright?
Sir.
Sir!
It is late.
Where are you going?
I'm going to take a walk.
Eunuch Chen,
why is His Highness not here yet?
Please inform the Crown Prince's Concubine
that His Highness's wound reopened
in a sword practice tonight.
I'm afraid he can't come.
The Crown Prince's Concubine should rest early.
Your Highness,
you shouldn't do this.
Don't worry,
His Highness will be back soon.
His Majesty is not feeling well.
The Crown Prince
has always been sincere and filial.
He'll be worried sick.
At this moment,
he is not in the mood to have a concubine.
He won't come.
You all get some rest.
I said don't fight,
but you insisted.
Imperial Physician Sheng advised you
not to practice swords and spears.
You also drank wine.
Imperial Physician Sheng,
is he alright?
This is great.
You have to rest for a while again.
You Yifan is in deep trouble.
Seriously, Your Highness.
He knows
you are still recovering from a serious injury
but still had a friendly match with you.
When Her Majesty returns to the palace,
I will report to her
and he'll be punished severely.
None of your business.
Permit me to leave now.
Your Highness,
you should rest.
Bring me my book.
It's late.
Your Highness, I informed her.
Is she angry?
No.
Did she say anything?
Nothing.
Not even a single word?
Your Highness,
she endured the complicated ceremony
of conferring
the title of Crown Prince's Concubine
for days on end.
She has lost weight.
She won't be able to stay awake
and wait for you the whole night.
That's why she slept.
What do you know?
Don't talk nonsense.
If His Highness doesn't go back,
she has to stay awake
until the next day regardless.
Your Highness.
Your... Your Highness!
Leave.
I thought you'd give me the cold shoulder.
Instead,
you didn't even look at me.
Why do you keep staring at me and laughing?
Your Highness,
did you sleep well last night?
Last night?
In the Eastern Palace, you have
the highest status after the Crown Princess.
The others should come to greet you.
I've instructed the Imperial Food Service
to prepare a small feast.
Jin,
you served Consort Zhuang
in the past.
Now, Her Majesty tells you to serve me.
Don't you feel insulted?
Your Highness,
no one wanted to help my mistress back then.
Had you not lent her a hand,
she might not die in peace.
I will always remember your kindness.
Her Majesty
wanted to send someone to the Eastern Palace,
and I volunteered for the assignment.
I will do my best
to perform any chores you have.
It's getting late.
I will get everything ready.
It may not be what you expect.
Nothing. You may go.
Yes.
Your Highness,
it's ready.
Jin.
Yes.
All of you may leave.
Sit here.
Being the mistress is different.
This is much better than
in the Imperial Food Service.
However, it is rude for me to sit here.
What should I do
if His Highness finds out?
He hasn't been here yet.
He hasn't been here?
That's not possible.
He didn't come to you
and you didn't go to him?
Haven't you reconciled yet?
I know.
What do you know?
You blamed Her Majesty
for forcing you to enter the palace.
Consequently, you hate the Crown Prince.
That's why you promised to marry him.
You will spend your whole life
torturing him.
Am I right?
I can't sit here.
In a while, when the concubines
of the Eastern Palace
come to greet you,
It'll be disrespectful if I sit here.
Sit there.
Your Highness.
Today...
There's no need to wait.
Today,
you'll eat with me.
How dare they give you a cold shoulder!
They've gone too far.
Your oil was too hot
when you fried the dough.
How can that be?
It's fragrant and crispy.
I fried it.
[Xunchong Pancake]
Don't try to talk your way out.
Manager Yin.
You must personally handle the puffer fish
that the Court of Imperial Entertainments
brings in.
Don't let other people do it.
Her Majesty
doesn't like asparagus soup.
Change it to burclover soup instead.
Cook more napa cabbage
and Indian wormwood herb.
Always be kind and gentle
to palace maids.
Don't order them around
or they will hate you.
In my absence,
be on guard against Yuehua.
Don't worry.
However,
you must find a way
to attract the Crown Prince.
To get a permanent foothold
in the Eastern Palace,
I must be careful of every one of
His Highness's consorts and concubines.
However...
Crown Princess,
none of them
greeted the Crown Prince's Concubine.
Miaoxian,
haven't you
greeted the Crown Prince's Concubine today?
Crown Princess,
according to rules,
we should greet the new Crown Prince's Concubine,
but...
This year's asparagus
don't look very tender.
Miaoxian,
early next morning,
go and ask for her forgiveness.
Do you hear me?
Crown Princess Sister,
I didn't mean to be rude.
I can't bear
the smell of smoke on her.
What smell?
She cooked in the kitchen all day long.
She smelled of lard and fish.
Who dares to approach her?
Perhaps His Highness
is very displeased with her also.
On the day the title was conferred upon her,
he didn't spend the night with her.
I should be slapped.
Is it true that the Crown Prince
did not spend the night with her?
His Majesty and Her Majesty
showed her all the kindness.
I thought she must be
an amazing person.
Who would have guessed
that she entered the Eastern Palace
and went right into "the cold cellar"?
Just now I saw the maids
opening the cellar to air the peony.
I wonder when will the Crown Prince
remember
the Crown Prince's Concubine
and ask her to get some air?
Things get rancid after being kept for too long.
His Highness' injury reopened.
That was why
he didn't go to the Xinuan Pavilion.
You mustn't be rude
to her because of this.
Neither should you
disturb His Highness when he is recovering.
You, in particular,
should not fool around,
or I won't let you off lightly.
Yes.
A while ago,
I made a new incense.
It can help you sleep.
Can it?
Come and visit me one day.
Who said the Crown Prince's Concubine
was not favored?
We should go and greet her.
Did she accept?
Yes.
What did she say?
What else can she say?
She expressed 1,000 thanks and 1,000 gratitudes.
I didn't witness that.
You didn't?
Then...
The Crown Prince presented gifts
to the Crown Prince's Concubine
to openly dote on her.
Had the Crown Prince's Concubine known,
she'd thank him profusely.
However, I went at the wrong time.
I was afraid that Your Highness
would be worried sick waiting.
So, I came back to report.
Had the Crown Prince's Concubine known,
she would come
to specially express her gratitude.
Your Highness,
you haven't gone to thank His Highness.
That is improper.
If His Highness finds out
and gets mad,
then...
After I reapplied my makeup,
two hours would have passed
and the palace commissioner
would be waiting outside.
If people heard about that,
they'd think I was disrespectful.
I can only blame
the gifts for arriving at the wrong time.
Did I come at the wrong time also?
Your Highness.
Jin, my clothes.
Yes.
Go out.
Don't touch.
Yes.
Jin!
Your Highness.
Please wait in the outer hall.
I'll be there to greet you soon.
I have something to ask you.
I'll leave after asking.
What do you want to ask?
Your Highness.
I don't want to ask anything now.
I'm staying here tonight.
Get ready.
Jin.
Jin!
Your Highness has not healed fully.
The imperial physician admonished you
to rest properly.
If
I let Your Highness stay overnight,
tomorrow Her Majesty will call me over
and rebuke me.
Do not worry.
Mother won't blame you.