[Royal Feast]
[Episode 29]
Is he still kneeling outside?
Yes, Your Highness.
His Highness hasn't eaten all day.
Please talk to him.
[Glutinous Millet Dumpling]
I'm here to pay my respect, Your Highness.
That woman tried to harm the Empress.
I can never pardon her.
So don't speak of it.
You refuse to eat.
Her Majesty is concerned about you.
Everyone at the Imperial Food Service is fearful.
If you're not willing to have this plain congee,
how about trying
the glutinous millet dumpling I made?
Leave us.
Your Highness,
Matron Meng is a witness
to the incident at Yongning Palace.
Crown Prince's Concubine,
please speak with discretion.
I...
The Imperial Food Service provided
all the drinks for the banquet.
If Lady Guo brought in poison,
how could it slip from Matron Meng's eyes?
If Matron Meng knows about this,
why did she keep quiet about it?
As to what had happened,
who should we ask
if not you?
Speak.
Your Highness,
Noble Consort Guo did have the intention
to take Her Majesty's life.
But as the person in charge
of the Imperial Food Service,
how could I do something like this?
So I reported this matter to Her Majesty.
Then,
His Majesty suddenly arrived that day
and failed to stop him from taking the cup.
Her Majesty knocked over the wine cup.
That's how His Majesty found out
Noble Consort Guo poisoned the wine.
His Majesty was extremely angry,
and so his disease suddenly worsened.
When the imperial physician arrived,
he was unable to save the situation.
Who was the imperial physician?
Your Highness,
it was Imperial Physician Sheng.
Summon forth, Sheng Yin.
Yes, Your Highness.
Your humble servant is here
to pay his respect to Your Highness.
I wasn't at Yongning Palace that day.
When I rushed to Qianqing Palace
to treat His Majesty,
it was already too late.
Imperial Physician Sheng is skilled
in the art of healing.
Since the day of His Majesty's demise,
you've been staying in His Majesty's chambers
to keep the truth from going out.
Aren't you curious
how His Majesty died?
I...
I'm not a coroner.
I want to hear the truth.
Your Highness,
Collected Cases of Injustice Rectified states
any victims who died from poisoned
usually have their mouths and eyes opened.
The face would look purplish or bluish.
The lips would be dark.
The toenails and fingernails
would look bluish-black.
There will be blood
from the mouths, eyes, ears, and nose.
To stop the smell of the corpse from getting out
and startling the people,
I've taken care of His Majesty's body.
His Majesty's lips may look bluish
and bloated on his lower limbs.
But there weren't any symptoms of being poisoned.
In that case,
Father found out
Noble Consort Guo poisoned the wine.
So he had a heart attack from being angered?
I heard
on the day of Her Majesty's birthday banquet,
Censor-in-Chief Li Shimian submitted
a memorial and discussed state affairs
and infuriated His Majesty.
He was sent to prison on the spot.
Why didn't you report this to me?
Your Highness,
Official Li talked back
at His Majesty's defiantly.
His Majesty was furious
and ordered the palace guard to break his ribs.
Fortunately, he's still alive.
He's still in prison now.
No one dares to mention this matter after that
for fear Your Highness might be upset.
What exactly did he say
to upset Father that much?
Well,
I don't know.
Order the imperial bodyguard to bring him here.
I want to ask him in person.
Yes, Your Highness.
Your Highness,
His Majesty wasn't poisoned
but had relapsed from anger.
Prince of Wei hasn't eaten
and has been kneeling outside all day.
Give this to him.
Also,
send some of his favorite
glutinous millet dumplings.
Father had always been kind.
Even if the officials talked back at him,
he never criticized them harshly.
Li Shimian has suffered such harsh punishment.
I'm certain he's guilty beyond forgiveness.
No need to bring him here.
Execute him.
Yes, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
[Li Shimian, Censor-in-Chief]
A sinner is here to pay respect, Your Highness.
Didn't I say to execute this man?
Your Highness, please calm down.
Commander Wang must have departed
from the west gate with the second edict,
while the ones who brought
Li Shimian must have come from the east gate.
As they come and go,
they've missed out on each other.
Li Shimian,
do you know the unforgivable crime
you've committed?
Are you deaf?
How did you behave defiantly
towards His Majesty that day?
Tell the truth.
If you want to live,
you can only say these two sentences
when you meet the Crown Prince.
I said
His Majesty shouldn't be closed
to the concubines during mourning.
The Crown Prince shouldn't be away from his side.
Just these two?
Yes, I spoke of nothing else.
It's just...
I wasn't articulate
and used the wrong choice of words,
which annoyed
and offended His Majesty.
I regretted my action.
You were just being frank.
A loyal official indeed.
Where's the memorial, then?
His Majesty was furious at the time
and burned it.
Burned?
Yes.
You can leave now.
Thank you for your mercy, Your Highness.
Your Highness,
His Majesty has passed away.
Concubines are to be buried along with him.
How many nameless palace maids will be buried?
The people follow the examples
of the imperial household.
Burying people alive is getting
more and more serious.
Can't you...
Zijin,
this is the ancestral instructions.
Can't ancestral instructions
be amended?
Only Noble Consort Guo
has three sons.
She's exempted from the sacrificial burial.
The crime of plotting poison
shall be dealt with
after the funeral.
This is great! It's great!
My mother doesn't have to die anymore.
My mother is saved!
Prince of Wei!
-My mother is saved!
-Prince of Wei!
-That's great!
-Be careful!
-Prince of Wei!
-My mother is saved!
-It's great!
-Slow down!
Be careful!
Her means are impressive.
She's still too young.
Your Majesty, His Highness has exempted
Noble Consort Guo from the burial.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, His Highness has exempted you
from the burial.
What's today's dish?
It's chamomile cold noodles.
[Chamomile Cold Noodles]
(A handful of picked chamomile leaves)
(with the morning dew washed away.)
(Wring the extract and add it into the flour.)
(Knead well and roll the dough thinly.)
(They're cut with a silver knife.)
(They're boiled and rinsed in cold spring water.)
(Such green noodles are more fragrant)
(than fragrant thoroughwort and sweet flag.)
How nice.
It tastes exactly like the ones
my grandmother made.
How nice.
Your Highness,
are you thinking about Lady Yan?
Lady Yan?
When my grandfather was alive,
he helped Jianwen Emperor to attack Prince of Yan
and almost got himself killed.
After that, the Guo family fell.
He had dozens of wives and concubines
and dozens of sons.
My father was sickly.
No one took care of us.
My father was critically ill once.
I kneeled in the mansion for two days.
It was my grandmother
who carried me back on her back.
She pawned off her winter clothes
to buy medicinal herbs for my father.
At night,
I saw my grandmother crying
with her back against everyone.
Do you know why?
She cut off her long hair to sell it.
But no one wanted to buy it
because she was prematurely aged
and her hair had turned gray.
She cried because she could save her son's life
even after she had cut off her hair.
After that,
I took the initiative to enter
the Eastern Palace.
I've been walking
on eggshells anxiously for 20 years.
I don't ask that the Guo family prosper forever.
I only want my grandmother
to spend her remaining years in peace.
I want them to remember
that I gave them their glory and wealth.
I want them to hold
my grandmother in high regard.
I want them to revere the concubine
whom everyone despised.
Twenty years.
It's been 20 years.
Just one step.
Just one step away.
Your Highness,
Prince of Wei has been kneeling outside all day.
His Highness, the Crown Prince, has told him
to go back and rest.
He'll come to pay his respect to you tomorrow.
You can finally reunite.
Why did you help me?
Sacrificial burial is cruel.
I want to help as many as I can.
You're a kindhearted
and smart person.
Remember this.
There's a long journey ahead of you.
You must live.
Your Highness,
please get some rest.
I'll bring Prince of Wei
to pay you a respect tomorrow.
Your Highness,
don't you blame me at all?
You were from Kunning Palace in the first place.
Why would I blame you?
Your Highness,
I may be from Kunning Palace.
But I never had any intention to harm you.
I was afraid of being implicated.
I was just scared...
His Highness has promised
to spare Noble Consort Guo.
You don't have to be scared anymore.
Come, comb my hair.
Your Highness,
Noble Consort Guo...
She hung herself
and had gone with His Majesty.
-Your Highness, you can't go in.
-Mother.
-Your Highness, please go back.
-Mother!
You shouldn't come here.
-Your Highness, please go back.
-Mother!
-Shan.
-Your Highness.
Big Brother, why?
Mother has been pardoned.
But why?
It was my fault.
Big Brother, what should I do now?
Father and Mother are no longer here.
What would happen to me after this?
Rest assured.
I'm here, am I not?
As long as I'm here,
I won't let anyone harm you.
Send Prince of Wei back.
Yes, Your Highness.
Let's go, Your Highness.
Your Highness, your edict has been sent
to Qingning Palace.
Why did Noble Consort Guo...
(In the sixth month of the first year
of Hongxi Reign,)
(the Crown Prince, Zhu Zhanji,
ascended the throne.)
(A general amnesty was proclaimed to the empire.)
(Empress Zhang is elevated to Empress Dowager.)
(The Crown Princess
of the Hu clan was made the Empress.)
(It's for the Great Ming's Xuande Emperor.)
-Long live Your Majesty!
Long live Your Majesty.
(Xuande Emperor has ascended the throne.)
[Qingning Gate]
(Empress Dowager moved back to Qingning Palace.)
Mother,
in terms of age, seniority, and family background,
the He clan is the most profound.
She's best to be appointed as a consort.
As for the positions of other concubines,
it's on this register.
What are your thoughts
on Lady Sun's position?
Sun is gentle, virtuous, and modest.
She's the most likable.
No one can be compared
to her position in His Majesty's heart.
Her position
should be decided by Mother and His Majesty.
I wonder what position you would...
Is there anything else?
When Your Majesty ascended the throne,
Prince of Han and Prince of Zhao sent envoys
to offer their congratulations.
Your Majesty also doubled
their monetary rewards.
Such grace is unprecedented.
Prince of Han proposed to provide
the basic needs to benefit the people.
Your Majesty carried it out immediately.
You shouldn't treat these feudal lords
with ulterior motives with such generosity.
Is there something wrong
with Prince of Han's memorial?
It's relevant
to the empire and the people.
Prince of Han has the courage to speak frankly
and lament the shortcomings of the times.
Every word is beneficial
to the people's livelihood.
I'd naturally accept his points.
My dear ministers,
Grandfather often told the Late Emperor and me
that we must take precautions
because my second uncle has an ulterior motive.
But the Late Emperor considered
their brotherly affection
and tolerated my second uncle.
It's all to repay evil with kindness.
But now, he has changed.
So I'll live up to the family relations
of the imperial household.
No one is allowed
to doubt my second uncle in the future.
Your Majesty is wise.
Shiqi.
Shiqi,
I think Prince of Han is trying
to sound out His Majesty.
He definitely harbors bad intentions.
You must warn His Majesty of this.
Don't underestimate
how ambitious Prince of Han is.
He's right.
Official Yang, why are you standing so far away?
Come and join us.
Sorry about that. My old sickness is relapsing.
Have you seen the bamboo forest His Majesty drew?
The strokes are broad and organized.
I'm sure
he knows how to draw.
-Yes.
-So, don't worry.
You really like joking. Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
Sir,
Prince of Han asked about His Majesty
in all his three letters.
How should we reply?
What do you think?
From what I see,
His Majesty ignored
the officials' criticisms against Prince of Han.
Instead, His Majesty praised
and rewarded the Prince of Han.
He even wrote a letter personally.
It can be seen that he wants
to win some good name
with kindness and generosity like
the Late Emperor.
After all, Prince of Han is his uncle.
I don't know what I did wrong.
I hope you can guide me.
You're right.
His Majesty is trying to win
this uncle to his side.
Someone from Zhangde is here too.
Please spare some time to meet him.
All right.
Prince of Han invites Father to rebel?
What did Father say?
His Lordship dare not agree to it easily.
So he ordered me to sneak into the capital
to ask for your advice.
Accept his offer.
What about the new emperor?
When Zhu Zhanji ascended the throne,
the imperial court and the empire may look calm.
In fact, the dark tide is surging.
To Father,
this is a good time to start his great cause.
Tell Father
that it's not the time yet.
Don't be impulsive.
Yes.
[Foods Office]
Greetings, Matron Meng.
The Empress Dowager had ordered
to restore the old system
in the early years of the Hongwu Reign.
She ordered me to take charge
of the affairs of the whole palace.
I'll be assisting the Empress Dowager
to reset the palace rules.
So I won't have time to manage
the Imperial Food Service.
For the time being,
everything here...
Hanying has been in the palace the longest
and has the most experience.
She's also the calmest.
You shall take charge.
Yes, Matron Meng.
As for the selection of the matron,
I still need to think about it again.
During this time,
you must do your duty
and don't slack off.
Yes, Matron Meng.
Xiang Qin.
Isn't it just moving
from the Imperial Food Service
to the General Palace Service?
Silly,
the Imperial Food Service is only
in charge of food.
General Palace Service is
one of the six major services in the palace.
It controls the Records Office,
the Communications Office,
the Registration Office,
and the Inner Gates Office.
It's the head of all six services.
Every regulation, protocol,
food, clothes, and utensils used
must be reported to the matron
before being carried out.
Now, our Matron Meng is among the six services...
I mean,
she should be the most powerful female official
in the Forbidden City.
You always lower your head
whenever you're here to pay your respects.
You look fearful.
Am I really that scary?
I wasn't.
Do you think
I was the one who forced Noble Consort Guo
to kill herself?
The Empress Dowager asked you a question.
It's disrespectful to stay silent.
Noble Consort Guo was raised
by her grandmother, Lady Yan.
They're very closed to each other.
Old Madam entered the palace today.
She made the chamomile cold noodles.
You're already in power.
Why did you have to force her?
She was the woman
whom the Late Emperor loved the most.
She also brought fatal harm to the Late Emperor.
That's why
I send her off to accompany him.
Then are you letting her be buried
at the mausoleum
and place her memorial tablet
enshrined at the mausoleum?
I have no right to ask you to pardon her.
But you could've asked her to be a nun,
guard the mausoleum,
or even take her own life as an apology
instead of publicly forcing her
to be part of the burial.
She still dies. What's the difference?
Being part of the burial
for being childless is already a tragedy.
Now one has to die a martyr
even when they're not childless.
Those in the imperial harem are frightened.
When this gets out,
there'll be endless disasters.
Noble Consort Guo's martyrdom shook
the imperial court and the people.
Her eldest son, Prince of Teng,
fears dying from illness.
Even the youngest son,
Prince of Wei cried day and night
in constant fear.
Your Majesty,
they're His Majesty's brothers.
The brothers aren't united now.
How would His Majesty feel?
Won't he feel sad at all?
Your eyes are filled
with dissatisfaction.
Are you secretly determined
to seek justice from me one day?
I dare not.
All these years,
I protected my husband,
my sons, and the imperial harem.
After this, I'll do my best
to protect the country
and the people of the Great Ming.
That's how Empress Ma and Empress Xu had lived.
While Noble Consort Guo, Hu Shanxiang,
you,
and most of the women in the imperial harem,
what can you do if you're in power?
Fighting for a man's favor
or protecting the family?
Forget about that.
You can't do anything.
So
as long as I live,
all of you have no say.
[Guang'an Gate]
You did your best, but you failed to save her.
Are you disappointed?
Under this blue sky
where the sunlight shines,
no one can go against the Empress Dowager.
So you shouldn't feel disappointed.
You should feel hopeless.
From now on,
stop having unnecessary thoughts.
After being harmed by others,
one ends up as the person
who uses power to harm others.
Why?
Directress Hu was certain
that only one of us could live.
What is it based on?
The founding emperor established
ancestral instructions.
There's a certain number of the concubines
and palace maids being buried alive.
The high-ranking officials, nobles, officials,
and landlords compete to follow suit.
How many innocent lives will be buried?
Is it still countable?
Do you think you can change this?
Well, not now.
Not now?
Huaping.
Yes, Your Majesty?
Did you see that?
There's another person
who wants to defy heaven's will.
Your Highness.
There's a long life ahead.
How can everything go smoothly?
But I won't feel hopeless.
But a journey of thousands of li
should start from the beginning.
Are you done painting?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Something's wrong.
If I may be bold and ask what's wrong?
Everything is wrong.
Come and paint me.
I can't paint
if your order is unbeknownst to me.
That painting of me looks
handsome and unrestrained.
But it lacks valor.
I see.
Valor.
The appearance of an emperor
should be dignified and extraordinary.
So the people would feel in awe
with respect and admiration.
Yes, Your Majesty.
You want to look majestic.
Are you done?
Your Majesty, don't move.
I can't paint well if you move.
Your Majesty,
take a look.
Does he look mighty
and majestic to you?
Does he look dignified?
I like the portrait you draw very much.
I painted this based on your requests.
I like it very much.
Keep it.
I'll paint one for you next time.
I assure you it'll be exactly the same.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Thank you for your grace, Your Majesty.
Perhaps I could make you look mightier.
[The First Year of Hongxi Reign, Mid-Autumn]
[Qingning Gate]
You want to appoint Lady Sun as the Noble Consort?
Yes.
Your late grandfather picked Lady Sun
as your official wife.
It's too bad that she has a poor fate.
So she's not worthy of being the Empress.
Now,
you've conferred Hu as your empress.
Both of their places are set.
Don't tell me
Lady Sun complained
about this.
Mother, you've misunderstood.
Zijin...
Lady Sun made no complaints.
It's my wish.
The position of Noble Consort ranks
second to the Empress.
You must choose someone who's obliging, virtuous,
and respected by those in the imperial harem.
Let's put this matter aside for a while.
I need to consider this.
Why?
Are you not happy?
Mother,
I didn't mean that.
Please wait for a while.
I heard
you have preferences towards Lady Sun
among all the concubines in the imperial harem.
Isn't that so?
Lady Sun is gentle,
and we had a predestined fate.
I'm inevitably
more tolerant towards her.
But I won't tolerate it
if she acts like a spoiled child
and causes trouble everywhere.
Don't worry, Mother.
All the concubines in the imperial palace
are the same in my heart.
It's the same
with Lady Sun too.
Zijin, you're here?
Let her come in.
Your Majesties.
Rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Since Your Majesty is busy with state affairs,
I won't keep you here, then.
Zijin can stay
and accompany me.
You can leave now.
Yes, Mother.
I'll take my leave now.
[Qingning Gate]
Your Highness,
His Majesty invites you to have a meal together.
Eunuch Yuan,
please convey my message to His Majesty.
I'm ugly
and not gentle.
I don't want
to defile His Majesty's eyes.
Also,
ask His Majesty to invite
the other concubines.
Since all women
in the imperial harem are the same.
You're defying His Majesty's edict.
Your Highness, look.
Fresh meat, fruits, mixed nuts,
egg yolk, and lotus paste.
They're all prepared.
Can we send these
to Qianqing Palace now?
Never mind.
According to the usual practice
in previous years,
all the mistress of the palaces
would send moon cakes to Qianqing Palace.
You're...
Which one looks nicer?
It's the mid-autumn.
Of course, it's the red one.
It's the color of celebration.
Here.
Thank you.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Big Sister.
Look at the lace.
How did you embroider it?
I knitted it with gold thread.
If you like it,
I'll teach you next time. Is that all right?
All right.
Good.
Your Majesty,
should we send someone
to deliver the moon cakes to Qianqing Palace?
Isn't that person good at preparing food?
No matter how nimble my hands are,
I can't be compared to her.
Why waste my time?
I prefer this one.