[Royal Feast]
[Episode 13]
Father.
Leave!
Father...
I said, leave!
Father.
What is so funny?
Grandfather, you don't have to waste your time.
When you asked Official Xia
to accompany me to visit the people
to understand the hardship of the people,
Official Xia forced me to eat millet.
I've held this grudge for a long time now.
So I sent someone to make a secret investigation
to find evidence of his crime.
But the people I sent told me
that there were only clothes
and pottery in Official Xia's house.
He has nothing else.
Executing Xia Yuanji is only a trivial matter.
Then
what do you think it's a serious matter?
Grandfather,
you've been ill twice.
I hope you can live for a long time.
Let me take your place
for the northern expedition this time.
What do you say?
Many people
live long.
But there's nothing more
to it.
When Yan Hui was 30,
his name was remembered for generations.
I want to do great deeds
that will last for generations.
I don't need to live long.
However, you mustn't go.
Grandfather...
I can go to the north without worries
because you're in Beijing.
I can't bring the future
of the Great Ming to be at risk.
Arughtai invades
our border every year.
How the people have suffered.
When I think of this,
how it hurts me so.
They can scold me for being ambitious.
Let them.
Scold me for being warmongering.
Even
if I leave a bad name,
I'll never allow the Great Ming to be trampled on.
Let alone the displacement
of the Great Ming's people.
My child,
your father has read many books
written by men of virtues.
He's been confused by a bunch of bookworms.
Since you think
that old thing from the Ministry
of Revenue is still useful,
I'll leave him to you, then.
Grandfather,
you've been on the throne for more than 20 years.
Many countries pay tribute to you.
How many
emperors from the past dynasties
had led a war expedition
themselves?
Do the imperial royal court ministers
even know of your aspiration and vision?
There are not many emperors
who'd brave the wind and rain.
Yet, many ministers are short-sighted.
After everything has been said,
only flattering works.
What other good words do you have
that are pleasant to hear?
Zhanji,
have you completed the task I asked of you?
Go and do it now.
Go on now.
Zhanji,
after I return with triumph,
let's go hunting together.
Yes.
I'll take my leave.
(In April, 22nd year of Yongle's Reign,)
(Zhu Di led hundreds of thousands of troops)
(for a fifth military campaign
to the northern desert)
(and ordered the Crown Prince
to manage the state affairs.)
(In June,)
(the Great Ming Army reached Dolon Nor River.)
(Arughtai fled upon hearing the news.)
(The Ming army searched the valley
for 300 li but found nothing.)
(The military provisions were running out.)
(Zhu Di called back the troops.)
(In July,)
(the Emperor reached Khailas-ausu.)
(Zhu Zhanji returned to Beijing to raise
military provisions under a secret order.)
(Soon,)
(a piece of news enough to shake the world)
(followed.)
Table Maid Yao,
don't you have anything to say to me?
I fear.
But you don't look frightened.
In March, I left in a hurry
after meeting Grandfather.
I only stayed for three days
when I returned in May.
I didn't summon you on purpose.
I wanted to see if you'll come to see me.
After not seeing each other for a long time,
don't you have anything to say to me?
Your Highness,
the Imperial Food Service prepared
[Braised Rabbit]
this braised rabbit, especially for you.
Matron Hu made this herself.
How could
you cook the rabbit I brought back
for you?
Your Highness, this...
I wrote to you.
But you only replied to me a month later.
I asked someone to send you a gift.
Yet, you braised it.
How touching to have such
a dedicated female official
like you.
What is so funny?
Your Highness,
it's a different rabbit.
The one you gave me escaped a long time ago.
How could I keep it until now?
I haven't been around for a long time.
Don't you miss me at all?
Your Highness,
I...
Your Highness.
Speak.
Your Highness?
Stay at the Imperial Food Service.
Don't go anywhere.
-Your Highness...
-Father!
You left too suddenly.
My heart is breaking!
Your Highness, calm down.
You're harming your health
from mourning too much.
You must take care of your health.
Your Highness...
Father...
Where's the Great Imperial Grandson?
Your Highness,
Official Yang Rong and Haishou returned
to convey the report in secret.
The moment the Great Imperial Grandson
heard the news,
he left the capital to retrieve
the deceased emperor
after reporting to the Crown Prince.
If the imperial court hears of this,
everyone will surely be afraid.
Convey my decree.
Seal this information.
When the Great Imperial Grandson returns
to the capital with the coffin,
we'll announce the death.
Yes, Your Highness.
Your Majesty...
(In August, 22nd year of Yongle's Reign,)
(The Crown Prince summons
the Imperial Grandson to receive the coffin)
(and mourn in the Kaiping encampment.)
Be careful.
Get down first.
Hurry.
Grandfather,
we agreed to go hunting in Nanhaizi
when you return from your expedition.
Now, the bow is here.
But where are you?
You always kept your word
and never went back on your words.
But why is this the only time
you lied to me?
Why?
[Xingyun Cottage]
Your Majesty, the name list.
Your Majesty.
What?
Your Majesty,
after our fore founder's death,
all 40 concubines of the imperial harem
were buried along with him.
According to the ancestral law set
by our fore founder,
any concubines who have no children
shall be buried along.
How many of them?
One hundred and sixteen
shall be buried along.
Your Majesty...
Wait.
Yes, Your Majesty.
According to the old practice,
the families of these concubines
shall be compensated.
Their fathers and brothers shall inherit
1,000 imperial guards.
Consort Zhuang has served Father for a long time.
We must send her off properly.
Go.
Yes, Your Majesty.
[Chunyou Gate]
You're not allowed to enter.
Her Majesty has conveyed her edict
to give preferential treatment
to Consort Zhuang.
Moreover,
we must feed the concubines
before sending them off.
Why make it difficult for Consort Zhuang?
Consort Zhuang,
this is the sweet walnut dessert
you frequently mentioned.
Please try it.
Does it still taste the same?
Not the same.
It doesn't taste the same as the one
my mother makes.
Help me.
Please help me.
Consort Zhuang,
please get up.
We'll always remember how much you care for us.
But we're just lowly maidservants
from the Imperial Food Service.
To be buried with the Emperor
is the ancestral law.
How can we go against that?
The burial is
after sunset today.
Help me leave the palace.
Help me leave.
Consort Zhuang,
are you...
Her Majesty refuses to see us.
I had no way to plead with her.
I'm not running away.
I only want to see my mother.
She has no sons
and no one to rely on.
I'm not asking for anything else.
I only need to see her once.
Even if
it's the last goodbye.
I'll return after I bid farewell to her.
Please help me.
Please!
I'll return after I bid farewell.
I...
I only want to see my mother one last time.
It's just a small request.
Can't you fulfill it?
You want to leave the palace?
Consort Zhuang,
there are only three of us here.
If you don't return before sunset,
all three of us will pay with our lives.
You have ways to send me out of the palace?
That's great.
I swear
I'll return.
I swear I'll return.
All right. Come back before sunset.
Yao Zijin!
You know that I'm going to die soon.
So you're brushing me off with this thing!
Leave!
All of you, go!
Get out!
Consort Zhuang!
Get out! All of you!
What's the matter, Your Highness?
Your Highness, calm down.
I'll prepare a new one and send it over.
(Today is the fourth day of the week.)
(They would usually set up
a market outside of Xuanwu Gate,)
(where you can go out with a token.)
(But the market has been suspended
because of the funeral.)
(Those who go in and out are those)
(who run errands for their respective bureaus.)
(As you walk ahead,)
(when you run into the patrol guards,)
(show them your token)
(and tell them)
(the number of ingredients sent
by the Palace Condiments Service is wrong.)
(So Matron Hu sends you to ask for an explanation.)
Next.
Token.
What's your problem?
I'm lining up here.
I came first.
What's wrong with me standing in front?
Why are you being unreasonable?
Do you know where you are?
Don't make a scene here.
Leave now!
Take them away!
Come with us.
Let's go.
No, it's her fault.
Go!
(After you get out from Xuanwu Gate,)
(the hardest obstacle to overcome
will be the Bei'an Gate.)
You have such a kind heart.
You prepared food seriously
for a person who's going to die.
That's all the more reason
not to argue with her.
When she's full,
only then can she go in peace.
Go in, then.
[Yongning Gate]
Why?
You're right.
I helped her in the past to gain some benefit.
But she's going to be buried alive soon.
She's someone of no value anymore.
Why do
you take such a risk to help her?
Why are you looking at me?
Did I say anything wrong?
We did prepare this sweet walnut dessert
according to Consort Zhuang's method.
Why doesn't it taste the same?
She's going to die soon.
Why care about the taste?
Fine.
Even if she manages
to pass Xuanwu Gate,
how will she pass Bei'an Gate?
I heard there are hundreds of guards
at all 18 post guards.
It's hard for her to escape even if she has wings.
Zijin,
if we bring her back now,
we can still make amends for our mistakes.
What do you think?
Zijin?
Zijin!
Could it be the walnuts?
Yao Zijin!
Only you'd trust her!
If I had the chance
to escape like her,
I'd leave the palace as far as I could.
Her Highness will come back.
She never goes back on her words.
In the face of death,
anyone would become selfish and weak.
No one is an exception.
You didn't have to send food just now.
Why did you come back?
Aren't you scared of death?
You'll be scared if you're alone.
Ziping,
she'll come back.
I knew it.
Nobody will come back and die.
Liar.
Yao Zijin,
you're such a fool.
Go!
Come on.
Hurry.
There's Consort Zhuang
from Yongning Palace left.
Quickly now!
Miss Yao.
Light up.
They'll be here soon.
Hurry!
We're almost there.
There's no time to waste. Hurry up.
Yes.
Leave.
Leave now.
Ziping.
Don't worry about implicating those
from Yongning Palace.
I'll stay.
Why are you saying that?
I was supposed to die.
I'm paying you with my life this time.
We'll no longer owe each other.
Why?
When my whole family died,
I was the only one who survived.
Do you think
it was my younger brother
who opened the cricket jar?
So you now know what kind of monster
you've been treating with kindness.
Leave now.
I'm not leaving.
Leave!
Ziping!
Open the gate.
Yes.
Why is it locked?
Knock.
Yes.
-Open the gate!
Open the gate now!
Open the gate!
Open it!
Yes.
I'll be serving His Majesty soon.
So I'll naturally have to dress up.
Who allowed you to behave insolently?
How rude of you.
Your Highness,
this way, please.
I thought Consort Zhuang would never return.
But
how did she pass Bei'an Gate?
Zijin.
Zijin?
What's the matter?
I thought you love crisp cake.
It's such a tasty crisp cake.
I can't help
but savor every bit of it when I eat it.
I don't know why
it doesn't taste as good now.
There are still some
of the ingredients left I used
for Consort Zhuang's sweet walnut dessert.
What's wrong?
Where do these come from?
The walnuts are from the Liao county
and Lingbao red dates.
These are high-quality tributes.
Over here.
The Medicines Office sent these ingredients
for medicinal food preparation.
It may be big.
But it's not as sweet and crisp as those walnuts.
It has an astringent taste too.
What is she doing?
It's too late to make sweet walnut dessert now.
Is it for Consort Zhuang?
The number of ingredients delivered is getting
more and more laxly.
The quantity of fragrant rice,
dried fruits, antlers,
and sea produce
from the East Sea is also not tally.
Directress Wang refused to accept them.
If I didn't try to persuade her,
she would have gone and questioned
the Court of Imperial Entertainments.
I see.
I fear Directress Wang might be too stubborn.
If she finds out...
I'll take care of it.
Yes.
Find out
where Zijin went today.
I don't need your help.
Your Highness!
Zijin!
Watch your manners.
Your Highness,
I've made a bowl of sweet walnut dessert for you.
Please try it.
Directress Wang,
I just want to do one last thing for her.
Zijin.
Ziping,
hurry.
Yes.
This is the flavor
of the sweet walnut dessert my mother made
when I was a child in Jiangnan.
Your Highness,
no matter how high-quality the ingredient is,
the best taste in the world
is the memory of one's hometown.
I'm sorry.
I lied to you.
When I left the Forbidden City,
I never planned to return.
But I've frightened the sedan chair bearers away.
I could only carry my mother on my back,
knocking on every door.
(But our clan members who clung on us in the past)
(dared not to defy the imperial decree
and take us in.)
(But I couldn't walk)
(any longer.)
Even if I have a pair of wings,
I can never leave this place.
Your Highness, it's time to go.
My last moment in the world
is warm.
Your Highness.
His Majesty has arrived!
His Majesty is here!
Are you here to see her off, Your Majesty?
I'm willing to die today.
Please remember your promise to me, Your Majesty.
Take good care of my mother
and don't let her be homeless
without anyone to rely on.
Your Majesty,
you must not defy the ancestral law.
Zijin.
Mother,
I'm leaving now.
Your Highness!
Your Highness, are you all right?
Leave me.
So
do you understand it now?
Insolence!
Concubines without children
will be buried with the Emperor.
Ministers with meritorious deeds are exempted
from death by law.
Besides,
His Majesty is healthy.
I just don't have
the heart to see that.
When our fore founder died,
some concubines who had children
were also buried with the Emperor.
Why don't you
think about the person who'll decide your fate?
You...
Your Highness,
you're trembling.
Let me send you back to your palace.
Ziping.
Ziping!
Yin Ziping!
Ziping.
Zijin.
Quickly!
Come back here!
Where are you going?
You know how to pass Bei'an Gate, right?
The whole country is mourning day and night.
We still have a chance.
Come on. Let's go.
Come back.
Tell me
why do you want to leave.
Martyrdom.
Those are for the concubines only.
We're maidservants of the Imperial Food Service.
Then promise me
that you'll ignore the Great Imperial Grandson.
Don't be a concubine.
We'll just work as female officials.
All right?
Ziping.
No matter how valuable the life
of luxury and gourmet is
means nothing in the face of death.
You saw what happened today.
I fear you'll end up like Consort Zhuang.
Rest assured.
I won't.
If you become a concubine
without any children,
you'll have to be buried with the Emperor.
As female officials,
we fear losing our lives
if we make mistakes.
If we leave the palace today,
we have no direction.
The whole city is under curfew.
How will we leave the capital?
How can we make a living
as girls?
Even if we start a business,
how do we sustain it?
Zijin,
what are we supposed to do now?
All the land belongs to the Emperor.
Do you think Consort Zhuang wanted to stay?
She wanted to leave.
But where can she go?
Even if she managed to escape,
her entire family members would be executed.
Escape?
We can never escape.
Since we can't run,
we'll just stay.
Ziping,
making people sacrificial objects is not right.
The way of the world is not right.
If it's not right, it must be corrected.
But that's ancestral law.
Even the Crown Prince can't openly...
I'm not afraid.
Ziping,
don't be scared.
Always remember
when there's a will, there's a way.
Think about it.
Whether it's a female official,
a concubine,
or even the common folks,
who has no difficulties?
There will always be a way.
No matter where I go
or how far I go,
as long as I have a companion
and am not alone,
I can walk far
with this belief.
The end
may be the way out.
(Directress Hu,)
(this is the medicinal cuisine I've written.)
(Can you spare some time to look at it?)
(She gave Consort Zhuang a jade pendant.)
(That's how Consort Zhuang managed
to pass Bei'an Gate.)
What kind of jade pendant?