Your Highness, why don't you try
which dessert you prefer?
For the winner,
Your Highness,
we'll grant one wish.
How about that?
These two
are playing games again.
What kind of wish?
If I win,
Your Highness will give me the sword in your chamber.
What do you say?
If I win,
Princess,
you'll divorce your first husband
and
copy the Women's Code 100 times.
How about that?
You're insane!
I'm a royal princess.
Why would I copy the Women's Code?
Your Highness should learn
how women should be faithful,
instead of having one
while eyeing another.
How dare you speak to Her Highness like that!
Do you have a death wish?
Mu Yunfan!
Today,
I'll make you feel what it's like to be a subordinate.
Fine!
I choose the mung bean pastry.
But you haven't
even tasted it yet.
No need to taste.
Just by looking at it,
I can tell the mung bean pastry is delicious.
Nange,
my second husband left without my permission.
How should he be punished?
Beat him to death.
That's too harsh.
How about this:
I'm in a good mood today,
so I'll give you a chance.
If you can make
a dessert tastier than this mung bean pastry...
I'll let you off the hook
What do you say?
It's a deal.
Mu Yunfan,
how the mighty have fallen.
Try this.
It tastes awful.
Fine.
It smells terrible.
Take it away.
Just take one bite.
Get it out of here!
Alright.
Are you
losing your hair?
Are you just trying to pick a fight?
Forget it.
You
can't make any good desserts anymore.
Bring me the previous one to taste.
No need.
I'll make you a new one.
Just wait.
I'll go make you a new one.
Three Cup Chicken.
Eat up.
It looks delicious.
Is it good?
It's not good.
It's terrible.
But this is what you
used to beg for every day.
You must be mistaken.
I
never eat the same food twice.
Your Highness,
are you deliberately making things difficult for Master Yun?
At least some people are reasonable.
Female lead
Jiang Weiyang
So beautiful.
Little Weiyang
Come here.
Come on.
You be the judge.
Between what they made,
whose tastes better?
Young Master Wei
No.
Wait.
Weren't you just defending me?
Him giving you a hard time
and Wei's pastries being delicious
aren't mutually exclusive.
His Highness's private affairs
are not for you to comment on.
Nange.
Your Highness,
it's been a long time.
The female lead is holding my arm.
Let me treat you all
to dinner in my private room.
Yes, of course.
I'm getting hungry anyway.
Neither of their cooking tastes good.
You two gentlemen should join us too.
Go.
How am I going to tell Xu
that I came here to take him away?
I can't let His Highness discover
my relationship with Weiyang.
Miss Jiang and the eldest young master
are old lovers.
How does he know?
What do you mean 'old lovers'?
I never agreed to separate.
The second young master is joking.
Miss Jiang and I
are complete strangers.
Xu,
how can you pretend not to know me?
What does Mu Yunfan mean by this?
He exposed the relationship between Jiang Weiyang and Wei Shixu.
He was on a mission
to make me divorce my husband.
He clearly has an old flame
yet still insisted on becoming the Princess's husband.
This behavior that damages male virtue,
Princess,
how do you think it should be dealt with?
According to the plot,
I die after divorcing Wei Shixu.
Mu Yunfan,
you're really ruthless.
With the original owner's temperament,
she would definitely divorce her husband.
Otherwise, my judgment yesterday was correct.
You are Su Jinli.
Your Highness,
this is Lidu liquor.
It's very strong.
That's exactly what I want.
I have never met Miss Jiang before.
You and the prince
are in love with each other.
That's really not necessary.
At most, what I did to you was
stealing your love.
It's really strong indeed.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm feeling dizzy.
I need to stop eating.
I can't drive now.
Mr. Mu, you should call for a designated driver.
What did you say?
You know who I am,
but you refuse to acknowledge me.
Axu,
I'm here to take you away.
Weiyang.
I can't turn back now.
I hope
you won't waste
your time on me anymore.
It's not worth it.
Miss,
are you alright?
Axu.
Why did this happen?
Sir.
It seems this Yun fellow
will be my biggest obstacle in obtaining the will.
Should I take care of him?
Before we find out more about him,
don't act rashly.
You're quite heavy.
How dare you say I'm heavy!
It's all your fault.
I almost died here.
After all these years,
you still haven't broken your biting habit.
It's none of your business.
Leave me alone.
Where are you going?
You're drunk.
I'll take you home.
Don't pull me.
I'm not drunk.
Am I usually asleep at this hour?
No, I'm not.
I'm working as your assistant.
I want to eat peach blossom pastries
and peach blossom soup.
I'll pay you.
I have plenty of money.
Make them for me.
Right now.
I want peach blossom pastries,
lamp wick cakes,
and sour jujube cakes.
You're being ridiculous.
Am I more ridiculous than you?
I'm at least a creative team leader.
I manage two people.
Yet I'm serving you tea and water every day.
Don't I have any dignity?
Do you think it's easy for me?
Alright.
Stop crying.
Don't cry.
Get up.
Stand up.
So beautiful.
Do you realize what you're doing?
Of course I do.
It's just a kiss.
It's not like we haven't kissed before.
Did you know who I was all along?
Yes, I did.
You're the one who peeled grapes for me.
You even fed me.
Who did you mistake me for?