At your age,
why are you still going along with her nonsense?
Do you think I can't see what's going on?
I wouldn't dare, sir.
It's just that
the princess and the second young master
truly have deep feelings for each other.
I couldn't bear to break her heart.
The imperial doctor
was instructed by me to say so.
If you're angry, my lord,
please punish me instead.
The Second Young Master
and his wife are deeply in love.
Why
did she choose that merchant Wei again?
Well,
I didn't know beforehand.
But
judging from today's situation,
the First Young Master
seems to have a grudge with the Chancellor.
The Princess was protecting his life
and had to give up the one she loved.
Whose child is it?
Say that again.
I have no marital relations with Your Highness.
Why did Your Highness lie to save me?
The City Lord granted amnesty,
but do you think the Chancellor will spare you?
The Chancellor.
The Second Young Master will at least be safe at Lanfeng House.
We'll make further plans later.
So be it.
At least she's still a person who values relationships.
But that Yun Lang,
don't let him suffer too much.
I have already sent word to Lanfeng House.
I believe they won't dare to mistreat him.
Hand.
Buttocks.
Chest.
That's right.
Lift your head.
Come.
Everyone stop for a moment.
Let me introduce someone to you all.
This person
is our former top performer at Lanfeng House, Yun Lang.
He was before,
and will be again.
All of you
need to get along well.
Understood?
He was returned by the Princess's mansion.
You talk too much.
Ignore him.
You
should rehearse well with them.
Go on.
Start dancing from this part.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Remember that?
Just this section.
Let's begin.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four, five,
hands up,
seven, eight.
Two, two, three,
come over,
three, four, five, six, seven, eight,
go back.
What's this?
Acting like a spoiled Second Young Master with me?
I won't tolerate this behavior.
If you want to make a living entertaining guests at Lanfeng House,
then you must listen to me.
If you're so capable, have Her Highness redeem you again.
I heard the City Lord made Her Highness choose between the two of you,
and she chose the First Young Master.
Her Highness really understands the principle of first come, first served.
Are you crazy?
How dare you hit someone!
Gossiping about Her Highness's private affairs.
Do you know what crime that is?
Your Highness.
Why don't you go beg the city lord
to exchange me for the Second Master?
Impossible.
If you go to prison,
you won't survive till tomorrow.
So you knew about me all along.
I did.
But I can't give you what you want right now.
If you're willing to leave this residence...
I'm not willing.
Your Highness.
I will definitely help you rescue the Second Master.
Your Highness,
the Second Young Master has been sent back to Lanfeng House.
Isn't this Yunlang, the former top courtesan of Lanfeng House?
Still as beautiful as ever.
Isn't this the Princess?
Ladies, please show some restraint.
What an honored guest!
So handsome indeed.
You dare stop me?
Is this how Lanfeng House treats its distinguished guests?
Your Highness,
please don't take offense.
The City Lord has ordered
that all entertainment houses
are forbidden to let you enter.
Our Lanfeng House...
Mu Yunfan!
I'm here.
I'm already a discarded pawn to Your Highness.
Don't worry about me.
What do you mean by that?
You should know why I'm doing this.
Your Highness's feelings run deep,
I understand that,
but our Lanfeng House
isn't a place you can visit just because of feelings.
Besides, even if our Yunlang were willing,
given the Princess's current situation,
I'm afraid you can't afford our top courtesan anymore.
Take my advice,
please leave.
Go now.
Go.
Your Highness,
please eat something at least.
If all else fails, I'll just abduct him back.
I'll go with you.
Calm down.
Lanfeng House is an official music establishment.
Are you trying to accuse His Highness
of treason?
Wait.
Can we buy someone's contract from Lanfeng House?
Let's buy his freedom.
With our household's current situation,
we can hardly afford
even a meal at Lanfeng House.
I have money.
Yangyang,
what brings you here?
Please sit down.
I've sent someone to inquire.
Today is Yunlang's first performance.
Many noble ladies from Hongcheng
will be attending to show their support.
This Lanfeng Pavilion
is too influential to offend.
They've finally decided
to auction off Yunlang's first performance,
to the highest bidder.
You need to go bid.
I've already reserved our seats.
Here it is.
Your Highness,
put on these servant's clothes
and come in with me.
Looking at today's turnout,
Lanfeng Pavilion
will likely fetch an astronomical price.
I secretly...
You brought money from home.
Are you still the Yangyang I know?
You even stole money from home.
Your Highness,
you once told me
I am you
and you are me.
Even though I don't quite understand,
as long as it's something you want to do,
I'll definitely help you.
Yangyang,
you're so kind.
I'll go change my clothes then.
Yangyang,
thank you.
Cheers.
Everyone, quiet down please.
Distinguished guests,
please welcome tonight's
main attraction.
Allow me to formally introduce
this gentleman,
who was once the legendary
top courtesan Yun Lang of our Lanfeng House.
As everyone knows,
our Princess Jinli
once paid a fortune to buy Yun Lang's freedom
and took him into her residence as her second consort.
Our Yun Lang
excels in emotional intelligence, talent, and beauty,
all in equal measure.
Tonight,
he goes to the highest bidder.
Starting bid:
500 taels.
Someone rejected by the Princess's household
isn't worth much.
I'll add one tael.
501 taels.
That's not entirely true.
I've heard that
just to see this Yun Lang,
Princess Jinli
was waiting outside Lanfeng House in the middle of the night,
desperately hoping for a glimpse of him.
I bid 600 taels.
This young lady is right!
600 taels.
800 taels.
Miss Jiang bids 800 taels.
850 taels.
1,000 taels.
Miss Jiang bids 1,000 taels.
1,500 taels.
2,000 taels.
A gold bracelet.
A jade hairpin.
A priceless luminous pearl.
Miss Jiang,
a luminous pearl!
Miss Jiang has offered a priceless jade pendant.
Going once for Miss Jiang.
Going twice for Miss Jiang.
Congratulations to Miss Jiang,
you've won.
Miss Jiang,
please come upstairs.
Thank you, miss,
for paying such a high price for me.
I'd like to toast to you.
Wait.
We should drink like this
to set the mood.
You've spent a fortune.
From today on,
I belong to you.
I have many talents
that will surely please you.
Why don't
we get started right now?
Mu Yunfan, that's enough!
Are you getting carried away with your act?
You're the one who's carried away.
You abandoned me for a game character
and let my child call another man father.
Child?
Are you stupid?
I made that up in a desperate moment.
Couldn't you tell?
You lied to me.
No, I didn't.
I was trying to save someone.
Then why didn't you save me first?
I was saving you!
You knew very well at that time
I had to save Wei Shixu first.
Once he was out of prison,
the Chancellor had ten thousand ways to kill him.
What would happen to you if he died?
Do you still want to complete your mission and go back?
I know.
I know everything.
You know?
You knew and still pulled that stunt just now?
Even though I know,
it still hurts.
Why is there always some random man
chosen over me?
By what right?
can you abandon me
time and time again without a second thought?
Don't think like that.
I just thought
staying at Lanfeng House would be better than prison.
Besides,
you get good food and drink here,
and don't have to suffer.
Right?
Not suffering?
Who told you I'm not suffering?
Really?
That madam...
I even gave her money
to take good care of you.
This won't do.
I'm going to settle this with her.
By order of the City Lord,
we're inspecting Lanfeng House.
No one is allowed to leave.
Nange.
Madam,
may I ask what you're searching for this time?
We'll fully cooperate with you.
Obviously, Lanfeng House
has some unwelcome visitors.
This is bad.
The City Lord's people are here to arrest me.
I'll take you to Miss Jiang's private room.
Follow me.
Axu,
Nange,
go to the back door and wait.
I'll notify His Highness.
Alright.
It's that Princess Jinli causing trouble again.
It must be her.
Who else could it be?
Can't even have a drink in peace.
She's truly arrogant and domineering.
Work with me.