♫ Oh my baby, don't you, don't you wanna chase me? ♫
♫ You're my rabbit, I want to hold you tight ♫
♫ You're my baby, the alarm keeps ringing all because of you ♫
♫ Don't be shy anymore ♫
♫ It's getting out of control, where do I hide? ♫
♫ My heart is beating, who dares to cross this line first? ♫
♫ Day and night, who said there were rules? ♫
♫ One positive and negative encounter will cancel each other out ♫
♫ What? What do I not have? ♫
♫ Let it go, love is in your hands ♫
♫ Ask me directly, speak out ♫
♫ I love you more and more and more ♫
♫ Oh my baby, don't you, don't you wanna chase me? ♫
♫ You're my rabbit, I want to hold you tight ♫
♫ You're my baby, the alarm keeps ringing all because of you ♫
♫ Don't be shy anymore ♫
♫ What? What do I not have? ♫
♫ Let it go, love is in your hands ♫
♫ Ask me directly, speak out ♫
♫ I love you more and more and more ♫
[Plus and Minus]
[Chapter 10: Trigonometric Functions]
Mr. Zheng.
Big Brother Yuki.
Ling Ling.
I walked and spoke so softly that I didn't scare away the cat.
Ling Ling, what are you doing here by yourself?
Dad must be overworking again.
Did you have a fight with my dad?
I meddle in other people's affairs too much.
I don't think so.
I also thought those clothes were taking up too much space.
You were just helping him take care of them, that's all.
A lot of times, we think that we're helping others resolve their issues,
but we often neglect to communicate with them.
Were you like that before?
No, not really.
Well, then why are you being like this now?
I also don't know.
Big Brother Yuki, do you hate my dad?
I really like your dad.
Big Brother, let me tell you. Ever since my parents got divorced,
I've never seen my dad so happy.
I've also been very happy, as I've gotten to know you and your dad.
Well, can you give my dad another chance then? Please?
What are you doing here so early?
This is for you.
Oh, you're giving me a flower now.
Just give me a couple of minutes, I'll be ready soon.
Why did you want to come to the baseball field?
Fu Ligong!
Thank you for liking me!
I really...
really... really like you!
We've come all this way. Do you want to play for a bit?
What are you lost in thought for? Hurry up!
Zheng Zeshou!
We're breaking up!
♫ This feeling... I'm still infatuated ♫
♫ A line that can't be crossed ♫
♫ That moment... of touching ♫
♫ Only exists between positive and negative ♫
What did you just say?
We're breaking up.
Why?
I realized I don't love you as much as I thought.
What are you saying?
Why is this happening all of a sudden?
Did I do something wrong?
I'm the one that made a mistake.
I always thought that I liked you,
but after we started dating,
I realized that I wasn't happy.
Haven't you liked me for a long time?
Didn't you say that we'd face things together?
Didn't you say that you'd always be by my side?
If there's something wrong, just tell me!
Fu Ligong!
Zheng Zeshou.
You lied to me.
I didn't lie to you.
I'll still be by your side.
It's just... that our relationship needs to change.
Zheng Zeshou.
Although we can't be lovers, we can still be friends.
We'll always be best friends.
♫ Carved in my bones and engraved in my heart,
I long to see you again ♫
♫ My longing for you still resides in that room ♫
♫ I want to hold you again, to hold you tighter ♫
Friends? That's nonsense.
♫ I wish you could feel how I feel ♫
Hello?
Brother.
What's wrong?
Mom... passed away.
You left us over twenty years ago.
I would have been lying if I said I didn't hate you at that time.
But what good is hate, anyway?
One must still get through one's days.
But I couldn't stop myself from wondering...
whether you...
were struggling or not,
or if something had happened to you,
or if you...
one day...
one day... might need or want me.
Why did you already look like this...
when you returned?
I rehearsed the words in my head ten thousand times,
but I couldn't say a single sentence.
Thank you.
For still thinking of me and our children, in the end.
You must...
You must return often.
You must return often, to see me and the children.
I've taken care of everything.
What are you doing?
Why didn't you accompany your dad and Xueqing?
I asked you, what are you doing?
I came to return your things to you.
Do you know?
When I was accompanying my dad as he laid my mother to rest...
I saw...
what it means to give without complaint nor regret.
Fu Ligong, how about we give...
I have some things to do. I'm going to go.
What are you in a daze for? Amy and the others are working much more earnestly than you today.
I'm just thinking about some things.
Are you thinking about Jian Yingze?
I acted presumptuously and angered him.
I don't want to know any details about it, thank you.
I'd never considered changing for a person before.
People more or less change themselves
when they fall in love.
Sometimes, so much so, that one feels that they're not much themselves anymore.
Perhaps, I will meet someone that I like one day.
And then, I'll also try to change.
Sis, you're in love.
Liking someone and being in love are two different things.
Liking someone can be one-sided.
Falling in love involves two separate people.
And it's a process of trying to reach a balance with another.
Sis, I want to take some time off.
I have to save something.
[A small restaurant for big meals]
Brother.
- Dad.
- What?
- Brother is here.
Dad.
What... What are you doing here?
I'm sorry.
I...
In the past, I've always hurt the most important person to you.
My mother.
I'm very sorry.
I haven't been very good at being by your side during this time,
and I hadn't felt your sadness.
I'm not a decent son.
Come, come. Since you've returned, let's eat.
Brother.
Come, let's eat.
Don't think so much.
We still have to get through our days, and we must still eat.
If your mom could hear you now, she would certainly be happy.
There's no need to worry about me.
I have you two, and that's enough.
Quickly, let's eat.
[Forever]
♫ Who cares about me chasing you when I can't hold your hand ♫
♫ How can it be seen as invisible, thus the pain
in my heart hides ♫
Do you still remember...
what you said to me that day when we were at the batting cages?
You were afraid that you couldn't follow me around everywhere.
You were afraid that the more you liked me,
the further I'd be away from you.
And you were afraid that we wouldn't be able to return to how things were.
You told me, we'd face the future together.
But I can't see a future for us.
I've thought about it a lot,
but at least we can still be best friends and brothers.
Brothers?
Yes.
Regardless of what happens, I will always be your brother.
♫ When the people around you can only give a silent reaction ♫
Do you know?
♫ You mean the world to me ♫
Being with you...
felt like I had a good student's grades given to me by accident.
For a split second,
I felt like I held the whole world in my hands.
This is over, but we'll still have our own futures.
We must continue to move forward.
And we'll still be in each other's lives.
♫ There are too many things in my heart that I can't say ♫
♫ But I'm still right behind you and I have nothing to ask for ♫
♫ Can you give me another reason to cheer you up, okay? ♫
♫ I don't have any memories in your world ♫
♫ When the people around you can only give a silent reaction ♫
♫ It would be nice if you told me, "I love you." ♫
♫ You mean the world to me, my love ♫
♫ Forget about what's right or wrong ♫
♫ If we meet again someday in the future ♫
Fu Ligong.
♫ Will you remember the promises we made to each other? ♫
♫ Forgive me for being impulsive ♫
♫ You were locked in my heart at that time ♫
As long as I live, I will never forget your love.
♫ Can you give me another reason to cheer you up, okay? ♫
♫ I don't have any memories in your world ♫
♫ When the people around you can only give a silent reaction ♫
[Forever]
♫ This time I won't let go ♫
♫ ...of your hands ♫
You're here. Just give me a moment.
No problem, I'm not in a hurry.
Yuki brought all of this here.
He knows that I like to brew coffee,
so he grabbed a small table, chairs, and utensils.
They're...
Just here for the time being.
The laundromat must stay open.
Did you want to grab Lawyer Zheng's clothes as well?
Sure. Sorry to bother you.
I think this is pretty good.
I think that combining a coffee shop with a laundromat is a pretty good idea.
Oh, she's done. She's out of class by now.
- Dad.
- Hey.
Hi.
And this is...?
Didn't you say that you'd already thrown them away?
Brother Yuki collected them and brought them back,
but I told him there was no need for that. He didn't listen to me.
Ling Ling, go and change your clothes first,
then we'll all have dinner together in a bit. Okay?
All right. Let's go.
You go ahead and wait for me. Okay?
All right.
I shouldn't have thrown away these clothes without asking you about them first.
I'm sorry, I could only recover these pieces.
It's okay.
I made a mistake, too.
Perhaps, these clothes... will never be picked up by anyone.
I just think it's really a pity.
They were just thrown away.
However, I also shouldn't have betrayed your good intentions.
Are you... willing to forgive me?
Are you willing to hand these clothes over to me?
So you two are... done then?
Did he agree to the breakup?
I've decided to go on a blind date.
I know that he and I both have our own individual paths to continue on.
But I don't know how to forget him.
Every morning... and every afternoon...
and every night.
I remember his enchanting and charming smile.
- Hey, I'm not ready yet.
- No problem, let's just take one more.
Here, I'll give you another chance.
Three... two... one...
You didn't look at the camera.
I think it's cute. Come on, let's take one more.
Three... two... one...
When you discover that what wakes you up every day,
isn't your alarm clock,
but rather, the reality that he has already left...
Perhaps, we should all raise up our glass and cheers to this cute and annoying love.
You're really not yourself today. You've become quite talkative.
I don't know who I am anymore.
- Lawyer Fu, long time no see!
- Hello.
I'm really sorry about last time.
The last time truly scared me.
I wondered how lawyers could end up doing such a thing.
Fortunately, you've returned.
However, I see that you are very nice and polite.
And you wish to go on a blind date.
Are there no women that like you?
No.
Well, they're blind then.
However, let me tell you. You don't need to date those girls out there that are unsure of what they want.
The girls that I introduce to you will certainly be suitable.
But I do want to ask you. As a lawyer, are you very tired?
What I mean is, it's not important whether you're busy or not, I'm simply afraid that...
Hello, my name is Mr. Fu.
Nikita, what are you doing here?
Didn't you say that you hated going on blind dates?
I'm very curious.
Why are you doing something that you don't enjoy?
People can change.
This is how I am today.
But I may be different tomorrow.
So are you... changing yourself...
because of him?
Yuki told me that day,
that he thought we were very similar.
Especially, in regards to emotions.
We are both the type of people...
who rush to find out the answer... when we are confused.
Have you found your answer?
Mr. Fu, hello.
And this is...?
I'm his girlfriend, hello.
What kind of game are you playing? You have a girlfriend and you're still going on blind dates?
Take care!
Why did you do that?
Didn't you say that life has no absolutes?
Please give me a chance, and go out with me.
Please give loving me a chance.
And please, try and forget about Zheng Zeshou.
I like you.
I want to become your answer.
I also think we're very similar.
Are you willing to change yourself for the one that you like?
I will change myself, for you.
Nikita.
♫ This feeling... I'm still infatuated ♫
♫ A line that can't be crossed ♫
♫ That moment... of touching ♫
♫ Only exists between positive and negative ♫
♫ I love you... ♫
♫ I miss you... ♫
♫ The lies are stuck in my heart inch by inch ♫
♫ Carved in my bones and engraved in my heart,
I long to see you again ♫
♫ My longing for you still resides in that room ♫
♫ I want to hold you again, to hold you tighter ♫
♫ The phrase "I love you" is still on the right side of the bed ♫
♫ I wish you could feel how I feel ♫
Thank you for taking care of me for so long, Uncle Wang.
Zheng Zeshou, pick up the phone!