Scripting Your Destiny: Episode 7
This is your last chance to give up and get out.
Are you sure you won't regret this?
Yes.
It's a pass! A pass! Congratulations!
You clap, too. Hurry.
I just don't get it.
Do you think I do?
You said to come to work at 12:30 tomorrow, right?
I'll get going now.
No need to bring anything. Just bring yourself. Just yourself!
- Are you really going to be like this?
- LIke what?
How do you expect me to hire my landlord as my assistant writer? That's awkward.
Shouldn't it be more comfortable since I'm a landlord?
You can fire me more comfortably.
Even if you fire me, I won't starve nor will my future be hopeless.
Your lines are good.
All right.
But do you know exactly whose assistant writer you've just been hired as?
I know. That you're Writer Yang Mi Soon.
You really did know everything.
But no matter how I look at it, it's so weird.
There are exactly three people who know I'm Yang Mi Soon.
My mom, me, and the RBS station director.
You said it wasn't my mom, and it wasn't me.
- Do you know our station director?
- No, I don't.
Then you really figured it out just by looking at the rental contract?
Let's say it's because of inevitable fate
that your landlord is your assistant writer.
Are you good now?
Not good.
- We haven't fixed this yet.
- Damn ...
Is he in a cult or something? Always talking about fate...
What the. Why is it not moving?
Is he just pretending to leave?
No way. What?
This is totally broken, isn't it?
I'll take 20 hotdogs.
- Hi.
- Are you getting a hotdog, too?
- Huh? Yeah.
I'll take one hotdog.
Give hers first since she's only getting one.
You didn't have to...
You live in this alley, too?
I am in charge of this area, yes.
I'll pay for hers as well.
Yes.
This oppa will buy you one. Enjoy.
Oppa...
You say "Oppa" ... You are probably way younger than me.
What?
You get cuter every time I see you.
No way. Do I have the same symptom as Ho Yoon?
Sunbaenim, this is not about me but about a friend of mine.
Yes, not you but your friend. Let's hear it.
- By the way, what is that?
- It's a hotdog.
You know God of Destiny, Samshin,
God of Land, God of Water, et cetera.
There are lots of gods, you know.
Do the gods experience heartaches
where their hearts throb and break?
Why would anyone go around and spill useless feelings on a human?
Apparently, that's what they say when it's their time to die.
Die?
To be exact, they get eliminated.
What does getting eliminated mean?
All memories are deleted and they disappear from the world for a period of time.
When a god has personal feelings toward a human,
the order of the universe falls apart. So that rule was set.
Recently, one punk...
Well...
- What's that, by the way?
- It' s a hotdog.
Up to what extent does "personal feelings" cover?
Bliss, sorrow, love, hatred.
Sometimes, even a mere shard of pity.
In my 117th or 118th year,
I heard a rumor that someone got eliminated on his first day of being a god.
Really? Who was it?
That I don't know. The higher-ups keep their mouths shut.
He must've fallen in love on his first day.
No.
No.  I heard he saved somebody's life.
Sometimes gods who've been scripting destinies for a long period of time make such mistakes
because they get too close to humans.
But that stupid punk, apparently, did that on his first day in the world.
Where have you been roaming about all day?
- What are you holding in your hands?
- I'm not sure.
Out of bliss, love, sorrow, and hatred, which do you think it is?
What's with you now?
- I've made up my mind.
- Don't!
I've never seen a decision lead to a good outcome.
You know I lived a long time, right?
- What is she eating?
- A hotdog. It's yummy even though it has become cold.
I bet it's killer when it's warm.
I want to wear a school uniform and eat hotdogs.
- I want to go to school!
- School?
That's ridiculous.
No one here has been to school. School, yeah right.
Right?
You're the one who's being ridiculous.
I'm clocking out.
Hey, why did you look at me like that just now?
By chance, have you attended school?
I want to go to school.
When he gets here tomorrow, we'll write the contract first thing.
Standard Employment Contract
Wow, I don't even know his name yet.
Real Estate Rental Contract: Shin Ho Yoon
I see... His name is Shin Ho Yoon.
Shin Ho Yoon!
Oh, I have heard his friend call him that.
Pull yourself together.
Gosh, Mom.  Somebody might think we're newlyweds.
♫  Suddenly, when you look at me  ♫
♫  You seem to see more than anyone before  ♫
♫  I'm all tingles and chills  ♫
Have you gone mad, Go Che Gyeong? Why are you imagining such a thing?
Mom!
I'm imagining weird st—
No, I mean, I think I need to drink a restorative tonic!
RBS
Sky Cash.
It's scheduled to air starting June 12.
I guarantee that next year's grand prize will come from Sky Cash.
All right. Kim Yeong Rae says he'd rather die.
Who'd like to receive next year's grand prize?
Would you like to receive it as a group? Co-direct?
Seriously, no one is going to raise their hand?
Me.
What?
I'll do it.
Mom.
I came at the time you told me to,
I came at the time you told me to, but you must tend to be late.
Mom's not here?
She told me the ten commandments of assistant writers,
gave me coffee, then took off for work.
Ten commandments...
According to number eight on the ten commandments of assistant writers, I should open the door.
What's this? Why are you in this house?
- I got hired as an assistant writer.
- Assistant writer?
- Really?
- Yes.
After Hyung Yeong Rae left, it's been decided today that I'll direct Sky Cash.
Finally, you took your first step toward becoming a famous director.
Assistant writers don't butt in on conversations like this.
I...
I ... I mean, my mom will be happy.
-  You're happy too, right?
- I couldn't ask for more.
I'm here, Ms. Writer!
Oh, Mom's not here right now.
So it was just the two of you here?
Why are you calling the coffee shop owner "Ms. Writer"?
She's not the writer. She is.
I was waiting...
for you to be comfortable enough to tell me, Che Gyeong.
Wait a second.  So right now, I am the only one now who didn't know?
You both knew who I am?
When did you find out?
I've known for quite a long time. Quite a long time.
That's quite vague.
I've known since day one.
Quiet, the two of you and sit down right there.
Did either of you ever tell anyone that I'm Yang Mi Soon?
Never.
You sound so different from when you talk to me.
- When will you clock out?
- I just came to work.
Did you hire him, Writer Go?
What do I do...
Wait... I was only joking.  Did I go too far?
It's not that.
This is the first time someone other than Station Director called me "Writer Go."
I'm just happy.  I had to hide it all this time.
You scared me. You're the best, Writer Go.
Writer Go, we should get to work.
What is he staring at so diligently? I didn't assign him any tasks.
Just now. Clearly...
What's wrong with me these days?
Ten Commandments of an Assistant Writer
Number one. When she asks, "What's the best drama you've seen lately?"
grill her meat.
When she says, "Isn't that writer so good?"
- Which high school did you graduate from?
- Why are you asking?
An interview is standard procedure among others when hiring an assistant
but we skipped all that, so I'm getting to it at least now.
You're saying you have lots of questions.
- What's the next question?
- When was your first love?
Why ask such a personal question when you're hiring an assistant writer?
- You asked me when we first met.
- I don't remember.
First love? Ridiculous.
It's true.
You were dumped. Big time, too.
You had a crush on the prettiest girl in school.  Get to work.
Come up with five incidents from when Geum Gang Seok was in high school.
I'm just surprised.
I've never taken such a long walk with someone before.
When Go Che Gyeong approaches me, my heart heats up.
It throbs when I'm looking at her face.
I can't bear it when our eyes meet.
♫  The slightly crumpled heart again unfolds  ♫
♫  Again, I'll engrave you  ♫
♫  Even if it's too late and we are too far apart it will be us again  ♫
♫  If it is destiny  ♫
Is the time now?  To show her a god's dignity.
Go Che Gyeong
Go Che Gyeong lifts her head and looks at the assistant writer.
Do you want to eat ramen?
I've seen that movie.
Wow. We have a nickel silver pot at home?
In TV dramas and movies, they always cook it in this.
The real cliché of a ramen scene is this.
When a man and a woman eat ramen, they always bite onto a single noodle together.
Then their eyes always meet. Cue romantic sound effect.
You let go. I'm the main writer.
You let go. I'm a god of destiny.
You must be blind to your own fate.
I have no mercy when it comes to food.
You are being competitive over such a weird thing.
No, this is just me cussing.
(TN: "seung-boo-yok" is competitiveness, "yok" is cussing)
All right, don't regret it.
I won!
Wow, what a pretty diary.
Make it a love journal.  You should fall in love next year. Lovey-dovey!
Oh, my, my, my. You're crazy! Crazy! Love, my foot.
Why not? Che Gyeong will take good care of her baby sibling.
I had a tiger dream last night.
No matter how I look at it, it was a conception dream.
You buy it, Mother. Does a tiger mean it's a son?
Hey, I had a tiger dream when I had Che Gyeong.
Could that have been why? Everyone asked if she was my son.
Even when I put on a pink hairpin, everyone said she is fit to become a general.
Everyone said, "She's dashing."
He got it as a gift from a five-year-old boy.
A friend he can't see anymore or something like that.
It's a piece of memory from 20 or 30 years ago.
♫  Carefully realize who you are...  ♫
♫  How you swept away by your lullaby  ♫
What's up?
What do you mean?
How could you put that on your dashboard without any contact info?
How long is "Just a moment"? I was just thinking those thoughts.
If someone is waiting, I'll know. Like just now.
Were you looking down from up above or something?
Go Eun Seon!
♫  Don't you know  ♫
Who's this?
This is my best friend.  This is my assistant
Wow. Go Che Gyeong, you really were a general.
Did you save a country in your past life?
Want me to check?
What?
He has a unique character. Let's go.
Bye.
Go Eun Seon?
Wow, daebak. It's been a gazillion years.  Did you always have this picture?
What?
- Go Eun Seon!
- Shin Ho Yoon!
♫  I wanna make love  ♫
♫  I wanna fallin' love love love love  ♫
♫  Once the moment which brushed by  ♫
♫  Stays with me  ♫
♫  I wanna make love  ♫
♫  I wanna fallin' love love love love  ♫
♫  Once the moment which brushed by  ♫
♫  Stays with me  ♫
♫  Stay where you are  ♫
♫  I wanna make love  ♫