DOCTOR STRANGER
Why are you trying to operate
on my patient without my permission?
What are you doing?
Move the patient to the ward!
Yes, sir.
Let me ask you a favor.
What favor?
If she gets one more shock,
that'll be really dangerous...
I've seen many hundred times more patients
than you've seen so far.
Who do you think you're talking to?
Don't you think this is too much, Dr Cho?
Oh Soo-hyun, shut your mouth.
Those are quite harsh words, sir!
Who do you think you're talking to?
What are you doing in front
of the operating room?
Dr Han, is this how you train
your doctors?
Do you train your doctors
by beating them up?
-What?
-You should stop.
Let go of me!
We didn't do anything yet.
-Let go of me, you little brat!
-That's enough.
Are you okay?
What the hell is happening?
I found the patient.
For our second round.
I found the patient for our second round.
EPISODE 12
Take a look.
You made this fuss because of her?
What do you think it is?
There's bleeding on
the right coronary artery near the stents.
Is that why you wanted to operate on her?
That kind of bleeding isn't that bad.
It might stop naturally,
unless she has a cardiac tamponade.
Don't worry about...
What if she did have a cardiac tamponade?
If a cardiac tamponade happened,
it means the bleeding
probably won't stop naturally.
I'm saying her bleeding isn't something
that can be stopped by medication.
The internal medicine department
will make that decision.
Why don't we make the decision this time?
I hope you remember that you told me
to pick the patient for round two.
So I want this patient
for our second round.
So do I win if I operate on her?
Of course.
You win if you operate
and save the patient.
Okay.
Dr Han?
Let's go.
This whole competition wasn't a bad idea.
Maybe we can do 100 rounds!
If Dr Han operates, you lose!
It doesn't matter
as long as the patient lives.
Dr Park!
Don't worry! Even if I lose this round,
the competition will still be tied.
I can just win the last round, right?
Bye.
Do you think you can do it?
I have no other choice.
The patient might die
if we don't do anything.
The internal medicine department
won't be happy.
I can ask the Chairman directly.
If I tell him that this is because of...
...complications from the first surgery,
he'll allow it.
But...
...what if there's a problem
with this patient?
-What problem?
-This could be a malpractice case.
What if the internal medicine
really screwed up her surgery?
-What year of residency is he?
-He's a third year resident, sir.
The stent procedure is very difficult,
and you let a third year perform it?
I'm sorry, Mr Chairman.
-Leave us.
-I'm sorry.
What should we do, Mr Chairman?
This might evolve into a malpractice suit
if her family finds out
that a resident performed it.
Tell him to not say anything to anyone
and send him to the branch hospital.
Yes, sir.
-The family doesn't know yet, right?
-No, sir.
How about the patient?
She's bleeding a bit,
but it'll stop naturally soon.
I hope so.
Otherwise, everything will be over
for all of us!
Hey, Jae-cheol!
What is this?
It's a hairpin. Let me help you with this.
-How do I look?
-It's really pretty!
Thank you.
You need to hurry and get better
so that I can, too.
Okay.
I want to forget everything
related to you.
-Both you and Hoon...
-Honey...
I'm sick and tired of it all!
Doctor!
Hi. How's your mom doing?
She's okay. Why didn't you operate on her?
Something unexpected came up.
But she'll have surgery soon.
Will you operate?
It could be me, or the chief
of the cardiology department.
-The chief?
-Yes.
His name is Han Jae-joon.
He's not the nicest guy,
but he is good at what he does.
I like you better.
It seems like you're close with your mom.
Of course. She's my mother.
Your mother...
This is Kim Tae-sool.
Prime Minister Jang is looking for you.
Tell him I'm out.
Where should I tell him you are?
Tell him that I'm delivering a doll.
He'll understand.
Is that you, Hoon?
So you don't have a mother?
I don't have a mom like yours.
What do you mean?
You don't want to know.
Your dad is here.
Dad!
You surprised me!
You made a smart move.
What do you mean?
I heard you gave Han Jae-joon
an awesome patient!
Patients are just patients.
Awesome isn't the right word
to describe them.
That patient might end up
in a malpractice suit.
The internal medicine department
really screwed up this time.
They let a third year resident
perform the stent procedure!
I'm sorry, Dr Han.
I can't tell you any more than this.
Tell me just one more thing, Dr Kim.
Did you operate on her?
A resident performing surgery without
consent is a classic malpractice case!
That's not what I want to hear.
-Why?
-What if Dr Han changes his mind?
Why are you worried about it?
If he doesn't do this,
we'll be the winner!
I sometimes really have doubts
about you.
-About what?
-Are you really a doctor?
Am I a patient then?
Sometimes you act like one.
An especially serious one, too.
It's you who are a patient, not me!
Damn it!
So you chose a patient
for the second round?
Yes, sir.
Dr Park suggested, and I accepted.
Really?
Let's take a look.
The rules are simple. If I succeed, I win.
You can't operate on this patient.
If I don't, Dr Park will operate
on the Prime Minister.
You still can't do it.
Are you worried about a malpractice suit?
Have you known all along?
And you still want to operate on her?
If that's the problem, I can tell them
there was a small mistake
during the surgery.
Do you think the family
will be that naive?
-Let me explain it to them.
-Explain?
That's not what you need.
You might have to threaten them.
I never heard of someone giving up
a malpractice suit for an explanation.
But if we don't do anything,
the patient might die.
Many patients die from complications.
If I operate, we can save her.
We can't just let her die
because we're afraid of a lawsuit.
Internal medicine department
will heal her!
Mr Chairman!
Don't you know that there are some things
that are better left untouched?
Once people find out that we let
a third year resident perform surgery,
we'll have to give up
operating on the Prime Minister!
If we admit our wrongdoing and explain it
to the family, we can prevent the lawsuit.
Be quiet!
You kneeled down in front of me
and said you'll do whatever I said.
Have you already forgotten?
Why are you so interested in this patient?
I'm sorry, Mr Chairman.
-But as a doctor...
-As a doctor?
As a doctor, you think this is unethical?
Fine.
If you want it that badly,
she'll be the patient for round two.
Yes, Mr Chairman.
Excuse me?
Right now, in your room?
Yes, we'll be right there.
-Let's go.
-Why me?
The Chairman wants to see you!
I don't want to see him.
Stop complaining and follow me! Hurry up!
I called you here
to talk about the second round.
Yes, I believe these two
already decided on everything.
I'm aware!
Follow me.
I assume everyone knows
about this patient.
-Is it 0-1, right now?
-Yes, Mr Chairman.
Let's make this patient for round two
as you wish.
Instead, there will be a different way
to decide the winner.
The one who succeeds
in the surgery wins, right?
No, the one who doesn't operate
on her is the winner.
Excuse me?
The one who operates on her will lose.
Understand?
I believe you lost once already, Dr Han.
If you operate on this patient,
that's another loss for you.
That would end the competition.
You'll be done then, Dr Han. Understand?
You have until tomorrow to decide.
If you both decide not to operate,
I'll pick another patient later on.
Are you going to do it?
Let's choose a different patient.
You're going to wait it out?
Even though we know how ill she is?
Then I'll operate on her.
But can you lend me your quack?
I'm afraid it won't be an easy surgery.
Hey, doctor!
I'll do the surgery for your mom.
So just be patient.
Really?
I just need to put my team together again.
What is it this time?
Don't worry, okay?
Yes, doctor!
-Let go!
-Take it off.
What are you doing?
Leave the hospital now.
Take a day off tomorrow.
A day off?
Actually, stay home until I call you.
Just relax.
This won't do anything, master.
You can't!
The moment you operate on her
is when our relationship ends!
Then I have nothing to lose.
Don't you need money?
Don't you want your girlfriend here?
That's true though.
There'll be one more round
even if I lose this!
Over my dead body!
Go home! Now!
You'll only do Han Jae-joon a favor
if you operate on that patient!
I am sure the patient's family
will be happy.
We're in a bloody war!
We can't worry about the patient's family.
This is a hospital! We must care!
We can't worry about them
because this is a hospital.
If there's a malpractice suit,
that will be the end of this hospital!
Master!
Just be quiet and follow me.
I'm sending you home.
Who are these people?
Get out of my way!
Come with me.
Taxi!
You must stay at home
until I call you, okay?
Okay? You...
Who are you?
Where did he go? Damn it!
Jae-hee!
How does your schedule look today,
Dr Han?
Dr Park...
What? Did something happen?
He's so funny!
Hello, Park Hoon.
Dr Park, your classmate is hilarious!
-My classmate?
-Have you forgotten already?
At the health research center
for our dear leader!
We spent countless hours
in our academic struggle.
"Academic struggle," he says!
-Let's get out of here.
-Sure. Shall we rejoice our reunion?
Sorry, but what do North Korean
call miniskirts again?
"Shortened dress."
Shortened dress! Funny!
-Why did you show up at the hospital?
-Me?
Of course, I showed up to cheer you up.
I don't think it's a wise thing
to show your ugly face everywhere.
I wouldn't have showed up
if you were doing fine.
What are you talking about?
I heard whoever operates
on that woman will lose this round.
Even I lose this time,
I still have one more chance.
Yes, the competition will be tied.
That'll only make the final round
more interesting.
So...
I am not here to see interesting things.
I came here to achieve a mission.
A mission?
A mission that's worth 100 times more
than what you ruined two years ago.
Is it about earning cash
for the regime again?
How is that related
to the Prime Minister's surgery?
You'll eventually understand
when the time comes.
Just know that my government
is deeply interested in this mission.
Is that why they dragged
a failure like you into this mission?
That failure brought
Song Jae-hee all the way here.
The love of your life.
So the same operative
can take her away at any time.
Dead or alive.
You would've killed her already
if you were going to.
But I haven't.
I can even show you the generosity
of my regime if you want.
Your generosity?
I can set you two free.
Just the thought of it must be exciting.
Living with the love of your life...
...without worrying about anything.
There'll be no reason to hide
from anything.
And I won't appear in front of you
ever again.
I can even give you enough money
to live the rest of your life in comfort.
As long as the mission succeeds.
Remember this.
If the mission is accomplished,
you and Song Jae-hee can be happy.
Dr Han.
Can you see?
This hospital has overcome so many crises
to get to where it is today.
Some of those crises
were malpractice lawsuits.
But I never allowed any lawsuit
that would hurt this hospital.
And that's why I'm still the chairman.
And you're my choice to be
the heir of this hospital.
I'm sorry for giving you
all these troubles.
The second round is coming up.
You can pick two patients
that you're confident with.
So you have nothing to worry about.
But you must remember that to be
the owner of this hospital, you must be
something more than just a doctor.
They say it'll be a simple surgery.
So you don't need to worry too much.
But it's still a surgery.
How can we not worry?
You could've waited
until I was more grown up!
Why?
Have you forgotten already?
I told you that I'll become a doctor!
That's right!
It doesn't matter!
You can get better this time, then get
sick again once I become a doctor!
Do you want your dad to be sick?
Why does it matter?
I'll cure him no matter what!
Okay.
I'll make sure to be sick later,
so become a great doctor, Sung-hoon!
Promise me!
-Understand?
-Okay, Dad.
Never forget.
My father is Lee Do-sun,
and I'm Lee Sung-hoon.
Never forget our names.
Remember the person
who will take revenge on you!
If you operate on this patient,
that's another loss for you.
That will be enough to end
the competition.
You'll be finished then, Dr Han.
I must make this choice
in order to destroy the castle.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Is my mom okay?
Your mom?
Are you asleep, Mom?
She's asleep every time I come here.
Do you want me to get
a nurse to wake her up?
No.
At home, she couldn't sleep well
because of pain.
What's your name?
My name is Jae-cheol.
Jae-cheol...
Is your name Han Jae-joon?
No.
Then what is it?
Do you know Dr Park Hoon?
I do.
He talked about you.
Dr Park talked about me?
He said Dr Han Jae-joon is a very
skilled doctor who is also very nice.
There is no way he said that.
He did say you're not the nicest guy.
But it's true that he said
you're a skilled doctor!
Dr Park said he'll operate
on Mom tomorrow.
But would you please operate on her
if Dr Park can't do it tomorrow?
If Dr Park promised you,
he will do the surgery.
I think so, too.
But he couldn't do it earlier today.
If Dr Park can't do it, please do
the surgery for my mom, doctor.
Hey, Jae-cheol.
You'll do it, right?
Okay, I'll consider it.
Dr Han isn't going to operate, is he?
I think so.
I'm just worried about Dr Park.
What's wrong with him?
He'll probably try to save the patient.
Has he asked for your help again
with the surgery?
No, not yet.
Will you help him if he asks?
I don't know.
Has he asked you to be
his first assistant yet?
You know he calls me a quack!
But I heard he asked you earlier today.
That's probably because he had
to do the surgery in secret.
Lend me your hand.
He's such a prankster.
He massaged my scalp and told me
I'm going bald because he found
my hair somewhere!
I've never met someone like him before.
Sometimes, he acts like an adult,
but sometimes, he's just a kid.
He's unpredictable.
It sounds like you like him.
Huh?
You can't stop smiling
when you talk about him.
Not at all!
Every time I think about his face,
I want to punch it!
Like this!
So, no.
Seoul's real estate prices
increased a small amount
since January, but it is now on the
decline as it fell by 0.03 percent in May.
How can this country be so calm
when our enemy is doing nuclear tests?
I'm afraid this one is a failure, sir.
A failure?
Then should I ask them to shoot some
cannonballs to get this country riled up?
Those two competitors at Myung-woo?
It'll either be decided today,
or we'll have to wait a bit longer.
If they have to do a competition,
I want them to fight until they drop.
That'll be good for business.
We must get prepared, too,
as our competitors are dueling.
Yes, sir.
Many things have changed
in the last 20 years.
Our citizens have learned to maintain
their calm...
...even when North Korea
threatens us with nuclear tests.
It's probably just because
they don't show it.
Foreign war correspondents are still here,
and many of our foreign investors
are taking their money elsewhere.
We've already accrued
more financial damage
than what North Korea asked us to give.
It seems like you enjoy crises.
I'm sorry, sir.
It's just that I think
we should prepare for the worst.
We just need to give them
a reason to meet with you.
These are the candidates
for my heart surgery.
The head of this hospital used to be
your main physician, right?
Yes, sir. He used to be.
Which one do you like the most?
Me?
It'll be your heart after all.
I like Min Kook Hospital the most.
I love you.
Just practicing!
Geez, isn't he nuts?
How may I help you?
I picked it up on the street.
When are you off?
We can do Japanese, Chinese,
Korean, North Korean...
You have a great body.
And you have great stupidity.
She's quite unique, as predicted.
Hey, hey!
I guess you don't know who I am.
I'm the kind of guy
who does one-shot, one-kill...
We're in public!
VICTORY TAEKWONDO
I know you very well, you pervert!
This really hurts.
Mister, can you help me?
Hey.
-You surprised me!
-What are you doing here?
How's your mom doing?
She's fine.
What's that?
I made some breakfast for you.
I'm pretty hungry! What good timing!
Bye!
You're going to operate on the patient?
Yes.
Your hand is okay now, right?
Yes, it's okay now.
When are you going to do it?
As soon as we have a scrub nurse
and an anesthesiologist.
Are you going to ask
Nurse Min to be the scrub nurse?
Yes, why?
I think she has an afternoon shift today.
I'll ask around.
Why don't we go with someone else?
-Okay, sure. Please ask around.
-Yes.
Dr Park is going to operate
on a patient from internal medicine?
You must help him, Dr Yang.
I know that anyone who operates
on her will lose the second round.
Is that why?
You can think whatever you want.
Please help him to have a successful
surgery since he's doing it anyway.
Yes, sir.
Have some tea, honey.
Can you change your shift
to an afternoon one tomorrow?
Dr Han!
-Do you have surgery?
-I have one later.
When will that be over?
It's a simple one,
so it shouldn't take too long.
Call me when you're done.
We're doing an off-pump CABG.
Are you going to operate on the patient?
-Of course.
-But...
I'll still have a chance to win
even after this.
-Is he aware of it too?
-Cha Jin-soo?
It doesn't matter.
You can't do this.
I understand where you're coming from,
but I can't just watch and do nothing.
You promised me that you'll do
whatever I tell you.
Let's just do whatever he tells us to do.
I made a promise with the family
that I'll operate.
Hoon...
I can't disappoint them.
Hey, Park Hoon.
Then how about me?
I believe I told you
there shouldn't be a final round.
If she dies, this might become
a malpractice suit.
Then the hospital will be disqualified
from doing the Prime Minister's surgery.
Would that be okay?
That's not something
you should worry about.
I am begging you.
I'll do whatever it takes
to win the third round.
So please let me operate on the patient.
What are you doing?
Repeat after me. "I'll do whatever
Cha Jin-soo tells me to do."
-Don't do it.
-That's not what I want to hear.
Say it.
I... will do whatever
Cha Jin-soo tells me to do.
One more time.
I'll do whatever Cha Jin-soo
tells me to do.
That's right.
You'll do whatever I tell you to do.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Doctor!
Mom!
What happened, doctor?
We're still trying to figure out
the exact reason.
It could genetic or perhaps
an allergic reaction to a medication.
Could it be that there was a mistake
during the surgery, doctor?
We perform the stent procedure
more than 1,000 times every year.
Our failure rate is less than one percent,
and those patients usually show
different symptoms than your wife.
I don't know what you heard,
but this kind of doubt
isn't good for you both.
I'm sorry, doctor.
-What is going on?
-That's none of your business.
Her heart keeps stopping
because of the cardiac tamponade.
We'll take care of her. Get lost!
Doctor!
Don't worry. I...
You'll do the surgery for my mom, right?
Doctor?
What's wrong, doctor?
Doctor!
-Are you okay?
-Doctor...
Doctor!
When is Dr Park doing the surgery?
It was actually cancelled.
-Why?
-I don't know.
Do you think the patient will be okay?
Why are you asking?
Her heart just stopped
because of the cardiac tamponade.
Doctor!
Jae-cheol...
Dr Park won't do it.
Please do the surgery for my mom.
You said you'll do it
if Dr Park can't do it!
Doctor!
Please save my mom, doctor!
Bring my dad back!
You said you would do it!
-I can't do it.
-Why not?
I can't do it.
-I can't.
-You can do it.
-You still have a chance after this!
-I said I can't do it.
You promised the kid
that you would do it!
Then why aren't you doing it?
You're a doctor.
You must keep your promise with patients.
For a split second, I just pretended
to be a doctor for a split second.
I'm not a doctor.
Stop talking nonsense.
The patient might die.
-Do you want to win that badly?
-I have no choice.
That's why I'm not a doctor.
You bastard!
I thought you were a doctor.
I thought you're different from me.
Assemble the team.
Are you saying you're going to operate
on an internal medicine patient?
As all of you are aware,
the Chairman opposes this surgery.
That's what I mean.
If someone wants out, speak now.
I'm not even sure what'll happen
to me after the surgery.
I still haven't finished my residency,
so let me go this time.
I want to ask one thing.
Will you be responsible for us
if we all get fired after this?
I'll do my best.
Fine, I'm in.
I'll do it, too, Chief.
Me too.
Fine, all we have to do is finish
before the Chairman finds out.
Is that even possible?
Let's get ready then.
Doctor!
You're going to do the surgery, right?
I never doubted you.
Is Dr Han operating on your wife?
Yes.
Hooray!
It's over!
What do you mean?
Han Jae-joon is going to operate
on that internal medicine patient!
We won! 2-0!
This will be my last surgery here.
Are you going to be okay?
My father won't let this slide.
There are many things I can't tell you,
but there is one sure thing.
My feelings for you.
Those are real.
Don't worry. Everything will be okay.
Are you here for my mom?
Please take good care of my mom, doctor.
I'm sorry.
I'm still on your team, right?
Yeah.
-What do you mean?
-Yes, Mr Chairman.
How can you rely on someone like Dr Han
if he can't understand you?
That little...
Dr Oh...
That's okay. This is your place, Dr Keum.
Is everyone ready?
Scalpel.
Mr Chairman.
I'm aware. So be quiet!
I didn't do it!
Chief, the Chairman is here.
Focus on the surgery.
-But, Chief...
-Hurry up!
Put Dr Han on the phone!
Stop it right now!
Once the surgery is over, I'll tell
the family the truth and apologize.
Be quiet!
Dr Han, get out of there right now!
He shouldn't.
I'll forgive everything if you leave now.
Now!
I'll get out once the surgery is over.
Once the surgery is over? Okay.
Everyone in there, listen carefully.
Get out of there right now.
Otherwise, I'll make you spend the rest
of your career in the middle of nowhere!
-What are you scared of, Mr Chairman?
-You be quiet!
If we tell the truth and apologize,
a lawsuit will not happen.
Such fantasy has never happened
in real life before.
That's because
we have never apologized sincerely.
We're so focused on our money
and prestige,
we have ignored the people
who lost their parents and kids.
I said be quiet!
I'll show you that you're wrong.
Dr Han!
Stay focused. Let's continue.
Keep going, Dr Keum.
Stay focused!
Section.
Chief...
Let's stop the bleeding first.
Suction.
Please take care of her, doctor.
If this ends in a table death,
call for a disciplinary committee meeting.
What would be the meeting about?
He snuck out a patient from another
department without permission!
Then should it be about
his disobeying your orders?
And have the legal department
prepare for a lawsuit.
-A lawsuit?
-That's right.
Have them tell the truth as he wishes.
The truth will be that Han Jae-joon
killed the patient during surgery!
All the blame goes to him! Understand?
Yes, Mr Chairman.
You should look before you step.
-Where are you going?
-You don't want to know.
-We need more blood.
-More blood please!
Suction!
-How are the vitals?
-They're falling.
-Have you found it?
-I can't see, Chief.
Calm down.
-But Chief...
-I said calm down!
Keum Bong-hyun...
Please let me in.
Why does everyone look like
you did something wrong?
You haven't done anything wrong.
So chin up.
The people who should be ashamed
are all up there.
Look.
You should be proud.
You're the only real doctors
in this hospital.