=The Palace Gambit=
=Episode 26=
(I'll Wait for You Next Life)
The ledger seized outside the palace
details their trafficking.
Please review it.
I've seized Consort Shu's illicit money.
Eunuch Yu, who transported gold for her,
has already confessed.
See for yourself.
I'm so resentful.
I've schemed with all my might
and calculated every move,
yet lost to a lowly maid like you.
When entering the palace at fourteen,
I became my family's cash cow.
My brother wanted money,
and my father desired power.
I clawed my way upward desperately
just to earn their notice.
None of this
justifies harming the innocent.
By what right?
In this harem,
everyone vies for favor.
What fault is mine?
You climbed over innocent lives.
Those commoners you slaughtered
never got to plead their innocence.
For your own selfish desires,
you've been so malicious.
You are truly heinous.
In the imperial harem,
whose hands are clean?
You all posture with false virtue.
Your Majesty,
look at these records.
Most of the wealth I amassed
has been given to your own aunt,
the Grand Princess.
If I'm left with no way out,
the imperial family's dignity
will be dragged through mud.
Guards!
Take her down.
Consort Shu,
don't think I'm blind to your schemes.
You believe the Grand Princess's backing
makes you invulnerable?
So you dare to blackmail me
for leniency?
Someone!
Summon the Grand Princess.
The Grand Princess,
I warned you long ago
to stay away from Consort Shu.
Why did you not heed my warnings?
Your Majesty,
I admit my wrongs.
Consort Shu
deliberately bribed me.
I merely accepted her money.
I never got involved
in what she's done, Your Majesty.
I know nothing
about what she has done.
As the Grand Princess,
my own blood aunt,
of such noble standing,
you sold yourself for money
and were drawn
into her human trafficking crimes.
You've shamed the imperial family.
How do you expect me
to answer to the court ministers?
Your Majesty, I was momentarily foolish.
I beg your mercy.
Yun Mi,
help me. I'm your sister.
Yun Mi.
Help me quickly.
Persuade His Majesty for me.
This concerns imperial dignity.
How disastrous if made public.
Sister,
with your crimes,
even I cannot save you now.
Your Majesty,
the law applies to all,
high and low.
The Grand Princess took bribes
to cover Consort Shu's crimes.
She must be punished too
by national law.
As the nation's sovereign,
Your Majesty knows
the empire's foundation.
If you fail to love your people
and punish your kin,
where is the authority?
Water bears the boat
and capsizes it.
If you lose the people's hearts,
this empire
will cease to exist.
Lu Jiuning,
how dare you!
Your Majesty,
justice resides in people's hearts.
It shouldn't rest solely on your decree.
Nor should it
be confined
to imperial authority and power.
You're overstepping!
Your Majesty,
though Lu Jiuning
is merely a palace maid,
she cares for the people.
Her counsel today
is an act of loyalty.
Please calm down.
Your Majesty, Lu Jiuning
rescued many oppressed innocent maids
from Hard-Labor Ward
while investigating
Talented Lady Wan's case.
She exposed Consort Shu's crimes
for the greater good.
To expose
the trafficking of common folk,
she spared no effort.
Every action and thought of Lu Jiuning
serves the common people
and Your Majesty's sovereignty.
Please judge fairly.
Very well.
Lord Ning speaks so eloquently.
Today, I shall
deal fairly with Consort Shu
and the Grand Princess.
However,
to preserve the imperial dignity,
Lu Jiuning and Eunuch Zhang,
two outsiders who know too much,
cannot remain.
They must die.
Your Majesty!
Bring it forth.
Lu Jiuning,
I promised you
a chance to plead your case.
I ask one final time:
Will you choose life or death?
The choice is yours.
If Your Majesty
can administer justice,
clear my sister's name
to give her justice,
and restore
righteous order to the realm,
I will die without regret.
Good.
Drink this poison,
and justice shall be served.
Your Highness,
I
can no longer serve you.
Thank you
for your recognition and kindness.
Thank you for letting me
feel genuine warmth
in this cruel palace.
You cherished me like my sister
and treated me with kindness.
I can never repay you.
See you in the next life.
In the next life,
I'll surely repay your kindness.
Lord Ning,
thank you
for always standing by me.
I'm eternally grateful.
Please set aside
your feelings for me.
As things stand,
we can never be together in this life.
Maybe next life.
I'll wait for you
next life.
Next life,
we'll surely
share our lives
and grow old together.
No, Jiuning!
My lord!
Jiuning!
No!
Consort Shu
harmed consorts and imperial heirs,
colluded with officials,
and shielded traffickers.
The proof was ironclad.
Her evil was profound.
She will
be stripped of her title
and given poison
to atone with death.
The Grand Princess
traded her influence
for wealth.
Effective immediately,
she's confined to Wuhua Palace.
Without my decree,
she'll never be pardoned.
Jiuning!
Jiuning?
Jiuning.
(Lijing Pavilion)
(Imperial Study)
I didn't die?
Jiuning,
you're awake.
Your Highness?
It was just a sedative tonic.
You slept like a log.
Your Majesty.
I never intended to take your life.
I merely wanted to verify
whether it's, as you claimed,
genuine care for the people,
or just vengeance in disguise
by borrowing my power.
Thank you for sparing my life.
The human trafficking epidemic
manifested
through an avalanche of memorials
piling up endlessly.
My tinnitus
relapsed
during that period.
Do you truly take me for a fool
and think me oblivious?
This matter
implicates powerful networks,
even reaching imperial kin.
Tug one thread,
and the whole tapestry moves.
Then how
did Your Majesty resolve to act?
Because of you.
As a mere palace maid,
defying power
and obstacles,
you pleaded for people.
You've shown me
a remarkable woman unlike any other.
Speak.
What reward do you seek?
Your Majesty,
might I request
leave from the palace?
I wish to fulfill
my sister's unachieved dreams.
I desire
to live freely and simply.
Very well.
If you insist on departing,
I grant your wish.
Go witness
the picturesque realm
under my governance.
Thank you for your grace.
You warned
Jiuning would never accept me.
I refused to believe
that in this world
exists anything beyond my grasp.
Jiuning
differs from other women.
Indeed.
I've never encountered
such an extraordinary woman.
Lord Ning,
have you truly made up your mind?
My sister faces punishment
because of her.
The imperial clan
will never accept her.
Reconsider carefully.
(Zhaoyang Gate)
Your Highness, stay.
Cease your tears.
In your delicate condition,
weeping harms your eyes.
I must leave now.
Take good care.
Jiuning,
though palace walls
may merely separate us,
your departure means
we may never meet again.
Jiuning,
beyond these walls,
live freely and joyfully
and fulfill
both your and your sister's wishes.
Your Highness,
you will become an empress
who embodies maternal grace.
One as compassionate as you
as empress
would bless the realm.
For His Majesty
and our people,
I'll dedicate my utmost.
The imperial harem
forever churns with schemes
and surging undercurrents.
Speaking of Miss Jiu,
Noble Consort Xian's favorite maid,
from a lowly convict maid
in the Hard-Labor Ward
to a favored maid by the consort's side,
her favor flourished effortlessly,
rising meteorically through the ranks.
Later,
she not only helped
solve the Jiangnan trafficking case
but also earned His Majesty's favor
and was elevated to consort.
Everything was too smooth.
She became a consort.
But fate plays cruel tricks.
Fortune and misfortune intertwined.
On the very night
of her consort ceremony,
- Miss Jiu...
- What?
Suddenly died.
She died?
Her corpse vanished,
leaving only an empty tomb.
Who caused Miss Jiu's
untimely demise?
Was her death
a casualty of palace schemes?
Are there undisclosed truths?
What truths?
To know what happened next,
come back
for the continuation.
Sister,
you also came from the palace.
Did Miss Jiu
truly die?
Yes.
She's dead.
So the storyteller spoke truth?
Not entirely true.
One thing he got wrong.
What thing?
Miss Jiu
was never a consort of His Majesty.
Then what?
Then
if you don't go home to eat soon,
you'll miss dinner.
It's getting late.
At the bridge's end,
a scholar in blue
holding an umbrella hurries over...
Jiuning.
Lord Ning?
I'm no Lord Ning now.
I incurred the wrath
of the imperial clan.
Now I'm stripped
of royal status and lineage.
Henceforth,
no Lord Ning exists.
Before you stands
but a commoner.
Jiuning,
in our youth,
you shielded me.
Now I'll protect you.
I'll marry you
and guard you all my days.
None shall harm you again.
♪For you, I am willing♪
♪Do you understand♪
(The End)