Are you all right?
Can you even remember getting beaten up?
Sure I can.
They totally crossed the line this time.
They need to be taught that
they can't lay a hand on someone so important to me.
Let me bandage you.
Does it hurt really bad?
Not too bad.
Does my face look really wrecked though?
I'm sure I will get yelled at by the cheerleading captain.
This is so like you.
After getting beaten up, all you care about is how you look.
Turn this way.
Sorry.
It's going to hurt a bit.
Bear with me.
This one will burn.
Ready?
Sorry.
♫ My heart sent to your heart while holding hands ♫
♫ Looking into your eyes and understanding
without saying a word ♫
Sorry.
Just a bit more.
♫ Walking hand in hand, spreading love ♫
♫ Don't care about anyone, I'm close to you ♫
Will you… stay with me tonight?
I told you I didn't bring anything with me.
How can I crash here?
About that…
I have bought everything you need.
Problem solved now?
You bought all that?
Soap, toothpaste, toothbrush, shampoo, conditioner, razor, shaving cream,
and underwear.
I'll take that as a yes. You can't go back now. It's late and dangerous.
Right?
Choose whether you want to sleep on a couch
or this soft mattress with me.
So?
[2gether the Series]
[Episode 9]
♫ We see each other every day, and every day is different ♫
♫ It seemed like there was no way, how could we fall in love? ♫
♫ But because of our closeness, there are no more excuses ♫
♫ I wasn't prepared for these wrong sparks in my heart ♫
♫ I used to be a person who never understood ♫
♫ I'm so addicted to you that I accidentally and unconsciously
fell in love with you ♫
♫ I've been caught in your trap, how can I resist your heart? ♫
♫ Excuse me for causing confusion ♫
♫ I'm sorry that my heart wants to have you by my side ♫
♫ Just being able to love you, I can't force
myself to forget about you ♫
♫ I've fallen in love with you, I can't force
I end up snuggling up with you anyway.
Why are you nestling up with me here?
You said you wanted to sleep on a couch.
We need to snuggle up due to the small space.
You didn't choose the mattress.
I said I wanted to sleep on a couch alone!
You didn't say "alone."
I'm letting you sleep on a couch as you wish.
And I'm keeping you warm here.
Stop complaining.
What are you looking at?
I hope you're not having any pervy thoughts.
I think I recognize one of them.
Who?
Do you know him?
I don't.
But I have a feeling he is a senior from the Faculty of Architecture.
Maybe… there's a reason behind this.
I don't know what's behind it.
But now… I'm more interested in what's in front of me.
Keep looking at me like that… and I will kiss till you drop.
Yes, please.
I'm just kidding. You asshole!
Sweet dream.
You wish!
By the way, how do you kiss people till they drop?
Like this.
Very cute.
I meant the dessert.
I know.
What happened to your hand?
I built a model with Chat last night.
I got cut.
My first time checking in here.
I have to go. My shift is over.
See you at the football field this evening.
Where are you going?
[Library]
What? Does it still hurt?
No. I'm cold.
I'm sitting right under the air-con.
Everywhere else is full.
We have to sit here.
I will go get my jacket for you. Wait here.
Why are you back so fast?
Are you studying?
Do you want to study with me? I can tutor you.
That's okay.
My friend just went out to grab a jacket. He will be back soon.
What are you doing?
Your boyfriend is cold. I just gave him my jacket.
No need. He has mine now.
Take good care of your boy.
Lots of people want him.
I am not afraid of other people.
I am not afraid of a dog.
A dog, you said?
I am on for a real fight, too.
Come on then.
See you on the field.
Let's continue our unfinished business there.
What did he mean by that?
Is he… one of the Architecture students that hurt you yesterday?
I don't know. Might be.
Of course, he is!
He bullied you because of Tine.
He will turn a football field into a battlefield for sure.
[Two Weeks Later]
Has anyone seen Tine?
Tine?
I am sorry. I woke up late.
That's okay.
Let me clip your hair up and apply foundation.
Wearing the wrong foundation shade is a hit now?
I don't think it's wrong.
This shade fits Tine's skin perfectly.
Sarawat, I think it evens his skin just fine.
If you don't approve, I won't do the foundation.
Eyeliner up next then.
I don't think he needs it.
His bottom lid is black enough.
No liners needed.
Not that black, I guess.
Bottom eyeliner is trending.
Just a bit?
If you don't approve, we can skip it then.
Let's skip to the blush.
A blush will make his cheeks redder.
I think they're too red.
Let's just not wear any makeup then.
You can go change now.
Go on.
- What are you doing?
- And what are you doing?
You are cute enough already.
Do you want to be cuter to attract more people or what?
What the heck are you saying?
I'm going to get changed.
Here.
I know you haven't eaten anything today.
Thanks.
So you can't play today.
I have to.
You gave me a promise.
If I win today, you will post a love confession to me.
This is not funny.
Promise me you won't play.
Yes.
- Promise?
- Yes.
Promise?
Do you want an extra ball boy?
No ball boy is needed here.
I just need an undertaker for Sarawat's dead body.
Just kidding.
I won't kill him. Disability is enough.
Sounds satisfying.
But wouldn't you be prouder to win a clean game?
Hey! Whose side are you actually on here?
Your side, of course.
I'm going to go warm up.
The players of both teams are walking onto the field.
Sarawat, the Political Science star player is sitting on the bench.
Is he injured?
That was a foul there.
The referee is giving him a yellow card.
Wait!
It's okay. I can play.
My knee!
Are you okay?
Architecture lads are hot-headed today.
I don't think he can play on.
I can!
You can't, Boss.
I am okay. Okay, okay, okay.
Ouch!! Slow down!
Sarawat!
The game has resumed.
Sarawat just goaled!
Tine, are you okay? You look a bit pale.
Right after he hits the field, Political Science leads Architecture one-nil.
I woke up quite late this morning.
Tine.
And I forgot to have breakfast.
Let me find something for you to eat.
I have a sandwich.
Okay.
Let's rest for a bit then.
- Guys! Tine has fainted!
- Sarawat just got tackled there!
Help! Bring me first aid and water!
An Architecture player is given a red card.
Looks like we have a situation here on the side.
Let him get some air!
Take this.
Are you okay?
You stay away!
Go!
What a dickhead!
You two go fight somewhere else.
Stop it!
Tine!
I am okay.
I will find you a fan or something.
Hey! Your leg!
Wat, your leg!
I am fine.
Don't worry about me.
Worry about yourself.
I am okay really.
- Some help here, please.
- Come on.
Okay.
You passed out. The seniors brought you here.
What about Wat?
He barely slept.
All he did was was look after you.
Man and I had to drag him out to see a doc for the wound.
He didn't want to leave you.
How is his knee?
Quite terrible.
A brace is going to be with him for a month.
The red mark there is either because of the tackle
or the infection when he ran to save you.
Don't worry about him.
Think about yourself first.
By the way, the Political Science won 1-0.
I guess you need to post a love confession as promised.
It was just a joke, wasn't it?
I am hungry. Let's find something to eat.
You okay?
Do you want to wake him?
No.
Since when did you like Americano?
It's for Sarawat.
I see.
Actually, Sarawat seems like a nice guy.
He really cares about you.
What are you implying?
At first, I thought you were just shaken by him
because you hadn't dated girls for a long time.
Now I am not sure.
Not sure about what?
You know I hate him.
If I ever get together with him,
you guys will tease me until the end of my days.
- Sarawat, can we take photos of you?
- Please.
- Have some, please.
What's wrong?
You should have gotten used it by now.
I haven't said anything.
Shit!
It's okay. We can buy a new one.
I had just one sip of it.
What a waste.
If you really wanted it, why didn't you hold on to it firmly.
It's up to you.
If you don't want to regret it later, try to keep what you want.
Try while you still can.
You can pick it up after you drop it.
But it's not going to be the same.
I think you should rest and come back next week.
I can't rest.
I have to show and promote a music contest next week.
I'll have no time for friends.
What is happening here?
We're discussing the show Sarawat has to perform.
I can perform. Just let me.
I asked your doctor.
Besides the injured knee, you have an injured wrist too.
I can't let you perform in this condition.
My wrist is okay now.
My knee won't be a problem. Let me perform.
No.
We don't want any substitution.
Without you, it's not Control S.
Please.
Let me perform.
P'Dim, will my show be good enough to substitute Control S?
What's got into your head?
I am not as good as Sarawat.
But I can perform by myself.
Great! I will perform a guitar solo after Tine's show.
Me too.
Us too.
It doesn't sound so bad.
We give this stage to newbies.
It might motivate more people to step up and join the contest.
Do you all know that?
When you are on stage, you carry the club's reputation with you.
I do.
This club accepted me and taught me guitar lessons.
It's time for me to repay it.
P'Dim is crazy enough to let Tine perform.
Fong, talk to him. He only listens to you.
Try to change his mind.
What's wrong with him playing for the club?
He is a newbie. He doesn't have enough time to practice.
The first time on stage is tough.
I don't want him to fail.
Do you know why Tine hasn't said yes to your confession?
How does that have to do with anything here?
Tine was always the one taking care of his ex.
But now he is the one being taken care of. I guess he is not used to it.
He might want to prove that he is good enough to be with you.
Don't be happy just yet.
If he fails this time, he might get too discouraged.
He might withdraw himself from a relationship with you forever.
Thanks.
Your food is right here. I'm going to go practice now.
Hey! I hurt my knee, not my eyes.
You can practice here. I can be your mentor.
Fine.
I will get you a chair.
Thank.
What are you looking at?
I'm just thinking… Ever since you gave me this guitar,
I haven't named it yet.
Is it the right time to name a guitar? Practice.
I am serious here.
If you were a guitar, you would want to play for the owner who gave you a nice name.
Up to you then.
Well... What kind of name do you like then?
Something that describes me.
Ringworm.
Just call yourself that.
Scrubb?
- Scrubb?
- Yes.
Don't you feel pity for them at all?
Don't ruin their band by naming your guitar that.
What name do you want then?
Just pick one already, Nuisance.
Stop being picky and practice.
Nuisance!
That's right. Nuisance!
Freaking right for my guitar.
You are awesome! You are clever.
Let me see your music chords.
Are you playing a Scrubb song?
Yes. Why?
The first time having a girlfriend,
the first heartbreak,
the first music video recording.
Scrubb songs took part in all of them.
This will be my first time on stage.
How can I play a song from other bands?
You're right.
I am jealous of Scrubb. They are your first of many things.
I want to be Scrubb.
Why?
So that I can be with you both, when you're happy and sad.
I want to be Scrubb.
Cheesy!
Let me practice already.
Otherwise, the true sadness will come if I can't play.
Wrong. Press harder.
Wrong.
Wrong. Press more firmly.
Isn't this firm enough?
If it's firmly enough, it won't sound wrong. Press harder.
Wrong. Press harder.
Here. Press harder.
Now play.
This is called right.
Memorize it.
Try it. Give me a pick.
Nobody holds a pick as you do.
Look. Use your point finger like this.
Spare the edge.
Grab it together with your thumb and you strum it.
Give me your hand.
Here.
Put a pick on your point finger.
Leave the edge.
Press it with your thumb.
Tine, will you marry me?
What the hell?
You're teaching me to hold a pick, not putting on a wedding ring.
Okay. Keep going!
Why are you smiling?
Who is?
Does it hurt your fingers?
Stop. Let me see.
All of them hurt?
Yes.
Just take a break.
If you practice too hard and hurt your fingers, you can't perform anyway.
Let me have a look.
See? Your fingers are about to bleed.
You have to be able to play when the day comes.
I'm trying to be gentle, but this is hard.
Sorry.
You know what.
No one has ever put a band-aid on for me before in my life.
And do you think I have done this for anyone?
Marry me?
Again? Stop it!
It's done.
Thank you.
Take a break for a while until your fingers heal.
Listen to the song in the meantime.
I said no practice.
Put it down.
[To help you see the chords more clearly.]
Good timing. We are teaming up.
This game, I will play your opponent.
What?
Be my guess. Play for the team you want.
What the heck is your problem?
That was one hell of a tackle.
Ouch! Shit!
What are you playing?
I'm doing what you did to my brother.
Yes! I am Sarawat's brother!
Fuck you!
You have an appointment for the x-ray tomorrow.
I am not available tomorrow morning.
Can we postpone it for later?
Your doctor is free only tomorrow morning.
After that, he is fully booked.
We can't postpone it.
Wat.
- Wat!
- Yes.
What is on your mind?
Nothing.
The nurse told me you have to come for an x-ray tomorrow.
Just come. I will be fine.
But you are performing.
Do you think I went through all the practice just to bother you at the end?
Can you take me somewhere today?
Where?
Why do you want to come here?
I can't come to see you tomorrow.
Just take it as a big rehearsal.
- Play?
- Yes. Go up on stage.
I'll be your audience.
Come on. If you can't perform for one person,
you can't perform in front of a bunch of people tomorrow.
Why are you fidgeting?
I don't know.
Being up here makes me nervous.
Hey! What are you doing?
Filming you.
Imagine yourself as a protagonist in a movie.
You are a well-trained guitar player.
It's a scene where you're about to perform in front of many people.
They are screaming and cheering for you.
You are so great. It's the ending scene of the movie.
A happy ending, you know?
- The ending scene?
- Yes. A happy ending.
That makes me even more nervous.
Well. It's not a big movie. It's just a short film.
Only a small project for your class.
A short film for class? It still makes me nervous.
I can't.
Let's say it's just a video clip, not a film.
A video clip that only I can see.
- Only you?
- Yes.
- You sure?
Fine then.
3, 2, 1. Action!
What? Action?
I mean… You can play now.
You can start now. Start.
- Now?
- Yes.
Should I play now?
Action!
- Now?
- Yes. Action!
Tine! Are you okay?
- Sarawat!
- What are you guys doing here?
We're bringing snacks for Sarawat.
- He is not here.
- Is he still in recovery?
Yes. But… if you leave them here,
I promise Sarawat will get them. Each one of them.
It's okay.
Leave them here.
Are you ready, Tine? The event will commence soon.
I am.
Just leave for now.
- Come back again when I'm done greeting. Okay?
- Yes.
Tine, keep fighting. We are rooting for you here.
Come back later.
Welcome everyone to our Music Club shows.
Our club members will perform acoustic songs for you.
If you're ready, let's welcome the first show on stage.
Go and slay.
Hi, guys. My name is Tine…
Tine, Mr. Chic! Let's cheer for him!
Hi, guys! I am Tine, Mr. Chic. The one and only.
I'm going to play you a song.
Some of you might not know this song. But I have practiced very hard for this.
Give him a big hand!
♪ No matter how cruel this world is ♪
♪ No matter how gloomy it is ♪
♪ Everywhere is full of darkness and sorrow ♪
♪ I've been through many bad situations ♪
♪ They've made me so sad ♪
♪ But it's totally fine ♪
Imagine yourself as a protagonist in a movie.
You are a well-trained guitar player.
It's a scene where you're about to perform in front of many people.
They are screaming and cheering for you.
You are so great.
Just try.
Tine! You okay? Keep fighting!
♪ I am never scared or intimidated by what is coming at me ♪
♪ I am ready to accept everything ♪
Sarawat.
♪ As long as I have you ♪
♪ You are all I ask for ♪
♪ Just you ♪
♪ I need nothing more, I want… ♪
♪ I want to be Tine's boyfriend ♪
♪ Can I be Tine's boyfriend? ♪
♪ Please, Tine ♪
♪ I need nothing more ♪
Tine, just say yes and be his boyfriend.
My friend here is too chicken to ask you himself.
That's why I'm doing it for him.
Just ask him already.
If you don't, I will freaking hit on him myself.
Tine.
I am so done flirting.
Will you be my boyfriend?
Directed by Weerachit Thongjila
♫ I don’t know if you came into my life or I came into yours ♫
♫ Maybe it’s just a coincidence, maybe it’s not,
I still can’t figure it out ♫
♫ All I know is that the one in my heart is you ♫
♫ I don’t want anyone to come between us,
we will stay side by side ♫
♫ Wherever you are, I’ll be right next to you ♫
♫ I own the space beside you,
because we are meant to be together ♫