Let's meet today's fridge owners.
Two people are here to show us chemistry
from total opposite sides of the spectrum.
Please come on out!
Please welcome today's fridge owners!
The two guests
with extremely polar chemistry!
Welcome, Sunwoo Yong-yeo and Lee Joon!
Yes, please come out and take a seat.
-Long time no see.
-Yes, "long time no see."
SHE ENTERS WITH A LOVELY GREETING
She's the trendiest 81-year-old in Korea
at the moment.
She recently opened up her golden age
as the oldest YouTuber.
Hi.
A celebrity icon on "flexing,"
please welcome Actor Sunwoo Yong-yeo!
Hello.
WELCOME, QUEEN YONG-YEO
What do you mean, the trendiest?
All I did was
show my everyday life to people.
Exactly.
One of them is the icon of flexing,
but the other one is
the icon of frugality.
Our first guest is someone
who drives her Benz
to eat breakfast at a hotel.
The other guest is someone
who drives his bicycle
to eat at a library cafeteria.
I'm not too picky when it comes to food.
And the cafeteria costs
6,000 won per meal,
where I can eat everything quickly
and save on time as well.
-You eat breakfast at a hotel. 60,000 won?
-It's 60,000 won.
-It's ten times as expensive.
-It is.
I don't have to go there every day.
-I go there three, four days a week.
-About three, four times a week.
-Six times four… Six times two, twelve.
-On other days,
-I eat a simple breakfast at home.
-Six times four, twenty-four.
As you speak, Joon was mumbling,
"Six times four, twenty-four."
I CAN PAY FOR SO MANY MEALS
AT A CAFETERIA FOR THAT AMOUNT…
He was crunching numbers.
It's better to be frugal
when you're young.
-I'll stay frugal.
-Of course.
But there's no need
for the old to be frugal.
QUEEN YONG-YEO'S PHILOSOPHY
Exactly.
I wondered how people responded to you,
and it showed
with the count of 3.7 million views.
The viewers still show
an incredible response to the video.
"I decided to live like her from now on."
"The role model of my life."
You became the wannabe of Gen Z
with just one video.
My gosh. What is this?
I thought only people over 81 years of age
would love my videos,
-but the younger generation loved it.
-Yes.
-It makes me so happy.
-I see.
She's receiving lots of love these days.
I saw on a portal website
that your birth date was listed
as August 15th, 1945.
-Yes, Korean Liberation Day.
-On Liberation Day?
-That is when you were born?
-Yes.
-Exactly on Liberation Day?
-That's amazing.
-The Liberation Day kid?
-Yes.
-I was called the Liberation kid.
-That's amazing.
-She is living history.
-That's right.
There is one man who feels anxious
and nervous about today's shoot.
Who is it?
It's Webtoon Artist Poong,
who's right next to you.
-Really? Why?
-Yes.
-His pseudonym, Kim Poong,
-came from the sitcom Soonpoong Clinic.
-Really?
Really?
-Poong came from that?
-Yes.
-Poong of Soonpoong?
-It was the year 1999.
-The year 1999.
I was the vice-sysop of a chat room
for Soonpoong Clinic fans online.
-Really? Wow.
-Yes.
-Sysop? What's that?
-Sysop is
-like the vice operator of a forum.
-A vice operator.
-Did you call it sysop then?
-Sysop is
short for system operator,
the operator of a forum.
-System operator?
-I was the overseer.
-Back during the dial-up era.
-That's right.
I was the vice-sysop,
so I visited the set a few times too.
-"What is this?"
-"What is this? Whatever!"
YONG-YEO'S BIGGEST BUZZWORD
-She was amazing back then.
-Yes.
Do you remember the fan forum's visit?
She wouldn't know.
Back then, all I ever did was work.
It'd be about 5:30 a.m.
by the time I'm done on Soonpoong's set.
Then my husband would demand breakfast,
so I'd start cooking.
-You were in your early fifties.
-You worked and cooked?
So I'd make food for him
and go back to work right away.
One day, I went home in the morning
after the shoot,
and he said, "I want food."
After you came home from work?
-"I want food"?
-I suddenly snapped at him.
"Why do you demand food from me
every time you see me?"
Wait, that sounds like…
-"Whatever!"
-"Yong-yeo!"
After I did that, I wondered
how he'd respond after the shock.
-You must've been nervous.
-She must've been scared of the outcome.
He said, "How do I open the refrigerator?"
He couldn't even do that?
-"How do I open the refrigerator?"
-Pull it!
-"Pull it!"
But since that day,
-he stopped asking me for food.
-This is interesting.
-Right.
-He must've served himself.
So I realized
women should raise their voice
every now and then.
You're right.
Yong-yeo doesn't flex
just on the breakfast buffet.
She even flexes on overseas day trips.
FLEXING WITH DAY TRIPS ABROAD
Like going to Japan to eat ramen?
Do you really take day trips abroad alone?
-I don't say what isn't true.
-Right?
-Where do you go on a day trip?
-Where?
-Fukuoka is great.
-Fukuoka.
I'd go there on the first flight
and take a taxi when I get off.
Then I ask,
"Take me to the best restaurant."
"Please."
The driver would say okay
and take me downtown.
What do you say to return to the airport?
"To Fukuoka Airport, please."
SHE CAN DO EVERYTHING BY ADDING "PLEASE"
-That was perfect.
-That was easy.
-It's easy. You need just a few phrases.
-It sounds easy.
-A few phrases, yes.
-You only need a few.
Anyway, you have another bucket list item
you want to cross out this year?
-Yes.
-What is it?
-I want to see the Northern Lights.
-The Northern Lights? Where at?
-Iceland?
-Iceland.
I want to go there before I die.
I want to feel that experience
in this world before I pass.
With your own eyes.
Going on trips basically means
seeing things with your eyes.
-You leave to taste and see it yourself.
-You're right.
-You can't get it on camera.
Of course not.
I wonder
what Yong-yeo keeps in her fridge.
This one right here is her fridge.
I can already see her pictures.
-My granddaughter and grandson.
-I see.
-But you live alone now, right?
-I do.
Yet you have two fridges here.
I couldn't pull out my fridge.
Then we just take what's inside.
We couldn't put everything into this one.
They pulled out everything from the fridge
and took it in this huge tub.
What did you eat for breakfast today?
I had no choice but to go to a hotel.
So you had hotel breakfast?
Yes, I had a hearty meal.
-The hotel buffet is your cafeteria.
-You're right.
Let's find out what she eats alone.
What does she have here?
We present Sunwoo Yong-yeo's fridge!
-Whoa.
-There's a lot of food.
We present Sunwoo Yong-yeo's fridge!
All right. I see a lot of food in here.
-Even though she lives alone.
-Yes.
You won't have to go to a hotel to eat
with this much food.
I don't see a lot of store-bought items.
-Most of them look homemade.
-You're right.
-You must use lots of pastes to cook.
-That's right.
I just like to eat simple meals
like mixing doenjang with rice.
-Just the paste?
-Yes, just the paste and perilla oil.
It's really delicious.
-Do you prefer mixed rice to soup dishes?
-That's right.
I don't really like soup dishes.
She doesn't prefer soup dishes.
Make sure you remember that.
I see some tomato sauce.
-Yes, I…
-How do you use this?
All I need is that tomato sauce
to make spaghetti.
I don't like adding many ingredients.
I just add some onion.
-Just some onion?
-Lots of onion
with just pasta, egg pasta.
-Do you not enjoy flour?
-I say "no thank you" to flour.
-"No thank you" to flour.
-No.
-She doesn't like flour.
-No noodles.
I see some eggs back there.
There's this egg boiler.
-The cooker?
-Yes, the cooker.
-I eat two of those.
-Thank you for the meal.
-Do you boil eggs?
-Yes.
-Do you not fry them?
-No, I don't like fried eggs.
-I see.
-She likes simple and light food.
-I don't like oil, period.
-Oil?
-No thank you to oil?
-No thank you.
Do you not enjoy fried food?
-I don't eat fried food.
-No?
-No soup, no fried food.
-Don't fry anything.
-No fried food.
-No, thank you, fried food.
-An emergency.
-That's rough.
KFC was very popular
back when I emigrated to America.
I pulled off the fried skin
before I ate the chicken.
-I pulled off the fried part.
-She's like Lee Se-dol.
THE MAN WHO REFUSED TO EAT THE FRIED SKIN
A MOMENT TO REMEMBER WITH SE-DOL
WHO KNOWS WHAT'S GOOD NOW
-My memory with Se-dol.
-That was another preference.
-I found some salmon.
-Salmon.
I eat that at home
whenever I don't go to the buffet.
I don't fry that, either. I steam it.
-I see.
-She steams the salmon.
-You steam your salmon?
-Doesn't it smell?
-So I sprinkle lots of lemon juice on it.
-That's why.
-Something fresh.
-Fresh and clean.
It's delicious when it's steamed
with lemon juice and ground pepper.
Like the Mediterranean diet.
You have lots of seafood.
I love seafood.
Some abalones.
When I lived in Seoul,
the only kind of seafood I had were
dried yellow corvina or cutlassfish.
Then I moved to Haenam for the first time
after I got married
and tried raw thin-legged octopus
for the first time.
It tasted so delicious.
That, sea cucumber, and abalone.
Thin-legged octopus.
-Is that an octopus?
-Wait, this is…
What's this?
-I found something odd.
-What is it?
Sea cucumber.
-Sea cucumber?
-Sea cucumber.
-Sea cucumber. Red sea cucumber.
-Those are huge.
Isn't this our first time
seeing sea cucumbers?
It's really delicious.
Do you see the yellow stuff in the middle?
It's really good as bibimbap
if you mix it with rice.
How do you eat the sea cucumbers?
-I slice them.
-You just slice them.
-You eat it raw?
-She eats it raw.
Then I put
some wasabi and lemon juice on it.
-You must love lemon.
-I do.
-It's so good.
-Did you see her when she mentioned
-It's so good!
-thin-legged octopus and sea cucumber?
You can remember that.
-It's so good.
-She likes seafood.
-And vegetables.
-Vegetables.
-She has some lemons.
-She does.
There are many lemons.
I don't keep a lot of vegetables.
-Lettuce.
-Lettuce and coriander.
-Coriander? Do you like it?
-I like coriander.
-I like it 100%.
-I see.
She likes it 100%.
Then you must like
Southeast Asian cuisine.
Tom yum soup is one of my favorites.
You said you didn't like soup.
It uses lots of lemon.
-Because of lemons.
-She basically loves lemons.
I'll make lemon soup, then.
-Just lemons.
-Let's make some lemon soup.
-It must be the secret to your youth.
-I guess so.
-Your skin is in great condition too.
-Yes.
She eats lots of lemons,
so her skin is in great condition.
And this one is sugar-free.
-I eat one every morning.
-What's that?
-Yogurt?
-You have lots of these yogurts,
and they're all sugar-free.
Do you manage your blood sugar?
I'm over 80 years old,
and I have high blood pressure,
so I can't develop diabetes.
-So sugar, no, thank you?
-Of course not.
-No sugar.
-No sugar today.
Are you Se-dol's mother?
-They're the same.
-What I hate the most is
-something too sugary and greasy.
-She doesn't like sugar.
Do you not like too much seasoning?
Seasoning, no, thank you.
No seasoning?
-I enjoy the taste of nature.
-The taste of nature.
What's this?
I wanted to ask the chefs.
Someone gave this to me as a present.
I didn't know what it was,
so I kept it in the freezer.
It's thinly sliced kelp
preserved with salt.
-Salted kelp.
-It's salted kelp.
-What is it?
-It's kelp.
You can add a little bit of it
when you make seasoned veggies.
-It adds a lot of flavor to broths too.
-Yes, it's all seasoned.
-It's natural condiment.
-What is this?
-Kelp.
-It's made with kelp.
-It's good.
-Isn't it?
But it's too sweet.
-It's made with salt, though.
-Let me give you some.
Is there a bit of salt?
-It's made with sugar.
-There's a bit of it.
But the savory taste of kelp is
already delicious.
-You can all take a little.
-Really?
This is great.
Can they use it as an ingredient?
Yes or no? No?
I can taste a bit of MSG,
so I don't really like it.
-You don't have much in the freezer.
-I don't.
I see some bread and fish.
And there's another fridge.
There are all kinds of kimchi.
How many are there?
I made some,
and my acquaintances made some.
I made leaf mustard kimchi
because I really love it.
I always need kimchi with Western,
Japanese, or Korean cuisine.
I always eat steak with kimchi too.
-There were a few don'ts today.
-It won't be easy.
-It sounds hard.
-Really?
It sounds so easy to me.
We just need to put lemon on your dish.
-Right? You don't need to season it.
-Exactly.
We just have to pour lemon juice on it.
You can't just pour it.
Just a little?
What kind of orders
did Yong-yeo put in today?
Let's find out her order. Show us.
-Whatever, I want a luxurious breakfast.
-Whatever!
She wants a luxurious breakfast.
I'm here with such famous chefs,
so I thought it'd be great if they made
something very classy to my taste.
-I see.
-Yes.
Let's find out the next order.
-What's this seafood dish?
-What is this?
-Seafood.
When I moved to my husband's hometown,
I tried thin-legged octopus
for the first time.
And you couldn't forget it.
-Abalone.
-Sea cucumber.
It wasn't just a regular one,
-but red sea cucumber.
-Red sea cucumber.
-It sounds fun.
-The three ingredients.
Thin-legged octopus,
abalone, red sea cucumber.
These are Yong-yeo's orders.
She had many things
she didn't want to eat.
Please make a wise choice.
-It sounds hard.
-Yes.
Gyeong-jun has the least stars,
so we'll let you choose first.
I need to win another star soon,
-so I'll go for the luxurious breakfast.
-The luxurious breakfast.
A luxurious breakfast
that's better than a hotel buffet.
Luxury goes well with him.
When luxury and food come together,
who would suit that order best?
-Son Jong-won?
-It's you, Luxury Choi.
I'll make a luxurious breakfast for you.
Gyeong-jun and Hyun-suk
are up against each other.
-A return match.
-All right.
-It's a return match.
-Next, seafood dishes.
The ingredients are great.
Abalones and red sea cucumbers.
I'm in Japanese cuisine,
so I should cook with seafood.
I'll go for it.
Ho-young goes for seafood
as a Japanese cuisine chef.
-Fabri.
-Fabri?
-Why?
-Are you going for the seafood?
The seafood.
I was smitten with your charms.
OH, MY
He fell for her.
-I became a fan right away.
-I see.
Chef Ho-young and Chef Fabri
will cook with seafood.
Then, please
let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
This is the first round
with Yong-yeo's ingredients.
The Louis Vui-bleep of chefs,
-Choi Hyun-suk.
-Louis Vui-bleep?
The Pra-bleep of chefs, Bae Gyeong-jun.
The two are up against each other.
Gyeong-jun had his debut two months ago,
and at that time, he took down
Choi Hyun-suk the Great and won.
But I heard you weren't so thrilled.
Chef Hyun-suk came to me and…
Keep it up, Gyeong-jun!
You can do it, Gyeong-jun!
It was humiliating.
It hurt my pride a lot.
It must feel awful.
He's never been bothered like that
over his entire career.
-Hyun-suk thought he was a joke.
-Yes.
I rooted for him with all my heart.
CHUCKLING IN DISBELIEF
-But he took it in a distorted way.
-Come to think of it, yes.
-It's heartbreaking.
-You must establish order again
-in the world of Western cuisine.
-I'm done for.
But your tone was suspicious.
-Really?
-You can do it, Gyeong-jun!
I'll change my tone.
You can do this, Chef Gyeong-jun.
-He should've done this.
-Yes.
I think this would be better.
CHEF HYUN-SUK'S INGREDIENTS: KELP VINEGAR,
CORIANDER, MULBERRY CHEONG, NATTO, LEMON
SEASONED DRIED LAVER, LEAF MUSTARD KIMCHI,
BUTTER, SALMON, BEET, YOGURT, RYE BREAD
The dish I'm making is called
Luxury Choice.
With Choi in choice.
When it comes to a luxurious breakfast,
-people often eat eggs Benedict.
-Yes.
-I saw some hearty natto.
-Yes?
I'll use those and make a healthy dish.
-Whoa.
-With natto?
I've made eggs Benedict
only once when I got licensed,
-so it's been 30 years.
-I see.
Do you enjoy eggs Benedict?
CHUCKLES
-Gosh, whatever.
-Whatever?
YONG-YEO CAN'T LIE
I'll have to try it and see.
It was a part of the breakfast, but…
-She's very honest.
-Yes.
Will you use lemons or salmon?
She loves salmon, so yes. And lemons too.
-He'll use salmon and lemons.
-He will.
CHEF GYEONG-JUN'S INGREDIENTS: WASABI,
BALSAMIC VINEGAR, TOMATO SAUCE, YOGURT
PICKLED GARLIC, CAULIFLOWER, PAPRIKA,
NAENGMYEON BROTH, SALTED KELP, AND MORE
Up against him is Chef Gyeong-jun.
What's your dish?
My dish is called Yong and Rich.
-Yong and Rich.
-Yes, Yong and Rich.
Not young and rich?
-It's for Yong-yeo, so Yong and Rich.
-It's Yong and Rich.
You had lots of Korean ingredients
in your fridge.
You had doenjang and leaf mustard kimchi,
so I'll use Korean ingredients
and turn it into a luxurious
-Mediterranean-style breakfast.
-Mediterranean-style.
-With Korean ingredients?
-Mediterranean-style?
-I think she'll love it.
-She will.
He'll use lots of lemons.
Are you using any flour?
-No?
-I have to use bread.
-That's flour.
-You're using flour.
-You're using bread?
-Yes.
-It's rye bread.
-Rye bread?
I can leave it out if you don't like it.
It's just a side dish.
-Rye bread?
-He'll use rye bread.
-It's not so bad.
-Not bad?
-It's not bad.
-You're saved.
-Rye is fine.
-It's not bad.
She's very strict.
She didn't want the salted kelp before.
Did you take it?
-Yes, I'm using it.
-Gyeong-jun is using it.
Good grief. Sweet mercy.
She just said, "Sweet mercy!"
-Chef Hyun-suk?
-Why is this here?
I DIDN'T DO IT
HIDING
He's so funny.
Weren't you two going to use it?
I won't use anything
you said no, thank you to.
That sounds great.
And now, let us begin.
-Are we starting now?
-Yes, we're starting.
He wants to defeat Choi Hyun-suk,
the top chef of the show right now,
and become the young and rich chef,
Bae Gyeong-jun!
But he claims no one can discuss
a luxurious dish without him.
The old and rich, Chef Choi Hyun-suk.
Which one of them will make
the most luxurious breakfast?
And now, all you want is
a luxurious breakfast, so…
Whatever!
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
THE LUXURIOUS BREAKFAST ROUND
HE BEGINS WITH SALMON
Hey, with that?
He's marinating salmon with salted kelp.
-She said she didn't like that.
-He used a lot of salted kelp.
She didn't like how it tasted like MSG.
-He just threw in MSG.
-A handful of that?
-Lemon zest.
-He should use it wisely.
Are you adding the fragrance?
Yes, that and seasoning.
That's a wonderful idea.
That's called a dry rub.
-Without oil.
-Dry rub.
HYUN-SUK BEGINS WITH SOME BEET
He's boiling some beet.
-Beet.
-He's boiling it?
Chef Hyun-suk is using bread too.
She didn't say "no, thank you."
HE QUICKLY PICKED IT UP
He's toasting the rye bread.
-He's making a hotel breakfast.
-Yes, right.
1. CHOP CAULIFLOWER AND BOIL
-What's that, Chef Gyeong-jun?
-Cauliflower.
-I see.
-It's good for you.
Yes, it's good for your health.
That's a great ingredient.
STARTING THE TIMER
ORGANIZING EVERYTHING NEATLY
He makes eggs Benedict for the first time
since the license exam.
The poached egg is the most important part
of eggs Benedict.
Both of them.
He's poaching the egg.
This is the important part.
This is the most important part
of eggs Benedict.
He added vinegar,
which helps the egg
stay together and harden.
He's done
if he fails to make the poached egg.
-Isn't that the key part?
-Yes.
THE TIMER RINGS
2. COOL CAULIFLOWER IN ICED WATER AND DRY
Chef Gyeong-jun, why did you break an egg?
-Gyeong-jun?
-I'm poaching it too.
-You'll make a poached egg too?
-Yes.
3. ADD VINEGAR AND CAULIFLOWER WATER
INTO BOILING WATER
SWISH
He's using a whisk
to create a twister in the water.
It went in nicely.
-They're using different methods.
-They are.
-Nice.
-Their styles.
-Their styles are different.
-One used a dish, the other used a ladle.
Fabri, who do you think is better?
WONDERING…
-Using a dish is the fine dining style.
-Yes.
-This is the usual style.
-Fabri liked Gyeong-jun better.
He's the Joseon style.
-The isolated king style.
-Yes.
OLD AND RICH
-That looks good.
-The salmon.
He pulled out the salmon.
They're both using salmon.
Keep an eye on them and see
who's using sugar and oil.
Whoa, was that sugar or salt?
-Salt.
He just salted the salmon.
She said she eats a bit of salt.
READING HER FACE
-Wasn't that too much?
-The salt.
-He's using oil!
-The oil!
Wait.
He needs to use a little bit of olive oil.
THE NEXT COMPETING CHEFS
ARE LISTENING INTENTLY
1. PUT SALMON ON A GRIDIRON
AND GRILL WITH OLIVE OIL
-He can use that much.
-Was that okay?
It'll taste good when it's simply grilled.
The salmon looks amazing.
He coated the salmon with olive oil
and began to grill it.
-The egg is done. Does it look good?
-I hope it doesn't pop.
Does it look good?
A little more time.
OVER THE POACHED EGG,
HE BEGINS TO MELT BUTTER
Did he just put butter in?
CHECKING THE OIL TEMPERATURE
-I see.
-Is that oil?
-Into the oil.
-Into the oil?
Just like that? He's confiting that.
-That's all oil.
-An oil dish.
He's marinading it in oil.
-Everything in there is oil.
-He's marinading it in oil.
-He just threw it into oil with kelp.
-She told him not to do that.
In the fashion of getting steamed in oil.
She told him not to do that.
HYUN-SUK IS FOCUSED ON THE SALMON TOO
Whoa, it's on fire!
Is it burnt?
Is it okay? Oh, no. I think it's burnt.
You'll turn it into some more,
salmon soot!
-Some more and salmon?
-Salmon soot?
THE SALMON IS TURNING INTO SOOT
-No!
-It's stuck!
-You have to save it!
ITS SKIN IS STILL STUCK
This isn't good!
-It's turning into salmon soot!
-Salmon soot!
-You have to put it out!
-It's burning!
-Save it!
-No!
-No, it's burnt!
-It turned into salmon soot.
Doesn't it look too dark?
-It's not.
-Is it because it's too greasy?
Is that so?
It's charred.
It's all right.
GYEONG-JUN MAKES SAUCE
Doenjang, sesame oil,
and balsamic vinegar.
ALL RIGHT
Gyeong-jun uses lemon too.
He added lemon.
BRUSHING THE SAUCE ON THE CAULIFLOWER
INTO THE OVEN
They only have
9 minutes and 52 seconds left.
-Time is flying too quickly.
-Yes.
-There are nine minutes left.
-Gosh.
2. ADD COOKED BEET AND WATER
WITH AN IMMERSION BLENDER
HE'S ABOUT TO GRIND THE BEET…
THE BEET JUICE FLOWS OUT
-Look at that!
-Hey!
-What's going on?
-It's so scary!
A horror movie! It's like a horror movie!
-It's horrifying!
-How scary!
It's the horror special.
Don't kill it!
-Don't kill it!
-He put in too much.
It's making us uncomfortable.
-What's that?
-The blood is seeping out.
How scary!
Is that supposed to happen?
-No, I've never seen that before.
-What are you grinding?
-Beet.
-It was like a horror movie.
Yong-yeo begins to frown.
HER FACE SAYS, "NO, THANK YOU"
-What's he doing right now?
-What's he doing?
-What was that?
-He's using lemons.
He needs lots of lemon juice.
Yong-yeo's favorite, lemons.
He added lemon juice into the beet juice.
-Yogurt.
-What's it for?
-It goes in there?
-He mixes it with beet.
With beet.
-Is he boiling yogurt?
-Sugar-free yogurt.
-He's boiling yogurt?
-That's a pretty color.
Can you boil yogurt?
Boiling yogurt will destroy
all its lactic acid bacteria.
-He doesn't care about nutrition.
-Goodbye, lactic acid bacteria.
It's sterile now.
Yong-yeo doesn't look so thrilled.
She doesn't look so happy right now.
Why do you think
she takes lactic acid bacteria?
She eats it for the lactic acid bacteria!
-How can you kill it all? Whatever!
-Whatever!
-What is this?
-No, the yo…
-That's a nice color, though.
-It is.
I'll have to wait and see.
-Things may change drastically at the end.
-Yes.
Let's watch until the end.
Gyeong-jun fishes out the salmon.
He's slicing cucumber.
YOGURT, WASABI, AND GINGER JUICE
5. MIX CUCUMBER, SALTED KELP, SAUCE,
AND ADD LEMON JUICE AND ZEST
THE MEDITERRANEAN CUCUMBER SALAD
WITH TZATZIKI SAUCE IS DONE
ABSORBED IN COOKING SALMON
Whoa, yes.
HE FINALLY REMEMBERED THE POACHED EGG
WHAT HAPPENED TO IT?
It's ruined.
-Do it over.
-It's been overcooked.
-He forgot.
-I forgot.
He's poaching the egg for the second time.
Was it ruined?
-Goodness.
-Oh, no. He's trying again.
Oh, no. He's trying again.
-It's been too long.
-I keep the ladle there
-and watch it until it's poached.
-Exactly.
He should've watched it
even if it took up some time.
It was overcooked.
Yes, so will you be quiet?
Why do you think we're here
if we have to sit quietly?
Why would I be on Chef & My Fridge?
You might as well cook at home
or at a temple!
Why would you cook here?
GYEONG-JUN CHECKS HIS POACHED EGG TOO
It came out perfectly.
-That's what it's like.
-Gyeong-jun succeeds.
The egg yolk should be translucent.
He's using cucumber.
I think he'll grind that.
He's using cucumber, tomato…
He's using lots of Korean ingredients.
I'm making cold Spanish soup
-called gazpacho.
-It's gazpacho!
He's making gazpacho.
He's using lactic acid bacteria
with kimchi water.
He added kimchi water.
-Lactic acid bacteria are great for you.
-Yes.
It looks like Chef Gyeong-jun got
more points so far.
BUT…
Why won't it work this time?
The blender isn't working.
-I think he needs help.
-Help him.
Can someone help me?
I guess he didn't check.
You're losing lots of time.
You have 6 minutes and 30 seconds.
-He's having trouble!
-Oh, no!
ANXIOUS
-It's like this.
-It is?
-He can't do it!
-That wasn't it!
It didn't fit perfectly.
You have 6 minute and 20 seconds!
-Like this.
-He should've checked.
-He can't grind the soup!
-You lost a minute!
-It's not working!
-No!
FAILED
-What now?
-Oh, no.
EVERYONE HAS A MELTDOWN
KWON SUNG-JUN GOES OUT
LEE JOON GOES OUT(?)
FABRI RE-ENTERS
HE FINALLY SUCCEEDS
Do you need help?
You got it?
RETURNING TO HIS SEAT
It's working.
SIGH
What just happened, Gyeong-jun?
You just lost 40 seconds.
In that while, Chef Hyun-suk
finished poaching the egg.
HE BEGINS TO MAKE SAUCE RIGHT AWAY
Kelp vinegar and egg.
-He's making the hollandaise sauce.
-Hollandaise sauce.
IT SHOULD BECOME SMOOTH LIKE SAUCE
BUT THE EGG YOLK IS TURNING INTO LUMPS
CHECKING FOR TIME
HE THROWS IT OUT
-Did it go well?
-Does it look good?
I failed.
You failed? Why? I thought it looked good.
The egg yolk was ruined.
Well, the poached egg is fine.
Are you doing it over?
A chicken had to go into labor
to lay that egg!
-It had to go into labor?
-The hollandaise sauce?
A chicken had to go into labor
for that egg!
-He's in trouble.
-A whisk.
This is a lot of fun.
And he'll start whisking now.
The hollandaise sauce will only look good
with at least three egg yolks or so.
But he's doing it by using just one.
-I think he's in trouble.
-Do you need me to hold your hand?
All right. Okay.
-He's in trouble. It's ruined.
-What is this?
-It was ruined again.
-It's fine.
Be quiet.
He looks the most flustered today.
-Really?
-Among the days I've seen him.
Sung-ju, it's an absolute mess!
Tell us what it's like out there!
-I'll go out and check.
-This is the worst.
-I've never seen him like that.
-Check on him!
He's such a veteran too.
-It was ruined. He said it was.
-It was ruined?
HE WASHED OFF LEAF MUSTARD KIMCHI
Goodbye, lactic acid bacteria.
-He just got natto.
-Natto.
He killed the nutrition in that too.
-You're right.
-You killed the bacteria in natto too?
-He sterilized it too.
-Even natto?
A sterilized dish.
The sauce made with ground beet.
-Yes, try that.
-Let me try this one.
The sterilized sauce.
Does it taste luxurious?
-Gosh, it's too sour!
-Too sour?
-Too much lemon juice?
-I think so.
She likes lemons,
-but it's too sour for me.
-Is it?
-He couldn't keep the balance.
-It may be sour to you,
-but it may not be to others.
-Yes!
Yes, this is strictly my taste.
He just added butter.
She wouldn't like a lot of butter.
-Do you like butter?
-Butter?
-Just let him do it.
-Let him do it?
-Just let him do it!
-Leave him alone.
GIVEN UP ON HIM
-Oh, no!
-Hyun-suk already fell out of her favor.
-This is a lot of fun.
-He's trying to make it delicious.
The leaf mustard kimchi is good.
He put it in here.
He just got the salmon.
Gyeong-jun just blended everything.
This blended thing. Let me try this one.
It's a Mediterranean cold soup.
Are you in the Mediterranean?
I am.
It must taste clean.
But he used Korean ingredients.
-That's amazing.
-I thought I was in Greece.
It's giving Greece.
Gazpacho is made
with red wine vinegar.
But he used kimchi water
for sourness instead.
-To add sourness?
-That's a great idea.
Yes, so it was fermented.
HE PUTS A DISH INTO THE OVEN
RUNNING TO THE FRIDGE!
HE HAD PUT A DISH IN HERE BEFORE
RETURNING WITH THE COLD DISH
-He's using leaf mustard kimchi too.
-He's using it too.
He's going to serve it as is.
He's pouring it now.
FILLING IT UP WITH GAZPACHO
It looks pretty!
-It looks like gazpacho.
-It's pretty.
You have two minutes.
RYE BREAD TOPPED WITH STERILIZED(?) NATTO
AND POACHED EGG ABOVE THAT
FINISHES THE EGGS BENEDICT
WITH DRIED LAVER FLAKES
LASTLY, THE BEET SAUCE
ADDING MULBERRY CHEONG
SERVING SALMON WITH THE BEET SAUCE
They both have similar color schemes.
The salmon goes
on top of the sauce as a whole.
It does look a bit burnt.
-Wouldn't it taste charred?
-No.
-It looks like soot.
-It's not.
He goes back to hollandaise.
He seems a bit pouty.
He's done!
Hyun-suk is done
with a minute and 30 seconds left.
GYEONG-JUN BEGINS TO MAKE SALAD
Gyeong-jun lost 40 seconds or so
while wrestling with the blender.
More lemon.
He added balsamic vinegar.
I think that's the salad.
You have a minute left.
We're only waiting for Gyeong-jun.
HYUN-SUK RANG THE BELL A WHILE AGO
ADDING SALT
DOES HE FORGET THINGS OUT OF HABIT?
Oh, wait.
You rang the bell already.
What are you doing?
-What are you doing?
-I'll take the bell back.
You'll take it back?
-He can take it back?
-It's my first time seeing it.
PULLING OUT THE DISH FROM THE OVEN
-He'll take back the bell.
-I almost let him run with this.
-He'll take back ringing the bell.
-He'll take it back.
Roasted cauliflower.
He cancels ringing the bell.
-He cancels.
-And he's finally done.
In the end, he hid the burnt portion.
TOP SECURITY(?)
-It's not burnt. It's crunchy.
-It's not?
And it's cooked to medium rare
on the inside.
HE MAKES SAUCE FOR THE CAULIFLOWER
8. GRIND CORIANDER, PARSLEY, OLIVE OIL,
BALSAMIC VINEGAR, AND PICKED GARLIC
FINISHED IN NO TIME
TOP THE SAUCE GENEROUSLY
OVER THE CAULIFLOWER
Gyeong-jun.
You have 20 seconds left.
You must finish within 15 minutes.
THE EGG WHITE SPLITS APART
TREMBLING
-No!
-You must finish within 15 minutes.
LANDED SAFELY
Hey, you saved it.
THE EGG YOLK IS PEEKING OUT
-It's still intact.
-Eight!
I won't root for him today.
SERVING THE CUCUMBER SALAD
-Five. Four.
-Four.
-Three. Two.
-Oh, no.
-Two. One.
And he's done.
Where's the topping?
I should've topped it,
but I didn't have enough time.
I see.
If you had it made, just put it on top.
May I just top it with the salad?
Shouldn't you get my consent?
You're right!
No.
DISAPPOINTED
He's in a tough spot today.
Go ahead.
BUT THE OLD MAN IS STILL GENEROUS
-He already had it made.
-Chef Hyun-suk was considerate.
-He's such a generous man.
-The last touch.
He had trouble with that
because of the blender.
Everything was finished.
THE LUXURIOUS DISHES ENTER
WOW
All right. First, Chef Hyun-suk's dish.
Please try Luxury Choice first.
SALMON STEAK
SERVED WITH LEAF MUSTARD AND BEET SAUCE
CHEF CHOI HYUN-SUK'S LUXURY CHOICE
-Pop the poached egg and eat it together.
-What?
-Pop the poached egg.
-Pop the egg.
-But I don't want to pop it.
-She doesn't want to.
-It's such a shame.
-It looks so nice and…
-Yes, it's a lot of hard work.
You have to pop it
and eat everything together.
-Is that better? Then I'll do it.
-Yes, it is.
-I'm sorry.
-She popped the egg yolk.
-It was cooked perfectly.
-Try it with the egg yolk.
You should dip it in some egg yolk.
-I have to?
-It'll be even better.
You can take a big bite.
That's how she likes it.
She tried the egg yolk too.
GULP
-It's good.
-Is it?
-It's not bad.
-I see.
How does it compare
to your usual hotel breakfast?
That place is just a buffet.
But this was a luxurious dish,
so it's different.
-So they're different.
-Yes.
-He put so much work into this.
-And it's luxurious.
This bread is quite nice.
Does the bread taste nice? The rye bread.
-He had it toasted.
-I see.
She's taking a bite
of bread, egg, and the egg yolk.
It looks good.
-It is.
-I see.
-The main dish is important to me.
-The main dish.
-She loves salmon very much.
-She does.
-Oh, my.
-I made the skin extra-crispy
-and soft and medium-rare inside.
-It's topped with coriander, my favorite.
-Yes, she's not listening.
-It's crispy outside and soft inside.
-She doesn't even listen to Hyun-suk.
-That's almost…
I don't have to eat this part.
SHE PUSHES THE SOOT(?) SKIN OUT
What's wrong?
She won't eat the skin.
She pushed it out.
-I actually love the skin.
-I see.
-But it's too…
-It looks nicely cooked.
-Don't push it out.
-It's not burnt.
The skin must be cooked deliciously.
-Try it with the sauce.
-It'll taste crunchy and delicious.
Please check and see if the skin is burnt.
IS THE SALMON SKIN ALL RIGHT?
It was cooked well.
-It wasn't burnt.
-And…
I thought it burned
when it caught on fire.
TRYING THE SAUCE FIRST
This sauce is delicious.
-"This sauce is delicious."
I knew it.
You said you didn't like
lots of seasoning or strong-tasting food.
It's a little too strong for me,
but it tastes great with lots of lemon.
It was too sour for me.
See? That's why he'll age faster.
You'll age faster.
Eat lots of sour food.
It's delicious.
So you think it's delicious
when it's that sour?
Yes, the sauce is very delicious.
-Gosh.
-Today, that sauce…
My stomach is going,
"Thanks a lot, Yong-yeo."
Oh, boy.
-It's thanking her.
-For putting in delicious food.
Her body is happy. Is it good?
JEALOUS
My stomach is going, "Thank you."
Her body is thanking her.
-It says thanks, not saying no, thank you.
-Thank you.
-I kind of like the sauce.
-She liked the sauce.
Next, Chef Gyeong-jun's dish.
It's Yong and Rich.
DOENJANG CAULIFLOWER STEAK
TOPPED WITH A POACHED EGG
CHEF BAE GYEONG-JUN'S YONG AND RICH
Gosh, this looks good.
Did you think it looked good
as soon as you saw it?
All of a sudden?
I made it with tomato
and leaf mustard kimchi.
WHAT'S LEAF MUSTARD GAZPACHO LIKE?
TASTING
What's it like?
There's perilla oil on top,
so please mix that in.
-There's perilla oil on top.
-Mix it in.
DROPPED!
You know…
You know,
he's done a great job. Here's why.
Leaf mustard is good for you.
It cleanses your blood.
It's amazing that he used it
with this sauce and made this.
THE LEAF MUSTARD IS AMAZING
Doesn't it taste like
a Mediterranean dish?
Do you feel that?
We have to learn
from the Mediterranean diet.
-We must learn from their diet.
-We must learn.
It's nothing like a buffet.
-It's luxurious.
-A buffet would serve just pumpkin soup.
-Right.
-Or cream soup.
-Yes.
It's amazing.
-She's amazed.
-And try the salmon too.
-It'd be nice if you try it with cucumber.
-With cucumber.
-With the tzatziki sauce.
-There's cucumber?
I see. It's down here.
There's that thing.
The thing she didn't like.
-The kelp.
-The thing she told him not to use.
He probably has a reason
for doing what you told him not to.
You should try it with the salmon.
That'd taste too strong.
There's a bit of wasabi.
It is a bit salty.
-Try it with the salmon.
-Try the salmon.
-You have to eat it with the salmon.
-No.
But still.
-Even so, it's too salty!
-You can't do that!
It should be good just as it is.
-Why didn't you put lemon on this?
-Why didn't you put lemon on that?
You didn't use lemon?
THIS TIME, SHE TRIES IT WITH THE SALMON
It would've been perfect
with a dash of lemon juice.
Gosh, the lemon.
-It's a shame that he didn't use lemon.
-The lemon.
Gosh, the lemon.
Now, the last one.
-Pop the egg and eat it together.
-Pop the egg?
-I have to pop this too?
-Yes.
I don't like popping the egg yolk
when I eat poached eggs.
-I see.
-I don't have to do it, right?
-No, you don't.
She wants to eat it her way.
AMAZED AT THE QUEEN'S SPIRIT
It's right for the customer
to eat it however they like.
You should've boiled the egg!
Why didn't you get that?
Hey, you have to stop it.
You punk.
I popped this egg
-because Hyun-suk served it with bread.
-Yes.
-I liked how it smeared into the bread.
-That's why she popped it.
But it's kind of weird
to pop it over the cauliflower.
She has clear preferences.
It's a bit greasy too.
A BITE OF JUST THE CAULIFLOWER STEAK
What's it like, Yong-yeo? Is it good?
You tried your best.
He tried his best?
What do you mean by that?
-You tried your best?
-What does she mean?
-He did try.
-He tried his best.
-Right? He tried his best.
She looked at everything
with strict preferences.
-Do you want to press it already?
-The remote control? Now?
-She went for the remote control.
-She made her decision already.
-She went for the remote control already.
-The remote control.
-She's ready.
-She decides quickly.
Here's one thing I want to say clearly.
It's tough to beat experience.
-Experience.
-It's tough to beat.
-I see. That was significant.
-Yes.
Joon, will you try it on our behalf?
Thank you.
-It's for Joon.
-I was starving.
Give him Chef Hyun-suk's dish.
I'm sorry to ask,
but are you happy because it's free?
I think you're happy that it's free.
I was already dying to try it
when they cooked because of the smell.
SUPER EXCITED OVER THE SMELL
-How do I eat this?
-Try Chef Hyun-suk's dish first.
They both tried hard.
Eat everything together.
Yes. That's how it's supposed to be eaten.
A BIG BITE OF THE NATTO EGGS BENEDICT
What is this?
NATTO STRETCHES OUT
-You've never had anything like it?
-What's this?
-Natto.
-That's natto. Beans.
-Beans?
-Beans.
You should've said those were beans.
How is he supposed to know what natto is?
Young-kyu, he's so clueless.
That could happen, Father. Come on.
You know,
this flavor is very delicious yet healthy.
It doesn't taste too strong at all.
Here's how it feels. Gosh.
HE FACES A DEAD END
He has to express this.
This is…
How can I put this?
It tastes like natto.
Yes, because he used natto!
Gosh, he has a perfect sense of taste!
Wow.
This is the main dish.
This is the main dish, the lemon sauce.
-The salmon.
-It's salmon, not the sauce.
-The salmon is the main dish.
-It's the salmon.
-Like this.
-It's really good.
Joon gives it a try.
WILL IT SATISFY JOON'S APPETITE TOO?
CURIOUS
-It feels like I'm at a vacation spot,
-Yes.
and a very talented local chef
just made me this under a palm tree.
-It tastes like a local dish overseas?
-Yes.
This is amazing.
-All right.
-Try that one.
-Give that to him.
-This time, Gyeong-jun's dish.
CHEF BAE GYEONG-JUN'S YONG AND RICH
Whoa, this is delicious. What's this?
He likes this kind of flavor.
His response is so obvious.
That's the Mediterranean-style soup.
Whoa, this soup.
-How is this so good?
-I see.
Is it because you've never tried it?
I think he added
some radish kimchi water too.
-You're right.
-He did.
This is a foreign dish, right?
But its balance with kimchi
is unbelievable.
Kimchi played a great role in this.
He's already used up his expressions.
-He used up his words.
-He's done.
-Cucumber and salmon.
-Tzatziki sauce.
NEXT, HE TRIES THE SALMON CONFIT SALAD
Now, so?
-Gosh.
-What is it?
-Do you like it?
-Is it good?
-It's so good.
-Gosh.
What is this… It's…
Is this raw fish?
Salmon.
It was cooked lightly.
I like my food cooked rare.
-When my mom told me to get bulgogi,
-Bulgogi?
it smelled so good
so I ate the raw meat.
In its marinated state?
Yes, in its marinated state.
I like that a lot, as well as tofu.
THE NEXT PARTICIPANTS ARE IN TROUBLE
-You had that raw?
-Wait.
IN SHOCK
But I'm alive and well.
It's not dangerous.
It suits me fine.
My checkups always look fine.
He likes how it isn't cooked too much.
-Try the egg.
-I'll pop the egg.
NEXT, THE CAULIFLOWER STEAK
He's different.
A BIG BITE
Does it have a new flavor?
The cauliflower may taste strange.
This is rather light.
This was the first time
he didn't say it was delicious.
-It's just light.
-It's rather light.
"You tried hard," and "It's rather light."
What do they mean by these?
He must like strong-tasting food.
-People who work out would love it.
-People who work out?
-They don't care about the flavor.
-No.
But the choice is Yong-yeo's.
-Goodness. Sweet mercy.
-Sweet mercy.
Press one for Bae Gyeong-jun.
Press two for Choi Hyun-suk.
Make your choice and press the button.
Only the fridge owner can press that.
Gosh, this was…
-Oh, here we go.
-Here we go. She pressed it.
Whatever, I want a luxurious breakfast!
Will Gyeong-jun win against Hyun-suk
two rounds in a row?
Or will Hyun-suk
get his revenge on Gyeong-jun?
Which chef
did Yong-yeo choose?
Whose breakfast was better?
CHOI HYUN-SUK WINS
CHOI HYUN-SUK'S LUXURIOUS CHOICE WINS
Choi Hyun-suk wins!
AS ALWAYS, HIS SWOOSH OF VICTORY
FEELS BAD AND AVOIDS LOOKING AT HIM
-I couldn't help it.
-What was the biggest difference?
The salmon skin was roasted perfectly.
It was broiled over fire.
And I loved the sauce a lot.
-The beet sauce.
-The sterilized sauce.
-The sterilized sauce?
-It was a great idea.
But he only tried his best
with the cauliflower.
-He tried his best and lost.
-It's over.
That's why I feel bad.
And for the salmon,
-I would've liked it if it were more sour.
-More lemon juice.
Do you have more lemons left?
I do.
You should've put more in!
-I've been regretting it.
-You should've made lemon soup!
I kept mentioning lemon.
She kept giving him hints!
Just add some minced garlic
to lemon juice.
-Add just a bit of minced garlic.
-Gosh.
-Then add a whisk of wasabi.
-Yes.
-Add some wasabi.
-She already gave you hints.
Then add lots of lemon juice inside.
That's the best sauce.
-That's the best!
-That's the best sauce!
I kept mentioning lemon.
-This is why experience is important.
-Exactly.
Chef Hyun-suk's experience wins,
and he takes yet another star.
-Please put it on him.
-Really?
Anyway, congratulations.
Please put the star on him.
Why do you have so many stars?
Share a little.
This is his ninth win!
Congratulations!
-Thank you.
-Congratulations.
The ninth win.
Next, the second round
with ingredients from Yong-yeo's fridge.
What's this seafood dish?
-Whatever!
-What is this?
Yong-yeo has the top three seafood
she enjoyed the most
over the 80 years of her life.
Red sea cucumber.
Abalone.
-Thin-legged octopus.
-They're all good.
You'll have to use
these ingredients today.
The top Japanese chef,
Chef Jung Ho-young is
up against Chef Fabri,
an Italian Michelin-star chef.
This is their first round.
As you have seen already
with Yong-yeo's evaluation,
-it's not easy to please her.
-No.
That's why I brought garlic and lemon.
You did that right away.
She also said in passing
that she didn't prefer instant rice.
So I decided to make rice myself.
LOOK AT HOW CONSIDERATE HO-YOUNG IS
That's a good move.
He's such a true chef.
And among the things she says
when evaluating, you should be scared of,
-"You've tried your best."
-If she says that, it's over.
"You've done well. Good work."
-It really hurt.
-"You can't win a star."
What about you, Fabri?
Since when I was four,
I grew up at a seafood restaurant.
-Really?
-Yes.
-He must be familiar with it.
-My family ran a seafood restaurant.
-Yes, in Italy.
He became a Michelin one-star chef
by using seafood.
-Fabri will win, then.
-Let's just say he won.
I'm sure no one here uses
as much seafood as I do.
-You studied in Osaka.
-I did.
So it's Osaka versus Italy.
THE EAST VERSUS WEST
CHEF HO-YOUNG'S INGREDIENTS: WASABI,
SCORCHED RICE, PICKLED PLUM, LEMON
THIN-LEGGED OCTOPUS, CUCUMBER, ABALONE,
RED SEA CUCUMBER, PERILLA OIL, BUCKWHEAT
Chef Ho-young, what's your dish?
My dish is called…
Sea cucumber, umber, umber
FATAL CHARMS
OH, MY GOODNESS…
Sea cucumber, umber, umber
It's called Sea Cucumber Lady.
-Sea Cucumber Lady.
Isn't the samba dance great?
-Yes, the samba dance is great.
-She's pleased.
-He likes to dance.
-He does?
Yes, it's a cook-off, actually.
If he likes to dance,
why didn't you get rid of your belly?
Gosh, she strikes home.
A CRUEL REMARK
-He lost a lot of weight.
-He's trying hard.
He lost a lot of weight.
You can keep going.
-Keep going.
I'll use sea cucumbers
as my main ingredient.
In Japanese cuisine,
there's a sea cucumber dish
made by boiling it in tea.
I'll also make rice in a pot,
and let you top the sea cucumber on rice.
I also saw pickled plums,
which helps with your digestion.
I'll turn it into dressing
and mix the dressing
with thin-legged octopus and abalone.
Those sound delicious.
CHEF FABRI'S INGREDIENTS: AVOCADO OIL,
PARSLEY, CAULIFLOWER, RED SEA CUCUMBER
BEET POWDER, DOENJANG, OMIJA CHEONG,
LEMON, NABAK-KIMCHI, AND MORE
Mine's called Abalone Risotto Ssambap.
I'M THE DANCING FAIRY TODAY
-What's going on?
-What is this?
WIGGLE WIGGLE
LOOK AT THIS GUY
Wait, whoa!
CHALLENGING
I WON'T LOSE AGAINST YOU!
FANCY STEPS
IT TURNED INTO A SAMBA DANCE-OFF
Samba!
They're good.
-They're good dancers.
-She looks pleased.
He's a good dancer.
-I'm the new generation.
-I see.
The new generation of the dancing chef.
-Abalone Risotto Ssambap?
-Yes.
-Ssambap with risotto?
-I'll make abalone risotto in the style
of ssambap.
-I love risotto.
-Can you do it in 15 minutes?
-She called it very good.
-She said it was very good.
-Risotto is pretty good.
-That's not all.
I'll make ceviche
-with sea cucumbers.
-Ceviche.
I'll squeeze lots of lemon juice into it
and make it extra sour.
He wants to win her favor.
Lastly, the octopus.
I'll parboil the octopus
-and top it with cauliflower purée.
-Cauliflower.
I want to make three dishes
with each type of seafood.
Samba versus ssambap.
I wonder who'll win this round.
From salsa to samba,
Jung Ho-young is here to show
the majesty of the original dancing fairy.
But this man will show samba dance
on another level with his long limbs.
The tall dancing fairy,
Chef Fabri is up against him.
It's the samba death match
here on Chef & My Fridge.
Who'll rise above as the winner?
-The seafood dishes.
-What are these?
Let the round begin!
Begin!
THE SAMBA DEATH MATCH STARTS
-He's moving quickly.
-He's making rice.
It's very tough to make
both rice or risotto in 15 minutes.
It is.
Both rice and risotto.
They're busy.
He's using cauliflower.
Shouldn't he get started
on the risotto soon?
Cauliflower is an ingredient
Gyeong-jun used
and received an evaluation that said,
"You've tried your best."
He should handle it well.
They're killing you many more times.
Please stop.
He didn't get a lot of points
for using cauliflower.
SCORCHED RICE
-I think he's using scorched rice too.
-I guess so.
Ho-young is using all four stovetops.
ABALONE GOES INTO THE THIRD POT,
BOILING WITH COOKING WINE
Is that buckwheat tea?
-It is.
-I love buckwheat.
She likes buckwheat.
FABRI IS STILL WORKING ON THE CAULIFLOWER
IN A HASTE
Wrap. Where's the plastic wrap?
-What?
-Wrap.
-Plastic wrap.
-Under the counter.
-Down there.
Do you need plastic wrap?
He'll cook it by microwaving it
-Instead of boiling it?
-No.
WORKING ON THE CAULIFLOWER
FOR OVER 1 MINUTE
IT FINALLY GOES IN!
RED SEA CUCUMBER IS UP
-Red sea cucumber.
-He got the red sea cucumber.
-It looks really fresh.
-It's huge.
-Look at the intestines.
-You'll see yellow stuff.
-What's the yellow stuff?
-The innards.
The innards?
-The innards are delicious.
-It's really good.
That's the real deal.
There are three delicacies in Japan.
Sea cucumber innards.
Gray mullet roe.
Lastly…
Anyway, it's one of the three.
FEELING SELF-CONSCIOUS
I really love sea cucumber innards.
WIDE-EYES
Ho-young must know what to do.
-He's a Japanese chef.
-So,
I just mix it with freshly cooked rice.
It tastes good raw anyway.
-It's good raw.
-She must love it.
-It's called the ginseng of the sea.
SURPRISED
He's using red sea cucumber too.
Do you eat sea cucumbers in Italy?
We don't eat anything like this.
-Not at all?
-No.
-They don't eat sea cucumbers.
-Not in Italy.
-No sea cucumbers.
-Maybe abalones.
It looks like Ho-young is
much better with the sea cucumber.
You don't even have to explain.
The Japanese chef has
a different skill set.
HE GETS HALF OF IT READY TO PARBOIL
THE OTHER HALF IS SERVED RAW
-He's using a spoon.
-He's scraping the innards out.
He uses a different skill
to remove the innards.
FABRI SECURES THE INNARDS TOO!
-He gets the octopus.
-The octopuses.
Fabri uses octopuses.
-He'll parboil those.
He puts the sea cucumber
into the boiling water too.
-Yes.
-He's cooking the sea cucumber.
If you cook it, it'll become tiny.
-It's very tough too.
-It's very tough.
-It gets tough.
-Really? It becomes tough?
Yong-yeo looks very concerned.
-I only had it raw.
-Right?
But he's cooking it too.
-He parboiled it too.
-He did.
-Only briefly, though.
-He parboiled it quickly.
He says that's a cooking method.
-He's cooling it off with ice again.
-All right.
-That'll make it firmer.
-Yes.
-He's putting it in and pulling it out.
-In and out.
-He goes back and forth.
-Hot water, iced water.
It's like a sauna.
GOSH, THAT FEELS GREAT
Fabri finishes parboiling the octopuses.
He cools them in ice.
HE'S DONE PARBOILING
THE WHOLE SEA CUCUMBER
I've never seen
cooked sea cucumber before.
Abalone.
He cooked the red sea cucumber.
He's throwing in thin-legged octopuses.
-Chef Ho-young cooks the octopuses too.
-The octopuses.
You're supposed to parboil it.
You can't have that raw.
Yes, that's right.
-He's parboiling it lightly.
-Very lightly.
All the ingredients, thin-legged octopus,
red sea cucumber, and abalone,
-give good energy to people.
-They all give great energy.
AND SOME CUCUMBER TO SERVE ON THE SIDE!
Look at the way he chops.
-Chef Ho-young is working on a cucumber.
-He's making cuts.
-It'll stretch out like a spring.
-He'll probably salt that.
He's making just cuts and not chopping it.
-He'll make it like an accordion.
-It'll stretch out like a spring.
-It helps it get seasoned better.
-It's easier to season it.
-Between cuts.
-Yes.
Here comes his skills.
WAVY!
FROZEN!
The samba dance.
The samba dancing cucumber.
He's salting it.
-It'll make it softer.
-Yes.
He's using a cucumber too.
-Cucumber.
Fabri has a different way
of chopping the cucumber.
He's chopping it differently
from Chef Ho-young.
Ten minutes.
-Ten minutes? Already?
-Ten minutes. You're in trouble.
PARSLEY, LETTUCE
FABRI IS DONE PREPARING THE INGREDIENTS
Abalone.
THE ABALONE IS READY TOO
-These are the innards.
-The innards.
He's mixing nabak-kimchi,
sea cucumber innards,
and lemon juice.
One second.
He's blending the innards with that?
He put the innards in?
He's using it as a part
of the ceviche dressing.
It's because she said
she liked the innards.
He's using pickled plums.
Pickled plums?
It looks like he'll grind those.
That's plum purée called bainiku.
It's a sauce that's mixed
with mollusks like squid.
It helps with digestion too.
It does,
-and it removes toxins from your body.
-I see.
-You have to eat that with fish.
3. MAKE SAUCE
BY BLENDING SCORCHED RICE WATER,
PICKLED PLUMS, AND BOILED COOKING WINE
Did the heat go off for your rice?
What? Why is it off?
SUSPICIOUS
-That was bad.
-Was it Fabri?
-No!
-I don't think so.
WILL THE RICE BE OKAY?
-Omija cheong.
FABRI'S 3 SAUCES: 2. OMIJA SOY SAUCE
-Soy sauce.
-He's using soy sauce.
She said she didn't like it
when soy sauce was mixed with other stuff.
Oh, no. I'm sorry, ma'am.
It's because I'm a foreigner.
I couldn't understand perfectly.
-It's all right.
-She says it's fine.
You're suddenly feigning ignorance?
-He says that when he's cornered.
-Only when he's cornered.
He calls himself a foreigner
when he's cornered.
I was making an excuse. I'm sorry.
Chef Fabri mixed
red pepper powder in the soy sauce.
-No.
-It's not that powder.
-It's beet powder.
-Beet powder?
It's beet powder? Not red pepper powder?
WHY DID I…
She had beet powder?
-You had to grind it.
-What?
You could've used it before.
Did I try too hard?
He said I tried too hard.
No, I didn't say that.
We thought it was red pepper powder,
but it was beet powder?
-So it won't be spicy.
-No.
Yong-yeo doesn't like anything
that tastes too strong.
HO-YOUNG MAKES HIS STATEMENT WITH GARLIC
Garlic is often used in Japanese cuisine.
-Yes, it's good.
-Yes.
Is that soy sauce and garlic?
Yes, it's soy sauce.
The parboiled sea cucumber.
-That looks good.
-Doenjang.
It looks good.
SLURP
PARBOILED SEA CUCUMBER IS FINISHED
-Seven minutes.
-Seven minutes?
Oh, no.
He has to make rice.
He hasn't started on the risotto.
When are you going to do that?
-He has less than seven minutes.
-The risotto.
It's not coming out.
-What's not coming out?
-The innards.
He has less than half the time.
You have 6 minutes and 35 seconds.
Fabri is still preparing ingredients.
You have 6 minutes and 30 seconds.
He's chopping the cooked abalone.
He's mincing abalone innards.
Ho-young seems to be much faster.
-Huh? Why isn't this working?
-Emergency.
-This is a mess.
-It's a mess.
Where's the perilla oil?
-Perilla oil?
-It's never there to begin with.
Over there.
Perilla oil!
What?
-What was that?
-Perilla oil?
Take it back after using it!
He has no time to do that.
He's using scorched rice.
-Scorched rice.
-He began cooking with scorched rice.
Scorched rice?
This can become quite a controversy.
An Italian chef is
using scorched rice to make risotto?
I guess he'll make risotto with that.
But he still only has five minutes.
Can he really do it?
Is Chef Fabri using lemon cheong?
-Lemon cheong.
DOENJANG, LEMON CHEONG
OLIVE OIL
-He's seasoning the abalone.
-Yes.
5. SLICE THE COOKED ABALONE
AND MIX WITH LEMON CHEONG AND DOENJANG
He's working on
the red sea cucumber innards.
Yes, the red sea cucumber innards.
This is something Yong-yeo loves.
Handle it carefully, Chef Ho-young.
BECOME SOFTER!
What will he do
with the red sea cucumber innards?
Is that the dipping sauce?
Maybe he'll put lemon in it.
-Wasabi.
-Wasabi and the innards?
-With red sea cucumber innards.
Adding a dash of wasabi makes it the best.
She said it'd be best.
Five minutes.
You can put in a little more.
-Jung-hwan, please go out.
-I did.
All right.
Osaka versus Italy.
Ho-young uses abalone too.
He's doing everything neatly
because he's a Japanese chef.
-Thin-legged octopus, abalone…
-Thin-legged octopuses are out.
Scorched rice.
WHAT WILL SCORCHED RICE RISOTTO LOOK LIKE?
ADDING WATER
-Will that become risotto?
-Yes, you're right.
He added abalone innards
into the scorched rice.
-I see.
-It'll taste great.
-It's like abalone porridge.
-Like porridge.
PICKLED PLUM SAUCE
He's straining the plum sauce.
What did you blend here? Pickled plums?
-I made sauce by blending pickled plums.
-Blending pickled plums?
-The pickled plums…
-Ma'am.
-Ma'am, look at him.
-Hey, you got a thumbs-up.
-He puts in lemon.
-A thumbs-up.
-Remove the seeds.
-The seeds.
It's okay. I eat the seed too.
She likes the seeds too.
-Did you remove the seeds?
-I did.
-You put in too much.
-The lemon juice.
It looks so good.
-It smells sour.
-Does it?
So? Is it so delicious
that it'll make you do the samba dance?
Is it so delicious
It's too sour!
IN SHOCK
But I think she'll like it.
-She likes sour food.
-Yes.
It's too sour.
LIGHTLY SWAYING
Fabri, what are you doing?
-He's slicing the red sea cucumber.
-The red sea cucumber.
The ceviche. Where's your sauce?
I mixed nabak-kimchi, innards, and lemon.
-I see. Lemon.
-He used sea cucumber innards.
I'm curious.
I've never seen sauce made
with blended sea cucumber innards.
-That's a first.
-Right?
Jung-hwan, is there any sauce left?
-There's lots of it.
-The pink sauce.
The pink sauce.
-The color is the same as her clothes.
-It is.
-That pink sauce.
-The pink sauce.
Does this one make you do
the samba dance too?
FROWNING
What's wrong? Is it weird?
It's not for me.
It's not for you?
She might like it, though.
Chef Hyun-suk won his round
with his pink sauce.
The pink one.
It's the kimchi and innards sauce.
1ST FLOOR, SCORCHED RICE RISOTTO,
2ND FLOOR, SEASONED ABALONE
3RD FLOOR, LETTUCE,
ADDING THE SSAMBAP ASPECT
-Two minutes left.
-Two minutes.
CHOPPING THE OCTOPUS
AND MIXING IT WITH PICKLED PLUM SAUCE
THE SALTED ACCORDION CUCUMBER
CHECKING FOR SALTINESS
CHOPPED CUCUMBERS ARE READY TO GO TOO
7. MIX OCTOPUS, CUCUMBER, AND ABALONE
IN PICKLED PLUM SAUCE
-It looks really good.
-It does.
He's mixing octopus with the plum sauce.
-It looks good.
-This one looks good.
-It's still too hot.
-The cauliflower.
-It's too hot.
-It's too hot for Fabri
CAULIFLOWER
AVOCADO OIL
DONE WITH CAULIFLOWER PURÉE
CHECKING FOR TIME
SERVING THE SEASONED OCTOPUS AND ABALONE
-You have 50 seconds.
-You got 50 seconds left.
Fifty. Fifty seconds left.
-Fifty seconds.
-Start serving!
Oh, no.
-Hurry up. Fabri is in trouble.
-Fabri, add more lemon juice.
Add more lemon juice.
-Chef Ho-young is done.
-Add more lemon juice.
FABRI FINISHES HIS RISOTTO SSAMBAP TOO
Perilla oil.
-Perilla oil.
-Are you telling me to do it?
-Where is it?
-Ho-young is all done.
-Thirty seconds!
You got the perilla oil. Thirty seconds!
Hurry up.
Fabri, please hurry up.
WITH A THIN-LEGGED OCTOPUS IN HIS HAND…
-Twenty seconds.
-Fabri is out of it.
-Hurry up.
-Oh, no.
-Hurry up. What's wrong?
Ten seconds left.
I can't watch!
I FOUND IT!
-Nine. Eight.
-Seven. Six.
-Perilla oil.
Fabri, keep it up!
-Fabri, keep it up!
-Perilla oil.
-Two!
-Fabri, keep it up!
-Two! One!
Time's up!
FABRI FINISHES ABALONE RISOTTO SSAMBAP
He's done.
EXHAUSTED
-Fabri had a dramatic finish.
-Place it on.
HE FINISHES EVERYTHING DRAMATICALLY
That was such a crazy sight.
-It looks like stir-fried octopus.
-There's a lot of food.
How did he make all these?
-How did he do this in 15 minutes?
-Right?
-But…
-This is insane.
Gosh, these are amazing.
Chef Ho-young finished first.
There's something I want to say.
-What is it?
-If Fabri agrees,
can she try mine later?
I want to let the rice sit for a while.
-You want to let the rice sit?
-I see.
-Is that okay, Fabri?
-Of course. I'll let him go last.
All right. Then you can try
Chef Fabri's dishes first.
ABALONE RISOTTO SSAMBAP
MADE WITH SCORCHED RICE
SERVED WITH THIN-LEGGED OCTOPUS
AND CAULIFLOWER PURÉE
CHEF FABRI'S ABALONE RISOTTO SSAMBAP
Wait, he parboiled the sea cucumber right?
Yes, he did.
Yet how does it remain so soft?
It looks soft,
even though it was parboiled.
This is a famous dish
from Central and South America.
Please try a bite.
YUM
It was a bit strange to me.
I've never had anything like it.
What do you think?
I think…
it would've been better with more lemon.
HE DIDN'T USE ENOUGH LEMONS
I told you to make lemon soup!
You should've poured more lemon juice!
-Come on, Fabri.
-Gosh.
I told you time and time again!
TELL ME ABOUT IT…
-Young-kyu, say something to him.
-Come on!
How many times
must my mother-in-law tell you?
-Listen to her!
-Try it.
This is so frustrating.
You try it, Young-kyu.
See if she needs more lemons.
How many times do I have to tell you
to use more lemons?
I don't want this anymore!
HE'S BETTER THAN THE ACTUAL CHARACTER
Bring me that. Hey.
Bring me some wasabi and lemon.
-She wants those.
-Wasabi and lemon.
-Bring her some wasabi and lemon.
-Let me have it. Come on.
Right here. I brought minced garlic too.
-Here's how I do it.
-Yes?
Let me show you.
-This is insane.
-She's adding more lemon.
-Right in here.
-Okay.
-A little bit of wasabi.
-A little. And minced garlic.
-I don't even need to put in much.
-No.
That looks good.
Try it now, Young-kyu.
-Yes, try it now.
-Let me try it.
Let me try it, Mother.
-Mmm.
-It looks good.
Was that better, Yong-yeo?
-Isn't it good?
-Yes! Whoa.
It's exploding in my mouth.
It tastes so good.
-It's not a joke.
-I'm serious.
You have to try this sauce.
My gosh.
-It's good.
-You like it very sour.
She put half a lemon inside.
Come and try it.
-That was strong.
-Try this.
-You have to try it.
-It wakes you up right away.
JOON TRIES A BITE TOO
-Gosh, that was strong.
-Wasn't it?
Yong-yeo added some more condiments
to fit her appetite.
Then it wasn't South America anymore.
It tasted like
a cold Chinese cuisine dish.
-With the garlic…
-I love cold salad.
-The flavor changed.
-I see.
But I get what you like now.
That's that, but you still have
two more main dishes.
This one looks really good.
-Does it look good?
-It does.
If you try every ingredient together,
-it'll feel like ssambap.
-I see.
-Abalone ssambap.
-Eat it with the greens.
Why didn't you add coriander?
-Coriander!
-How many times do I have to tell you?
She kept saying
she loved coriander for a while.
But it's good. This one is good.
Is it good?
-Great job with this one.
-This one must've been fine.
ANOTHER BITE
-Is it good?
-Yes.
AGAIN, SHE GIVES IT
TO HER SON-IN-LAW FIRST
-You care so much about your son-in-law.
-Mothers-in-law do that.
She takes good care of him.
HER LOVE FOR THE SON-IN-LAW
-Is it good, Young-kyu?
-Isn't it good? You try it.
-Try it.
-Is it good, Young-kyu?
JOON TAKES A BITE
SUNG-JU HAS A BITE TOO
WHOA, IS IT OKAY?
-Isn't it delicious?
-Yes, it's good.
This is good.
-I don't really like scorched rice.
-I see.
-You don't?
-But this is really good.
-It's…
-Scorched rice is so good!
-I'll try to like it from now on.
-Yes.
-Anyway, the balance here is great.
-Isn't it excellent?
It doesn't feel like Korean food.
Which country is this from?
-It's just made by Fabri.
-Yes.
-It's like a dish overseas.
-It'll feel like couscous from Italy.
-But couscous doesn't have…
-He made scorched rice instead.
I can still feel the texture.
-What's the last dish made of?
-Octopuses.
I mixed beet powder,
soy sauce, and omija cheong
and laid the octopuses out
on top of cauliflower sauce,
something you love very much.
-This is really good.
-Is it?
-She must like this cauliflower flavor.
-It's good.
He saved the cauliflower.
Next, the octopus.
-He didn't do anything more.
-Wait.
How did you cook these octopuses?
Why is it so tough?
A HARSH REMARK COMES RIGHT AFTER
-Is it too tough?
-Right?
The octopus.
SHE GIVES IT A TRY
What's it like? Yes?
-It's not tough.
-Is it tough? No.
-It's good.
-It's not tough.
-It's good. Excellent job.
-It's good.
-It was delicious.
-Great job.
-It's not bad.
-It's good.
-Right?
-It's not tough.
The cauliflower purée
goes so well with the octopus.
It's very tender.
-Yes.
-It's tender and delicious, right?
It's not tough at all. It's like gum.
-Like gum?
-That means it's tough.
-Gum is tough.
-You can't chew it down.
-Soft gum.
-Do you mean the flavor?
-It's like chewing gum.
-Right.
-I loved the texture and smell.
-Isn't it good?
Yes, it was good.
Next, please try Chef Ho-young's dish.
USING LOTS OF RED SEA CUCUMBER,
ABALONE, AND THIN-LEGGED OCTOPUSES!
ONLY MADE TO SATISFY YONG-YEO'S APPETITE
+RED SEA CUCUMBER INNARDS
CHEF JUNG HO-YOUNG'S SEA CUCUMBER LADY
Should I serve the rice for her?
Hey!
He brought a lemon.
Everything I love is here.
What was that one thing you brought?
-Chef Ho-young?
-I heard the evaluation
and ended up bringing
half a lemon out here.
Please try it without the lemon first.
You can try it and be the judge.
The rice looks great.
-Does it?
-Put the sea cucumber on top and eat it.
This is nice.
Gosh, these look so appetizing.
-Here's what I do.
-This is it.
DROPPING LOTS OF SEA CUCUMBER PIECES
I'm not sure if this is the right way.
-And this.
-Will you pour that in too?
It goes in here.
POURING
IT LOOKS AMAZING
-That's it.
-It looks good.
-Have you never tried it?
-You can have it first.
-We'll eat it later. Please evaluate.
-We'll try it later.
A POSITIVE SIGN
It's over.
SWOOP
-It's over.
-She won't have to eat anything else.
The smell of the innards
comes strongly into your nose.
It feels like I'm in paradise.
-Like she's in paradise?
-Even paradise?
-May I try it?
-This was something
-my husband use to make me.
-I see.
He made this
whenever we went to a Japanese restaurant.
I've only dipped it
with white fish before.
-Isn't it delicious?
-Hey, Young-kyu.
You don't need to season it anymore.
The texture is crazy.
I didn't boil it for a long time.
If I switch between cold and hot water,
it'll help sea cucumber get cooked softly.
I parboiled it in buckwheat tea.
I see why he went back and forth
between cold and hot water with this.
-Right?
-I've never had anything like it.
-Sea cucumbers are…
-Whoa!
-My gosh.
-You surprised us.
-Sea cucumbers are…
-Whoa!
-My gosh.
-You surprised us.
-See? I told you!
-That was shocking.
-I told you.
-This is…
-It happens to you.
-The sea cucumber shocked him.
-Whoa.
-It doesn't taste firm.
Do you like it?
I've never had anything like this.
It tastes like paradise.
Yes, this isn't served at a cafeteria.
-They can't use sea cucumbers.
-This isn't served at a cafeteria.
I've never had that kind of texture
in a sea cucumber.
-This is interesting.
-It's the texture.
That was a surprise.
-Try the next one.
-The octopus dish looks so good.
Even sick cows would stand back up
when you feed it raw octopus.
-Yes.
-It gets up.
I seriously think she's Se-dol's mom.
When cows are exhausted,
they'd be recharged
after eating some raw octopus.
Even sick cows would stand back up
when you feed it raw octopus.
I seriously think she's Se-dol's mom.
-The cow getting up again.
-Why?
WILL IT MAKE YONG-YEO GET UP TOO?
I seriously think she's Se-dol's mom.
-The cow getting up again.
-Why?
-It's good.
-Is it?
Do you need more lemon?
-No.
-No?
Great job.
This is the best.
-This is the best.
-This is bad.
It must be seasoned.
It's really good.
-Is it really?
-Yes.
SHE TAKES ANOTHER BIG BITE
-Try it.
-Yes, ma'am.
You care too much about Young-kyu.
Gosh, my mother-in-law is
giving me too much food.
Come on, Young-kyu.
-Good for you.
-Yes, man.
A HUGE BITE
-Stop eating so much.
-That's enough. Give it to him.
Give some to Joon too.
Tell us what it's like.
The savory taste of octopuses is
-brought out with the sour lemon flavor.
-Also,
-it's not tough.
-No, it's not.
He cooked it perfectly.
This really is the best.
And not only is the texture is great,
but it gets even better as you chew.
And there's abalone too.
-Isn't it really good?
-It's really good.
-Whoa.
-Look at Hyun-suk.
What do you think, Joon?
It tastes so clean and pure.
-It's just complete.
-A complete taste.
Like a desk.
I can see the ins and outs perfectly.
-He salted the cucumber a little.
-Yes, the cucumber.
-That was a great touch.
-That balances everything out
in texture, softness, crunchiness,
and savoriness of the dish.
He just said everything I wanted to.
GREAT JOB
Excellent job.
He said everything she wanted to.
-Do you agree with him?
-Thanks.
-Yes, I agree so much with him.
-You agree.
She agrees.
-The cucumber was salted perfectly.
-Yes.
Try some more octopus.
-The more you chew it, the more…
-Joon's eating so well.
Aren't you eating too much?
-"Aren't you eating too much?"
-See?
-It's good.
-It's cooked perfectly.
Only these four are eating these.
-Wait.
-My chin is about to drop.
Our dear Nam-no.
-Nam-no!
-He needs to eat something.
Mother, can we give it to Nam-no?
Give it to him.
HAPPY
FOOD DELIVERY CEREMONY
My gosh. This is…
TAKING A BIG BITE TO FORGET HIS WAIT
THESE TWO TRY A BITE TOO
EXHILARATING
What do you think, Nam-no?
Pickled plums have
piercing sourness and saltiness.
When it's mixed with cucumber
and coriander,
-they all work together.
-Right?
It's excellent
when it's mixed in your mouth.
-I see.
-I have nothing to say. He said it for me.
Do you agree with that too?
-Yes, I agree with everything.
-You do?
I can't express it like them,
but I agree with what they say.
-I see.
-Now, shall we hear it from him?
Let's give a star to Chef Ho-young.
-Let's hear it from them.
-Fabri.
-Let's hear it from him.
-We don't need to do this.
I'm sorry, Fabri.
-She said sorry.
-She apologized.
You can't just say you're sorry.
-She said sorry.
-We don't have to do it.
-There might be a twist.
-Of course.
-Yes, maybe.
-There could be a twist.
Press one for Jung Ho-young
and two for Fabri.
Goodness, sweet mercy.
Please press the button.
-Press it?
-Do it.
Gosh, this is crazy. I can't help it.
You can't help it.
You've already decided.
Stop saying you can't help it.
-We have a rough idea
-Yes.
which one of them won.
-But let's check just in case.
-Of course.
Let's find out the result. Who won?
Who could it be?
I wonder who it is.
What's this seafood dish?
Will it be Fabri or Jung Ho-young?
-What is this?
-Who did Yong-yeo choose?
Who won?
The winner is…
JUNG HO-YOUNG WINS
JUNG HO-YOUNG'S SEA CUCUMBER LADY WINS
THE SAMBA OF VICTORY
THAT'S OUR DANCING FAIRY
Ho-young wins!
DO YOU SEE THIS, FABRI?
I'M THE DANCING FAIRY OF THIS AREA
I TOTALLY AGREE…
That's hilarious.
A 360-DEGREE END RESULT
Chef Ho-young received
a great compliment with his victory.
It was an overwhelming win.
Let's hear from him.
I'm so thrilled that Yong-yeo chose me.
I'm also happy that I won
in both dancing and cooking.
FABRI'S 2 LOSSES
I know how good it feels
to win both in dancing and cooking.
-Please put a star on Chef Ho-young.
-Oh, my.
-Yes.
-How many does he have so far?
This is his third star.
-That's not so bad.
-Jung Ho-young.
-He wins against Fabri.
-Congratulations.
-He wins a star.
-Congratulations!
-Let's give it up for Fabri too.
-Fabri!
Joon is famous as the frugal idol star.
I've even had just plain rice.
I'd watch videos of rice harvesting.
At times, I eat just rice and kimchi,
so I watch someone making kimchi.
If you eat it with that video,
it tastes really good.
His mother sent a hand-written letter.
"He'd say, 'I'm leaving now'
and arrive home in 15 minutes."
You're making her do
Chef & My Fridge every morning.
-Mom, I'm leaving now!
-Mom!
-Wait a moment, my son!
-You're fighting against time.
I'll make something really spicy today.
Nam-no! Yoon Nam-no!
They both add lots of love.
These dishes are for your son.
Whoa, what was that?
-Your son is almost here!
-Please!
There's no traffic.
This is the Chef & My Fridge cafeteria.
It's about time he rose up here.
I must fight him and win.
-I'll do well as a former kitchen police.
-He's fast.
-How does my sweet and sour pork look?
-It looks bad.
Yours look bad too.
I have no time.
-Can you finish this?
-Why am I so busy?
You can't do that now!
This is just crazy.
How does it make sense?
My gosh. This is really good.
You'd find everything delicious.
Subtitle translation by: Eunsook Youn