[English subtitles are available]
Sergeant,
have you confirmed the list of Sunday’s outings?
Who’s on the list?
Gao Liang.
Anyone else?
[Poor martial arts.]
Mancang.
What?
How about
we exchange our
permission to go out
this Sunday?
No way.
I made a deal with Gao that
I would go out with him.
How about a pair of nylon socks
for a place to go out?
And a bag of fish-skin peanuts.
Well, that’s a happy decision.
Deal.
♫ This power is iron ♫
♫ This force is steel ♫
Sergeant Cai.
Look.
My old friend gave it to me.
Well, you can put a little bit of that in your cooking.
The pepper smells great!
This would be great if it were meat.
You wish.
What are you going to do?
I'll take this bike. Do you need anything?
You can't ride it.
There is a rule in the company that
the bicycle is the only mean of transportation in the company
and cannot be lent.
I’m not borrowing it.
I’m purchasing for the cookhouse squad
on my own time. No thanks.
I'm leaving.
What a smart-ass.
I think it’s the training that didn't wear you out.
Sergeant Cai,
here you are.
They’re wild gingers.
I just dug them in the field.
It would be nice to put it in the cooking.
Well, thanks.
What do you want? Just say it.
Don’t get me wrong.
Where is the bicycle?
I saw it at breakfast this morning.
It went shopping for food.
You are here,
and the bike went to buy food by itself?
Yeah, right. It went to buy food
and took Gao Liang with it by the way.
Comrade,
come on.
Push harder!
Are you okay?
How about I throw you a rope,
and take you running with us?
I’ll go first, see you.
How’s the repair going, sir?
Mule Gu.
How about I pull a rope to drag you?
Gao, no need to drag me.
How about I sit behind you?
Take me with you.
Of course, it’s no problem.
But you shouldn't do that.
When you hitchhiked just now,
you got on the truck happily.
Now you see his truck is broken, and just walk away.
You need to help the driver repair the car. Why don’t you go the extra mile?
Sergeant,
he is in charge of repairing cars in our squad.
I’m sure you can let him repair the car.
I'm leaving.
Gao, wait.
Let go of me.
I’m in a hurry.
Who is not in a hurry?
I’m really in a hurry
I have an appointment with a comrade.
It’s her birthday today.
Really?
Today is my birthday too.
Every day is my birthday.
Gao Liang.
Comrade, do me a favor please.
Stop. Show me your credentials, please.
Okay, you can go in now.
Thank you.
[Disciplined revolutionary teams.]
Jiang Nanzheng.
Gao Liang.
I heard that you guys completed the long-range raid with arm.
That is a challenge to the limits of life.
That kind of willpower is really admirable.
It's no big deal.
Are you going out?
Yeah, I'm going out.
After I arrived at the division headquarters,
it was my first day out.
Why are you here?
I'm here to see you.
See me?
Come on, I don’t buy it. Tell me the truth.
I…
I’m here to find an old friend of mine.
But I brought you a bag of delicious food.
Are you here to see our Sergeant Han?
Well, old friend, you know.
I'm telling you,
Sergeant Han always praises you,
saying that you are a good soldier.
It makes me jealous.
She never praised me like that.
She treats me like
the autumn wind sweeps away the fallen leaves.
You’d better not speak ill of your sergeant behind her back.
I can’t bear it.
Where is Gu Yiye? Did you see him?
Well, Gu Yiye, I saw him.
He’s helping people on the road,
fixing a car.
Seriously?
Really.
He hasn't finished when I left.
It’s gonna take a while to fix.
Jiang Nanzheng.
Where are you going? I’ll give you a ride.
Never mind, you should go to find your old friend.
It’s rare to go out, you should go quickly.
It’s okay. I’ll give you a ride.
No, really. I’ll go first.
[August Town]
Don’t wait, everybody.
The bus broke down on the way.
Will there be any buses coming today?
There is another bus at 7pm.
Wow, 7pm, it’s too late.
Let's go back, there’s something else going on.
It’s too late.
Jiang Nanzheng.
Gao Liang.
Why are you here?
I'm not going to see my old friend.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to the seaside.
To the seaside.
Let me take you there.
No, thanks.
Jiang Nanzheng,
listen, let me give you an analysis.
It takes you two hours
to walk there.
I'll ride you there
for over 40 minutes.
If you cheer for me,
maybe it can be faster.
How about it?
Come on.
[Eternal life to the revolutionary martyrs.]
What are you doing?
Look for someone.
Who are you looking for here?
♫ The smoke of war is telling ♫
♫ My youth is burning ♫
They are the three martyrs of the Third Red Company.
♫ Say goodbye to you at that moment ♫
♫ In and out of my dreams, you were there ♫
[Notification of Fallen Soldiers Gao Shan]
This’s your brother's watch.
♫ The mountains and rivers are telling ♫
♫ Green youth inspires me ♫
♫ Side by side with you at that day ♫
♫ It’s hard to part. You keep me warm ♫
♫ Yearning for you, watching over you ♫
♫ Yearning turns into winds. Read my mind, read your mind ♫
Do you miss your brother
when you saw those tombstones?
♫ Yearning for me, looking at me ♫
My brother has been
a beacon in my heart
for so many years.
♫ Time turns into flowers, like you, like me ♫
When I have any difficulties,
when I can’t get through anything,
I always think of him.
But things have changed.
I’m sitting here with you.
Don't talk about me, talk about you.
What are you doing here?
My dad was
a company commander in the Third Red Company.
He left
when I was born.
He’s dead?
No, they were divorced.
Mother said that
although he did not die,
he left everything on the battlefield.
And there was nothing left for my mom and me.
So they separated.
When he left,
he didn’t know my mom was pregnant with me.
Later, I grew up with my mom
and took her surname.
Mom never told me
why they got married
and why they separated.
I asked her many times,
but every time she shook her head
and said it was a mistake.
So you also come from
a military cadre family.
Not exactly.
When I was a child, I was very thin
and always bullied by boys.
At that time,
I decided that I would join the army when I grew up,
so that no one dares to bully me
and I can protect others.
No one will dare to bully you in the future.
Because I'll be here to protect you all the time.
In fact,
it was not until I made this decision
that my mom had a serious talk with me.
Marrying a man like your dad,
for me,
is both lucky and unlucky.
Your dad is
like the sun that can illuminate everything.
He has infinite masculine power.
This is
the only notebook
I keep from his youth.
Take a look.
When you were young,
I didn't want you to know that
you had such a dad.
But now that you are grown up,
you are determined
to join the army,
and I can't stop you.
I was thinking
it’s time to
tell you everything about your dad.
It’s time to let you know that
you came into this world
and should see the sun.
Did you see him?
He doesn’t know you’re in the army, right?
I don’t think
I'm ready yet.
I’m not ready to tell him.
He should not be ready either.
He should not be ready to know that he has a daughter.
Why don’t you meet each other?
Today I saw the rows of
Martyrs’ bones lying there,
and I felt a little closer to him.
Wait.
Your mom’s infiltration operation
is flawed.
You are in the army.
If you meet each other,
won’t he recognize you immediately?
Why would he recognize me?
Come on, you’re his daughter.
You must look like your mom
and him.
Couldn’t he recognize his own daughter?
Mom said,
if that’s the case,
then he’s no different from
the hundred infatuated men
at the entrance to the conservatory.
There would be no chance of becoming my dad.
It turns out that cold-blooded, ruthless
and hard-hearted tough guys
are more attractive to girls, right?
I see.
[Vigorously Prospering Socialist Science, Education and Culture.]
[August Town]
Jiang Nanzheng.
Look what I found.
It’s a tiger cowrie.
The beautiful tiger cowries
have been at the bottom of the sea of despair for many years.
If the waves hadn’t brought you to the beach,
I never thought
I could see such beautiful sunshine.
What are you talking about?
This is a poem written by Ai Qing, called Tiger Cowries.
It's one of my favorite poems.
It’s a poem.
It’s nice.
Well, it’s better than Whitman,
that unbuttoning thing.
It’s yours.
Really?
Yes.
I’m telling you,
I can give you all these things
except the ocean.
Gao Liang.
I do enjoy hearing you
brag sometimes.
And it’s touching.
I’m not bragging.
I mean what I say.
Stop it
and listen to me.
I know you’re good to me.
And I know how much effort you’ve spent.
I really wanna be nicer and more passionate to you.
I really do.
Because you are such a nice person.
Look at you being so nice.
You don’t have to be so polite.
But I can’t, Gao Liang.
I’m afraid that I might hurt you
with my unintentional words.
I can’t be more nice to you anymore.
I’m sorry.
What are you sorry about?
Comrade Jiang?
Comrade Jiang, where are you going?
I’m good so long as you’re my
comrade-in-arms.
This.
Take it as a birthday present.
Okay?
A birthday present.
Take it.
Just take it.
[United, solemn, intensive, active. Strive for advance, strive for perfection.]
Nanzheng.
Here.
[To Ninth Company, Regiment 720, Comrade Jiang Nanzheng.]
Letter from Jiang Weixing.
How persistent. A letter every day.
It’s like an overripe banana.
Mushy.
I met Gao Liang when I was going
back to the barrack.
His car’s broken too.
We didn’t make it
and we overleft.
Sargent scolded me hard.
Gao Liang was worse.
He was punished to clean toilets for a week.
But I think it’s OK.
I sang happy birthday for you
on my way.
I celebrated your birthday
in my own special way.
I was thinking about
the osmanthus tree in the yard
of your company.
If it was blossoming
when I was there,
[Happy Birthday. Gu Yiye.]
I’d have taken one
and gave it to you.
Nanzheng.
Happy birthday.
[Happy Birthday. Gu Yiye.]
Next: scripts from company health center.
[Company history room]
Left turn!
Comrade Bao Xiaowei, the Good Doctor.
Comrade Bao Xiaowei of the health center,
is a medical personnel working in the front line.
He takes the health of his comrades-in-arms as personal duty
and treated them like family.
[Company history room]
Be it a head officer or a new recruit...
[Remember the history. Honor the past.]
...Taking care of every comrade-in-arms...
...Soldiers are having increasingly intense training...
...While he soothe wounded comrades-in-arms...
Company commander.
I saw you sneaking around from far away.
Tell me.
What are you doing here?
Nothing, company commander.
Why did’t you take us here
in this area of the company?
Take you here?
Do you know
that this military history museum
is like a shrine of people.
Ancestors and sacrificed warriors are respected here.
Just look at yourselves.
In people’s words,
you’re unworthy descendants.
I’ll be ashamed to take you here.
It’s not that bad.
Well, it’s not the time for you.
Company commander.
Does every company
have this kind of room?
Like, Third Red Company
or the first pacesetter company .
This is not the dining hall.
Those are units with history.
Model units.
Other companies
have no history, records or heroes.
Even if they have the room,
there’s nothing they can fill it with.
Enough.
Stop changing the subject
and tell me.
What are you doing here?
I’m just here to learn
about the history of the troop,
to get inspired.
I didn’t know that our troop
has such a salty history.
It’s “solid history.”
Solid.
Look at you.
Talking about learning military history.
[Remember the history. Pass on the glory. Honor the past. Forge the future.]
It’s a good step.
Come here.
Let me tell you
[Model Hero]
the campaigns that our division 234
have participated in.
Three defensive campaigns in Benxi river, and four defensive campaigns in Linjiang river.
Battle of Anshan, Xinkailing siege,
Tashan strike,
the list goes on.
We fought from the northeast
all the way south to August town.
Company commander,
How many company commanders of Third Red Company
that participated in these battles
are still here in our military region?
You’re good, kid.
You know that our Ninth company was the Third Red Company
previous existence.
Let me think.
Zhou Xiangqian.
Currently the deputy commander of the region.
Zhao Zhanlei.
Currently the deputy commissar of Army A.
Oh right,
deputy commisar Zhao
is the father of Zhao Hongying, the company commander
of Communication Company.
Is that so?
Next is division commander Zheng Yuan.
They were all company commanders of the Third Red Company.
Company commander.
Has any of them had a divorce?
Do they have children?
What are you talking about?
It’s...
I’m just thinking
that do these company commanders have a happy life
after so many campaigns.
What do you have in mind?
Quit beating around the bush
and talk!
What are you trying to do here?
Company commander.
To be honest,
I’m asking for your sake.
I think that
company commander Zhao of Communication Company
has a crush on you.
Shut up!
I hope that our company commander
can take down this objective as quickly as possible,
and make a good example for us
in terms of tactical moves and techniques.
Get outta here.
Little brat.
In the 70s,
the female communication soldier on the painting I am a petrel
inspired generations of communication soldiers.
And in the brand new 80s,
communications are the eyes and ears
of the army.
It’s the key for officers to win the battle from afar.
[Saving water is everyone’s duty.]
Comrade Han Chunyu, sergeant of the first squad, female platoon of our company,
studied hard on her skill
and mastered her telecommunication technique.
She often says that
the switchboard room is no less than the battlefield.
On April 8 this year,
our country has launched
the first communication satellite...
Did you hear?
The participant in the telecommunication contest
can get a quota of promotion.
Telecommunication contest?
What are you whispering?
I heard it all.
That’s way better than long-range raid with arm.
We ran so much and were so tired,
but all we got was some verbal praise from the company commander.
Yeah.
If we get a promotion, we can have relationships.
The promotion quota
is rarer than pandas.
Jiang Weixing told me that
sergeant Zhang of the Ninth company
has been a soldier for 10 years.
and has never got a quota of promotion.
So
do we new recruits even have a chance?
No.
Conventionally,
it’s gonna be one of the veterans.
Then there’s no need for a contest.
It has to be either sergeant Han
or sergeant Song Xiaoluo from the third squad.
That’s bad.
Sergeant Han is popular,
and Song Xiaoluo is the Number one
when it comes to switchboard operating.
No one can beat them.
The telecommunication contest
is more than sitting in the room and operate.
There’s the part of setting up antennas in the field.
I thought female soldiers’ score are not counted.
Our work is not counted,
but the contest is.
Nanzheng.
I remember last time when we were cross country running,
you were way faster than Song Xiaoluo.
If the gap of operating is not too big,
you may have a chance, right?
Nanzheng, did you get the message from the company?
You’re assigned by the company to participate.
[Political persistence]
You have your own advantage
that is your resolve.
I’ll do what I can.
Ma’am.
What is it?
I’d like to know more about telecommunication contest.
It’s not sergeant Han who told me.
It’s a big deal.
Words are flying around the company.
Can we new recruits have a quota of backup member
in the telecommunication contest of the region?
Let me make it clear.
You new recruits just joined the company
and have no experience of telecommunication skills.
What do you have to compete
with the elite communication soldiers of the whole region?
It’s no child’s play.
You’ll be representing the communication soldiers of the Division 234
and strive for honor for the whole division.
I’m confident that I will not lose to anyone.
Come, to the switchboard.
Show your skill.
Timing start.
Chief No.1.
To regiment 700.
Hang up.
Regiment 720, Machine gun Company.
Regiment 702, the first Company.
Connect to Regiment 702, the third Company.
[Raise vigilance, Protect motherland, Follow strict requirements, Practice and prepare for real.]
Hang up.
Regiment 700,
Military Affairs Unit.
Stop.
Did I plug anything wrong, company commander?
You didn’t plug anything wrong.
You used 8 minutes and 5 seconds.
You didn’t do it wrong,
but
you used 3 minutes longer
than the best record 5 minutes and 3 seconds.
I can improve.
Yes, but that’ll need time.
Do you still have any problem?
Then go.
Company commander,
she’s so talented.
She has only been practicing on the machine for less than a month,
and she is familiar with all numbers and sockets.
That’s right, she does have potentials.
Let’s do this.
Starting from tomorrow,
increase Jiang Nanzheng’s practices.
If her ability
improves very fast,
we can consider
making her the backup team member.
Yes.
Commander Qin.
Hail, commander!
Hail!
[Bathroom]
There’re male soldiers, close the door.
We are taking a shower.
Let’s go.
I specially changed a new uniform
for today.
Look at this.
It’s all wet.
So,
did your company
get promotion index?
How can it be easy?
Getting promotion will be
harder and harder for the soldiers.
I just came from the division commander.
I was thinking about pulling some strings
for our sergeant of the Ninth squad.
I didn’t even ask
before he showered down his criticism.
He said I was not thinking of the bigger picture
and not familiar with structural changes
in nurturing troop leaders.
He also said
that student officials like
Lu Pingfan and Zhai Qingnian
are going to be mainstream in future army.
Right, right, right.
I brought some Kiwi fruit for you.
It’s the speciality of my hometown Yichang.
A fellow-townsman brought them back from his vacation.
I wanted to save them,
and now they are a little dried out.
Thanks.
No, yours, yours taste bad.
Not authentic.
Only my hometown has this.
They are sweet and sour,
and authentic.
Then I’ll eat the ones you gave me first.
Got anything to eat?
I’m a little hungry from all the walking.
Qin Hanyong,
you really think this is your home, right?
Here.
These are the grain coupons I saved,
along with some from a few platoon leaders.
There are 75 jin altogether.
We know you male soldiers don’t have enough to eat,
just keep them.
This, this is so embarrassing.
I,
I wasn’t going to ask you for grain coupons.
Charge!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
I’m starving, sergeant!
That’s fine, the destination is right in front of us.
That mountain is our destination.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
There’s meat for lunch! Hurry!
Don’t listen to the sergeant!
You know what’s comforting oneself with fantasy?
That’s what he’s playing!
Keep up!
[Unit 53082 of People's Liberation Army]
I followed the sound to the pit,
and parted the grass.
I saw our soldier fell in it.
How could I not try and get him out?
Thank you so much, thank you!
Thank you, thank you!
What’s to thank for?
The soldiers and people are bonded, I did what I should.
Now that the soldier is back here,
I won’t interfere your work.
I’ll just go.
We’ll write a thank-you letter to you later.
That’s not necessary.
See you!
Thank you!
How did you fulfill your sergeant’s responsibilities?
Your soldier went for a shorter route
into the woods,
fell into an animal trap,
and couldn’t get out, and you had no idea.
Luckily that fellow saved him!
[Unit 53082 of People's Liberation Army]
Alright,
he’s back, then everything’s fine.
Don’t expand on this.
Take him back.
Take back!
[Unit 53082 of People's Liberation Army]
Hongliu,
don’t get freak out,
just tell us.
I failed my leaders.
I failed my comrades.
I was helping company commander wash his clothes
when there’s the emergency muster.
Commander didn’t have clothes and was embarrassed.
I made a mistake while on stand guard.
My gun discharged accidentally,
ending up with the company got searched.
Also cutting the short route.
I cut the short route
so that I could improve my grades.
I was drawing everyone’s back every time.
I need to inspect myself.
Hongliu,
don’t be sad.
Your intentions were nice.
Also,
you didn’t draw our back.
Right, Hongliu,
we are in the troop together, we are brothers.
Brothers experience happiness
and pain together.
Plus,
that’s what brothers should suffer
or how can we be brothers.
I really,
really want to improve myself.
I don’t want draw the team’s back anymore.
But I am just bad.
I’m bad at everthing.
Hongliu, you are not bad at everything!
If it wasn’t for Honliu,
how could we get first place in the internal affairs competition?
Exactly!
That’s right!
Just tell me,
why could you fell in the pit and not get out?
For this, I,
I really have to tell you all about it.
The pit I fell into,
I saw it ahead,
so I went around it.
But not before I could take two steps,
I heard some noise from behind.
So I turned around,
and I saw the giant wild boar, this big, really big!
It ran straightly towards me.
Who am I?
I’m a soldier of people’s liberation army!
Could I be a coward?
Of course not!
I went directly to fight it.
But I got slippery, and failed.
Then it got me in the pit.
Boar!
How long has it been since we smelled any meat!
If there’s a bowl of braised pork at noon,
that would be so nice!
Add some green capsicum, garlic seedling.
Boar!
Get it.
I can’t work anymore.
I’m starving now.
How can I get something so exhausting done!
I’m tired out!
Keep up! Don’t stop, hurry up!
I can’t work anymore. I’m exhausted.
Think about the boar!
Wouldn’t it be nice if we can catch that thing and have some meat?
Hurry up!
You can get two pieces of meat when we get it.
Your words!
Give me two extra pieces
to compensate the energy
I wasted.
How is that wasted?
We are investing!
Do you understand? Investing!
Alright, investing.
Just give me two extra pieces of meat.
[Never shed tears even for bloody sweat. Never be left behind even being peeled of the meat.]
Hey, get up!
Get up! Hurry!
Let’s go!
Comrades.
Comrade Gao Liang,
[Be frugal and against waste.]
led the other comrades in the squad
to dig a trap outside
in their spare time.
They caught a big wild boar
with a weight of 250 jin.
It has solved
the problem of insufficient food and water
caused by
the high intensity of training in our company.
Right now,
I would like to
praise comrade Gao Liang.
Don’t shout so hard,
you should save your energy to eat meat.
- Dinner time!
- Yes, sir!
Sergeant, have a fat one.
The meat tastes so good.
What a hearty meal!
Chief Song.
I smelled it at the regiment headquarter.
Chief Song’s nose is so sensitive.
Come on, have a taste.
I've already had dinner.
You’ve come over, so have a taste of the meat.
No, no.
No, thanks.
Are you guys full?
I'm in a hurry.
Save some meat for me and the commissar.
Don’t eat them all.
Gorge on meat.
What’s the chief doing here?
I don’t think he’s here to share the meat.
That’s the boar we just ate.
It’s not a wild boar.
It’s a domestic pig.
How is that possible?
Can domestic pigs run into the woods in the middle of the night?
Do wild boars have such short teeth?
Wild boars have tusks, don't you know?
Today, a villager
lost a pig.
He followed the footprints and
found the company nearby.
Now it can be basically concluded that
it is the one you ate.
This is gonna be
a big problem.
Seriously?
We already ate. What are we gonna do?
Come on.
Why didn’t you say earlier?
We already ate.
How could I say?
The villager hadn’t confirmed yet.
Can I ask the whole company to wait and not eat?
[Raise vigilance and strengthen combat readiness. Contribute to the construction of safeguarding the Four Modernizations.]
You guys have to be reasonable.
How can this happen?
Yeah, you're absolutely right.
I found the soldier and sent him back to the army.
What have you done?
You found my big pig and
stewed it directly!
Don’t worry.
We must criticize and educate the soldiers.
It was supposed to be the harmious fish-water relationship between Army and People. You guys are so wrong.
Yeah, you're right.
You can take this.
See the villager to the door, Wang.
Yes sir.
I’m so sorry.
Goodbye.
A pig that big,
and you three caught it?
Report!
This has nothing to do with Niu Mancang.
I forced him to go.
Okay,
you can go.
Get out of here, don’t you understand?
Yes sir.
Report!
I didn’t ask you to talk.
Come here, Qin.
I'm thirsty.
I've tried to minimize the impact.
This is gonna help me a lot, Song.
Thank you so much!
Now someone has to take responsibility.
It’s just a pig.
Is it that serious?
What do you mean it’s not that serious?
To tell you the truth,
you hit the muzzle this time.
It's your muzzle again.
Oh, my goodness!
You think too highly of me.
Do you know what month it is?
Month of rectification of style and discipline in the military region.
The newly transferred commander is personally responsible for this discipline.
The commander said that
negative examples should be caught
in all divisions and regiments.
You’re in trouble.
No need for others to catch,
you are ready-made living teaching materials.
Have you heard of
the new commander’s style?
He can turn his back on his flesh and blood, and remain result oriented.
The pig farmer
is also a tough guy.
He complained directly to the military region.
Now the leader has said that
this matter is serious and
bad in nature and
must be dealt with seriously!
Maybe someone has to
take off their uniform.
I'll take the responsibility.
What a righteous man!
But I want to ask you,
can you, a person who has been demoted and punished,
bear the burden for them this time?
I'll be a platoon leader if I have to.
Qin Dapao, I am telling you,
I am a man of principle.
Disciplines must be observed!
Of course, sometimes you can handle it at your discretion.
But
don’t bargain with me!