=The Zero Complaint Flight=
=Episode 16=
You can eat first.
Don't catch a cold.
You're manly.
Do you think this looks good?
Yes, it's pretty good.
In such a beautiful place,
should we do something meaningful
to make the scene worth it?
We can start anytime.
Come on, let's take a photo.
Huang Li, you are such a buzzkill.
Be observant, please.
What happened?
Are you two together now?
I don't get it.
Come on.
Let's take a picture.
- Hurry up.
- Coming.
Ready.
Look at the camera.
Three, two, one.
Li Er is back.
- Grab your things and we can go.
- Let's go.
- Here.
I'm gonna take this.
Alright.
Hello?
What?
This is not what we agreed on.
These five people are all my students.
They have all passed the assessment.
Why only four can be admitted?
I understand you need to lay off people,
but this is out of line.
We can talk tomorrow.
Let's go.
Let's talk about it tomorrow.
I don't want to be a spoilsport.
It's okay, Ms. Yan.
You can tell us.
We can cope with it together.
For our company,
due to the bad economy,
the overall performance is declining.
There's a large-scale layoff
going on right now.
For each group,
the last one will be eliminated.
Each group is limited to four recruits.
That means,
one of us can't be a flight attendant.
It-it's nothing.
I thought it was something worse.
I didn't want to
be a flight attendant anyway.
I can just drop out.
They all did well.
I'm okay with that.
Not a big deal.
Come on, grab your things and go.
Grab your phone.
You lost one last time.
Come on.
Let's go.
Bye.
We can come up with another solution.
Exactly.
That's right, Haixian.
You were talking nonsense.
It isn't settled yet.
Why are you so serious?
You know me, right?
Everything I do doesn't last long.
I don't want this job anymore.
I'm okay.
I'm going to the loo.
Wait downstairs.
Pack your things and come.
Be quick.
Come on. Bye-bye.
Why am I crying?
I don't want to be a flight attendant.
I came here to chase Li Er.
Now he is my boyfriend.
Mission accomplished.
Oh my.
I should be happy.
You don't want to
be a flight attendant at all, right?
Wang Haixian.
You're so weird.
You...
I can't be a flight attendant anymore.
Wang Haixian.
Haixian.
Hi.
Wang Haixian, what's with you?
You really aren't coming?
What's the matter with you?
You made a decision without us.
Why didn't you pick up?
It's dead.
Are you okay, Haixian?
I'm fine.
Look at me, happy and alive.
It's your first visit to my home, huh?
Come on in.
Come on.
Let me show you around my place.
There are many good things inside,
come on.
This is the living room.
And,
this is a big balcony.
It's very nice, right?
What?
You all look sad.
Not interested?
Or is my house just not nice?
I'll take you to see a secret room.
Let's go.
Welcome to my secret room.
Come in.
This is a limited edition white T-shirt
I won from my first participation
in an eating contest.
And then...
Look at this.
This is my first motorcycle helmet.
I went through quite a lot
to learn how to ride a motorcycle.
My legs were bruised and battered.
And this thing.
Haixian.
Why don't you wait
until Ms. Yan talks to management?
Yeah, Haixian.
You don't need to give up for us.
When we get the result,
we'll find out who's the last.
We can all accept that.
You shouldn't offer
to give up your position.
We can't get peace of mind
since you give up your opportunity.
What are you talking about?
You're talking nonsense.
It's your first time to be here.
I need to be a good host.
I'll bring you some fruit.
Wait for me.
Have a seat first.
Sit wherever you want.
I'll check on her.
♪In front of love, we're the same♪
♪Different backgrounds, the same belief♪
♪Regrets bring heartache,
and aspirations bring longing♪
♪No need to resist. I'll head
towards the future with you♪
♪I will promise you♪
♪I won't let you feel lonely again♪
♪Never losing you♪
♪You've always been by my side♪
♪No matter how long the road ahead,
I'll be your sun♪
♪I will promise you♪
♪We can fill the gaps together
until it's complete♪
♪Love can make us brave to have hope♪
♪I will promise you♪