♪There are flowers, a river, and you♪
♪In my dream♪
♪It breaks the convention♪
♪When the wind blows into the heart♪
♪There's an order♪
♪For women going into their 30s♪
♪I suddenly see you again♪
♪We'll go back to where we started♪
♪Can we not mention the date of return?♪
♪Let's take a photo with the stars
and snow as the background♪
♪Can I be sad and escape
for a little while?♪
♪Remember my problems
and the secret we shared♪
=Winter Night=
=Episode 23=
(The Difficult Farewell)
(Starry Sky Restaurant)
I know why
I'm destabilizing.
When two universes converge,
the two versions of me cannot co-exist.
If I stay...
Then the Zheng Daqian from
these two universes might disappear.
Have you told Lizi?
I don't know how to broach
the subject yet.
If we go back,
Aunt Hui and Zixi
cannot have
their Mu Zili back.
Perhaps
Lizi wants to go back with you.
Uncle Mu just passed away.
Aunt Hui is what she is now.
He can't leave them behind.
Daqian.
Don't be pessimistic.
What if there's a solution?
If he can't go back this time,
maybe he
can go back
to your universe the next time around.
But no one knows when that will be?
If he misses it,
he might have to wait
for several decades
or all his life.
What do you plan to do then?
Let me think it through.
Zixi, come down here to eat.
Mum, the food is ready.
Stop looking for it.
I threw the old one away.
Look, I bought you a new one.
It's so much better
than your previous one.
Come and put it on.
Come. I'll put it on you.
Not bad, isn't it?
What else do you like?
The long one or the short one?
If you don't like this,
I'll buy you another one.
I think this one is quite good.
♪The glowing light
of that shooting star♪
♪Shines on the lonely silhouette♪
♪In the night,
that pair of eyes is gazing at♪
♪The return path in the future♪
♪Don't be scared and stop struggling♪
♪The harder you pretend to be fine,
the harder you can't let go of it♪
♪Time keeps asking the words
you hide deep inside♪
♪Are you brave to answer it now?♪
♪Or are you being silent like before?♪
♪I believe that the flame
will eventually disappear♪
♪I still stubbornly stick
to my foolish idea♪
♪Don't be scared and stop struggling♪
♪Let the tears fall as they wish♪
♪In the other universe,
she must be over there♪
♪It's inevitable to get hurt
while growing up♪
(Perhaps)
(Lizi wants to go back with you.)
You're going out?
I'm driving my mum to the hospital.
Her condition is getting worse?
She keeps mentioning my dad
and starts talking to herself.
So why did you come here?
Nothing.
I want to pay Aunt Hui a visit.
I'll come with you then.
No need. Zixi is with me.
If everyone comes,
it makes my mum nervous.
Wait for me back home.
I'll come to you once I'm back.
Okay.
Mum.
What are you doing?
Didn't you promise me
that you wouldn't leave?
Great timing.
Daqian.
I need your input.
Which one?
We don't have any more space.
Daqian.
Which one do you think makes me look
more sprightly
when I take a stroll by the beach?
Just wear nothing.
Don't you mock me.
Look at all the random things
you put in your luggage.
A curtain. A tablecloth.
You might as well bring
the entire wardrobe with you.
Another complaint
and I'll return the tickets right away.
Any one of you can tell me
what is going on?
These two then.
Your mum's workplace is organizing
a trip to Sanya
for all its senior workers.
You can come along too.
But it will be full of old people.
Mum, you're actually bringing dad
with you?
I mean,
this kind of freebie hardly comes by.
Everyone is coming with their spouses.
I can't go alone,
so I'm bringing him with me for show.
Yes, for show.
Fine.
I highly doubt you two
want me to tag along.
I won't be the third wheel.
Put in the hat too.
No more space.
One hat for each of us.
Put it on.
What do you think?
When are you leaving?
The flight is in two days.
Airplane.
Okay.
Pack it in.
Daqian.
What do you want?
You can give me a list.
What are you tinkering about?
Want to paint nails together?
What's wrong?
You look down lately.
Is it because your dad and I
were displaying our affection
publicly and you got embarrassed?
No, I couldn't be happier about it.
Then what happened?
You look so sad.
Tell me.
Mum, I have a question.
If one day, I go missing,
like I disappear completely,
will you come find me?
Of course I will.
Don't you underestimate your dad and me.
Those few days
when you ran away from home,
I was worried sick.
You had no idea.
If you went missing,
I would leave everything behind.
I would pack up
and search for you everywhere.
What if you can't find me?
Will you look for me forever?
Definitely.
I won't do anything else
other than looking for you.
I made you.
Don't you get it?
When a mother
loses her child,
it's as if a part of her soul has left.
You'll know when you have kids.
Your nails are long now.
Let me fix them for you.
No.
You cut them very short.
It hurts.
Whatever.
Great manicure you did there.
Needless to say.
I can't go to Shenzhen to work
without picking up a trick or two
beforehand.
Mum, come.
Paint my nails too.
I'm going to Hainan
and I can flaunt my nails.
You're staying indoors
during the winter.
No one will see your nails.
Just paint them.
When I miss you, I'll look
at my toenails.
Then you have to promise me
that wherever you go,
you have to let me know.
You hear me?
Give me your foot.
Apply several layers then.
Thick layers.
So thick that it won't fade
after several months.
It will be there forever, all right?
Zixi.
I don't want to be in the hospital.
Let's go home.
Mum, we'll go home
after we consult a doctor.
(Area C Consultation Room 1)
The brain scan is normal.
There's nothing wrong.
That condition only appears
on those who are traumatized
or who just lost
their loved ones.
Doctor.
Is there any treatment available?
Let her rest. We'll observe for a while.
If this persists
for a month
or even a few months,
then it's pathological.
You might need to bring her
to a neurologist.
Are there no other alternatives?
Family company
is the best solution.
Surround her with optimism,
vim and vigor.
Guide her out of the grief.
Mum, I made you bird's nest soup.
I'll put it here.
Mum, what else do you want to eat?
I'll make them for you.
I'm not hungry.
You can eat it.
All right.
Let me know when you're hungry.
It seems like today's dinner
is not to her liking.
You failed.
No. I think this is delicious.
Have some more.
(Bonehead Li)
Hey.
I am back from the hospital.
I am at your doorstep now.
Are you home?
Yes.
I'll come out now.
Lizi is looking for me.
I'll go out now.
Go. Go.
What did the doctor say?
Nothing too serious.
You must be tired.
Go home when you're tired.
But I can't see you when I'm home.
Why did you come to me during the day?
I told you already.
I wanted to pay Aunt Hui a visit.
Liar.
I missed you.
I wanted to hang out with you.
Let's hang out in somewhere warmer.
(Just a bit longer.)
(Maybe I should wait a bit longer
before telling him.)
Miss, mister.
I have cakes for you.
It's my son's birthday.
Thank you. Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Happy birthday.
Thanks, miss, mister.
Daqian, Lizi.
Man the shop for me.
Sure.
Let's have the cake.
I just realized
you can celebrate your 29th birthday
again.
Indeed.
Who would have thought
that I could celebrate my
29th birthday twice.
Last time we celebrated your birthday,
I hit Guan Zhe.
And you ran after me.
And then...
It was...
It was quite fun.
- Then you...
- Go ahead.
You said you wanted to tell me something
when you came back to Baihe.
What is it?
We're already here.
We might as well be together.
We might as well make do
with each other.
Daqian.
I'm serious.
It's not
a slip of the tongue.
I have never been this serious.
Me too.
Then
how do you plan
to spend your second 29th birthday?
No idea.
After that day,
we have to go back.
Lizi.
You worry about Aunt Hui, don't you?
I have been here for a few months.
This is like my home.
I'll do my best
to make my mum recover sooner,
before I leave, ideally.
If, I mean
if we don't go back,
we forfeit our original universe
and stay here,
will you do it?
Of course.
As long as we can be together,
I don't care which universe we're in.
But I know that's not right.
It's not fair to us
in the other universe.
It's not fair to Yan either.
Besides,
it's selfish of me
to hog the other Mu Zili's life.
Right?
Let's celebrate your birthday together.
The last one left us with regrets.
This time,
your 29th birthday will be
a perfect one.
Come.
(Starry Sky Restaurant)
Look.
When you're preparing
the condiments,
do not mess up the order.
If you do,
it will affect how it tastes.
When I'm gone,
it'll count on you.
Okay. Let me show you the dishes.
Bill, please.
36 yuan.
Yan, you're early.
The dinner is tonight.
I came to help.
Lizi isn't here?
He's keeping Aunt Hui company.
What did he say?
I haven't told him.
I plan
to tell him after the dinner
tonight.
If Lizi plans to stay,
what do you do?
I have to tell him the truth
no matter what.
You know me.
I can't keep a secret.
If I lie to him
and ask him to come back with me,
sooner or later,
we will become
two different individuals.
I see.
A few months pass by so quickly.
A few months ago,
there was nothing here.
Now, it's all good.
Indeed.
If it wasn't
for the relocation compensation,
I wouldn't have been able
to open a restaurant here.
My money wasn't enough as well.
It's thanks to everyone
that we have this place.
I owe everyone so many things.
No.
It's all thanks to the Zheng Daqian
who likes to stir up trouble.
She came to Baihe.
She changed a lot of people,
and a lot of things here,
including me.
When I go back,
I'll have my relocation compensation.
I'll be rich.
I can make a fortune for real this time.
Daqian.
Serve some beers to this table, please.
I'll do it.
(Starry Sky Restaurant)
- Don't pour him that much.
- This kid.
He loves sweet drinks.
- Coming through.
- Fried oyster mushrooms.
Let me have a look.
Niuniu must be hungry.
Your teeth have broken off.
Stop drinking.
Daqian, don't worry about this.
Sit here, you two.
I'll handle the rest.
- Sit.
- Okay.
I'll peel the prawns for him.
Sorry, I'm late.
Where are your mum and Zixi?
Mum took her meds and is sleeping.
Zixi is doing his revision.
He'll look after her.
Coming.
- Coming.
- It has arrived.
The food is ready.
The last dish.
Did you miss me?
Everything is here.
Thank you.
Don't worry about it.
Eat.
Let's eat.
Zheng.
Drink with me.
Sure.
I'm not good with words.
I don't know
what to say now.
If Mu was here...
If he was here,
he would be talking
about the sky and the moon.
All sorts of things.
As if we are all into them.
If my dad was still here,
we wouldn't be able to eat
for another 30 minutes.
Right.
I'll keep it brief.
The kids are all here.
I came back this time.
I have met
all I have to meet,
and done all
I have to do.
It's time for me to go.
Only by living
a meaningful day
that you can go home in peace.
I wish all of you
happiness and fulfillment.
Cheers.
Why so gloomy?
It's not like
I won't come back.
I will
when it's time to come back.
Come. Cheers.
Cheers.
Come.
Yan Zhonghui.
We're all old now.
Take care when you're out there.
Sure.
Come.
Cheers.
(Starry Sky Restaurant)
Lizi. We'll leave now.
My son has to go to school tomorrow.
Okay.
Come.
Say goodbye to your uncles and aunties.
Bye bye!
Bye.
- Bye, Niuniu.
- Bye.
Goodbye.
Until next time.
Bye.
Let's go.
This farewell dinner for Uncle Yan
is quite sentimental, isn't it?
Uncle Yan is a great cook.
I'm sure he'll prosper anywhere he goes.
Yan, don't worry about him too much.
Okay.
There will always be departure.
Don't be that rueful.
No one knows what the future holds.
Don't you think so?
Perhaps when we're 70 or 80 years old,
we can have a reunion
in a space station.
Exactly. No one knows about the future.
I'm sure there will be reunions.
Are you cold?
No.
Just go back.
I want to tell you something.
That day at Tieyuan Station,
I got a call from her.
She told me something.
In that accident,
the other you
passed away
in the other universe.
That's why I'm destabilizing
but you aren't.
And that means
if we go back together,
the Mu Zili in this universe
will disappear completely.
You should go back.
Zili.
What's the matter?
I'm fine.
If you still want to leave
to find a job,
just go.
I can take care of the family.
I'm serious.
We're a family.
Dad told me
no matter what,
we should support each other.
Focus on your exam.
I'll take care of this family.
(The other you)
(passed away)
(in the other universe.)
(If we go back together,)
(the Mu Zili in this universe)
(will disappear completely.)
Mum.
Let's go to the photo studio together.
I can help you print the photos too.
It's fine.
I can do it alone.
Lizi.
You don't have to keep me company
every day.
Help Daqian and others out.
Go now.
Okay.
I'll go to the restaurant.
(No. 3, Xinhua Street)
Mum, you made so many dumplings.
For you to eat.
What if you're hungry
when your dad and I aren't home?
Dumplings are convenient.
I'm almost done.
I have frozen some in the fridge.
I'll be sick of dumplings
if I have them every day.
Suit yourself.
Your dumplings are so plump.
Just like you.
It's like a gold ingot.
You know what they say,
have dumplings before you leave
and noodles when you come back.
If you have dumplings before you leave,
you'll leave with a tummy full
of gold ingots.
It'll bring fortune to you
wherever you go.
They also say
having dumplings before you leave
allows you
to bring back more money.
What about noodles then?
You don't know?
Noodles are long.
Having noodles is wishing the family
to stay together for a long time.
Forever?
Forever.
What's the matter?
Nothing. The flour got into my eyes.
Come on.
Your dad and I aren't moving to Hainan.
We'll be back in a few days.
Besides, you're here.
When we're back, you'll pick us up.
What is going on?
Why are you crying?
What happened?
Nothing.
I'm fine.
I'm truly fine.
What happened?
I'm fine.
Xiaoqin.
I just realized something.
We will be leaving on her birthday.
I know.
I...
Well...
The company decided the date
and everyone flies together.
I can't change the tickets.
I get it.
We have to get her
a cake at least.
A three-layer cake.
A big, three-layer cake.
You'll celebrate it with your friends,
okay?
And when we come back,
we'll bring you a huge present.
It's fine. Don't worry about it.
It's not fine.
You'll be 29.
You'll be in your 30s soon.
My daughter will have a fresh start.
Mum.
To be able to see you two
is already a fresh start for me.
Mr. Mi.
Come in.
This is my absence notice.
For a very long period.
Yes.
Don't neglect other subjects.
Don't think that others
are not important after you have
your art exam.
If you flunked your art exam,
you would have to rely
on other subjects.
Yes.
(Teacher's Opinion: Approved)
I have faith in you.
Don't be nervous when you're taking
the exam in Tieyuan.
Just do your best.
Thanks, Mr. Mi.
Thank you.
(Entrance)
Junze.
After I leave,
you have to take good care of your mum.
You have to work hard too.
And try to stay on good terms
with your colleagues
and superiors.
I know.
I'm still worried
about
Daqian's restaurant.
If you have the time, do visit it often.
They are good people.
If anything happens to any of you,
you'll help each other.
Don't worry.
Take this.
I can't have it.
Take it.
(Passengers to Tieyuan
can now board the bus.)
It's time now.
I have to go.
Go back.
Well...
Eat them
in your trip.
(Intercity Bus)
Dad.
Have a safe journey.
Come back often.
♪Time crept past us just like that♪
♪Departure, drunkenness, regrets♪
♪Time never freezes for anyone♪
(Baihe Intercity Express)
♪Flying like you know how it's done♪
♪But never once understanding you♪
♪Wrong, right, remorse♪
♪Coming to terms
with the taste of growing up♪
♪There, there. Don't despair♪
♪The memories are real. Am I right?♪
♪We have accepted♪
♪That the moments of regret
we've missed out on are gone♪
♪And the foolhardy me
stubbornly loves you♪
♪To sacrifice it all for you♪
♪I kept searching through the crowd♪
♪I always believe
we'll meet again one day♪
♪I tried to shine brightly
in the starry skies of the winter night♪
♪To give you light and warmth♪
♪So you'll remember this moment♪
♪We have accepted♪
♪That the moments of regret
we've missed out on are gone♪
♪And the foolhardy me
stubbornly loves you♪
♪To sacrifice it all for you♪
♪I kept searching through the crowd♪
♪I always believe
we'll meet again one day♪
♪I tried to shine brightly
in the starry skies of the winter night♪
♪To give you light and warmth♪
♪So you'll remember this moment♪
♪This moment♪
♪I kept searching through the crowd♪
♪I always believe
we'll meet again one day♪
♪I won't be sad
even if the memories disappear♪
♪We'll be unforgettable memories
for each other♪
♪I tried to shine brightly
in the starry skies of the winter night♪
♪No matter how many obstacles
during the meteor rains♪
♪It'll pass because we've all grown up♪