Mom, I haven't eaten anything today.
I don't want to fight anymore.
Please don't hit my mom.
Since you don't want to see me,
just help me to eat.
Silly child, don't be afraid.
As long as mom is here,
no one dares to bully you.
I'll make her bones are broken.
Why is the room suddenly changed?
This look is killing me.
The system has been activated.
The supermarket has been opened.
The owner has the intention to talk to me.
Supermarket?
Isn't that a must-have?
Yes, but the owner needs to accumulate points
to exchange the products in the supermarket.
You want to exchange points?
Little bitch.
What are you doing?
Come, please.
Mr. Li Zheng,
you saw it just now.
This Jianxiu,
she is not only talking nonsense,
but also hit my mother-in-law.
Mr. Li Zheng,
you said that my mom would be beaten to death
if I didn't pay back my mom's money.
Your mom has been beaten to death.
Zhang,
Zhang's village is full of trouble.
Can't you be quiet?
That's not what I said.
My fourth brother has a lot of family members.
He eats a lot and does little work.
I taught him a few words,
what's wrong with him?
Dad must have fallen off the bed again.
Brother.
Jianxiu, are you okay?
This is my husband.
He is handsome.
He can't walk on the street.
Dad, don't worry.
Mom is great.