I've seen you lose your eyes long ago.
I'll kill you for Yangzi's sake that day.
I don't want to be Yangzi.
Who dares to touch my child again?
I'm not polite to him.
You bitch.
You play with a bitch.
This Jianxiu was low and Buildal accordingly.
He even dared not to stop her blow lol.
How could you ever change?
Who could be on sleeping shell?
Sierce,
check it out how scared the old lady become
by youlaughter all your contacts
and chords for two days.
I can't take it anymore.
I'll lose to you.
Why wouldn't you want us to eat?
Why don't you let us eat?
The chickens, pigs and cows in this village are all raised by us.
We not only want to eat, but also want to eat the best.
From today on, I eat a chicken in the four rooms.
I eat a duck tomorrow.
The day after tomorrow, I will kill that pig and give my husband a body.
What?
I think you dare.
You see if I dare.