Rumor has it there were four mysterious sects in the Jianghu.
According to motivation, skills and sects, they are divided into
Mojin, Faqiu, Banshan and Xieling.
Faqiu and Mojin are jointly called Mojin Captain.
They are good at seeking treasures and the Book of Changes,
while the Banshan and Xieling sects are rarely recorded
who are more mysterious.
It is said that the Xieling sect depends on strength.
Thousands of its disciples work together
and they can move a mountain to explore treasures.
So it is called Xieling.
The Banshan sect depends on skills.
They are not seeking for treasures
but for elixir.
For thousands of years
Banshan has been seeking for the Dust Bead
to lift the curse of their clansmen.
Originally, Xieling and Banshan each goes their own way.
However, the fate brings them together
risking lives in the mysterious and dangerous Bottle Mountain
to perform an earth-shattering act.
=Candle in the Tomb: the Wrath of Time=
=Episode 12=
Careful.
So many.
Load them all.
Commander Luo.
Okay, okay. Alright.
Step aside.
Does it hurt?
I'm asking you if it hurts.
It hurts.
Yeah, it hurts.
Great.
I'm not dreaming, right?
Brother Partridge Whistle.
My dear brother. Come here.
It's… This is... is...
Is this the so called
Lingxiao Palace of the Jade Emperor?
This used to be an ancient palace
for making immortality pills by Emperors.
Look at those octagonal colored glaze lamps.
These are jewelry and lamps
which have thousands of years history.
The lamp wicks are specially made,
and can last for thousands of years.
Today,
I really entered into a whole new world.
Oh my gosh. The treasures inside must be very valuable.
I've never seen
such a luxury and magnificent palace before.
Leader Chen.
Leader Chen. Where's Leader Chen?
I don't know.
The soil here is so hard,
and there are so many layers of rocks between them.
They dug through them anyway.
Yes.
Have you seen how they did it?
Yeah, we all saw that.
Those two Xueling Pangolins
just kept digging and digging.
Only in half a day,
they've dug a tunnel like this.
Our men all said that
such mountain-digging skill is absolute genius.
Leader.
Leader. Here you are. Finally.
Look. Look at this.
Have you ever seen such a huge palace?
I haven't anyway.
It's really an eye-opening day for me.
This time, we finally find
the real treasures.
Congratulations, Commander Luo.
You, too.
They're not for my own.
Everyone here, you all have a share.
Commander Luo, please.
Leader Chen.
You are the bellwether and backbone
of our team.
If you don't give an order,
no one dares to act rashly.
If someone does, I'll shoot at him immediately.
Don't say that.
What did I do?
It all owes to Xieling brothers' help.
If anyone is willing to take my job,
I'd rather be a recluse in the mountains,
and become indifferent to wealth and fame.
Leader, that's not true.
In my opinion,
we should all cut the crap.
We can live without anyone in our team,
but we can't live you, our Leader.
Am I right?
- Yeah.
At your service, Leader.
Let's go inside and rob the bloody treasures.
Brothers,
we should all keep our eyes open.
First, we need a group of people
to build a bamboo bridge
at the bottom of the mountain
to ship the treasures out.
And we need another group to explore the way ahead.
Do be careful.
Yes, Leader.
Let's go.
Brother.
Do you think there might be
any gimmick here?
It shouldn't be a trap of fake tomb or grave.
But we shouldn't act rashly.
To be honest,
we've suffered great losses at the battle in Urn city.
I still haven't gotten over it.
Don't worry, Brother Chen.
How about this?
I'll go first.
You just follow me with other guys.
That's not fair.
It's quite hard for you to find this hole.
Just leave the exploring work for me.
Don't worry about it, Brother Chen.
Leader.
Follow me.
- Yes.
You guys,
Leader always brings Red Girl with him.
What happened this time?
Is she out of favor?
What?
Don't talk nonsense.
Red Girl is no longer young.
Maybe this time, she falls in love
and wants to have a relationship with that guy.
That guy?
You idiot.
Partridge Whistle.
Right?
But Red Girl is so hot-tempered.
Last time, she hit me in the mouth,
and I couldn't open my mouth the entire night.
I can't imagine whether it's a bless or a curse
for the man who marries her.
Come. Come here.
Come here.
Elder brother.
The Rooster is awake.
You two follow me.
Follow me closely.
Hey, you. Did you hear that?
Got it, elder brother.
Leader Chen.
What's this?
It's an octagonal colored glaze lamp.
Colored glaze lamp?
It must be valuable.
Of course.
Lieutenant Yang.
Yes.
Tear it down and take it with us.
No hurry.
We can keep it for lighting now.
It's not too late to take this
when we've moved everything else.
You're right.
Yang.
Yes?
When we've moved everything,
and before we leave,
no matter the lamp or the light stand,
take them both.
Got it.
Careful.
Everyone, be careful!
Don't shoot at my treasures.
They mean money to me.
Dust the lime powder.
Help him!
Old Foreigner.
It's impressive.
Yeah.
- Great.
Thanks to it.
Right.
What a wonderful Rooster.
Leader Chen. Brother Partridge Whistle.
You two really amazed me.
I admire you both.
Ask your people
to dust all our lime powder
throughout the palace
to prevent these poisonous things.
Got it.
Dust the lime power.
Yes!
Lieutenant Yang.
Yes?
Light up.
Got it.
- Yes.
How much are
the jewels on the pillar worth?
All the treasures here
are of the top grade used by royal households.
They are priceless.
Plus, it's quite vivifying and full of vigor here.
These antiques still look like new ones,
which makes them worth even more.
Awesome.
It's time for us to make a fortune.
It's troublous times now.
You have guns and you are the king.
If we get these treasures,
then thousands of British fast guns
and dozens of British cannons
can be bought soon.
Commander Luo.
You have to send more soldiers
to open a mountain road
for mules to transport the treasures.
Okay.
Lieutenant Yang.
Yes?
Brother Cripple.
You two are in charge of this area.
Tear them down and take them all.
I want everything.
- Okay.
- Also,
the mountain road must be heavily guarded.
If anyone
tries to steal treasures and escape,
just shoot him on the spot.
Yes.
My brothers.
Listen up.
If you make down-to-earth efforts,
you will have a handsome reward.
The one who tries to play tricks on me,
I'm gonna give him a hard time.
Understood?
- Roger that.
Now get back to work.
Commander Luo.
Do you know that
the most valuable treasures here actually
were already robbed by the Yuan troops?
The left ones are not that valuable.
But we can think this way,
hundreds of years have past,
these antiques now become treasures again.
I just regret that
I wasn't born
hundreds of years earlier.
You don't have to care about it so much,
Commander Luo.
I guess there must be countless treasures
in the tomb of the general of Yuan Dynasty.
There must be a great meal waiting for us.
I can't wait.
I want to go inside and take a look right now
to find out what exactly
are there waiting for us.
Leader.
Our guys found a stone gate.
You stay here and watch the gate.
I'll go inside and check it out.
Alright.
Be careful.
Be careful when you're
dealing with the treasures.
Be careful.
Focus on your work.
What happened?
Brother Cripple.
I was taking out the jade on the wall,
and he just roughly smashed the wall with chisels.
Several jades were damaged.
I tried to talk to him,
but he wouldn't listen and even hit me.
How I take out those jades
is none of your Xieling people's business.
Don't you dare say it again. Say it again!
Shut up!
What happened?
Two guys
quarreled because of several jades.
Put your guns away.
Brother Cripple.
You see...
It looks like that my guy
hit yours.
How about this?
Let me apologize to him for my guy.
- Brother Cripple, he hit me first.
- Shut up.
You chiseled the jade?
How can you be so careless?
They all belong to Commander Luo.
Don't you know that?
Keep pedaling.
Generate electricity. Hurry up.
Brother Cripple.
You guys are right.
It was my people's problem.
Please forgive us.
We are all brothers.
Just be careful the next time.
Yes, of course.
We don't need those fake, polite greetings.
So, it's over now?
It's over.
Get out of here and go back to work.
Get back to work.
Let's go.
Lieutenant Yang.
With all due respect,
we Xieling sect has our own methods of
digging jades and gold.
I'm not an expert,
but how about I teach you guys our methods
so as not to destroy these jades
or waste any of them.
Brother Cripple.
Xieling sect's unique skill
is all that we could wish for.
Thank you, Brother Cripple.
You guys,
learn the skill from Xieling brothers.
Understood?
- Got it.
Get back to work.
Hualing.
I found that this Rooster is like you.
Eat and sleep every day.
Live a careless life.
You are the careless one.
Who is the sleepyhead of us, eh?
How dare you talk to me like this?
You should learn from the Rooster.
You are the Rooster.
Elder brother.
What's this?
Don't touch it.
Careful.
What's this?
What's going on inside?
Inside?
They are digging treasures now.
Where's the Leader?
I don't know.
It looks like that
he's going further into the tomb.