[My Bargain Queen]
[Episode 16]
[Theme Park Adventure]
There's no one here. That's kind of strange.
This is not too high.
Zhening,
we have reserved the entire park for ourselves.
Shall we get an annual pass?
Can you get a couple more?
Well, that's not enough.
We should also get a set of half-year passes.
Or...
two-year passes?
And...
Not just two years—
It's getting late. You should sleep.
You should rest early, too.
Also,
I think we should not let Ning Meng know about us for now.
Got it.
Hubby, have some breakfast before you go to work.
Sure.
Hubby,
I won't bring food for you to the hospital anymore.
I'll get up early to make breakfast for you, okay?
Okay. Thank you, Wifey.
Look at these heart-shaped eggs. Are they cute?
- Yes, they are.
- And I drew a smiley face on top.
They're very cute.
What are you laughing at?
Nothing. I just feel so happy now.
Me too.
Eat some food.
No, I want to watch you eat.
Sofa, washing machine, and TV. Don't send them over.
What about the clothes for Miss Xia?
Just send one over. Remember to take off the tag.
Okay, got it.
How much is this dress? Where did you buy it?
On Taobao.
(T/N: a popular Chinese online shopping platform famous for its cheap prices)
I used a coupon. ¥320.
Well.
I need to check.
[Original Intention Classic Dress 2021, Gentle and Elegant, French Retro Style, ¥320]
Do I look nice?
Very nice.
This is Evergreen's 30th anniversary—
You're having a board meeting today. Why was I not invited?
Director Gao, when did you come back?
I was abroad on a business trip for just a few months,
and now we have a new GM after I returned?
Director Gao, you were abroad and had no idea of Evergreen's personnel changes.
This is quite normal.
What's the agenda of today's meeting?
Looking into the 30th anniversary.
Mingcheng Group is a long-time customer of our hotel.
So are Yongli Group and Kangming Tour.
I remember we invited them on our 25th anniversary.
Why are they missing from the VIP list this time?
There's more reason to invite them for the 30th anniversary.
Director Gao, what do you mean? You've been nitpicking since you came.
Nothing.
I think that for such a big event like the 30th anniversary,
GM Sheng must come back to do this.
If GM Sheng doesn't come back,
the Housekeeping Department won't cooperate.
Since Director Gao insists on it, I will ask GM Sheng to come back.
Let's continue.
Director Gao is back and asks you to come back to Evergreen to take charge of the 30th anniversary.
He said that if you don't come back, the Housekeeping Department won't cooperate.
What did GM Qin say?
GM Qin also said to the shareholders that he wanted you back.
Got it.
Assistant Sheng! Time for the meeting.
I'll be right there!
Let me know if there's any update at the hotel.
Although we're girlfriend and boyfriend now,
we have to separate work from life.
Next time you're late for meetings, I'll deduct your salary.
Okay. Next time... There won't be a next time.
Time for the meeting.
Xiao He.
President, are you looking for me?
We have an opportunity for further education at the hospital.
[Philip Psychological Clinic
Application Form for Further Education]
Further education?
This opportunity is different from before.
Our partnering clinic, Philip Psychological Clinic, adopts a treatment approach that is based mainly on face-to-face interviews
and uses medication as support.
This is the same as your specialization.
It's a rare opportunity.
We can only send one person, and we have a few candidates.
But I think you have the biggest chance.
Thank you, President.
I did pay attention to this clinic. Their psychological counselors are very experienced.
Although they adopt a rather conservative approach, the recovery rate of their patients is very high.
Thank you, President, for giving me this opportunity.
There's no need to thank me.
You should be grateful for your own effort.
It's not that. I know that this clinic has world-class psychological counseling services.
My seniors and I have always wanted to go there.
So this opportunity is very competitive.
The candidate not only has to be skilled at work,
but also excellent in every way.
I will take everything into consideration.
Thank you, President.
- Keep working hard!
- I will.
Take care, President.
For this anniversary gala, we need to invite a lot of Evergreen's long-time clients for sure.
Those clients have been supporting Evergreen since the previous GM Sheng.
If you are not there, they'll become suspicious.
Also, you coordinated all the previous anniversary galas.
You have more experience than I do.
You've rested for so long,
isn't it time to come back?
I know.
You've worked so hard during my absence.
It's my job.
Right. When I come back this time, don't arrange any specific position for me.
The main reason for my coming back is to assist you.
As you wish.
Hello?
Zhening, are you coming home for dinner?
I am.
Great! I'll wait for you.
All right, I'll be back soon.
Are you in a relationship?
Then hurry up and leave, don't make her wait.
But I need to pay the check.
As usual?
Okay!
- Charlie!
- Yes?
What's up?
I saw you wearing a ring a few times before,
but it is suddenly missing today.
I guess they broke up.
I saw him smiling while checking his phone.
I guess they didn't break up.
I lost the ring, I ordered a new one but it's not in stock.
GM Sheng, you won!
- Put it on my tab.
- No problem.
Thank you!
I'm heading out now.
All dishes are here.
- GM Qin had something for you?
- Yeah.
I'm going back to work at Evergreen.
You scared me! I was worried something bad had happened.
We can't work together anymore.
Going back to work at Evergreen is good.
What is the saying? "If love can last forever,
would a day or night matter?" Right?
(T/N: reference to a Chinese poem from the Song dynasty)
Aren't you sad at all?
Why? I'm not a kid.
There, there. Have some food.
Have some food.
After GM Sheng fell in love, he did change a lot.
You were the one who made better guesses.
What about you?
I have a feeling that you've been interested in her for a long time.
When it comes to love, the more you want to suppress it,
the harder it fights back.
Sanity won't work.
Why don't you drink with me?
All right.
Here.
How is it? Is it too tight or too loose?
Just right.
Why are you looking at me?
I want to kiss you.
You're almost late for work.
I'll see you when you come back tonight.
How do I look?
To tell you the truth, after spending so much time with you,
I almost forget you were the GM of Evergreen.
As long as you remember that I'm your boyfriend.
I'm leaving now.
By the way, I won't be back for dinner.
Put the dishes in the sink after you finish dinner,
and I'll wash them.
Got it.
Bye.
President, your cake is ready.
How much is it?
How can I accept your money?
You're sharing my cake with your friends,
that's free advertising for me.
I should thank you for that.
I really do think it's delicious.
You use the best ingredients,
and it does taste very different.
I just looked at the recipe and then made it with my intuition.
Maybe it's because I was picky as a child,
now I have an advantage in gourmet cooking.
Xiao He is so lucky to have a wife like you.
He does nothing else but works all day.
Zhijuan is not the articulate type.
I hope you can help him out in the future.
Xiao He is very capable.
The hospital wants to help him grow.
Although I was being conservative when I talked to him,
you can be assured.
He will definitely be the chosen one to study abroad this time.
Study abroad?
What are you doing?
Sister Qian, there's something I'd like to ask you.
Go ahead.
Are you really dating Sheng Zhening?
Yeah.
I thought you said he's hard-to-please, unreasonable, and doesn't have the spirit of contract?
What do you like about him?
Did I say anything like that?
You've got such a bad memory!
I don't remember.
I didn't realize how great he was back then.
Meeting at the banquet hall at 8:30, and board meeting at 9:30.
Then we'll visit Mingcheng Group at 11:00.
At 2:00 p.m., the Catering Department will confirm the menu for the anniversary.
Let's move the meeting with the Catering Department to 1:00 p.m.
But it takes at least one hour's drive from Mingcheng Group to the hotel. Your lunch...
I'll just grab some food on my way back.
Okay.
From 11:00 p.m. to 2:00 a.m...
Livestream e-commerce?
This is Lie'er, the famous livestreamer.
Lie'er?
Here's the thing. Last week, a livestream e-commerce company spoke to me.
They often need to negotiate prices with the vendors.
The lower the price, the more the buyers.
They need to find a balance point in the price.
That's why they want to work with us.
Actually, I'm quite interested in this livestream e-commerce model.
So I consulted them about it.
They said that if we're interested and are willing to collaborate,
they can sign a livestream contract with us and let us try.
What do you think?
I think it's a pretty good idea.
You've just watched for a little while, and you think it's pretty good?
Let me tell you. Bargaining with the vendors is what we're good at.
Now there's just one more step.
We just have to sell the discounted products.
One more step, but more commission as well. That way we can earn more.
I've thought about that.
We're good at bargaining, but we're not good at selling the products.
I'm not sure if we can make that money.
We can learn.
Let's have a try then.
Okay. Let's give it a try.
So we want to shoot a promotional video with you, GM Sheng, as the lead character,
to help the public get to know the leader of Evergreen and the corporate culture of our hotel.
This is not a good idea.
What Evergreen achieved today is the result of all of us working together.
I think we should make a video about the excellent employees,
the story between our long-time customers and our hotel,
and their blessings to us.
Being genuine is the most important thing.
Understood.
[What are you doing?]
What are you doing?
[I'm eating.]
I'm eating. Have you eaten? Are you tired from work?
I've eaten. Don't worry about me.
GM Sheng, the wine we ordered for the anniversary has arrived.
When will you come back approximately?
Has the invitation been designed yet?
I forgot. I'll arrange it right away.
Has the theme of the promotional video been confirmed?
Yes. We'll discuss it again during tomorrow's meeting.
Time is running out. We'll work overtime tonight.
Got it.
Hubby, you are back. I'm sure you haven't eaten.
I'm going to prepare you something.
Mengmeng, come sit down.
I want to talk to you about something.
Today, President came to me.
He said you told him we are having a baby this year.
So he reserved that study abroad opportunity for another doctor.
I do indeed have that idea. We've been married for a while,
we should plan for a baby. Right?
Do you know how rare this opportunity is?
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity in my career.
Zhijuan,
I don't want to separate from you. I don't want you to leave the country.
Can you not be mad at me?
Studying abroad is part of my job,
I'm not leaving you.
Can you not keep living in your own judgments?
Do you know how important this is to my career?
You said you want to spend more time with me.
That's right.
I'm already tightly tied up by your side,
where can I go?
Hubby, I'm wrong! I made a mistake!
I'm going to text the president tomorrow that
we are now not having a baby.
You can go study abroad. Oh! Let me do it now, okay?
- Are you not feeling well?
- Nothing.
Something suddenly came up at the hotel,
I won't be able to join you for breakfast. Sorry.
Be careful.
Thank you so much, Anan.
You are welcome.
That's right,
What made you decide to bring back GM Sheng's luggage here?
It's too tiring for him recently.
It takes 40 mins to drive from my house to the hotel. That's almost two hours' return.
Now, if he moves back here,
he'll have more time to rest.
You are so considerate, Miss Xia.
Have you discussed this matter with GM Sheng beforehand?
I know this is for my own good, but...
There is no but, no negotiation.
Sheng Zhening,
you need to listen to me on this unconditionally.
There was so much luggage, you should have waited for me to pack them.
Okay.
Whatever you say, I got it.
You brought the luggage over, right?
Yes.
I thought you and Miss Xia had discussed this.
I'm innocent!
One self-reflection statement,
- and deduct two months bonus.
- No.
She didn't discuss this with you?
I thought she did.
I...
Have you made a decision on the livestream?
No problem. We can give it a try.
Can we meet this afternoon?
This afternoon? I can.
Then, we'll meet at your office at 2:00 p.m.?
Okay. See you later.
I'm sorry... Can we change our meeting location to Evergreen Hotel?
No problem.
Great!
I have read the contract, there shouldn't be any problem.
I still need to confirm with our legal department.
I hope we can seal the deal soon.
Good. When we launch the project,
we'll provide you full support on the preparation in the early stage,
till the technical aspect in the late stage.
Also, we will send a team of specialists to assist you.
That's wonderful!
That would save me a lot of preparation time in the early stage,
we can get ready to go online as soon as possible.
Yes.
If you have further questions, feel free to reach out.
Then, we'll just need to sign the contract.
Excellent.
- Looking forward to it.
- If there's anything, you can call me.
- Sure. Goodbye.
[Anan]
Hello?
Anan, is GM Sheng at the hotel right now?
He is.
Do you know his exact location?
I'm not sure about his exact location. I'm outside right now and won't be back until later.
But according to his schedule,
he should be at the restaurant to discuss the gala menu with the head chef.
What is it, Miss Xia? Do you need anything from him?
There is a reason, of course.
I need to discuss something with him.
You go ahead. I will hang up now.
I want to take advantage of this Anniversary Gala,
to promote our Building No. 2.
Building No. 2's restoration is almost done.
It is a great opportunity to do a warm-up with our guests.
Come to my room.
I miss you.
I know you are really busy.
I'm here to see you today,
I didn't do it on purpose.
I miss you too.
Why don't you pick up the call?
It must be regarding the Marketing Department meeting. It's okay.
Can you not pick up the call?
What happened to your forehead?
I sleepwalked last night
and bumped into something.
Maybe I should move back.
I'm worried about you being alone.
GM Sheng,
the Marketing Department wants me to ask you when we can start the meeting,
so they can prepare for it ahead of time. Can you give them a time?
Give me ten minutes.
GM Sheng will be there soon.
Oh, Miss Xia is there as well?
Perhaps I should cancel the meeting.
Cancel it!
Change it to tomorrow!
You cannot cancel the meeting.
GM Sheng is heading there now.
So... who should I listen to?
Okay. Wait a moment.
Are you sure just a moment?
Confirmed!
Okay!
This status...
I'm leaving now.
Let me hug you a bit,
just ten seconds.
Okay.
As you wish.
Still working overtime?
Is the kitty sick?
I'm sorry,
your call cannot be connected at the moment.
Please try again later.
Turns out that you are vomiting hairballs.
I thought you were sick.
Hey, kitty, you must stay well.
It seems your owner can't take care of you at the moment,
but you need to stay strong.
Being his cat is not easy at all.
Sorry for what you've been through.
Scared me.
Hebo, I heard that
you invited Sheng Zhening back to Evergreen.
That's true.
Director Gao, the long-time shareholder of Evergreen, is back.
That was his idea.
And he still has a lot of influence at Evergreen.
I better not stand up to him.
Besides, it's the 30th anniversary. Sheng Zhening should be present.
The GM Qin that I know
isn't so passive.
Power outage at Building No. 2, the reviewer getting trapped in the elevator,
changing the renovation price comparison budget,
leading Sheng Zhening to make massive purchases of termite-infested
African logs.
You used to be very decisive about these things.
Also, how are things going
with Director Gao? Should I step in?
No need. I have my plan.
Shutting Director Gao up is easy.
It's his stocks that I want.
Very well, then.
Hebo, a word of advice.
Don't get softened up just because Sheng handed over the general manager post to you.
Don't forget what I told you before.
He remains one of Evergreen's biggest shareholders.
It'll be easy for him to kick you off from your current position.
Only when Lihe Capital acquires Evergreen,
gives you your shares, and calls on the entire board to back you up,
your place as the general manager
can truly be secured.
Understood, Director Xue. I'll hang up.
I'll let you know when I have news.
- Watch out!
- I'm sorry.
Are you blind?
Your Evergreen Hotel's Building No. 2 renovation materials
are being bargained and managed by my company.
I am working hard so that your hotel can save money.
When I did the price comparison,
how come it didn't occur to me that there's a risk of termites in the wood?
If it had been written on the report, maybe they wouldn't have bought it.
I am usually very sensitive about those details.
[Old Driver]
- Hello?
- Hello, Shuangshuang.
Did you come to my place today?
I saw that you forgot your bag here.
I noticed that the kitten vomited at noon.
I called you, but the line was busy.
So I came by to feed it. It was vomiting hairballs. Nothing serious.
So that's where my bag has been. I've been looking.
Anything important in it? Should I bring it over now?
No need. Nothing important.
You can just courier it tomorrow. I'm in the middle of something. I'll hang up now.
Why did you buy me this watch?
Your horrifying sleepwalking habit is beyond understanding.
What if one day you sleepwalk to the street
and get hit by a car?
This watch has a built-in GPS.
I'll know if you sleepwalk at night.
This is way too much.
Don't underestimate this watch, it has a lot of functions.
You can make and receive calls with it.
If your cell phone battery is dead, you can call me using this.
And I can locate you through it. Double security.
- Fine. Fine.
- Your watch looks so lame.
What so lame? Can't you talk nicely?
Honestly, it's really lame.
He knows nothing. It's very cute. You look good with anything.
I think so, too.
Men are damn good liars.
- Aren't you one of them?
- I'm different from him.
How different?
- I'm—
- Indeed different.
What's with him today? Acting so weird.
Maybe... he's poisoned?
- Thank you.
- You are welcome.
Lie'er is so cool. The goddess of my dream.
If we can invite her, it will be phenomenal.
Wow! If we can invite her, then my dream will come true.
In your dreams!
A fast learner, aren't you?
- Come on in!
- Look.
She should see your moves.
Your dream has come true.
Am I dreaming?
Why did you stop? You were dancing so well.
Be serious!
Are you dreaming? Does it hurt?
- A little.
- Funny kid.
Don't encourage him.
Allow me to introduce to you.
These two are our new project supporting partners,
Lie‘er and Xiaoai.
- Let's welcome them.
- Welcome!
Lie'er doesn't need any introduction. Everyone knows her.
She's an experienced and excellent live-streamer.
She will be leading our first few live-streaming sessions as a guest.
This is Xiaoai, she is also an outstanding brand selection manager.
Anyway, if we have any questions about live streaming in the future, we can directly seek help from them.
No, not "seeking help," it sounds so formal. If you have any questions, just feel free to ask.
Great!
Welcome to dinner tonight. I'm buying.
I bought a contour stick when you live streamed yesterday.
You did? That's a very good gift for your girlfriend.
Haven't got one yet. I'll save it for later.
- Save it, save it.
- Funny guy.
- Qianqian.
- What is it?
- I'll leave you to talk. This is Xiaoyan.
- Okay.
Qianqian, I won't join you tonight.
I'm not feeling well. You guys go ahead.
Not feeling well? Are you okay? Should you go to the hospital?
No need. It's just I haven't been sleeping well the last few days.
Just a little headache. Maybe getting a cold.
Very well. We've got this.
Have some good rest.
I'll get back to work, then.
Qianqian.
I'm afraid my work hasn't been satisfactory lately.
Sorry for letting everyone down.
Nothing to be sorry for.
Everyone has bad days at work.
We are a team, we'll share the good and bad times together.
What's it with you today? Something's bothering you?
Nothing. Just a bit under the weather.
Nothing to worry about. Go ahead.
You were looking for me, GM Qin?
Can you courier this bag for me?
Sure. To where?
Forget it. No need to courier.
Very well.
You!
Yes, I'm talking to you.
Did you do something wrong so she doesn't want to see you anymore?
Or are you not cute anymore so she's tired of you?
Why isn't she coming to see us?
It seems that she doesn't want to see us.
If she doesn't, do you?
Do you? Perk up. Do you?
If you don't want to, then I'll ask for myself.
Don't blame me.
Let me buy you dinner tonight.
I'll bring the bag also. Same old place. See you there.
♫ You said don’t understand, then don’t understand ♫
♫ No need to research, just be happy ♫
♫ Unintentionally run into a beautiful ocean ♫
♫ Want to make a trip to bring you here immediately ♫
♫ Humans are weird, nothing unusual ♫
♫ No matter good or bad, just expecting ♫
♫ Just giving the heart, it is not generous ♫
♫ I will be a loan shark for life  ♫
♫ Love is so fun, love is so complicated ♫
♫ Love is so speechless, love, love ♫
♫ You can cheat, you can guess wildly ♫
♫ You don’t need to be good, don’t worry about the future ♫
♫ You can be exasperated, you can be stubborn ♫
♫ I am here anyway ♫
♫ You can cheat, you can guess wildly ♫
♫ No one can replace Heaven’s arrangement ♫
♫ You can play dirty, overthrow, and restart ♫
♫ I am always here anyway ♫
♫ The spoiled one is forever a kid ♫
♫ Don’t let waiting, let down waiting ♫
♫ People’s patience is a talent ♫
♫ Where there will be flowers, just plant them and bloom ♫
♫ Shouldn’t walk too quickly for a long journey ♫
♫ No deserving, only ought to be ♫
♫ We together love the present time more  ♫
♫ I bought candy, a whole bag ♫
♫ It is the piece you wanted yesterday ♫
♫ Love is so laborious, love is so simple  ♫
♫ Love is so terrible, love, love ♫
♫ You can cheat, you can guess wildly ♫
♫ You don’t need to be good, don’t worry about the future ♫
♫ You can be exasperated, you can be stubborn ♫
♫ I am here anyway ♫
♫ You can cheat, you can guess wildly ♫
♫ No one can replace Heaven’s arrangement ♫
♫ You can play dirty, overthrow, and restart ♫
♫ I am always here anyway ♫
♫ The spoiled one is forever a kid ♫