[False face and true feelings]
[Episode 16]
Be careful.
♪A new dress, the dim light♪
♪Fake smiles, false lies♪
♪Singing alone
in the middle of the stage♪
Qingyan.
I know you remember everything.
Perhaps
it's the only way to repay you.
I got the message from Mr. Liu.
This is the stuff you want.
I heard about it when I was in Yuncheng.
It is an addictive thing.
Once a killer is addicted to it,
he is doomed.
Given his trust in you,
you don't need it.
Just kill him.
I can help you.
No.
I want him alive
to see all his things gone.
Mr. Mo must have many supporters
since he could rise so rapidly
in Rongcheng.
Meng Huaizuo is just one of them.
There must be some other forces
we don't know yet.
But only Meng Huaizuo
and Song Manlin
have been helping him openly
in the past years.
We can't find out
the forces behind them.
Since Ye Yifan is Mr. Mo
and they always stay in the nightclub,
it must
be their base
to deliver messages and intelligence.
It's a list of the dancing girls
who have worked there
for over three years.
Maybe their regular guests
are the people we are looking for.
[List of Dancing Girls]
You want to figure out the deployment
of their forces in this way?
Since we're doing this,
we will terminate them all.
You are getting unchecked.
Mr. Mo.
Why are you sending Miss Su away?
She just worried about you.
Gu Qingyan
deceived you once already.
Amnesia?
She is just playing dumb.
Don't be fooled again.
Are you challenging my decision?
I dare not.
Then keep your mouth shut.
But why dare you
not to tell her the truth?
Gu Tingwei led the men to kill...
Kill dozens of the Mos.
He just paid for it with his life only,
how could she do that?
Meng Huaizuo.
Tell me directly if you want to die.
What have you found
in Yuncheng?
Shen Annian has been
developing his force there.
He used Gu Tingwei
to build connections
with the forces in Yuncheng secretly.
I guess
he has been helping the Gus
because he wants
the treasure map in the Fair Shura.
He wants to take over the Shens
by growing stronger.
Now Gu Tingwei is dead
and Qingyan is with me,
I should be his main target.
Exactly.
He began
to collude with Master Luo stealthily
and used his force
to ruin one of our deals.
Since the Luos crave death,
I will help them.
Time for Mr. Mo
to show up.
Why did Mr. Mo call us here?
I have no idea.
- I wasn't informed in advance.
- I was called here suddenly.
Why did you come, too?
- Mr. Mo called you?
- Yes.
Bring him here.
Are you glad that you made a fortune
a couple of days ago, Master Luo?
It was alright.
I should thank you for it.
Thank me?
You mean
you robbed me of my business
with the British company?
Mr. Mo.
I don't get it.
Ring a bell?
I was wrong.
Please forgive me.
You ruined five deals of mine at least.
I should have buried you alive
for that.
But since you are an admired elder
in Rongcheng,
I have a way out for you.
One finger for one deal.
Mr. Mo,
the Luos
have been influential here for decades.
Aren't you
going too far?
Mr. Shen.
Master Luo is in this situation
because of you.
Feel free to take his punishment
if you like.
I should meet you
since I have been here
for several years.
You're all doing business in Rongcheng.
I hope you can be honest
and cooperative.
If anyone else
plays any trick stealthily,
he will end up worse than this man.
Please
keep that in mind.
What?
Any objection?
No.
Not at all.
Since you have no objection,
enjoy yourselves.
Miss Su, why did you come here?
Gu Qingyan.
How could you be so indifferent
after your father died?
You want to say
I'm not an amnesiac again?
Isn't that the truth?
Look,
your father
was just a shameless
and treacherous liar.
So a liar's child
can only be another liar.
What did you say?
I said your father was shameless,
and so are you.
Your father gave you
to Yifan to keep his life.
And you?
You pretend
to love your father's killer
to get what you want.
Gu Qingyan.
Don't you find yourself shameless?
I suppose you don't know.
Your father
knelt to beg Yifan
to accept you as a gift.
His death
served him well.
Apologize!
[False face and true feelings]
♪The affection within reach♪
♪Became taboo words♪
♪Between you and me both♪
♪Whose hurt hasn't been mentioned?♪
♪This heart being torn♪
♪Is willing to accompany you into danger♪
♪Whose love is so ardent and throbbing?♪
♪Trying so hard to touch♪
♪The exhausted body♪
♪The solemn pledges of love♪
♪Betray the choice♪
♪Whose tears are running bitterly?♪
♪And breaching desperately♪
♪When the wound is recovered♪
♪There is no time to avoid♪
♪The fate of longing for you♪
♪Whose surging tears
are burning fiercely?♪
♪I try so hard to touch♪
♪The exhausted body♪
♪The solemn pledges of love♪
♪Betray the choice♪
♪Whose tears are running bitterly?♪
♪And breaching desperately♪
♪When the wound is recovered♪
♪There is no time to avoid♪
♪The fate of longing for you♪
♪And the forbidden choice we made♪