[False face and true feelings]
[Episode 10]
♪Guess silently and wildly♪
♪Why keep silent to make me nervous?♪
♪Are you still the person like before?♪
♪Who made us become this?♪
♪Couldn't we enjoy the lasting love?♪
You are making me
believe you have compromised.
From the moment
you showed up in front of me,
I have compromised.
Gu Qingyan.
Listen up,
you are my woman.
You must keep yourself alive
no matter what happens,
or I will not forgive you.
♪I'm used to sorrow now♪
♪Our love seemed♪
♪To be absurd in the first place♪
♪Nobody knows how it will end♪
♪I'm still pretending to be tough♪
♪It seems in our hearts♪
♪There is always a wall♪
♪You left the familiar place in the end♪
♪I'm used to sorrow now♪
♪Our love seemed♪
♪To be absurd in the first place♪
What is on your mind?
Nothing.
The scar here
was caused by a blade, right?
You were so young.
Who did it so viciously
to kill you?
It happened long ago,
so you don't have to know it.
But I want to.
15 years ago,
my whole family was killed.
This scar
was left then.
When the blade stabbed into my body,
I thought I was dying.
It was my mother
who distracted that man.
Hurry.
Run.
Mother.
Is that man dead?
Not yet,
but he will soon.
Let me help you.
What?
When you
find that man,
let me help you to take revenge.
I'm your woman,
right?
[New Metropolitan]
Master Meng said
he found something about Gu Tingwei.
Where is he?
Master Meng is confirming it
and it won't take long.
I see.
Mr. Mo.
If Gu Tingwei
did kill your whole family
and robbed you of Fair Shura,
what would you do?
Try to keep it from her.
What brings you here?
It's been a couple of days,
so I missed you.
Where have you been?
I prepared a present for you.
A present?
What is that?
Open it.
[Gu Qingyan is removed
from all the posts in Cloud Hall]
From now on,
you are no longer a member of them.
Qingyan.
You are free.
It must be perilous.
How did you do it?
Did you get hurt?
They don't matter.
Qingyan.
I know you hate killing.
You don't
have to kill anymore.
Should something go wrong,
I will handle it for you.
You just need to have a happy life.
Then I can only
be with you.
Don't push me away.
Okay.
Qingyan.
No matter what awaits us in the future,
I will keep you safe.
Miss Su.
Miss Su. Please stop.
Yifan.
Was what Master Meng said true?
What did he say this time?
He said...
He said you were dating Gu Qingyan.
Yes.
I don't buy it.
You are deceiving
and using her,
right?
Yifan.
You promised my dad
that you would
take care of me all my life.
I did promise him,
so I will take care of you.
That is not what I mean.
Yifan,
Gu Qingyan isn't a good person.
Her hands were tainted
by blood.
So what?
I killed people, too.
Send her back.
Yifan.
I will go nowhere
and I'm just waiting for you here.
[New Metropolitan Nightclub]
I used to live as a killer.
I can't even get used
to such an easy life suddenly.
Do you know
when I was the happiest
when we were kids?
The happiest?
When?
It was snowing
on one New Year's Eve.
We went to a deserted temple
because we had nowhere else to go.
The village opposite
let off fireworks suddenly.
I thought I was going to die.
But with your company,
I didn't feel it was too cold.
Did you forget it?
You know why I brought you here?
I gave you the word
that I would
let off the fireworks for you alone.
Now I am fulfilling my promise.
What?
You brought me here
to show me the fireworks?
So you remember it.
Yifan.
I'm afraid of being alone.
Will you leave me one day?
Don't think about running away from me
because you will always be mine.
Wherever you are,
just stay right there,
and I'll go to find you.
[False face and true feelings]
♪The affection within reach♪
♪Became taboo words♪
♪Between you and me both♪
♪Whose hurt hasn't been mentioned?♪
♪This heart being torn♪
♪Is willing to accompany you
into danger♪
♪Whose love is so ardent and throbbing?♪
♪Trying so hard to touch♪
♪The exhausted body♪
♪The solemn pledges of love♪
♪Betrayed the choice♪
♪Whose tears are running bitterly?♪
♪And breaching desperately♪
♪When the wound is recovered♪
♪There is no time to avoid♪
♪The fate of longing for you♪
♪Whose tears
are so ardent and throbbing?♪
♪I tried so hard to touch♪
♪The exhausted body♪
♪The solemn pledges of love♪
♪Betrayed the choice♪
♪Whose tears are running bitterly?♪
♪And breaching desperately♪
♪When the wound is recovered♪
♪There is no time to avoid♪
♪The fate of longing for you♪
♪And the forbidden choice we made♪