[False face and true feelings]
[Episode 18]
Annian.
Tell me the truth.
What exactly did you give me?
Did you use it?
Answer me.
Didn't I ask you for morphine?
How could Ye Yifan
be in a serious condition?
Qingyan.
Don't make the same mistake.
Remember,
he killed your father.
Tell me,
or I will
drink up the rest of it
and die with him.
It's ephedrine.
I knew it was you.
Mr. Meng, calm down.
Mr. Mo is lying right there.
How could you still help her?
If you kill her now,
Mr. Mo will kill you first
when he wakes up.
Go tell Dr. Zhang.
I didn't want to kill him.
I thought
it was a tonic.
Let me check on him.
Miss Gu.
No matter what your purpose is,
I won't let you get close to him.
You'd better pray that he can make it,
or I will come after you.
I do.
I believe anything you say.
No matter what you want,
I will get it for you.
Like I said, Qingyan.
You may do whatever you want
with me.
I will let nobody hurt you
and keep you safe.
Qingyan.
Don't make the same mistake.
Remember,
he killed your father.
Gu Qingyan.
Yifan did hurt you,
but your father
wasn't an innocent person.
You will regret it
if you hurt him.
Young Lady.
You have sat here for two nights.
Why don't you take a nap?
How is he?
No news.
You know,
they even guard against me.
To think I'm worrying
about the one who killed my father.
You do worry about him?
I saw him kill my father.
That is the truth.
But why does everybody say
it served my father well?
I have been bewildered
and cannot see things clearly.
Mr. Liu.
You followed my father for many years.
So tell me
if he did something guilty.
I...
I have no idea.
Young Lady.
Your father was
just an honest businessman.
I see.
You may leave.
Yes.
Father.
If he dies in that way,
you will be avenged.
But why am I not happy at all?
Why do I feel so uneasy?
What are they keeping from me?
So soon.
It's winter already.
Qingyan.
This is our home from now on.
Mr. Mo.
How are you feeling now?
Much better.
Good to know.
Would you mind dancing with me?
Here?
Yes.
Okay.
♪Guess silently and wildly♪
Meng Huaizuo said it was me
who poisoned you.
Why didn't you suspect me?
I said
I would believe anything you said.
What if it was really me?
♪We always have to hurt each other
at the most wonderful moments♪
I'm still willing to believe
that you didn't mean it.
Maybe you shouldn't have believed me.
♪You left the familiar place in the end♪
Mr. Mo.
I had a dream once
in which you wanted to kill me
and I wanted to kill you.
Wasn't it a nightmare?
So who was killed in the end?
I killed you
with my own hands.
It's good
that you killed me.
Why are you so kind to me?
Did you forget it?
You are my woman.
It's cold outside.
Get inside to rest.
It's snowing heavily.
Since you have just recovered,
you should go inside, too.
Ye Yifan.
What reason makes you
trust and tolerate me
unconditionally?
If you do care about me,
why did you kill my father?
[False face and true feelings]
♪The affection within reach♪
♪Became taboo words♪
♪Between you and me both♪
♪Whose hurt hasn't been mentioned?♪
♪This heart being torn♪
♪Is willing to accompany you into danger♪
♪Whose love is so ardent and throbbing?♪
♪Trying so hard to touch♪
♪The exhausted body♪
♪The solemn pledges of love♪
♪Betray the choice♪
♪Whose tears are running bitterly?♪
♪And breaching desperately♪
♪When the wound is recovered♪
♪There is no time to avoid♪
♪The fate of longing for you♪
♪Whose surging tears
are burning fiercely?♪
♪I try so hard to touch♪
♪The exhausted body♪
♪The solemn pledges of love♪
♪Betray the choice♪
♪Whose tears are running bitterly?♪
♪And breaching desperately♪
♪When the wound is recovered♪
♪There is no time to avoid♪
♪The fate of longing for you♪
♪And the forbidden choice we made♪