Guys, breaking news!
We've just found the disgraced star,
Yin Shanshan!
Guys in the livestream,
follow our drone camera
for an unprecedented aerial broadcast!
Stop following me!
Yin Shanshan!
The roof is dangerous!
Come down with me.
Who... who are you?
I'm the one who accidentally entered your room...
You're with the paparazzi, aren't you?
I'm begging you...
Please, just stop filming me!
I'm the general manager of this hotel.
I'm Shen Jiaqin.
Come with me.
What are you doing? Let go of me!
Let me go!
Jin!
Don't call him!
Quick! Yin Shanshan is over there!
Yin Shanshan!
Hurry, hurry! She's here!
Shanshan, we heard you've been bullying
other actresses on set. Is it true?
Is that true?
Many crew members have revealed
that you're the real boss on set,
even the director listens to you?
Really?
Is your innocent image just a facade?
Is it true?
Answer us!
Is it? Tell us!
Shanshan!
Say something!
Shanshan, please answer!
Shanshan! Shanshan!
Shanshan, answer us!
Shanshan, careful!
Help me!
Save me!
Somebody help!
This is my hotel room?
A nightmare...
It felt so real.
Did I die and get reborn?
Shanshan, quick, quick!
It's time for hair and makeup!
You can't be late for today's event!
Today's event?
The red carpet was yesterday, wasn't it?
Yin Shanshan!
The 27th?
Wasn't yesterday the 27th?
Was that just a nightmare?
Why is it the 27th again?
This confused state I'm in...
is definitely not my usual style.
Normally, I'm
the one who gathers all the starlight,
Nation's Little Sister
That's right.
I'm the superstar, Yin Shanshan.
Sometimes, fame is a pain.
It makes you a target for all kinds of people.
Over here! Look here, Shanshan!
Like Xia Yan, who's about to walk the red carpet with me.
A rookie from the same company,
shows me, her senior, no respect,
and always tries to steal my spotlight.
She claims she's the new top star.
Xia Yan! Xia Yan!
Xia Yan!
Xia Yan! Xia Yan! Xia Yan!
See?
Today, Xia Yan's trick is to wear the same dress.
Wearing the same outfit isn't the issue,
the scary part is Yin Shanshan still thinks she won.
Can Yin Shanshan's team find someone else to leech off?
A fading star buying PR to outshine a rookie.
She's really trying hard to stay relevant.
Yin Shanshan insists on putting others down.
Can Yin Shanshan stop embarrassing herself?
Yin Shanshan purposely wore the same dress!
Plastic sisterhood shattered!
Okay, now,
let's invite the bridesmaid
to present the rings and her blessings.
Right after the event,
I rushed non-stop
to the wrap party for another project.
I know Cao Wen has been jealous of me for ages.
I never thought for the final scene,
she'd still change the script to mess with me.
Shanshan,
you are my best friend.
On your most important day,
I want to give you my blessing.
Here.
Cao Wen, what are you doing?
There's no wine-throwing in the script!
See, Director?
If we don't discuss it beforehand,
Shanshan can't handle the scene at all.
Shanshan, I didn't call "Cut"!
How can you break character?
I...
Shanshan, even if the script changes,
unless the director says "Cut",
you have to keep acting!
You've been an actor for seven or eight years.
Don't tell me you don't know
such a basic rule?
Is this a normal script change?
After throwing wine, my makeup and hair are ruined!
Let me tell you,
if one detail is off, we have to reshoot!
All the time will be spent
on me!
I think you're just...
A sudden splash of wine
left me stunned.
But it became proof of my bad acting and diva behavior.
Poor Cao Wen!
Does an art-house actress deserve this?
They should investigate her past co-stars.
Probably many were bullied too.
Yin Shanshan is so good at hype.
Is she trying to steal attention by whitewashing herself?
Always heard Yin Shanshan had a bad temper,
didn't know it was this awful.
Look at this!
Flipped from outshine articles to on-set bullying scandal!
Is this the end for Yin Shanshan?
Ironclad proof Yin Shanshan is past her prime!
Everyone kicks a person who is down.
In the evening, I was forced to attend
a dinner with that creepy investor, Boss Zhao.
Forced to drink glass after glass,
I got dizzy and stumbled into the wrong room.
Jin, open the door!
Then reporters swarmed the door.
My carefully built Nation's Little Sister image...
completely destroyed.
Scheming two-faced bitch Yin Shanshan fooled me for ten years!
Give me back my youth!
Entertainment industry sure is wild.
Yin Shanshan will do anything to get ahead.
Yin Shanshan's resources are ridiculously good.
With her bad acting, she still gets S+ projects?
This is the "pure" little sister you praise?
Meeting tycoons at night, drunk and disorderly?
From on-set bullying to night meetings with tycoons,
Yin Shanshan's rise is more dramatic than a palace intrigue!
Who'd believe she has no powerful backer?
To escape the paparazzi,
I ran to the hotel roof,
only to be followed.
Is it true?
Answer us!
In the chaos,
a strong force pushed me off the building.
Who would've guessed,
when I opened my eyes, I'd be back
in my own bed,
and the date was still the 27th?
Shanshan, quick, quick!
Time to go to makeup!
You can't be late for today's event!
The 27th?
It's the 27th again?
Why am I back on the worst day
of my life?
Is this a rebirth or a nightmare?
Let's get ready to go.
I see the photographers are setting up.
We'll get stunning photos today for sure.
I remember in yesterday's dream, on this red carpet,
Xia Yan purposely wore the same dress,
stole my spotlight, made me look bad.
Is Xia Yan here yet?
Not yet, why?
Don't worry,
you'll definitely outshine that fake socialite.
If everything from the dream is real,
then I'm in big trouble.
What's going on?
It's exactly the same as my dream.
Why the same dress?
This red carpet again, Xia Yan again,
planning to wear the same dress again.
What's wrong with me?
Why is this terrible day
happening again?
Give me the makeup bag.
Here.
Xia Yan,
this time, let's see how you play the same dress game.
Shanshan!
Shanshan! Shanshan!
Shanshan, so beautiful!
Shanshan!
Hey.
Just to steal the spotlight,
you purposely wear the same dress?
Sis,
we're supposed to be the sister duo.
Wearing the same clothes
gives the reporters more to talk about, right?
Ladies, look here for a photo together!
Sis, keep smiling.
You don't want the paparazzi catching you roll your eyes, do you?
The female lead for Coming for You will be mine.
And when Eternal Resentment airs,
the top billing will be mine too.
Over here!
After the dinner tonight,
Boss Zhao is even inviting me for tea.
You know what kind of man Boss Zhao is!
I know.
So what?
What's a little sacrifice for success?
If those words you just said
were heard by your rich boyfriends,
what would they think?
Smile!
They're filming us!
Okay, now,
let's invite the bridesmaid
to present the rings and her blessings.
Cao Wen again.
If it's like yesterday's dream,
You are my best friend...
that scheming bitch will splash wine in my face again.
I want to give you my blessing.
Here.
Cao...
Just like the dream.
Wait.
Cao Wen is doing this on purpose.
She wants to make me lose my temper.
Fine.
Since fate let me see the future
in my dream,
Cao Wen,
I'll play along.
You're my best friend,
why would you do this to me?
You two...
I'll give you what you want!
Cut!
Great! Excellent!
Shanshan, that improv was fantastic!
I thought it was... brilliant!
Come here.
When Cao Wen changed the script,
I was worried,
but now it's clear,
Shanshan,
you are this project's
fated leading lady!
Thank you, Director.
Cao Wen,
why did you freeze up?
Why didn't you keep acting?
Director, let's do another take.
I can definitely do it better this time.
That would waste so much time.
Forget it.
Doesn't matter.
The shot won't focus on you anyway.
Cao Wen, even if you change the script,
before the director calls "Cut",
we have to keep acting, right?
You've been an actress for over ten years.
You must know that basic rule, surely?
Yin Shanshan's acting is this good?
Guess I was only noticing her looks before.
Cao Wen always boasts about being a veteran,
but she pulls shady tricks on set.
Luckily our Shanshan's acting is impeccable,
she can handle anything.
Did you see Yin Shanshan's expression shift?
Textbook-level acting.
Now that's professional.
Someone should take notes.
Yin Shanshan's improv is so good!
Shanshan, you're amazing!
You predicted she'd try to sabotage you!
You were prepared.
This is perfect.
She tried to scheme but got caught in her own trap.
She's in trouble now.
How's the script looking?
Don't like it.
But this is the one you wanted originally.
This is Director Chen's first film
in five years!
So many people are fighting for a spot.
I'm not doing it.
Fine, don't go.
Suit yourself.
The company prefers to push Xia Yan anyway.
I heard they're already negotiating the contract.
The script...
Also, I asked around
about who influences the casting.
I heard
the behind-the-scenes owner of H Hotel
might invest in this film.
They say the owner comes from a prominent family.
What's the name again...
Shen Jiaqin.
Shen Jiaqin?
Got a photo?
I'm the general manager of this hotel.
I'm Shen Jiaqin.
It really is him.
Shanshan,
no matter what, we need to get on the investor's good side.
It'll help
our chances of getting the film's female lead.
Everything that happened today
is just too strange.
It's her.
Shen Jiaqin.
Everything from yesterday felt so real.
Was it a dream, or did it happen again?
Why is this happening?
The one who saved me on the roof yesterday was Shen Jiaqin.
No.
I need to find a way to get some answers.
Hi.
Haven't we met before?
Hello, Miss Yin Shanshan.
I'm the executive assistant at H Hotel.
My name is Lu Yun.
Here's my contact information.
I think I...
saw you in my dream.