Boss,
I heard you managed to
win Yin Shanshan's heart again,
made her fall for you all over again.
Well, everyone was gonna find out eventually.
I don't need to take this medicine.
I think you should take it, stop you from gossiping.
Boss,
you're the one in the situation,
I'm the one on the sidelines.
I still remember,
when that car came speeding towards you,
Yin Shanshan ran to you faster
than the car itself.
It was just...
like lightning striking,
and you both passed out at the same time.
But the strange thing is,
you both woke up at the same time too.
Don't you think that's the biggest...
fate?
Boss,
you've been so low-key depressed
since you woke up.
What's wrong?
Even the fact that Yin Shanshan likes you
can't make you
a little happier?
When I was in a coma,
it felt like I fell into a
pitch-black little room.
All my past memories
flashed before my eyes.
But I'm convinced
it must have been her.
Boss,
could you explain it a bit
clearer?
The Yin Shanshan I met when I was seventeen,
was from the future.
She's the present-day Yin Shanshan.
The one we know now.
Then why were you in such a hurry to be discharged?
To avoid her?
Because
I'm not ready for her questions.
Excuse me,
which room is Shen Jiaqin in?
Shen Jiaqin? One moment.
He's already been discharged.
Discharged?
Honestly, what's with him?
He didn't even come to see you after waking up.
You're in the hospital because you saved him!
It's like he's avoiding you.
He's definitely avoiding you on purpose.
He's avoiding me?
Yeah!
Probably scared of having to pay compensation.
You were in a coma for so long,
think of the lost time and opportunities.
I was only out for a few days.
A couple of ads and I'd make up for it.
It was more than a few days.
You were in a coma for almost a month.
I was in a coma for a month?
Yeah.
Then Coming for You must have started filming already!
The female lead is in a coma,
an investor is in a coma...
How could they start filming?
Good that it didn't start.
Good that they didn't replace me.
Shanshan,
you just rest well in the hospital for now.
Leave everything else to me.
Eat.
Eat more.
Good girl.
You need to eat another one.
Enough, enough! I really can't eat anymore.
I bought all of this especially for you.
This hospital, you know,
is completely unreliable.
And your company won't agree to transfer you.
If you ask me,
your company is unreliable too.
Look at that guy, Zhang.
I'm almost embarrassed to say it...
He's so ugly.
Doesn't look like a good person at all.
Ms. Yin, when will you learn
not to judge people by their looks?
Who doesn't like pretty things?
Look at my daughter.
The more I look, the prettier she gets.
The more I look, the more beautiful she is.
It's so good to have you.
It's so good to be back.
Visit home more often.
And, uh,
help me keep an eye out...
Which patient's family are you?
I knew I'd find you here.
Do you know you're not even healed yet?
The doctor told you not to overexert yourself!
Keep your voice down.
Don't disturb them.
Worry about yourself first.
She has plenty of people taking care of her.
Let's go.
Come on.
Do we have to sit like this?
Just do me this favor, please?
I'm really fine, physically.
You and my mom,
one of you confiscated my phone,
the other locked me in my room.
Right now, I feel like I'm in prison.
Shanshan,
your mom is really worried about your health.
As long as your next full check-up is clear,
I'll let you be discharged.
The next full check-up...
That's not until next Friday!
Isn't the company anxious?
Isn't the crew anxious?
They...
I'm sure they're very worried about you.
After all, you were in a coma for a month after the accident.
If you go straight back to work after waking up,
they'll definitely think
they're exploiting you.
Well, that's true.
Then I'll just film a video now
saying I've recovered,
and show it to my fans.
They haven't seen me for so long,
they must be worried about me,
they must miss me.
Shanshan,
I'll arrange all of that.
You just rest well in the hospital.
Be good.
Shanshan,
Mom's going to get food for you.
You be good, okay?
Behave.
Wait for me.
I will.
Ruru.
You've been so busy lately,
I think you've lost weight.
Don't run around everywhere.
I'll be good.
These candidates now,
they just don't have any viral potential.
Can't you find some
male guests with more buzzworthy topics?
The ones you have here
aren't even as interesting as my fake friendship
with Yin Shanshan was.
What are you all doing every day?
Shanshan.
I told you to find someone with couple chemistry,
not just repeat what I say.
Sis Shanshan!
Congratulations, Xia Yan.
Or should I call you
the new top star?
Oh, stop it.
You have no idea,
I'm so happy
you're out of the hospital.
If you hadn't come back,
Coming for You wouldn't have been able to start filming.
Boss Zhang was so worried.
Or should I say, overjoyed?
That online gossip,
was that your doing?
Online?
Sis Shanshan,
Move.
What online gossip?
I don't understand what you're talking about.
I've been hoping for your recovery all along!
Even when the producers said
they'd let me take the female lead and start filming,
I turned them down!
I swear!
Shanshan.
Sis Lin Ru.
We're such good friends,
there's no way you'd smear my name, right?
Right?
Y-Yes, of course!
I'm just so happy you're out of the hospital.
Really.
Yin Shanshan!
You really know how to run around.
Is it really necessary?
Boss Zhang has ordered the whole company to blacklist you!
Just because I had an accident
and delayed the movie's production?
Boss Zhang pulled a lot of strings
to arrange for Xia Yan to play
the lead in Coming for You.
But then you convinced the whole crew
to hold a public vote.
And once you won,
all of Boss Zhang's connections went down the drain.
Whether Xia Yan acts,
or I act,
doesn't Boss Zhang make money either way?
Xia Yan has a backer, an investor.
He was going to invest in the company,
but because the role wasn't finalized for her,
he pulled his investment entirely.
So she does rely on a sugar daddy.
I got the female lead role
purely on my own merit!
Shanshan,
are you sure there's nothing else
going on between you and that Shen Jiaqin?
Why don't you believe me?
I already told you,
I saved him
purely out of a sense of duty.
Shen Jiaqin is an investor for Coming for You.
The live public vote giving you a chance was his idea.
If you really think about it,
you're the one with the sugar daddy.
So Boss Zhang thinks
that when Xia Yan finds a backer,
it makes him money.
But when I find a backer,
it ruins his plans.
For now,
let's just lay low here in the hospital.
No.
I want to go to the Coming for You set.
I've already seriously
studied the script.
I really like this script.
I won't give up this opportunity.
I want to use this chance
to become a real actress.
But this is a movie, after all.
The big screen will magnify your performance.
This character is a female lead with a terminal illness.
Most of her scenes require a bare face, no makeup.
Shanshan, I'm just not sure
if this role is really the right fit for us.
But in the beginning,
you were the one who gave me the script.
You told me to fight for this role.
And I fought for it and won it.
But while you were in a coma,
the production team held many meetings.
Director Chen isn't very confident in your acting skills.
He strongly insisted on replacing you.
What exactly is it about Yin Shanshan
that doesn't meet your standards?
Director Chen.
What do you think is the problem
with Yin Shanshan's performance?
Director Chen,
I'd like to discuss this with you from a professional perspective.
I really think Yin Shanshan's acting is very strange.
Why does she try so hard,
but her acting is still no good?
This is just a question from
an avid film enthusiast seeking knowledge.
No soul.
Terminal illness and love both require genuine empathy.
Genuine empathy...
I think yours is much cuter than mine.
They're both cute enough.
Hello.
You look unfamiliar.
Are you a patient's family member, or...?
I saw the hospice ward information online.
I saw you were looking for volunteers.
I thought so.
Actually, I recognized you!
Yin Shanshan.
Researching for a role, right?
Interested in volunteering with us?
Of course.
This place,
is basically for patients who have been, well, sentenced...
with a terminal diagnosis.
We try our best to let them
live their final days
with dignity and happiness.
Besides medical care,
we also need many volunteers
to help them
fulfill their final wishes.
Are those people in mascot costumes up ahead
going to perform a show later?
Yes.
You're just in time.
We have a young patient named Keke.
She was recently transferred to our hospice ward.
She has a tumor here,
pressing on her optic nerve.
She's basically lost her sight.
She keeps talking about
wanting to go to an amusement park.
So,
we're preparing to let her experience
an amusement park-style performance.
Performing for terminally ill children, huh.
Shen Jiaqin?
You know our Team Leader Shen?
Team Leader Shen?
Yes, he's the leader of our volunteers.
He was one of the earliest volunteers to join our ward.
We should do more
of these activities in the future.
Go team!
Go! Go!
Shen Jiaqin!