Do we know each other?
Miss Yin.
We do now.
You are a public figure.
This is a public space.
Occupying a public elevator...
Do you find that appropriate?
Miss Yin.
Currently, we do not have
a program to recycle secondhand high heels.
Please take them with you.
Shanshan.
It's about to start over there.
Let's hurry.
What's wrong?
Nothing, nothing.
Let me see.
Don't overthink it.
It's just gossip accounts talking nonsense.
He posted it on his own Weibo.
No one's twisting his words.
I don't care who he's with.
Shh.
Keep your voice down.
Maybe it's just promotion for a new project.
When Jin finishes filming and returns,
he'll explain it to you himself.
My love life is over.
Okay, okay, okay.
There, there, don't cry.
Don't cry.
Don't I have a press conference to attend?
Right.
Fix my makeup.
Xiao Xia.
I absolutely cannot go to the wrong room this time.
I must ask Jin to clarify.
Why did he break up with me?
Jin's room is...
Found it.
Jin!
Jin, open the door and tell me,
why did you break up with me?
We've been together for ten years.
How could you bear to break up with me?
Hey, Jin.
Why is it you?
I thought...
I'd never see you again.
I'm not that drunk.
Who are you?
What do you mean, who am I?
This is my home.
This is my home!
Get out, you pervert!
What pervert?
Jin, open the door!
Hey, Jin.
Why is it you again?
What are you doing here?
Who am I?
Hey, where are you going?
What are you doing?
Please don't break up with me.
I really like you.
I miss you so much.
You didn't shave today?
Xu Jinbai, your stubble is so prickly.
I'll poke you to death.
Let me tell you...
I am not Xu Jinbai.
About today's events...
Can you just pretend nothing happened?
What compensation do you want?
I can satisfy any of your requests.
You should leave.
Um...
No one will know you were here.
We have an obligation to protect our guests' privacy.
Good hotel.
I'll have my agent contact you tomorrow.
I'll film a free commercial for your hotel.
She's out! She's out!
Yin Shanshan! Yin Shanshan!
Over here! Look over here!
The reporters swarming... just like in the dream.
It's you.
You called these reporters.
Why would you do this?
What exactly do you want?
Say something!
Let me tell you,
I won't let you get away with this.
She's out! It really is Yin Shanshan!
Yin Shanshan! It's really Yin Shanshan!
Yin Shanshan, why are you here?
Shanshan, over here! Shanshan, here! Shanshan!
Yin Shanshan, look here! Shanshan, here!
Can you give us a straight answer?
Quick, call an ambulance!
What's going on now?
In the dream, I fell to my death from upstairs.
Today, I got stabbed to death.
Does that mean today...
I'm destined to die no matter what?
Shanshan!
I'm okay.
Did I get too drunk and have a nightmare?
Thankfully, Shen Jiaqin brought me back to my room.
That nightmare felt way too real.
Shanshan, quick, quick!
It's time to go to makeup!
Yin Shanshan!
Yin Shanshan, hurry up!
The 27th?
It's the 27th again?
Lin Ru.
Pinch me.
My lady, your highness, my ancestor,
are you out of your mind today?
If we don't leave now, we'll really be late.
Just pinch me.
You're trying to kill me!
Do you know you've bruised me?
How many days will it take to heal?
Yin Shanshan!
I only know that if you're really late,
your prima donna reputation will be confirmed.
The persona you've built will be gone forever.
Persona...
It's the persona.
It's happened twice now.
Whenever my image collapses, I die.
And then my day starts over.
The first time,
I was cornered by reporters on the rooftop.
I fell from the high building.
Then I woke up back in this bed.
The second time,
I was surrounded by reporters
outside a man's door,
and I was stabbed.
And then...
I was back in this bed again.
What kind of logic is this?
Restarting my life?
A single-day loop?
Lin Ru, help me think.
Why is this happening?
How can I break this cycle?
Alright, Shanshan.
Don't worry.
I'll get someone to help you right now.
I knew you'd have a way.
Yes, yes, it's her.
She's been rambling nonsense here.
Please take her away and get her some treatment.
What's going on?
Lin Ru, you can't abandon me!
Lin Ru, I'm not sick!
Lin Ru!
Put me down!
Mr. Shen.
Preparations are complete.
Please inspect, President Shen.
The two main guests...
how many similar press conferences have they attended?
Staff, entourage, number of fans...
Approximately how many reporters?
Let me tell you.
Over sixty times.
This information is available online.
Why wasn't it researched?
And these vases...
could pose a safety risk to the guests.
Understood.
I'll remove them immediately.
This...
Replace it.
Jump.
Spin around.
Tonight,
one of the main guests is Yin Shanshan.
She's the global ambassador for CW Luxury.
She will definitely wear the latest
red carpet limited edition high heels.
Average height is about nine centimeters.
They're only for the red carpet.
Even you, a man, can't stand steadily in them.
Do you think she can stand firm?
Fired.
Mr. Shen.
You fired the team leader
in front of everyone.
He's the nephew of the Shen Group VP.
Publicity is extremely important for the hotel.
Especially for Coming for You.
This project...
But tell me the truth,
did you invest in Coming for You
because of Miss Yin?
You agreed to the crew's harsh terms.
You're the Chief Assistant.
A future pillar of the hotel.
General Manager.
You should focus your mind on your work.
My new work is about to be released.
This time,
I played a mermaid in the deep sea.
I hope everyone will look forward to it. Thank you.
Please look forward to my new work.
Why didn't Yin Shanshan wear the dress I prepared?
Was the intel wrong?
Shanshan, you're here.
Actually, friends who know me are aware
that I'm not very skilled at acting.
I'm still working hard on it.
I hope you can criticize me a little less.
Shanshan, you've been in the industry for seven years,
your acting hasn't improved.
You're called a black hole actor in the industry.
You're twenty-seven,
and can only act in silly, sweet idol dramas.
Have you ever reflected on yourself?
What's wrong with being twenty-seven?
As long as the role fits,
and the image suits,
age isn't a problem.
New generation actors are already winning awards.
You're twenty-seven and still playing the Nation's Little Sister?
Yin Shanshan, where did your acting spark go?
Do you think your current performance
is worthy of your fans?
It's been reported that you were late
on set and during variety show recordings.
Is this true?
Have you reflected on yourself?
Okay.
Alright, that's enough.
Why did you come down early?
Didn't you tell me before
that Director Chen would be meeting someone
in the back garden around seven?
I want to try for a role in Coming for You.
I don't want to keep playing those
brainless, sweet characters anymore.
But don't we still have to meet with...
Don't worry.
I'll manage the timing. No problem.
Heaven is taking pity on me.
It keeps giving me chances to relive and survive.
An investor like you...
Many people ask to meet me.
This time, I must focus on my career.
I won't let my fans down.
Win over Director Chen.
Let's go.
This time, no prima donna behavior.
No lovesick foolishness.
No jinx named Shen Jiaqin.
I'm sure to successfully win over Director Chen.
Land the role.
Bid farewell to silly, sweet roles.
When it comes to art,
I'm, well, all-encompassing.
My shooting style is basically...
click-clack, a-click-clack.
It's you again.