Yuhi Minamizawa,
a journalist for a weekly magazine,
was strangled to death here
on the 20th of this month.
They still haven't found the culprit?
You need to be careful, too.
The murderer could be in this area.
- Is the startup going well?
- Yeah.
I have an investor
who seems interested in investing.
As long as I have Masato. I'm fine.
I don't need anyone else in this world
as long as he's there.
CODEPENDENT ON HER HUSBAND
She's gotten worse.
Why would I kill her?
You said that I'm innocent.
Then who did it?
Mio Kamishiro's husband.
Masato Kamishiro did it.
He killed both of them.
Mr. Ishiguro, are you listening?
Huh? What were you saying?
I said, he was tapping his foot!
Well, as I said, uh…
- I can't remember.
- I'll start from the beginning then!
Make it short. In under 400 characters.
What?
So, first of all,
my aunt died from a heart attack.
I see.
- Wait, who?
- Her name was Aya! I told you!
This lady.
She was kind, clever, and rich.
I was proud to be her niece.
I see. She's beautiful.
She had problems with her heart
but after she married this younger guy
who was very kind to her,
she said she was doing better.
Then she suddenly had a heart attack.
- These things happen!
- True.
She did have an illness
and the police said
that there were no signs of foul play.
Okay.
And?
And then…
the foot tapping!
Huh?
He was tapping his foot
a lot at Aya's funeral!
Who was?
The kind husband!
He pretended to wipe
his tears with a handkerchief.
But he looked like he couldn't wait
for the funeral to be over.
That's creepy.
Wait…
Are you saying
that her husband killed her?
Made it look like a heart attack?
That's what I'm looking into right now.
The husband's past gets darker
the deeper I dig into it.
I see, I thought you
were acting suspicious lately.
I'm sorry.
Anything I can help with?
No. I want to do this by myself.
I'm doing this for Aya.
I've recently realized that I can't keep
depending on you all the time.
It's been on my mind a lot.
That makes me a bit sad!
Well then….
Here.
An independence gift.
It's from where I went
to cover a story on… I forgot.
It was a shrine.
There was a big line to buy that!
Wow!
Thank you very much!
It was a spur of the moment.
It might not bring much luck.
I love it.
Please let me continue!
I promise to get a scoop on it!
Yes.
As I said, I can just pay
for this room myself!
No!
Never mind. You can fire me if you want.
Goodbye.
Huh? A date?
Yeah.
How about enjoying
my rare day off together?
Really?
I'd love to!
Let's buy our wedding rings.
What?
Remember?
What you said a year ago.
You didn't want a wedding
and you didn't want a ring
until the mark
of your previous one disappears.
I said that because
after I tried to kill myself,
I didn't think I'd be able
to be a good wife for you.
But…
now, I'm really--
It's gone now.
I'm really…
happy.
I think I want this one.
Yeah.
I like it.
Can we have matching rings?
Certainly, sir.
With names engraved?
- Yes, please.
Wow, I can see it so clearly!
Yeah, it looks beautiful.
We're going there
the day after the rings are ready.
I feel so lucky.
When we get the rings…
let's exchange them.
Hmm?
For our trip, I reserved
a small wedding hall near Mt. Fuji.
What?
No guests.
Not even a priest.
A wedding just for us two.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Hey!
Are you okay?
Uh… yeah.
Let's go sit down.
Okay.
Can I help you?
I'm Ishiguro, I was Yuhi's supervisor.
I'm so sorry.
Minamizawa! Hey!
- Yes?
- Focus! You'll miss the deadline!
Mine's all finished already.
Oh, okay.
Did you look into your aunt's husband?
Well…
I feel more anxious
the more I look into it.
Let me help out.
That's an order.
But…
Hey, Ishiguro.
- You, come here.
- Yes!
Talk to you later.
Okay.
- Something wrong?
- Yes!
This article! You can't write about this!
I told you before!
Why not? It's all true!
Whether it's true or not doesn't matter!
We could go out of business
if we publish this!
But we need to expose it now
before the other companies do!
It's great that
you're passionate about this,
but you get too heated, for Christ's sake!
- For example, this.
- What's wrong with it?
Mr. Ishiguro!
- Huh?
- Yeah?
I'm off to cover a story.
Okay.
- Oh, hang on!
- Hey!
- We're not done here!
- Sorry!
- I'll call you later, okay?
- Hey…
Minamizawa!
Wait!
That was the last time I saw her.
I'm so sorry.
It's all my fault.
I don't understand.
Why are you apologizing?
I have many regrets, too.
I should've stopped her
from going to Tokyo.
I should've talked her
out of being a journalist.
I'm sorry.
It was all Yuhi's choice.
I almost forgot.
Please take this as a memento.
You gave it to her, right?
Uh…
I feel like I know you well.
She talked about you
so often on the phone.
"I got scolded by Mr. Ishiguro."
"I got praised by Mr. Ishiguro."
"Mr. Ishiguro gave me a good-luck charm."
Mr. Ishiguro this.
Mr. Ishiguro that.
Really?
But…
I guess the charm didn't work.
Even God couldn't help her.
So there was no way you could have.
I'm sorry. I don't mean to be rude.
Do you want a drink?
- I have this nice local sake.
- Uh…
No, thank you.
I'm heading to Kobe after this.
I see.
It's the true culprit's hometown.
- The true culprit?
- Yes.
The man that people claim
is the suspect isn't the true culprit.
Yuhi was trying to uncover a case and…
was murdered.
The evidence she collected
was destroyed by the culprit.
So…
I need to uncover the truth.
Thank you.
I hope it goes well.
Me too.
Oh…
And thank you for this.
Are you anxious?
Huh?
You're shaking.
Recently, I don't like crowded places.
Don't worry.
Keep holding my hand.
Close your eyes.
No one's here.
It's only the two of us.
Okay.
Feel lonely?
No.
Not if you're with me.
Okay, let's stop here for today.
Thank you.
Hey, Mio.
Can you stop doing the meditation
with your husband?
What?
But I feel so much better
since I started it!
I even take fewer meds now.
The thing is…
Doing stuff like that
without specialized knowledge
can be dangerous.
But Masato said…
Just do as I say.
I'm sorry.
But it affects our sessions.
Let me ask Masato first.
Fine.
I'm struggling to understand you.
I do have another request.
No!
A ladybug!
Yeah.
It's not moving.
It failed to hibernate.
Maybe it got lost.
Hold it for me.
There you go.
It's beautiful.
It is, isn't it?
Wash your hands later, okay?
Ladybugs have toxins.
- Toxins?
- Yeah.
All beautiful things have them.
You have a beautiful face.
Thank you.
Masato!
- Hey, you're back!
- I am!
Hi, Nozomi!
Do you live around here?
- Do you know her?
- Yes.
She goes to Mizuki's clinic.
She said she's an orphan.
I wonder if she's okay.
She's fine.
- She seemed really well.
- Yeah?
How about you?
- Do you feel good?
- I do!
Do you even still need
to go to the clinic?
I don't think so,
but apparently it's complicated.
Actually, Mizuki asked
if you could come with me next time.
What?
Me?
She wants to ask you
how things are at home.
You don't need to talk
about things you don't want to.
You're not the patient after all…
Sorry.
- I know you're busy. I can decline.
- No.
- I'll do it for you.
- Really?
I'll go with you.
- Thank you.
- It's okay.
What were you talking about with Nozomi?
Hmm?
It's a secret.
That's not fair!
KOBE
Did you find anything?
No.
I see.
In that case,
all we have left is unidentified persons.
Masato Kamishiro never lived in Kobe.
I was in elementary school
when we moved from Tokyo to Kobe
because of my dad's work.
I was there when the earthquake happened.
Is it all lies?
Hey…
who is Masato Kamishiro really?
What?
Akane!
- Welcome back!
- Thanks.
I bought you food.
I thought I was going to die!
Akane, don't say things like that lightly.
Okay!
Oh?
We're home!
- Welcome back!
- You're back!
What are you eating?
Why is this here?
- I bought it.
- I see.
You stole it again, huh?
Stealing such stupid things!
Why can't you go steal money instead!
- Toshiki!
- You…
Keep out of this!
Huh?
What are you doing? Huh?
Tami! Enough!
Get off!
Ridiculous!
Why do I have to discipline
someone else's child?
Hey.
Give me your arm.
Your arm!
Your arm! See!
Punishment.
- Stop it!
- Hey!
That's enough!
Toshiki, it's your fault. Apologize!
No!
Please, be good!
For me! I can't survive without Tami!
You need him, too! We're dead without him!
We're not.
What are you whispering about?
- Hey!
- Fine then!
Stay outside until you apologize!
You too, Akane!
- No!
- Come on!
Why can't you discipline
your kids properly?
I said I'm sorry! Stop being so angry!
I'm so irritated!
Hey, no!
Let me shower first!
- Hey!
- But you smell good.
You smell so good!
- I said, no!
- Nobuko…
- Come on, now.
- Hey!
Why not? Huh?
It's no use.
- Are you cold?
- Yes.
Huh? What's happening?
Akane!
Toshiki!
Get out!
Toshiki?
Akane…
Mom?
Where's mom?
Guys! It's too dangerous here!
We need to evacuate!
Mom will be fine!
Please take my sister! I'll follow soon!
- Okay.
- No! I want to stay too!
Listen to me!
- Toshiki!
- Let's go!
Mom!
Mom?
Hey! Over here!
She can't be saved!
Hurry, help me!
Come on!
What are you doing? Hurry!
Use a stick as leverage and move this!
Hurry up!
You idiot!
You'll die anyway.
What?
But I won't be satisfied with that!
Hey…
What on earth are you…
Hey!
Hmm?
I've never seen you make that face before.
Where did you go?
To my childhood.
My mom and my dad were there.
I see.
And you?
I was walking around town
and no one was around except for us two.
Hmm…
IWATE PREFECTURAL TOKOHA HOSPITAL
"Before the day ends,
you will depart
somewhere far away, my sister.
Sleet has fallen,
and outside is oddly bright.
'Please bring me some sleet.'
From the reddish,
horrifyingly gloomy clouds,
the thick sleet comes down relentlessly.
'Please bring me some sleet.'
To collect the sleet for you,
I took two chipped ceramic bowls
with blue water-shield patterns on them,
and ran outside like a stray bullet.
Into the dark. Into the icy rain.
'Please bring me some sleet.'"
GOOD-LUCK CHARM
Minamizawa…
you're amazing.
Good morning.
Long time no see. I thought you were dead!
Don't say that.
You're early.
I had to work all night
because no one was helping me.
Our sales have plummeted,
and I'm so worried we might go bust.
We'll be fine.
Okay.
I'm counting on
your celebrity news articles then!
I'll write as many as you want
once I'm done with this.
You're still on that?
Minamizawa succeeded
in revealing a monster.
What?
She protected this data with her life.
What data?
Data collected on Masato Kamishiro.
I'm proud to call you my brother.
I've had such a shitty life
but I'm about to start over!
Damn it!
Masato, we'll meet again
when you're a better man.
What is it you want?
This is Masato.
Masato Kamishiro is…
Subtitle translation by: Emily Johnson