Hmm?
Oh, it's nothing.
- Do you want seconds?
- Yeah!
- So, work's going well then?
- You can tell?
Kind of.
We had some issues,
but we managed to pull through.
It was a huge task.
I see…
Everything's going well…
I think we're almost there.
Ms. Momose?
Hello?
No, I haven't.
What?
The body of Ms. Iroha Koizumi was found
in a bush in Asaoka early this morning.
- She was found completely naked.
- No…
What's wrong?
Ms. Koizumi…
Due to the choke marks, the police are
investigating it as a murder case.
- Her belongings haven't been found yet…
- Why?
She worked
at a famous patisserie in Asaoka,
but apparently she was absent
without leave yesterday.
It is believed that she was involved
in an incident during that time.
Get back, please! Get back!
- Get back! Come on!
- Ouch!
What is your problem! So violent!
- There were rumors about him!
- Really?
- Look!
- There he is!
- There!
- That's him!
- Get back, people!
- He did it?
- How awful.
- So creepy!
- Mio.
- Ms. Momose!
What's going on?
He's being investigated
as a person of interest.
I can't believe this. Our chef…
There's no way…
We don't know if he did it yet.
True, but…
What's going to happen to the shop?
Why me?
You two were arguing over money,
were you not?
We've seen the messages
between you and her.
I see.
That was on her.
What?
Nothing.
She was blackmailing you.
We know it all already.
We've seen the video, too.
I didn't kill her, though! How could I…
We found semen inside the victim.
It's not mine.
Can you cooperate with us
until we get the result of the DNA test?
- Hey!
- Ouch!
- Hello.
- How's it going?
He claims he's innocent
but he'll cave soon.
- I wouldn't be so sure.
- What do you mean?
I bet he killed the journalist, too.
Well, let's see what the test says.
It's been three days since the incident.
The patisserie remains closed
while the chef's questioning continues.
Chef Oyamada is also suspected
of being involved in the murder
of a female journalist last month,
and is under thorough investigation.
Chef Oyamada lives above this patisserie…
Oh…
How long are you going
to stand there looking like that?
Sorry.
You talked to the police, right?
- I have.
- You have to leave it to them, then.
Don't stress too much.
You're right.
Maybe I should look for a new job.
I'd say take it easy for now
and think about it
when we get back from our trip.
Okay. Thank you.
Hey, can you get back early today?
Hmm?
I…
I feel really anxious.
About what?
I don't know.
Don't worry.
- I'll come back early.
- Thank you.
Smile!
Brightly!
I'll try!
WEDDING ANNIVERSARY TRIP TO SAIKO
Oh, no. You're leaving already?
I have a meeting.
- I wish you could stay longer.
- I apologize.
I would love to be with you
all the time if I could.
I need to work hard to make it possible.
I see.
How's it going starting a new business?
Everything's going well.
Hmm… You're lying.
I know you too well, Toru.
So, tell me what's going on.
No…
I can't cause you any more trouble.
- I'll pay you back as soon as I can.
- I don't care about the money!
The investor I'm talking to
has demanded unreasonable terms.
See? I did warn you, didn't I?
You need to consider
more than one investor to create
a competitive environment.
- I guess you're right.
- Here.
So…
Let me invest.
- What?
- How much do you need?
Ten million yen?
- Twenty million?
- No, I can't accept it.
You know, I have an eye for people.
I know you're the real deal.
So I need to claim you
as mine while I can.
Are you sure?
Of course! But just promise me…
Don't ever lie to me.
Understood.
Everything's going well!
Yeah.
You're home is something.
Were they all your pets?
It makes you look like
a corpse-loving psycho killer!
Not corpses.
I've given them a second life.
I wouldn't repeat that to others.
It's creepy!
Can you let me go already?
Why would I kill her?
I…
- I lov--
- Okay.
Here's your savior!
- The test results.
- Okay.
See? I told you!
It wasn't me!
Breaking news, regarding the murder
of the patisserie staff!
A DNA test has revealed that
the semen found in Ms. Koizumi's body
matched Chef Oyamada's,
the owner of the shop
where Ms. Koizumi worked.
The police have now arrested
Chef Oyamada on suspicion of murder.
It's presumed he'll also
be questioned about his involvement
with the case of the female journalist.
It is thought that Oyamada met up
with the victim after work
on the day of the murder.
Told you, you jumped the gun!
Due to the earthquake,
Chef Oyamada's shop was…
It can't be him.
…so he had closed earlier than usual.
What is this?
What on earth is this?
Why?
I…
It wasn't me!
- Call an ambulance!
- Yes!
A 99.99% DNA MATCH
OYAMADA ARRESTED, SUSPECTED OF MURDERING
A FEMALE STAFF MEMBER
Everything's going well.
LIFE INSURANCE POLICY
INSURED: MIO KAMISHIRO
BENEFICIARY: MASATO KAMISHIRO
INSURANCE COVERAGE: 150 MILLION YEN
RECEIPT OF DEATH BENEFIT IN THE EVENT
THE INSURED COMMITS SUICIDE
- What's this one?
- Huh?
That's a gateau invisible!
The inside is filled with apples.
Oh… Is it good?
They're all good!
- I'll have this one, then!
- Okay!
- These are fresh out of the oven!
- Thank you!
- On the way home from work?
- Yes.
I'm jealous of you, Mio!
Although I'd be worried if my husband
was this good-looking!
What? Don't say that!
Sir!
Yes?
I wanted to give you some coupons.
Oh… Thank you.
It's nice to meet Mio's colleagues.
You really love her.
Is it that obvious?
Liar.
I know your secret, sir.
I'll wait for your call, Masato.
CUSTOMER PARKING LOT
Hi.
Hello.
Drink?
No, thanks.
I'm working after this so make it brief.
Make it brief? That's not possible.
What do you know about me?
Hmm…
Let's say I know who you really are.
Maybe.
Well…
That makes one of us.
We could talk all night.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
- Can I have what she's having?
- Sure.
You've been to this hotel before,
haven't you?
Yes, I have. On business occasions.
That was business?
It didn't look like business!
You like older women?
She's just an investor.
She invited me to her room for some wine.
So, you don't mind
if I show this photo to Mio?
You must be joking.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
I think we might be quite similar.
You and I.
You have one too. A gateau invisible.
What?
Nothing!
Even when I first met you,
I could tell that there was
something about you.
I knew you and Mio were incompatible
because you're such a bad guy.
And we're compatible?
Who knows.
It's the chef again.
He's so annoying.
He's a creep, you know.
He hires sex workers
on Tuesdays and Fridays,
dresses them in the shop's uniform,
and tells them to call him "Chef."
So gross!
Hmm…
Also, you know he has a crush on Mio.
I'm sure of it.
Are you okay with that?
No. It's not okay.
Do you really love Mio?
I do.
Liar.
I want to know more about you.
I like you.
You're beautiful.
I'll take you to my hideout sometime soon.
- Come in.
- Thank you!
Wow! What is this place?
This is amazing!
I come here to be alone.
You're the first person I've invited.
Really?
So cute!
- Yellow boxfish.
- Wow…
That's a blackspotted puffer.
- And this plant?
- Don't touch that one.
Aconite. It's highly poisonous.
What?
How scary!
A room of poison.
Huh?
That's why I brought you.
Those with poison
in their veins are beautiful.
You're beautiful.
Thank you.
Smile.
Brightly.
- PAY ME OR I'LL SHARE THE VIDEO LOL
- PLEASE DON'T
- WHAT WILL HAPPEN TO THE SHOP
- I'LL PAY. PLEASE GIVE ME MORE TIME
You are amazing.
What's going on?
- What?
- Are you doing this?
What's happening? I don't like this.
No! It hurts!
What did you want?
Love…
What?
I wanted to be loved.
Liar.
Hello? Toru?
Masumi?
What's wrong? Are you okay?
Um… Yes.
I'm okay.
I…
I'm being chased down
by some nasty people.
I need to leave Japan at once.
What do you mean? Tell me what happened.
I can't.
I could put you in danger if I told you.
I'm dumping this phone.
- What? Hang on…
- I'll be fine.
I have a friend in Taiwan.
I'll double your investment…
and return it to you.
Don't worry about that now.
- Hey, Toru…
- Let's get married when I get back.
We'll have the wedding
at The Ritz-Carlton in Maui.
Everything will work out.
Good evening.
Thank you for taking care
of my wife the other day.
No worries.
You first.
Good luck with your job.
Thank you.
- I'm home!
- Welcome back!
- Is the bath ready?
- Oh my god, why are you so sweaty?!
I hadn't been exercising much…
so I ran home.
You're kidding! Hurry and wash up!
I worried for nothing. You seem fine.
What do you mean? I'm doing fine!
- Are you taking the meds?
- Not recently.
I'm glad to hear that.
You don't often invite me out for lunch
so I thought something had happened.
I was feeling down,
but staying at home made it worse, so…
- I'm thinking of looking for a new job.
- I see.
How's it going with your husband?
- Really good, actually.
- Nice!
Hey…
Is something on your mind?
Huh?
No!
Okay.
Cool.
I realized recently…
how lucky I am that I met Masato.
As long as I have Masato. I'm fine.
I don't need anyone else in this world
as long as he's there.
EVEN MORE CODEPENDENT ON HER HUSBAND
BORDERLINE PERSONALITY DISORDER
POSSIBILITY OF ATTENTIONAL NARROWING
She's gotten worse.
But why?
Nice to meet you.
My name's Ishiguro, and I'm a journalist
for Gyokuseki Weekly Magazine.
Gyokuseki Weekly Magazine?
Yes.
The journalist, Yuhi Minamizawa,
was my co-worker.
I didn't kill her.
Yes.
I was just so happy she liked my cakes,
I kept sending them to her.
I know.
You're not the culprit.
I didn't kill Ms. Koizumi either.
I know.
You are innocent.
I am on your side.
Ms. Koizumi was…
a big fan of the sweets I made.
She came to my seminar so many times.
Even after she joined the staff,
she'd stay late to study.
A hard worker.
And she was talented.
One day…
I couldn't get in touch with her, so…
I went to check on her.
Goodness me.
Ms. Koizumi?
Oh, god!
Her fiancé had left her
right before the wedding.
She survived…
and came back to work at my shop.
But it was no use.
She wasn't herself anymore.
Why would I kill her?
I…
I loved her.
Even after she had changed.
I see.
Mr. Ishiguro…
you said that I'm innocent.
I did.
Then who did it?
Mio Kamishiro's…
husband.
What?
Masato Kamishiro did it.
He killed both of them.
Wow, this is beautiful!
I bought it for our anniversary trip.
- It's your favorite brand, right?
- Yes!
I really wanted this! Thank you so much!
It's so pretty.
- It looks good!
- I want to pair it with my clothes!
I will reveal
who he truly is to the world.
So…
please hang in there.
Did you look into her husband?
I feel more anxious
the more I look into it.
I need to uncover the truth!
No one's here. It's only the two of us.
He was tapping his foot
a lot at Aya's funeral!
- Did you find anything?
- Masato Kamishiro never lived in Kobe.
What?
Subtitle translation by: Emily Johnson