And 5, 4, 3, 2...
Action!
Hi, Stars!
I'm Tala Monteverde and
I'm going to tell you my...
Cut, cut, cut!
Sorry, Tala. Let's do one more take.
What is going on?!
I'm sorry, Miss Tala.
"I'm sorry"?
You do know that we're
currently in a shoot, right?
Are you new here?
You aren't, right?
Do you know that we got delayed earlier
because you didn't prepare the products
and now you're ruining the shoot?
What the heck!
How incompetent!
You're already stupid,
and you're weak too!
You're fired.
You're so arrogant.
Just because you're a celebrity?
Excuse you.
I'm not arrogant.
I just happen to respect and value the time
of everyone here.
Aren't you ashamed in front of them?
You're wasting their time, including mine!
You will fail too, mark my words!
Just wait until your day comes!
Can't wait!
As if.
How dare she threaten me.
Who does she think she is?
She has a lot of nerve!
Sorry, everyone. I'm so sorry.
Shall we take it from
the top? Is that okay?
Yes, yes, yes.
- Okay.
- Relax, relax, relax.
Okay. Camera are rolling.
5, 4, 3, 2...
Action!
Success isn't just about
getting what you want.
It's about
becoming the woman
everyone wishes they could be.
The glitz, the glamour.
The life people only dream about.
For some people,
it's entertainment.
For others,
it's a escape.
They watch you because somehow
they get to live through you.
So, if you're lucky enough to become
that woman,
You do everything you can to stay heard.
Hi, Stars! I'm Tala Monteverde,
and this is my secret to
looking fresh and beautiful.
Tada!
- Hey!
- Mom!
Where do you think you're going, huh?
I have a side job.
What side job?
Huh?
Wedding, baptism, or funeral?
If it's a funeral,
don't you ever bring home
food from there, okay?
It's considered bad luck, son.
Grandma, it's neither of those events.
- What is it then?
- It's a fan meet.
Fan meet? Really?
There's a celebrity? Who is it?
Her.
Wow, OMG! I know her!
That's Tala!
She's really popular nowadays, brother.
She's so beautiful.
So Latina!
- You even did that, huh?
- Of course!
I idolize her, son.
Is it possible for you to
get me an autograph?
Come on, son! Please.
I'll try, Mom.
My ride is here already.
I have to go, Mom.
- Alright, son.
- Bye, brother!
Be safe, son!
Do your best!
- Don't forget my autograph.
- I got it, Mom.
Thanks, bro.
I don't know.
You know what...
Maybe the personal assistant
I fired earlier is his girlfriend.
Ride safe!
He's the only one who
gets my angles right, Moi.
What am I going to do now?
I don't have a personal shooter anymore.
It doesn't...
What the heck?
Are you stupid or what?
Wow!
I'm the one being stupid,
yet you're the one
who wasn't looking at the road?
Then why are you blocking the way?
Ma'am,
can't you see that the road is wide enough?
Plus...
Hello?
What are you looking for?
I'm in front of you!
Oh. Nothing, Ma'am.
I'm just looking for the sign that says.
"Tala Monteverde" on the road.
But I guess there's nothing.
So that means you don't own the road!
You are so arrogant.
Tala, Tala! What are you doing?
I've been waiting for you for a while now!
I know. I'm sorry.
What's happening here?
Is there a problem?
No. There's no problem here.
Actually, we're just talking
because I bumped into him.
I'm really sorry about that, Sir.
I'm so sorry. Here, take this.
Let's go.
- The organizers are already there.
- Okay.
Sir, please excuse her manners.
Sorry about that.
- Let's go.
- I'm really sorry, Sir.
Sorry, Sir!
That's fine as well.
I'm sorry. It's just that he
was blocking the way earlier.
Tala!
You're so fake!
You act so innocent!
I know that it's all an act.
You act as if you're kind,
but you're actually mean!
Ma'am, please don't act this way.
And why do you care?
You look like a wimp!
That's considered as
alarm and scandal, Ma'am.
Don't add slight
physical injury to the list.
Sir, please help us!
Please escort Tala inside, okay?
Make sure that she's safe.
Go on. Go with him.
See you later.
Thank you very much for your help, Sir.
By the way, My name is Moi—
Tala's manager.
Thank you again for helping Tala.
She's always been like that.
She only has a sharp tongue, but
when put in danger,
she just freezes up easily.
That's why I'm very thankful for your help.
By the way, what is your name?
Uhm...
Here.
I'm Michael. Michael Maragtas.
Oh my God!
- You're the shooter for today's event!
- Yes, I am.
Sorry.
How about this...
So we can make up for what happened,
just say whatever you need and let me know.
Don't be shy, okay?
Anything. I will take care of it.
Uh...
Really?
Can I have a signed poster of Tala?
My Mom is a fan.
Of course! Here.
Thank you!
You're just a freelancer?
Yes. Just doing side jobs here and there.
Ah...
Do you want a regular job?
What?
Just send me your portfolio
and I'll contact you.
Really?
Okay?
Yes. Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
Thank you again. Thank you so much.
- Thank you!
- Just send me the portfolio, okay?
- Bye!
- Thank you!
This is good.
She's so beautiful!
Mom, you really placed Tala's poster right
next to Mother Mary.
Grandma.
You might as well offer
food to her poster too.
Just leave me be, children.
This is the first time I've received an
autograph from a celebrity.
Thank you for the poster, son.
That's just a poster, Grandma.
What more if it's a video greeting?
Yes, my child.
My birthday is coming soon.
Is it possible...
to receive a video greeting
from Tala as a birthday present?
Please, son.
Oh my goodness, Grandma.
Oh, come on.
Just leave me be.
This only happens once in a while.
You really are something, child.
I'm not really sure if I'll see her again.
Let's see.
[phone beeps]
MOI: It's confirmed! I have a job for you.
Got you, Mom.
Thank you! Yes, yes, yes!
You see?!
"I'm sorry"?
You do know that
we're currently in a shoot, right?
Are you new here? You aren't, right?
Do you know that we got delayed earlier
because you didn't prepare the products
and now you're ruining the shoot?
What the f—?
How incompetent!
You know what, Michael?
I love your ideas! I saw your portfolio...
You're so talented!
Good afternoon, Ma'am.
You again?
Yes, Ma'am.
It's me again.
- Moi?
- Mhmm?
Have you seen the video?
Yes.
Now shut up and let's talk about it later.
Anyway. Tala, this is Michael.
He was the shooter on your fan meet.
Your new sh...
No.
Him?
No way.
First of all,
he's late. Do you know what time is it?
See?
Secondly,
really?
Long sleeves? In this humidity?
Look, you're sweating profusely.
And third,
he looks so arrogant.
He has a lot of nerve to show up late.
Ouch, Ma'am.
It really hurts to be judged
and rejected personally by Tala Monteverde.
Miss Moi,
you should've given me a heads up that
I will be woring with Miss Tala.
I thought I'd be working
with a different talent.
Then I shouldn't have
accepted the job at all.
Maybe I'm not worthy
of Tala Monteverde's kindness
and greatness of heart.
Really?
You think you're so funny?
You aren't.
Stop being so sarcastic.
See, Moi? This is exactly what I mean.
He's so unprofessional.
Shh.
Moi, I don't want to...
Tala,
I can vouch for him.
I saw his previous works and coverage.
And it was all good.
And also,
you haven't thanked him yet.
He was the one who stopped your basher.
And girl,
he's already approved by the management.
You won't find another like Sir Jess.
Remember what the management said?
"Post more to drown the noise."
How will you even post
if you don't have a shooter?
Fine.
Contractual.
Thank you, Ma'am.
Three weeks.
Copy, Ma'am.
No.
Let's make it two weeks.
Okay. Thank you, Ma'am.
But I have some ground rules.
Can you do it?
Yes, I can.
I can definitely do it.
Really?
Thank you, Ma'am!
- Thank you.
- Congratulations, Michael.
- I know you can do it.
Thank you.
Oh my God!
This is my favorite cake!
Look at it!
Tada!
It's so cute and perfect.
I just want to eat it!
Oh my gosh. So cute!
Wait on a sec, Ma'am.
Can you relax? Your stiffness
is showing on the camera.
Rule Number 1...
I'm your boss.
Okay?
My studio. My rules.
So don't try to change the way I do things.
Got it?
Ma'am!
Get.
Off.
Me!
"Get off me!"
Yes, daddy.
I'm fine. I'm happy.
Of course.
It's just that I'm really busy with work.
You know how work can be.
The usual.
There are brand deals,
collabs, and all that stuff.
I'm actually really busy today.
I have a lot to finish.
Rule Number 2...
Whatever you hear,
Whatever you see,
All confidential.
Got it?
Uhm...
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
It's not my intention to eavesdrop.
Whatever.
Rule Number 3...
The most important rule.
Only capture me when I'm happy...
because people want to live through me
vicariously.
Got it?
I thought you're good at what you do?
Why are your shots terrible?
It's good, Ma'am.
Good?
What's good about them?
There really isn't any
photo where I'm smiling.
What can't you
understand? Didn't I tell you
to only capture me when I'm happy because
people want to live through me vicariously.
Vulnerability is not my branding.
But at least those pictures humanized you.
With more emotions.
More real.
Not fake.
Right?
You know what?
We should finish this brand collab
tomorrow.
Let's finish this and after that,
we can call it quits.
You don't have to worry.
I'll still pay for the entire month.
[phone beeps]
Tala, it's okay.
It's part of being an influencer.
It's okay.
Remember what management said...
"Ignore, delete, forget."
Comfort is key.
- The—
- [phone rings]
I am sorry, Ma'am.
Just hold on for a moment.
Let's roll again. 3, 2, 1, action!
Comfort is key.
- The—
- [phone beeps]
Ma'am,
What is it, Michael?
Just answer the call.
JAJA: Uncle, where are you?
It's okay.
- Is it?
- I'm really sorry, Ma'am.
- You already handled it?
- Yes, Ma'am.
Comfort is key.
That's why wherever you go,
what you wear should also move with you.
It should be light,
breathable, and stylish.
It should be available from...
Morning runs to afternoon errands,
You shouldn't have to choose between...
Ma'am!
You're okay.
You're safe, Ma'am.
Ma'am.
Are you okay?
I am right here, Ma'am.
I won't leave you.
Why is this happening to me?
Am I really a bad person?
Do you want an honest answer, Ma'am?
Am I a bad person?
No, you aren't.
You're just tired.
That's why you were irritable.
You're always smiling for the cameras,
always repressing your anger.
But Ma'am,
you're not a bad person.
Ma'am,
I know that
you're a strong person.
But that doesn't mean you
should always be perfect.
Why?
Why are you still kind to me even though I
was so bad to you?
Why are you still here even
though I want you gone?
Is it because I pay you?
My Mom always told me that
you'll never
be able to feel
what others are feeling if you never put
yourself in their shoes.
That's why after my older brother passed,
it was me who acted as the older brother.
I felt that
the world isn't actually that easy.
It turns out life wasn't that simple.
Ma'am,
I understand you.
do you want an ice cream?
Thank you again, Michael.
For saving me and for
listening.
How about the ice cream?
You won't say thank you?
I bought it for you.
Can you stop calling me "Ma'am"?
We're almost the same age!
You're making me feel old.
And,
as for this,
don't worry. I'll reimburse it.
There's no need, Ma'am.
It's okay.
But I hope somehow
you feel a little lighter inside.
I remember that my older brother
used to bring us ice cream
whenever we feel terrible inside.
We share the ice cream with each other.
The problem might not go away,
but somehow,
it feels lighter.
You know, Michael?
I hope you don't mind but
what really happened to your brother?
Silent killer.
Heart attack.
I'm sorry.
That's why
when he passed,
I was left with my niece.
I was doing side jobs from left to right.
I need my niece to graduate college.
That's why me and my mom...
My mom!
What time is it?
Why? What happened?
It's her birthday today.
Then go home immediately!
But we're not finished with the shoot.
And isn't it my last day today?
You know what?
Let's settle that for another time.
I know how it feels to have
somebody special miss your birthday.
Thank you so much, Miss Tala.
Oh.
I mean Tala.
No biggie.
Alright. Go on.
Thank you.
Hm?
Can I maybe...
ask you to do a video greeting?
My Mom is a fan.
Of course!
I owe you one.
But wait...
Why stop at video greeting?
Hm?
Where's Mom?
There— has been sulking
for a while now.
You promised her lunch
but it's already past that.
Happy birthday, Mom!
Mom, I'm sorry that I'm late.
But I have a suprise for you.
I'm sure that you will like it.
Just take a look at it first, Mom.
Hi! Mommy Raphaela, Happy birthday!
I hope that you're happy today.
Even though Michael is a bit late.
But Michael loves you so much.
Thank you, son!
Happy birthday, Mommy!
Tala!
Am I dreaming?
You aren't, mommy. Happy birthday!
Thank you, son!
Thank you.
Here.
Thanks.
Your family looks happy.
Happy?
Messy happy.
Tala,
I know I'm not allowed
to ask personal questions but,
Come on, Michael.
You've broken all of my rules already.
And now you're asking for permission?
You almost got fired.
So I'm not fired yet?
Hmm.
Since you're good at your job,
you can actually teach photography.
When it comes to videos,
you're 'so-so'.
You really are honest.
What was your question?
Make it quick or else I'll change my mind.
I'm just curious.
Where is your family?
Well,
my parents migrated to Canada.
Don't you miss them?
Sometimes. But,
not really.
I mean,
growing up, they've always
been travelling for business.
So, I'm kind of used to it.
Uh...
Do you know why I...
freeze up when I'm in danger?
Why?
Because,
I'm so scared of the thought
that no one will save me.
Because I'm alone.
You know, Tala?
You don't need a savior.
Sometimes
you just have to be brave for yourself.
Oh my goodness.
We can be your family if you want.
You're eavesdropping again, Mom.
Yes, Miss Tala.
Here,
you're always welcome—
Doesn't matter how long you'll stay.
Not only here.
If you want to relax,
my Mother left me a land in Sta. Cecilia.
If you're tired of shoots
or want to stay somewhere else,
or if you want to see nature...
Mom.
What will Tala even do there?
There's no airconditioning
so she won't be able to sleep well.
Miss Tala,
is it possible
to get a picture with you?
Another picture? You already
have lots of pictures together!
Come on, Michael. It's okay.
How come it's alright
with Miss Tala but not with you?
You're just her camera man.
How dare you give me orders?
- Why not?
- You really are something.
So meddlesome.
He really is.
Hurry up!
Alright, Mom.
You're such a killjoy.
1, 2, 3!
Another — wacky!
Thank you.
You're ugly.
Mommy Raphaela sent so much.
I'm just one person anyway.
Wow.
My diet is going to be ruined.
You've known her for just an hour
yet you call her 'Mom' already?
Well...
She has an altar of you at our house and
she even invited you to Sta. Cecilia.
Are you her daughter?
Come on. I'm just kidding.
Why are you messing around? Are we close?
Aren't we close already?
Tala?
Calm down, Tala.
Tala, listen to me.
Inhale.
Exhale.
Tala, calm down.
Calm down.
Inhale.
Exhale.
This is getting out of hand.
I asked the management
to make a police report.
But...
They said that they
will talk to Myrna first.
I'm pretty sure it's that darn
P.A. behind all of this.
Didn't she threaten me before?
Why can't we just bring her
to the police already?
They said it will cause more noise.
It will tarnish the management's image.
What will the public think?
That the management
can't protect its artist?
So?
What do you propose we do now?
They asked you to lie low for a bit.
What?
What about my brand deals?
The contracts that I've already signed?
They said they will take care of it.
Tala, you need rest.
Maybe...
Out of the country.
Moi, please.
I really don't want stress right now.
It's difficult to be a burden.
What if they don't want
to pause my projects?
There's a lot on the line up.
Then have a vacation near here.
Ah, whatever. No work for now.
Tala?
I have an idea.
Are you up for it? I'll double your pay.
For Jaja's college fund.
Who is Jaja?!
Come on. Didn't Mommy
Raphaela invite me?
Who is Raphaela?!
Right? Didn't she say I was welcome?
Don't blame me, okay?
Hey! Hold on, I'm so confused.
What do you mean "don't blame me"?
Where are you "welcome"?
Hello?!
Tala, Michael, I'm here!
I don't understand what's going on.
Okay?
Can you inlude me, please?
Can I be included?
Oh my God.
- Oh, Tala! You're going to enjoy it here!
- So itchy!
It does seem like she's enjoying, Grandma.
She is just so stubborn. I already told
her that it would be difficult for her.
Oh, tomorrow you'll have more fun
because we're going to
harvest some vegetables!
- You're going to love the fresh air here!
- Hold on!
Look!
Oh my God. Oh my God. Oh my God.
What happened?
Are you okay, Tala?
She can do it. She's the
one who insisted after all.
I'm okay!
May God bless you.
Cousin!
- You brought so much stuff.
- Can you please help me?
Go ahead and help him.
Alright.
Oh my, finally got to take a vacation here.
Tala!
I still can't believe
that you're here with us.
Is this real?
Yes! This is as real as it can be.
Really really?
Ja,
come and help me cook.
It's embarrassing to Tala.
- Come on, Grandma!
- Come now.
Let's cook — Tala might be hungry.
Tala, can you teach me how to become as
beautiful as you later?
That cannot be taught!
You're still young
to be thinking about
those things! Goodness!
Your mom seems really
hardworking, doesn't she?
Hardworking?
She's the most hardworking mom to ever
grace this Earth.
Oh, Tala. By the way,
there are two rooms here.
One's for mom and Jaja, and the other
one is for you.
Clarence already cleaned
them, don't you worry.
How about you?
Where will you sleep?
Here.
No. I don't want you to.
That's not allowed.
This is for Jaja's college fund.
I just thought of something.
I was reading hate comments from
bashers last night.
And I realized that the internet thinks
that I'm a diva because
I'm rich and I'm classy.
They were saying that if I were to be put
among the locals,
I wouldn't thrive.
And I think that this is the
right time to prove them wrong.
You're still think about work, huh?
Think about it!
"A Day in the Life of Poor Tala"!
Right?
I could copy or actually do
what Mommy Raphaela,
or I could even help with
the chores in this place.
Right?
You know that already, right?
The usual activities or food that
people eat from...
poor communities.
Oh.
Are you referring to us?
We're part of the "poor communities"?
The "poor"?
No! I mean...
That's not what I meant!
What I mean is that people want to see
my vulnerable side.
And I think that this
is the perfect chance.
Tala, that's not vulnerability.
It's scripted.
Between us, who is the influencer?
Why does it seem like
you know more than me?
Tala, whose house do you think this is?
And who do you think your boss is?
Okay.
After all, you're the one with five
million followers.
Good.
Good thing you know.
Tala!
- Yes, mom?
- Come outside!
Come and help us!
Enjoy the province life! Hurry!
This is it!
Go ahead and film me, okay?
Just a sec, mom!
Come on and hurry up!
- Go ahead and vlog!
- You're so slow!
Wait!
Hold on.
Ready? Rolling?
A Day in My Life living a simple life
fetching wa-ter in the province!
Child, are you doing okay there?
Goodness! This is just
the start of our day here.
Cut!
I'm fine, mom.
- She's fine, Grandma.
- It's just heavy.
Is there no water service provider here?
This is so heavy!
What do you mean it's heavy? It's
almost empty
because it kept spilling!
I will get more!
Alright, take two!
Okay, take two! Rolling!
A Day in My Life
living a simple life here in the province!
So, today we're going to fetch some water
because we need water to do laundry.
A Day in My Life living a simple life
chopping some wood for our food!
Look, guys. We're chopping wood
so that we can eat food!
There!
I already told you to not do that!
It hurts!
Let me see!
It hurts. I can't do
this — it's so difficult!
That's because you're so stubborn. Hold on.
I already told you to not do
that. You didn't listen to me.
Gosh, Tala.
Didn't I tell you that it was dangerous?
You're so stubborn.
You're doing everything just
for the sake of those videos.
Shut up and film me!
You talk too much!
Just be careful, okay?
Okay!
3, 2, 1 — be careful!
Go!
No pain, no gain!
Michael, hurry!
Go ahead and film me.
No, not there! I want mom and Jaja to
be included.
Move to the other side.
Oh wow! We're really included, huh.
Ja, move aside.
Of course they'll bring in more views!
You really don't know anything.
Alright.
Do we really have to plant these?
Are these really going to sprout?
These seem like just stems.
Of course they'll grow.
Haven't you seen
anyone planting plants before?
This is called bag rooting.
If it grows,
then it can be sold.
It's just our side line.
Well,
it looks like you've
never touched soil before.
With hands as dainty as yours.
Jaja.
Don't tease Tala anymore.
She's just not used to it.
Besides,
she's already tired from all the chores
she did all day.
Is this what you do every day?
Don't you get tired?
We do get tired.
However,
it needs to be done
because there is no
one else to do it but us.
Don't you set aside time just for yourself?
Or have a vacation just to relax?
Of course we do.
It's just that
that is already considered a luxury for us
if we spend time for ourselves.
Also,
we weren't born rich.
If we are being lazy,
we will gain nothing.
Let me help you with that.
Let me plant the rest.
Are you sure, Tala?
I will try my best.
How about this? Is
this still okay to plant?
Yes, it's okay to plant that.
It's amazing how your eyes don't disappear
whenever you laugh.
You're such a workaholic.
Gosh. It's because I get
lonely when I'm not busy.
That's because you're a people pleaser.
Tala,
you're not a robot, okay?
I know.
Maybe I just got used to being so busy.
I just don't want to be a
disappointment to people.
I didn't get any validation before so,
when I got validation from social media,
there!
I made a career out of it.
What about you?
You don't seem to have a lot
of problems. You look very chill.
I do have problems.
Tala, I'm a breadwinner.
I do side jobs from left to right.
It's because I promised my brother that
I'll help my niece graduate college.
You know, you're really
resourceful, Michael.
Your future wife will be lucky.
That's way too soon.
What about you?
It seems like it's hard to have a
relationship when you're a celebrity.
Actually, it's not that difficult.
I've had boyfriends before.
Actually, my last boyfriend,
he was the one who helped me start being
a content creator.
But he was such a red flag.
He was so violent — he hurt me.
I had to cover up bruises with make up
before I go outside.
That level of violent.
That's why we broke up.
And then I met Moi.
You know Moi already, right?
You didn't deserve to be hurt.
I know. Nobody deserves to be hurt.
I'm so tired of controlling my emotions.
I'm tired of being a breadwinner!
I'm tired of being bashed!
I'm tired of having multiple side jobs!
I'm tired of being alone.
Me too.
We're both tired.
But
we have to keep on going.
Keep going.
Mom.
Aren't you going to wake Tala up?
Goodness.
She might be too tired
from her chores yesterday.
We need to go home before it gets dark.
You take charge here, okay?
- Yes, mom.
- Alright, son.
Oh, she's already awake.
Mom, where are you going?
We're going home.
Jaja has school tomorrow.
I see.
It's okay. You're going to survive!
After all, you can do house chores now.
You're a fast learner, Miss Tala.
Alright.
- We'll get going before it gets dark.
- Okay, mom. Be safe.
Be good, okay? Make sure to listen well.
Be safe, mom.
- There's food inside, okay?
- Be safe!
Take care of yourselves, okay?
Yes, mom.
Bye!
- Ja, take care of mom.
- Yes, uncle.
Excuse me.
Tala!
Tala.
Yes?
About last night...
Which part?
When...
That's nothing, okay?
We were just drunk.
No meaning.
[phone rings]
Moi?
Hello, Tala?
We already talked to Myrna.
She said that it wasn't her
that caused trouble with you.
She just let those words slip out
because she was deeply hurt.
Plus, she's already in Japan.
But...
Wait, wait, wait!
I'll call again later.
I just have an emergency meeting.
Bye!
ANONYMOUS: Unless you want to drag
them into this mess. I'll wait.
Tala, wait. Stay here—
It's not safe yet.
Tala, I'll go with you.
Tala, aren't you going to talk to me?
Will you please shut up?
This has nothing to do with you.
Something came up, okay?
You don't need to meddle in everything.
Tala, I'm just worried about you.
I don't need your worry.
Who are you anyway? What are you to me?
I thought we were okay.
That's what you thought.
Stop assuming
and please stop following me around!
You're fired.
[phone beeps]
ANONYMOUS: Think about it.
ANONYMOUS: Unless you want to drag
them into this mess. I'll wait.
Jace?
Hi, babe.
What are you doing here?
Did I surprise you?
Don't you "hi, babe" me!
We broke up long time ago!
But tonight,
you'll come back to me!
Hell no!
Really?
Is that how you should welcome me?
You're so expensive to bring down!
What?
In social media, right?
The video where you got bashed?
You're already stupid,
and you're even weak!
I bought that from your PA.
You're sick!
And the fans who kept on taunting you?
You're also mean!
Those all cost money.
Jace, what's your problem?
Why are you doing this?
Because I want to...
punish you.
You only broke up with me
because of your job, right?
Because you became too much of a show off!
Before, I was the only one
who filmed your content.
I made you, Tala!
But you got rid of me so easily.
Jace, you were abusive and toxic!
You might as well just kill me!
That's the reason why we broke up...
Not because I got famous!
It's the start of your downfall now.
And I'm the only one you need.
It's simple.
Come back to me, Tala.
And everything will be okay.
You're insane...
Really?
If you ever think I'll come back to you.
I would rather freaking die.
Why?
Is it because you have a new shooter?
Where is he now? Reveal him.
Where is he?!
I'm here!
Gotcha!
Tala, didn't I tell you that
even though we're tired,
we have to keep going.
No one gets left behind.
What?
Michael!
Give that to me!
Let go of the phone!
You asshole!
Michael!
She'll never love you!
She's always going to choose her job.
Her fame!
Did you know that she only met me because
she doesn't want me to publicize
the photo of you two kissing?
You should listen to me.
We're both going to end up the same.
Tala, you don't need a savior.
Sometimes, you just have
to be brave for yourself.
Tala!
Michael!
Tala, are you okay?
Michael, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Because...
Are you okay?
Hi, Stars!
I'm Tala Monteverde.
And
if you've been following
me for a long time,
you'd probably know me as someone
who loves perfection.
But,
after a few days,
after everything I've been through,
I realized something...
perfection is not about looking perfect.
Perfection is not about
the perfect lighting,
the perfect filter...
It's not about pretending that you're okay.
Imperfection is what makes life beautiful.
And I've learned to enjoy it that way.
So this time,
I'm showing you who I am.
Without the makeup,
without all the glam.
I'm showing you myself without my shield.
My armor.
This is who I am.
I'm not perfect.
And that's perfectly fine.
Bye, Tala!
Be safe.
Girl, I'll go ahead.
Michael.
Bye!
So...
What's your plan?
I think...
I think I need to find myself
better without the noise.
Something like a retreat.
Somewhere isolated and far away.
A place with no signal, no workload.
Somewhere sabbatical.
I don't know.
I'm not really sure yet.
Is this a goodbye to our tandem?
Tala, what are we?
What am I to you?
Because for me,
I really
really like you, Tala.
Michael...
I understand.
Maybe what we want in
this world just doesn't align.
Maybe...
Maybe we both aren't ready yet.
Bye, Tala.
Alright, guys. In street photography,
you must not be obtrusive.
If you want a person to be your subject,
it should not be staged and
genuine interactions are a must.
And it's important to respect
the privacy of each person.
Copy, guys?
Yes, sir.
It's also important to
pick your best shots.
The composition should be
good, as well as the colors.
These should be based on the lighting.
Yes, sir.
Copy?
Copied, sir.
Okay.
Take some shots then
return here after an hour.
- Yes, sir.
- Okay, sir.
Don't wander too far, alright?
How are you?
Just here.
Teaching photography.
Still shooting for weddings, baptisms, and
funerals sometimes.
How about you?
Well...
I just returned from a retreat.
I really needed that.
And also, my parents are
asking me to come to Canada.
We're much better now.
Moi is asking me to come back to work but,
I'm not too sure if people still like me.
Tala.
I'm sure that the people still like you.
Many have been asking when will you return.
Wow!
You're more updated than I am, huh?
Stalker levels.
Tala...
I missed you.
I missed you too.
Really?
You barely even made your presence felt.
I needed to disappear
for me to return whole.
For me to return more prepared.
What about now?
Rae you ready now, Tala?
Come to think of it...
Why will you be ready? Who am I to you?
What even are we?
Before, I thought that
success was the glitz and the glamour.
The lights, the cameras,
the applause.
The millions of people watching,
wishing they had the life you show them.
I like you, Michael.
And yes,
I am ready now.
But now,
I know.
Success cannot be measured by
the number of your followers or likes.
Not by the number of people watching you,
Hello?
I told you, I like you!
I heard!
So?
Oh my God! I'm so sorry!
You're already married?
What do you mean married?
So, what is it?
But by the people who stay.
The people who see
you for who you truly are.
When the lights are gone,
the cameras,
and the applause.
You're still the one that
I want, Tala Monteverde.
Even if you don't say anything,
you're the one that I'll choose.
Always.
You know what?
I really don't know where this will end.
But I know
that this is what I want to start.
So do you think
that now
can we finally be together?
That is what I want to start.
Us.
No more what ifs.
No more maybes.
Us.
No more what ifs.
No more maybes.
And if there are people
who still choose you,
even if only your true self is what's left,
at this point of my life,
that's what true success is.