[Shadow Love]
[Episode 17]
[Sixu Clinic]
Boss.
I've finished all the work.
Then I'll…
You can go.
Okay.
Wake me up tomorrow morning.
Got it.
Is it that hard to make it official?
Please, just go home already.
I have to get up early every day
to train at the General's Residence.
It's killing me already.
If Shuang finds out
you've been drinking at my place,
she'll probably make me train harder.
I'm feeling down
and want a drink
and a chat with my friend.
What's wrong with that?
If you don't tell and I don't tell,
how would she know?
Just don't tell her, simple as that.
Besides, Lu Xin,
when have I ever sold you out?
Don't you trust me?
It's not that.
I'm just curious—
do men care about titles too?
Men and women are equal, okay?
On this point,
I agree with Li Shuang.
You're desperate for a title.
Is it because the Crown Prince is coming
and you're feeling unsettled?
I do feel a bit uneasy.
But don't you think
since the Crown Prince betrayed her,
she should've…
let go of the past?
If romantic feelings
were so easy to let go of,
there wouldn't be
so many lovesick people in this world.
Stop drinking.
You don't need to be so pessimistic.
If you ask me,
you're not
much worse than the Crown Prince.
Really?
Really.
You're both grown men,
both young and handsome.
And besides, as you said,
all people are equal.
It's just that…
the Crown Prince and Shuang
share an irreplaceable past,
while you
don't even remember your own past.
That really is a shame.
Sometimes,
I want to tell her
about my past experiences,
but I don't know where to begin.
Have you ever thought
that perhaps you and Shuang
had met before?
A fleeting glance
in a vast crowd.
You and she are meant to be.
That's how it's written
in all the love stories.
Drink up.
Okay.
Years ago,
I heard about a method
to restore memories from folk tales,
but I've never tried it.
After all, patients like you
are too rare.
Hold on, Lu Xin,
what do you mean by that?
You want to use me
as your test subject again?
Have you forgotten
what happened to my beard last time?
What I gave you was just tonics
that were good for your health,
totally harmless.
Besides, I'm not giving you
any medicine this time.
How about this?
Why don't you tell me
more stories instead?
No more stories.
If you're not willing, forget it.
Perhaps one day you'll wake up
with your memories back.
Maybe tomorrow,
next year,
decades from now,
or centuries later.
Finish your drink and leave.
So what is this method?
Clear your mind of stray thoughts,
fix your eyes on it,
and imagine yourself
getting drowsier,
and drowsier,
and drowsier.
Well? Sleepy yet?
If you are, sleep.
Not at all.
Don't talk.
You'll get sleepy soon.
W-Wait a sec.
What is it?
Did you remember something?
Are you alright?
You can't hold your liquor at all.
It's so late.
Why are you still up?
I had a few drinks with you earlier
and then went out to sober up.
How come you were gone for 2 hours
and came back smelling even more of wine?
Is it that bad?
Lu Xin made me drink.
I refused at first.
I reminded her
that she had training tomorrow morning,
but she insisted I drink.
She said I looked upset
and offered to drink with me.
I said I really couldn't,
but she said I had to.
I...
I couldn't refuse her,
so I had a few drinks with her.
You nitpicked about my manners
in every way
and then went out drinking yourself.
How shameful.
As my teacher,
shouldn't you be setting an example?
Yes.
I was wrong.
As your teacher,
I should...
What did you say?
Mr. Jin'an,
am I serving you tea
in a proper manner?
It's proper.
Your request was sudden,
but the proper etiquette
must still be observed.
These 5 items
symbolize diligence in learning,
dedicated teaching,
good fortune,
success in examinations,
and perfection in virtue.
But I recall
that the traditional student's gifts
include 6 things.
Dried meat is too expensive.
All right.
You're not just an ordinary teacher to me,
so my gifts for you
cannot be ordinary either.
The Crown Prince is coming to Lucheng
to reward the troops.
I'll be busy for a while.
This bead contains my blood.
When I'm not around,
you can use it in emergencies.
Why did you hurt yourself again?
You've risked your life for me
so many times.
Compared to that,
this is nothing.
Your Highness,
the Crown Prince has entered Liangzhou.
He'll be in Lucheng within 2 days.
What's the situation
along the way?
All the prefectures
are loyal to Prince Li.
Even if the Crown Prince wants
to win them over, he can't.
But before he set off,
he met with Li Wei's son,
Li Ting.
I planned to let him off for the sake
of our brotherly bond,
but he just can't behave himself,
fixated on winning the Li family over.
If he had both the prime minister
and the Li family on his side,
he'd be unstoppable.
As long as he's breathing, he's a threat.
Our men are already in place,
waiting for your word.
Go tell them
to make it clean and quick.
Yes.
Don't blame me
for being a ruthless brother.
If you must blame someone,
blame yourself.
[Lucheng]
General,
the Crown Prince sent word earlier,
telling you to wait in camp.
Why did you still come out to welcome him?
His Highness doesn't want to trouble us—
that is his kindness.
But if I hadn't come,
it'd be seen as disrespectful
to the future ruler.
But aren't you
and the Crown Prince old friends?
Why care so much about formalities?
Li Shuang, general of the Changfeng Army,
welcomes the Crown Prince.
Shuang,
didn't I tell you
to wait at your residence?
Why did you come all the way out here?
Get up.
Your Highness came from afar.
I had to welcome you personally,
or I'd be breaking protocol.
You've all waited long.
Soldiers,
your health comes first.
Please rise.
We'll set out at once.
Your Highness,
you've had a long journey.
Everything's arranged
at the post station.
Welcome the Crown Prince into the city!
Thank you
for being so considerate, General.
Protect His Highness!
Move!
Don't kill him!
If they're all dead,
how will we investigate later?
Shuang!
Your Highness!
Send for the army physician.
Let's hurry to the post station.
We don't know who the assassins are.
The post station may not be safe.
Help His Highness onto the horse.
We're going back to my residence.
Your Highness,
we were eager to protect you
and acted rashly.
Please forgive us.
Lock down all information.
No one is to hear of this.
Yes.
You're hurt?
What happened?
I'll explain later.
I'll get His Highness treated first.
Though the wound is deep,
thankfully, it missed the vitals.
But you need proper rest and care
to completely recover.
You may leave.
Your Highness.
Shuang,
what are you doing?
I failed to protect you
and let you get injured.
Please punish me.
Why should I punish you?
Look, I'm right here in one piece.
Protecting you
is my duty,
but at that critical moment,
you saved me instead.
It was my fault that you got injured.
I owed you.
Of course I had to save you.
Your Highness.
These past 3 years,
have you been well?
Your Highness.
Thank you for your concern.
All is well…
in Lucheng.
Shuang,
it's just the two of us here.
Do you still need to be so formal?
You can push me away,
and I know the reason why.
But for these 3 years,
I've wanted to come to see you every day.
Yet I couldn't.
Your Highness,
walls have ears.
If someone overheard,
it could tarnish your reputation.
Earlier at your residence,
I saw a man.
As I recall, you've only ever kept
female attendants by your side.
Your Highness,
that man
once saved my life.
He had no family,
so I took him in
and gave him a job.
I've heard things have been
unstable along the border.
When it comes to household staff,
it's best to use people you know well.
Yes.
Summon him.
I want to meet him.
Yes.
Shuang told me
she found you in the woods
and brought you back.
What were you doing
in the wilderness?
I was attacked
by a beast in the mountains
and blacked out.
People in Lucheng are kind and friendly.
I never thought
even the wild beasts here
were somewhat kind too.
It attacked you
but didn't eat you.
If Your Highness doubts me,
you can go into the mountains
and see for yourself.
Jin'an!
Don't talk nonsense.
Your Highness,
Jin'an hasn't been here for a long time
and hasn't learned proper manners.
It's fine.
Did you just say
his name is Jin'an?
Yes.
It means lasting peace
and prosperity in Taijin.
It's a good name.
You gave it to him?
Yes.
Since General Li has
high expectations for you,
you should behave yourself,
serve her diligently,
and learn a servant's manners
as soon as possible
so she won't be let down.
I'm afraid you've misunderstood.
I'm not a servant
who takes orders from just anyone.
General Li has served me tea
as my student.
I'm her exclusive personal teacher,
staying with her and teaching her
arts and etiquette.
Jin'an!
Your Highness,
Jin'an meant no offense.
Please forgive him.
You're still injured.
Get up.
We grew up together.
If he's your teacher,
then in my presence,
there's no need for such formalities.
Life in the army is dull and hard.
Music, chess, calligraphy, and painting
do help ease the boredom.
By the way, Shuang,
have you read the biographies
I sent you?
Your Highness, if there's nothing else,
I'll take General Li back
to dress her wounds.
You…
Shuang,
I know
you have feelings for me.
As long as you say yes,
I'll go to Father tomorrow
to revoke the decree
and cancel my engagement to the Ji girl.
Your Highness, don't come in.
It could stir gossip.
I've been
keeping this hairpin for you.
Now that Your Highness is getting married,
I should return it to you.
This hairpin
was left to me by my mother.
I gave it to you.
Do you still not understand?
Do you truly mean
to cut off all ties with me?
He is the Crown Prince.
You provoked him again and again.
If he's truly angered,
no one can protect you.
He caused you to get injured,
so he's at fault.
If you hadn't returned alive today,
then forget the Crown Prince—
I'd even destroy the entire Taijin court
to avenge you.
Jin'an!
I'm sorry.
I was just worried about you.
Don't ever say
such reckless things again.
Also,
during this period,
stay away from the Crown Prince
to avoid trouble.
I'm a general of Taijin.
My country, my family,
and the Changfeng Army—
I'll risk my life to protect them all.
Protecting the Crown Prince
is my duty as well.
You want to protect everyone,
but have you
thought about protecting yourself?
My life
belongs to Taijin and the Li family.
I'm ready to die at any time.
What about me?
There's a bond between us.
Have you thought about what I should do
if you die?
[General's Residence]
Your Highness,
everything has been taken care of.
Rest assured.
Is your injury serious?
It's nothing.
Your Highness,
Prince Li has always seen you
as a thorn in his side.
I never expected him
to be so bold this time.
You arrived in Lucheng
and were attacked right away.
In the capital,
bound by Father's authority,
he wouldn't dare go too far.
Now that I'm out here alone,
it's the perfect chance to strike.
I just didn't expect
he'd be so impatient
and dare to attempt
a brazen assassination.
I believe
the more impatient Prince Li is,
the more likely he'll trip himself up.
But there's one thing I don't understand:
Your Highness is of royal blood.
Not punishing General Li
is already showing her mercy.
Why did you take that blade for her?
It all started because of me.
I told Shuang not to come receive me
precisely because I didn't want her
to get hurt.
But she came anyway.
Three years ago,
I let her down.
Now that we've met again,
I can't let her get hurt for me again.
But Your Highness,
Prince Li is powerful
and well-connected now.
Your relationship with General Li
has long been a threat to him.
If…
General Li will surely
become your weakness.
To my brother,
my past, my present,
and everyone around me
are all my weaknesses.
So what is there to fear?
[Imperial Palace of Taijin]
Your Highness, please.
Father, you summoned me.
May I ask the reason?
Father, please don't be mad.
With heavenly tribulation imminent,
you actually tried
to assassinate the Crown Prince.
I knew nothing of the tribulation.
I only wanted to ease your burdens.
Please believe me.
You fool.
The sacrificial ritual has strict rules.
If he dies before the tribulation,
the formation will collapse.
I was ignorant.
I deserve nothing less than death.
I've always valued you,
but you're too impatient
and never learn caution.
How can I rely on you?
Father, you're visionary.
I will remember your teachings.
The Bureau of Astronomy reported
that Mars will soon appear near Antares.
Lucheng is the best site
for the sacrificial ritual.
I'll give you a chance
to make up for your mistake.
Set out at once for Lucheng
and assist in the ritual.
On the day of the tribulation,
bring the Crown Prince to the altar
and cut his heart out.
Then it's all done.
Remember—
until then,
there must not be the slightest mistake.
I will do my utmost.
But what if
the Crown Prince refuses to die
as a sacrifice?
You're his elder brother.
You'll have to give him a push.
I'm giving this dagger to you.
It carries my authority.
He dares not disobey.
Yes, Father.
He actually survived.
What incredible luck.
I heard he was slashed
and barely survived.
He truly has a fate strong enough
to take the tribulation.
I underestimated him.
So what should
we do next?
This brother of mine
appears gentle and modest
but is actually calculating,
always opposing me.
This trip to Lucheng—
we'll settle both old
and new scores.
Your Highness, now is the perfect time
to go to Lucheng.
Your Highness,
His Majesty's head eunuch, Jin Bao,
has been quite devoted to your cause.
He replaced the golden pills
with poison made from aconite,
and His Majesty never got suspicious
after taking it.
By the looks of things,
the day of a power shift is near.
Father's days must be numbered.
Otherwise, he wouldn't be
so desperate for a sacrifice
to extend his life.
I don't believe in astrology,
but just in case—
we absolutely cannot let the Crown Prince
actually die on the altar.
His Majesty definitely
has eyes and ears in Lucheng.
If we act too early, wouldn't it...
Do you think I haven't thought of that?
Su Muyang's life
can be spared until the day of the ritual.
Just kill him before he gets on the altar
and then throw his body up there.
By the time I return to the capital,
Father will have succumbed to the poison,
and I will be able to legitimately
ascend the throne.
To be the Crown Prince
has never been my goal.
If I'm to be anything,
I'll be the supreme one—
the ruler of the nation.
Attention!
His Majesty has spoken.
The Changfeng Army has guarded the border
and defeated enemies,
making outstanding military achievements.
His Majesty is greatly pleased
and is offering
the entire army treasures, fine silk,
and 100 jars of imperial wine
to reward your loyalty.
End of the proclamation.
The Changfeng Army thanks
His Majesty for his grace!
Long live the Emperor!
Long live the Crown Prince!
General is here.
General.
General, here's to you.
To you.
Drink up, brothers!
General, here's to you.
General.
Good wine! Fill my glass.
Drink up!
Fill it up!
Good wine! Drink!
Come on, fill it to the brim!
Cheers!
Come on, drink!
-General.
Drink to your heart's content!
Li Shuang of the Changfeng Army
requests an audience
with the Crown Prince.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Please rise.
There are no outsiders here.
No need for such formalities.
Shuang,
what brings you here?
Your Highness has not fully recovered
but personally rewarded the army.
It's truly a blessing
for the Changfeng Army.
I must thank you in person.
Also, this...
It's the finest wound salve,
a gift from a renowned
physician friend of mine.
It works wonders for sword wounds.
No wonder you're distant with me.
I've missed so much
of your life.
Three years have passed in a flash.
Here at the border,
you've made new friends.
I'm glad you have.
Her name is Lu Xin.
She saved me when I was injured.
She's a close friend
to whom I'm indebted.
If you're willing,
tell me more, will you?
I've been fine
these 3 years at the border.
Besides Lu Xin,
I've made another friend
called Jin'an.
Though I found him and took him in,
he's saved me many times from danger.
He didn't mean
to offend Your Highness earlier.
I'm willing
to accept any punishment for him.
I've never cared much for etiquette.
Why would I hold it against him?
The more trustworthy
the people by your side,
the more at ease I can be.
Thank you for your understanding.
You haven't fully recovered yet.
You should head back and get some rest.
I still have
military matters to attend to.
I'll take my leave now.
Your Highness, it seems
General Li still cares about you.
Otherwise, she wouldn't have
come in person to give you the salve.
I'll certainly
be nice to her friends.
But seeing her so careful with me
makes me really sad.
Have you investigated
Jin'an's identity?
There's little information about him.
Nothing seems suspicious.
It's said that when General Li found him,
he had already suffered a head injury
and lost his memory.
Besides,
he was the one who killed Huo Du.