[Shadow Love]
[Episode 19]
[Sixu Clinic]
I'll first slow down
the flow of blood and qi
in Your Highness with acupuncture.
I need some time to figure out
the one last ingredient
of this poison.
Your Highness,
sorry for the discomfort.
This is going to hurt a bit.
The therapy has provided some relief.
I'm feeling better now.
You two may leave.
This assassination attempt
was not arranged by me.
I only bribed the assassin.
Despite the thorough plan I made,
an accident still happened.
Will you forgive me?
As a humble subject
of Your Highness,
who am I to give forgiveness?
I know...
over the past 3 years,
you've always blamed me for failing you.
But, Shuang,
how do you know
I didn't beg my father
for you?
Father,
my heart belongs to another woman.
I can't marry Chancellor Ji's daughter.
So, Father,
please withdraw the decree.
A king must keep his word.
I can't revoke that command
just because you say so.
Marriage is a lifelong commitment.
Don't I even
have the right to marry
the woman I love?
You would have that right,
if you were a commoner's son.
But you're the Crown Prince.
Even your marriage has to
serve the kingdom's interests.
Father,
I'm neither capable nor knowledgeable.
People are not convinced of my competence.
I'm hardly qualified
for the role of Crown Prince.
If being the Crown Prince means
I must give up on my beloved woman,
then
I beg for your imperial edict
to relieve me from this position.
You're throwing away the throne
just for a woman?
I'm well aware
that you're in love with Li Shuang.
But don't forget that you're my son
and my liege.
You don't get to decide
your future spouse
or your own dismissal.
But, Father...
A father's love runs deep.
If you defy my orders,
I won't kill you,
but I will definitely kill Li Shuang.
As a royal member,
I have to do things against my own will.
I failed you
only to protect you.
For me,
that decision
also tore my heart apart.
Prince Annan?
Prince Annan...
Who's there?
That man is clearly Prince Annan.
Why is he
with the Crown Prince of Taijin?
I must bring this message
back to Yao State.
Who are you?
After following you guys
all the way here,
I still can't find Jade Linglong.
What's worse,
the trail has entirely gone cold.
Why did you kill him?
Mister,
that's not a fair judgement.
There is no roof or wall around.
All the animals here
can come and go as they please,
let alone humans, don't you think?
You smell the poison
that the Crown Prince was inflicted with.
Was it you
who meant to poison His Highness?
How come you accuse me of
a new crime with each move I make?
Can't you be reasonable?
You must come with me.
If you're innocent,
you'll have your chance
to defend yourself.
I have urgent matters to attend to.
I'm done with you.
Stop it! I yield!
You're so reckless, Mister.
This hurts yourself and others.
Please refrain from doing so.
I'll go with you
to wherever you want.
The flame patterns...
He is exactly
the shadow puppet.
Your Highness,
I've never blamed you
during these 3 years.
Now,
all has been decided for us.
Let's
put the past behind.
But why?
How could we just erase
those beautiful memories?
Your Highness...
You're right, though.
My life is coming to an end.
What can I hold onto now?
It was no secret to you
that I bribed the assassin,
yet you never questioned me about it.
I don't know
why Your Highness did that,
but I have faith in you.
I believe you had your own reason
for making such a move.
My brother wanted to kill me.
I thought I could escape that fate
by bribing the assassin.
But to my surprise,
my brother already saw me through.
I had a messenger come over
to tell you not to attend the reception
because I hoped
you could stay away from this strife.
Little did I expect
that
you'd still be dragged into it in the end.
Shuang,
I know
I can't do much for you,
though I owe you a lot.
This time,
I'm finally relieved from guilt.
Your Highness.
Your Highness!
Lu Xin!
His Highness fainted.
How is he?
Shuang,
embrace yourself for the worst.
It's not a dead end yet!
Ladies,
nice to see you again.
You know each other?
What's
going on here?
An assassin appeared,
so I chased after him.
But by the time I caught up,
he had been killed.
This man was on the scene.
I also smelled the scent
of that mysterious poison on him.
Give us the antidote now.
Then I'll implore the king to spare you
from capital punishment.
Did you hear that?
You two make quite a great couple,
as you falsely accuse someone
in the exact same manner.
It's too late.
The Crown Prince is at death's door.
Even if there is an antidote,
there won't be time for it to take effect.
Arsenic.
Curculigo.
Ruojian.
Toxic toads.
Whoever poisoned him
must have nefarious motives.
How do you know the ingredients?
I can tell the formula
of any poison with a simple glimpse
of the symptoms.
Nonsense.
Except those from Wuling Mountain,
nobody in the world is able to do that.
So you're from Wuling Mountain?
In just a moment,
His Highness will be gone forever.
Instead of probing into my origins,
why not let me save his life first,
General?
Under such circumstances,
we might as well let him try.
A guiding drug of this poison
is called Snow Golden Lotus,
which carries rare toxins.
Fortunately,
everything has its antagonist.
This Icy Jade Worm of mine
specifically feeds on that lotus.
What you smelled earlier
was the scent of this worm.
Why didn't you explain it?
Did you give me a chance to speak?
How did I not?
Hold his arms! Don't let him hurt my worm.
Your Highness...
Now my worm is finally fed.
The toxins have really been cleared.
His Highness will recover
after a few days' rest.
Thank you.
Sir, for your commendable contribution,
the Crown Prince will surely
reward you when he wakes up.
It was a small favor.
Don't mention it.
How noble of you.
I'd deeply impressed.
But I'm afraid
you'll be troubled with the Crown Prince's
medication
before His Highness recovers.
If you don't mind,
why not stay a few days at my place?
It can also be a chance for me
to repay your generous help.
General, young though you are,
you're already an expert in telling lies.
You're not being hospitable,
but seeking
an excuse to interrogate me.
That's right.
You'll be interrogated.
It's non-negotiable.
The grand General's Residence
must be magnificent.
Not everyone gets to see it.
Given your cordial invitation,
General,
I'd like to accept this kind offer.
What's that guy's background?
Shuang,
you're a general,
and Jin'an is too aggressive.
Why not let me
talk to that man?
Sounds nice.
Have Cuiyun accompany you.
Stay cautious.
This way, sir.
Miss Li appears rough.
But who would know
she actually has such good taste?
General Li told us
that you're a distinguished guest,
to whom we must offer the best service.
You're not needed here.
Go get some rest.
May I have a look
at your worm?
It bites.
It really amazes me
that you're from Wuling Mountain.
Since we both practice medicine,
why not exchange
opinions on our expertise more often?
You must be thirsty.
Have some tea.
Are you really going to stay here?
Why not?
I've never had a stay
at the General's Residence.
All seems fresh to me.
What's more,
I'm an honored guest here now.
I wonder if you're genuinely naive
or just pretending to be.
They call you an honored guest
only to sugarcoat
their real purpose of confining you here.
If the Crown Prince's conditions worsen,
you'll be the first one to be held liable.
The silver lining is,
I can put in a good word
for you with Shuang
and plead for leniency.
Then all problems will go away.
However, as you know,
I am a renowned physician after all.
Acting as someone's advocate
is beneath me.
How about you teach me
some of your medical skills?
Then we'll be even. What do you think?
Miss, is this
a threat?
You can put it that way.
Medical practitioners
must have moral probity.
I'm impressed by the fact
that you completely ignore
the code of ethics, Miss Lu.
You're the one lacking morals.
To be honest,
I slipped deadly poison
into the tea you just drank.
If you want to live,
you'll have to ask me for the antidote.
You call that speck of dust
poison?
In fact, Miss Lu,
don't you feel
itchy and prickly in the throat,
and pain in the stomach now?
Not at all.
Are you not feeling sick?
How despicable of you.
Let's see...
Let's see how long it'll take...
b-before you collapse...
Miss Lu,
when you poison someone next time,
try not using laxatives again.
Master,
Mo Yin is staying at
the General's Residence now.
What a resourceful junior I have.
He managed to enter
the impenetrable General's Residence
with such ease.
The credit goes to
your marvelous strategy, Master.
Mo Yin has become part of the game now.
But I'm afraid...
the Empress Dowager's patience
is wearing thin.
What should
we do next?
Qiao is remarkably strong.
Although I managed to weather through
all adversities by transformation,
Shuang would be hurt
every time I resorted to
the supernatural strength.
It'll be perfect
if I can protect Shuang
without changing forms.
Thanks.
Qiao,
you have extraordinary skills
and limitless strength.
I am
truly in awe.
Now that you know I'm good,
you'd better go away.
Or you might get hurt
and have no one to blame.
I have an idea.
Look,
you're an amazing martial fighter.
Could you be my tutor?
Think about it.
If I'm half as formidable as you are,
the General's Residence
will be much safer, won't it?
Are you doing this
to protect the General's Residence,
or just to please the general?
What...
What's the difference?
The Crown Prince is visiting Lucheng.
The general is with him all the time.
Your provocative moves aren't working now.
So you're looking to learn new tricks?
Look how frivolous he is.
You must've said it right.
A rat! Qiao!
Qiao!
It's okay.
I'm not afraid.
Indeed.
You all have excellent skills,
but you're not vigilant enough.
I stood back there for a long time,
yet you didn't notice me at all.
How about this?
Let's make a trade.
You teach me martial skills,
and I'll instruct you
on sharpening your 5 senses.
Okay.
The first lesson for you
is to defeat me.
Help...
He sure knows how to keep his cool.
He shows no curiosity
about his origins at all.
Come in.
You're in luck, Mister.
I've specially brewed
a nice pot of tea for you.
Why not sit down
and enjoy it with me?
It seems you've anticipated my visit.
You didn't plan for
the assassination attempt
or poison the Crown Prince,
but you oddly appeared
beside that dead assassin.
What exactly are you up to?
Don't be so tense, Mister.
I'm interested in no one,
but you
and the flame patterns on you.
You're thirsty for blood
and loyal to your master,
with the abilities to transform
and heal automatically.
Am I right
about all that?
A shadow puppet's power
is really something to be reckoned with.
You claim to be from Wuling Mountain.
You also know perfectly well about
my peculiar traits.
So, I'm sure this state I'm in
is somewhat related to you.
Is it correct?
Don't be so rude.
Since you know of Wuling Mountain,
haven't you also heard of
the treasure of it,
named Jade Linglong?
Are you saying
these anomalies are associated with
the Jade Linglong in me?
Yes.
It is both a medicine and a poison.
Once it is planted inside a human,
this person
will become a shadow puppet,
with infinite strength
and self-healing ability.
But Jade Linglong's power
is sustained by blood.
The blood provider
becomes the blood master.
The blood pact
formed between the puppet and the master
makes the former
completely obedient to the latter,
with an instinctive urge for intimacy.
Being well aware of
Jade Linglong's terrifying power,
those in Wuling Mountain
made a rule
that this item must be strictly guarded.
Unexpectedly, years ago,
Jade Linglong was stolen.
We searched extensively
but couldn't find it,
until recently,
we heard a man in black
showed up in Lucheng.
That was what led us here.
If I'm not mistaken,
Miss Li
is your blood master, right?
The blood pact between me and Li Shuang
was formed entirely by accident.
I understand that, of course.
I bet the person who stole Jade Linglong
intended to turn you into a shadow puppet
for his or her own use.
However, something went wrong.
You lost control, fled,
and took Li Shuang as your master
by mistake.
If what you're saying is true,
this person will go after Shuang
in order to regain control
of Jade Linglong.
You've lost all your memories.
Shouldn't you be curious
about your own origins first?
I was curious before.
But now...
My home is
wherever Shuang is.
It's good enough
if I can protect her for a lifetime
with my current abilities.
I'm afraid
it's just wishful thinking on your part.
The anomalies happening to you
are still evolving till this day.
Can you deliver any lifelong commitment?
As Jade Linglong merges with you,
it'll gradually corrode your will.
Eventually,
you'll completely lose control
and become a killing machine
without feelings.
When that happens,
not only will you forget Li Shuang,
but also probably hurt her,
or even kill her.
I'd sooner end my own life
than cause any harm to her.
I understand your overconfidence,
since the worst is yet to happen.
But I doubt if you can take your own life
with Jade Linglong in your body.
That aside, I have a question.
Every time
you released the power of Jade Linglong,
did Li Shuang
feel unwell and fatigue?
Her blood and qi
are the very source
of Jade Linglong's power.
The deeper
you integrate with Jade Linglong,
the worse her health will be.
Even without you killing her,
she'll inevitably perish
due to depletion of blood and qi.
How is she?
How long have you been experiencing
these dizzy spells?
Probably...
since the Battle of Lucheng.
You're suffering from melancholy,
combined with deficiency
in both qi and blood.
Shuang!
If this continues,
there will be serious consequences.
You really need to recuperate properly.
Leave with me
for the removal of Jade Linglong.
Only in that way
will she and you
stand a chance of survival.
You think this supernatural nonsense
can fool me?
Overestimating yourself, aren't you?
I saw your good nature,
so I decided to tell you the truth
instead of pushing you into anything.
But you misinterpreted what I said
with that petty mind of yours.
Suppose you did tell me the truth—
I swear
I won't transform anymore,
or use the power
of Jade Linglong.
It seems
you've finally got the gist.
In our previous fight,
you were already much stronger
than ordinary people
even without transforming.
This is proof that Jade Linglong
is becoming a whole with your body.
Before long,
you'll entirely
morph into a shadow puppet
that can harness
Jade Linglong's power anytime
without pressing acupoints
to induce transformation.
When that comes true,
every simple movement of yours
will cause harm
to your blood master.
The facts are right in front of you,
yet you wouldn't accept them.
Or is it
because you simply refuse to admit
the close bonds
between you and Li Shuang now
are merely attributed to
Jade Linglong's effects?
Provoking me will get you nowhere.
Besides,
Jade Linglong
originated from Wuling Mountain,
which you're part of.
So you're not innocent.
Unless...
Unless you find
the one who started all this,
I have no reason to believe you.
In addition,
I'm sure you're aware
that the power I have now
is strong enough to protect Shuang
and to crush you.
So, rid your mind of shady ideas.
Do not wag your tongue
at Li Shuang.
If you're in for a losing battle,
I'll oblige you to the end.
What a stubborn man.
The firewood is ready.
Send it to Cuiyun.
Got it, Qiao.
The changes of my power
had better be kept secret.
Jin'an...
Qiao,
Jin'an is here!
Why sneak around?
Qiao.
Don't try to butter me up.
Did you do your morning practice?
He didn't.
I saw it.
The martial training
is just too arduous.
I don't think I can keep it up.
I'm terribly sorry.
Goodbye.
Fine, I'll stay. Alright?
Why the rush?
The key to martial practice
is perseverance.
Once the process begins,
you can't quit halfway.
That's right.
Beat him up!
Yeah. Go at him!
Dodging?
Strike him!
As expected of the elite guardians
of the General's Residence,
you all started your martial practice
in early morning.
Miss, you're full of vigor and strength.
I'm impressed.
I...
You're not bad yourself.
The air is filled with spring chills,
yet you're strolling with a fan.
Aren't you worried to catch a cold?
I happen to know a bit about martial arts.
Jin'an, if you don't mind,
shall we have a friendly match?
I'm not interested.
What do you want?
Are you not fighting back
out of fear of giving yourself away?
I'd love to see
how long your disguise can last.
Qiao!
Though you're the general's guest,
as an outsider,
you're not allowed to bully Jin'an,
since he's one of us
on the general's team.
Honored guest,
watch your behavior.
You're right, Miss.
That was rude of me.
I shall take my leave.
My back...
Jin'an,
are you alright?
Qiao, Ling,
despite your harsh words,
you're big softies.
Why that gaze?
Pick up the firewood
and send it to the woodshed.
Get a move on!
General,
word from the capital
says Prince Li is on the way.
He will reach Lucheng
in just a few days.
That assassination attempt
on the Crown Prince was a serious matter.
I knew it'd be revealed sooner or later.
Why didn't
His Majesty assign
someone else than Prince Li
to ascertain the truth?
General,
does His Majesty really not see
the hidden reality?
It's a power struggle.
What's between His Majesty and the princes
is beyond our understanding.
Now that Prince Li
is coming here with a fanfare,
we might as well get ready
to welcome His Highness.
As for the rest,
we'll do what we can
under specific circumstances.
Yes.