[Shadow Love]
[Episode 20]
Shuang.
You'd go drown your sorrows alone
whenever you were upset.
So this time,
I've warmed up the wine
for you in advance.
How did you know I was upset?
Didn't I tell you
my senses are extraordinary?
I heard everything
you and Ji Ran discussed
in the side hall.
Can't you control your senses?
You were talking with the door open.
It didn't seem to be that private.
Besides,
even without this ability,
I could've heard everything
just by passing by.
Besides
enhanced senses of
smell and hearing,
do you have any other special abilities?
Can you
see through walls?
Get your mind out of the gutter.
I know not to look at what I shouldn't.
My abilities are just enhanced.
I don't know magic.
I can't see through things.
That's a relief.
Anyway, it's clear
Prince Li wants the Crown Prince dead
since he hired assassins
and even poisoned the blade.
Luckily, the Crown Prince survived.
But now Prince Li's coming to Lucheng.
Are you worried
he'll harm the Crown Prince again?
Prince Li is high-ranking and powerful.
The position of Crown Prince
originally belonged to him.
Holding this grudge for three years,
I'm sure
he'll seize any opportunity
to eliminate him.
The Li family and Changfeng Army
have always been your Achilles heels.
Crown Prince must be protected,
and Prince Li can't be offended.
Rather than walking on eggshells,
why don't you
entrust the Crown Prince to me?
To you?
I can't guarantee I'll get along well
with the Crown Prince,
but I'm sure
I can protect him.
Do you have other concerns?
The matter of the man in black
has reached the capital.
Crown Prince hasn't mentioned it,
but I still feel uneasy.
Actually,
besides my enhanced senses,
my strength has also changed.
I no longer need to
rely on
the Lingxu acupoint to fight well.
And it seems
my strength keeps growing.
I once appeared as the man in black
to avoid your suspicion.
Now that you know who I am,
I don't need to hide anymore.
The man in black
will probably never appear again;
just Jin'an.
Your bodily changes are so unpredictable.
If left unchecked,
could you end up hurting yourself?
Mo Yin is from Wuling Mountain.
Since he cured Crown Prince of poisoning,
perhaps
he can also unravel
the secret of your body.
I'll go ask him.
I know you worry about me.
But actually, I've already
asked him myself.
He said...
He said
if I keep my power under control,
I'll be fine.
What about you?
Have you taken the tonic
Lu Xin prescribed
for your qi and blood?
How have you
been feeling?
If you can control your power well,
I shouldn't suffer from backlash.
Besides,
since returning from Cang Mountain,
I've been very healthy.
That's good.
Did Shuang get you
to come escort me?
Does it matter?
If it was Shuang's idea,
I need to know the reason.
If you took it upon yourself,
all the more do I need
to know your motive.
Prince Li will arrive in Lucheng soon.
From today on,
I'll personally attend to Your Highness.
Are you scared?
Understandably so.
You survived
assassination attempts and poisoning.
By now,
you must be well aware of
why Prince Li is coming to Lucheng.
I'm the Crown Prince.
If Prince Li wants to kill me,
those around me will be in danger.
By being my bodyguard,
aren't you afraid of death?
If you die,
the one who suffers won't be me
but Shuang.
By protecting you,
I'm safeguarding Shuang's peace.
Besides,
it's not that easy
to kill me.
Quite confident, aren't you?
Prince Li is
surrounded by skilled fighters.
What makes you so sure you can protect me?
Last time, you were willing to die
for Shuang.
That was when I knew
you really like her.
Since we're both serious about her,
there must be a winner.
Until everything is settled,
Your Highness must stay alive.
Your Highness hasn't fully recovered.
Be careful not to catch a cold.
Your Highness,
are you still troubled about Prince Li?
You're of noble status.
No matter how bold Prince Li is,
he wouldn't dare act openly,
especially here
in the General's Residence,
with General Li present.
Huai'en.
We've been in Lucheng for days now.
Have you heard anything
about the man in black?
Since defeating the Yao Army,
that man seems to have vanished.
Have you discovered something?
Isn't it odd that
he accomplished such a great deed,
yet there's no trace of him
and even no mention of him?
Could he be
hiding in Changfeng Army,
or perhaps here?
Don't make
baseless claims.
Noted.
Over there!
Father is here.
I'm so scared.
Don't be scared.
With Father here,
you have nothing to fear.
Don't be scared.
[Lucheng]
I wanted to keep a low profile
on this trip.
This is rather extravagant.
Your Highness has had
a long, tiring journey,
Ensuring your comfort
is just my duty.
General Li is still waiting for you
at the post house.
Should I send someone
to inform her?
I'm tired.
[Liu Yu]
[Governor of Lucheng, Taijin]
Then please rest well, Your Highness.
I'll take my leave.
Is Your Highness
planning to meet Li Shuang in person?
I must find out for myself
what
she really thinks.
It doesn't matter
if the Crown Prince is
still alive.
He'll have to meet his end eventually.
If he's dead,
it'll save me considerable effort.
By then,
even if Li Shuang refuses to surrender,
she'll still be implicated.
What if the Crown Prince isn't dead?
Then it depends on Li Shuang's attitude.
In the worst-case scenario,
we must make them understand that
the Li family's backing of Crown Prince
is useless.
[General's Residence]
Unaware of Your Highness's arrival,
I failed to welcome you properly.
Please forgive me.
Last time, due to my negligence,
I kept you waiting at the post house.
Do you hold a grudge against me?
I wouldn't dare.
When news of assassination attempts
on Crown Prince reached the capital,
the court was in turmoil,
and memorials
impeaching the Changfeng Army
piled up like mountains.
But considering the Li family's
generations of meritorious service,
I personally intercepted them all.
Just to
do you a favor, General Li.
If someday
I need your assistance,
I hope you'll support me wholeheartedly.
When the time comes, don't forget
that I was the one
who preserved your life
and your family's honor.
Greetings, Brother.
I didn't know you were coming.
Sorry for the late greeting.
Please forgive me.
We're brothers.
No need for such courtesy.
You've lost weight, Crown Prince.
Are your wounds healing?
Has your poison been fully neutralized?
Thanks to you,
I'm out of danger now.
That's good.
General Li and I were just
discussing
the assassination attempt on you.
How's the investigation going, General Li?
Your Highness,
the assassins' identities
haven't been fully confirmed,
but we've gathered substantial evidence.
I believe the truth
will come to light soon.
Then, we'll report every detail,
however minor, to the court.
But I've heard that
on the day of the incident,
all the assassins
were killed on the spot
by Crown Prince's guards.
If they'd arrested someone alive,
the investigation
wouldn't be so difficult.
Crown Prince's guards
are so inept,
unable to protect their master
nor make proper arrests.
Baoxing.
Yes.
My guards have followed me for many years;
all absolutely loyal.
Don't be naive.
If they're just loyal, that's fine,
but what if someone harbors ill intentions
and conspires with rebels?
How would I explain to Father then?
I've brought quite a few men with me
this time.
I'll leave some clever and reliable ones
here by your side.
As your elder brother,
I'll feel more at ease this way.
Help!
Crown Prince!
I haven't seen you before.
When did Crown Prince recruit you?
Your Highness,
I serve the Li family;
temporarily assigned
to serve the Crown Prince.
But didn't they say
only female servants work
at the General's Residence?
It's understandable though.
Stationed at the border,
General Li must have many lonely nights.
Just as men traditionally have
multiple wives and concubines,
General Li now has a wife
and a concubine.
How delightful!
Your Highness.
I, Li Shuang, am solely devoted to
protecting the homeland
and nothing else.
Please—
Your Highness is naturally brilliant
and all-knowing.
I am
truly in awe of you.
You're a clever one, huh?
Go on.
How am I so brilliant?
Just now, Your Highness mentioned
the Crown Prince's poisoning.
However,
the public only knows about
the assassination attempt
and not his poisoning.
This must mean
Your Highness has
exceptional perception.
Of course,
with your meticulous mind
and your love
for your brother,
it makes sense that
you noticed his pale lips and weak qi,
and logically inferred
that he was poisoned.
General Li.
I heard Crown Prince was poisoned
and on the brink of death
but was saved by a miracle doctor.
Bring this person
to dine with us.
Go invite him.
I'm not going.
After freeloading
at the General's Residence for so long,
surely they can ask you for a favor.
Freeloading?
I've moved all my belongings here.
I see patients
and write prescriptions all day
and brew medicine all night.
My delicate skin
has been ruined by the heat and overwork!
I'd really love to leave.
Would your general let me go?
Don't waste your time.
Bureaucratic gatherings
filled with fake niceties
are beneath me
and my refined elegance.
The situation is urgent
and delicate.
After I help Shuang through this crisis...
I'll consider your proposal
to return to Wuling Mountain with you.
On one condition:
you must behave yourself.
In my eyes,
you are no different from
my medicine utensils.
Who are you to order me around?
This outfit is exquisite,
while this one's elegant.
Which do you think is more appropriate
for the event?
I've heard that
in our previous battle with Yao State,
a heroic man in black swooped in to help
defeat the Yao Army.
Mr. Mo Yin,
since you're skilled in detoxification,
could you be
that very man in black?
Is that an insult, Your Highness?
That man masked his face
with black armor,
so he must be extremely hideous
and ashamed of his face.
I'm drop-dead gorgeous.
How could he be
mentioned in the same breath as me?
You're amusing,
very much to my liking.
Speaking of the battle at Lucheng,
Li Zhangyi was ordered to supervise
but neglected his duties
and nearly caused a disaster.
But General Li, in your memorial,
you accused him of treason.
May I ask if that was an exaggeration?
Your Highness.
I merely
reported the facts.
That Li Zhangyi was
putting on airs
in the name of Your Highness.
I didn't want your reputation
to be tarnished
because others mistake you
as covering up for him.
I didn't expect you to be
so considerate of me.
I've really failed to
appreciate your kindness.
It's only right that I offer you a toast.
The life of a warrior is
brutal and harsh,
yet you still have such fair skin,
outshining my pampered concubines.
Your Highness!
Your fine clothes are stained,
undermining your dignity.
You should get changed.
Those uninvolved should vacate the room.
We'll take our leave.
I told you
such impulsivity would
harm others and yourself.
Regain composure
and control the Jade Linglong—
Jin'an!
Calm down!
When the shadow puppet goes berserk,
it truly loses all sense of rationality.
No way.
Why don't I remember anything?
At the banquet just now,
if I hadn't stopped you
for fear of exposing the secret
of Wuling Mountain,
I'm afraid everyone in that room
would have died on the spot.
There's no more room for delay or excuses.
Today,
you must leave with me.
No.
I can't.
Shuang is still in danger.
I can't abandon her.
You still don't get it?
Right now,
you're her greatest threat.
Jin'an.
What happened just now?
Was it because of that flame pattern?
You're bleeding!
It's because of me.
I'm sorry.
I lost control in my rage...
and hurt you again.
I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
Although Prince Li is domineering,
he'll take Changfeng Army into account
and won't go too far.
I understand you're resentful.
But now isn't
the right time to turn against Prince Li.
A little self-inflicted injury
to rekindle old feelings
and win hearts.
Well played, Brother.
Though I'm not gifted,
I'm not one to court death.
The poison I'd been given
is extremely rare.
With your power,
there's nothing you can't know.
I'm sure you
understand the situation
better than anyone.
Is that so?
Everything I have is bestowed by Father.
If you have any doubts,
you may plead your case before Father
and let him make the final judgment.
You worthless dog!
If Prince Li were hurt,
could you bear the consequences?
I'm sorry I wasn't sturdy enough
and startled Your Highness.
Please spare my life, Your Highness!
Have mercy, Your Highness!
I beg for your mercy!
Your Highness,
in this world,
the greatest danger is
falling from great heights.
Nothing's more reliable
than your own family.
In that case,
the most suitable candidate
would be my brother.
I'll have to trouble you
to serve as my stairs, Brother.
Your Highness,
the Crown Prince is of noble status.
Would it be appropriate?
You have a point.
In that case,
you can take his place.
-Watch it—
-As your brother...
I'm willing to serve you
to my best ability.
Your Highness!
Hit the road!
Your Highness.
How preposterous
for a prince to
humiliate the Crown Prince in public.
If he keeps giving in
without fighting back,
I fear things will only get worse.
You've smashed almost everything.
Still not satisfied?
If you're not done,
keep smashing.
Your Highness.
With such a reaction,
aren't you afraid of eavesdroppers
reporting it back to Prince Li?
So what if he finds out?
Isn't this what he wants to see?
He was clearly
trying to back you into a corner.
Yet I couldn't do anything about it;
only submit to his bullying.
Your Highness.
I've led troops to battle
for many years.
No matter how uneven the odds,
I never admit defeat
until the very end.
Just like these damaged flowers,
as long as there's a glimmer of hope,
they won't simply wither away.
But Prince Li has
made thorough preparations.
He wouldn't make things easy for me.
Shuang.
Will you help me?
Your Highness,
as long as you're in my residence,
I'll do everything to protect you.
Shuang.
You're all I have now.
Don't be so courteous.
It's our duty.
Actually,
my visit to Lucheng
isn't just to reward the troops.
Father has also entrusted me
with another important matter:
to find the man in black
and bring him to meet Father.
This man in black was vital
in Changfeng Army's triumph
over the Yao Army
in the battle of Lucheng.
If such a talent
could serve the imperial court,
he'd surely
make a formidable general.
Your Highness,
the man in black is incredibly powerful,
but his whereabouts
are unpredictable,
and he never shows his face.
Finding him won't be easy.
This man is
extraordinary,
yet his identity
and allegiance
remain completely unknown.
As a general,
you didn't bother investigating him.
Shuang,
this isn't like you.
Or perhaps...
You've actually already
discovered his true identity in private?
If it weren't for the Changfeng soldiers
risking their lives
and fighting fiercely,
how could the man in black alone
have turned the tide?
So,
rather than relying on one man,
we should unite as one
and build a prosperous nation,
such that
millions of citizens will
all be like the man in black.
What does Your Highness think?
Your Highness,
I've fought alongside him,
with our lives entrusted to each other.
I haven't investigated deeply,
but I'm willing to trust him.
Very well.
I understand.
If there isn't any other matter,
we shall take our leave.
Wait.
Shuang.
Isn't today
your birthday?
If you're willing,
could I join you for a few drinks?
Thank you for your concern,
but it's been a while...
since I've celebrated my birthday.
Besides,
you haven't fully recovered,
so you shouldn't be drinking.
Please rest early.
-Shuang!
What's wrong?
I'm probably just tired.
I just need some rest.
I'll take you back.
I'll take you to your room
and then call Lu Xin.
No need to make such a fuss.
I'm fine already.
Now's not the time to put on a brave face.
This is clearly another backlash reaction.
It's all my fault
for losing control today again.
Since I promised you
to take good care of myself,
I'd keep my word.
I'm really fine now.
What's wrong?
I'm scared.
Don't worry.
You won't lose me so easily.
Actually,
I cherish myself
more than anyone else.
As a general,
I absolutely won't
allow meaningless sacrifice.
For you
and for the mission
I carry on my shoulders,
I'll stay strong and live well.
You mean
protecting Changfeng Army
and repaying Grand General Li?
Yes.
But not just that.
Do you remember
why I named you Jin'an?
"May Taijin
enjoy lasting peace."
All my life,
I've practiced martial arts,
not only to repay my father
for raising me,
but also to fulfill my own wish...
That is, for everyone
to enjoy lasting peace.
But now Taijin is
in turmoil.
If matters get out of hand,
bloodshed will be inevitable.
Over the years,
His Majesty has been
obsessed with immortality,
neglecting state affairs.
Except for border matters,
everything else
is handled by Prince Li.
If someone power-hungry
like Prince Li is given power,
he'll only desire more.
So you're willing to make an enemy of him
to protect Su Muyang.
The Emperor is incompetent,
and Prince Li is cruel;
neither is fit to rule the nation.
But the Crown Prince is different.
He is benevolent
and kind.
If we do our best to protect him,
Taijin might
still have a glimmer of hope,
and the commoners
will get to lead better lives.
So,
with so many things left to do,
I'll stay strong and live well.
Come with me.
To think there is
such beautiful scenery
in these deep mountains.
The water over there
comes from the hot springs
on the mountain,
so it's warm here all year round,
with flowers always in bloom.
How did you find this place?
When I was restless at night,
I slipped out for a walk
and chanced upon it.
What a pity
that such a picturesque place
has no visitors.
The Crown Prince said
that today's your birthday,
so I brought you here
as a birthday gift for you.
♪ Memories dye the red thread completely ♪
♪ A tiny spark burns in the heart ♪
♪ Asking the moon
if the old friend seem as at first sight ♪
♪ Silently the threads of affection pull ♪
♪ Yet they turn into
this endless longing ♪
♪ The bonds of this life
are hard to untangle ♪
Actually,
today isn't my birthday.
♪ Heaven and Earth cycle endlessly ♪
♪ In a fleeting glance,
affection lingers ♪
Today is
the anniversary of my father
bringing me back home from the streets.
♪ I wish to stay with you,
watching fate fade like smoke ♪
So...
I consider it my birthday.
All these years,
♪ Counting the days and nights ♪
I've always celebrated it alone.
♪ Gently caressing every inch of time ♪
Has your father never celebrated with you?
Father has been good to me.
♪ Traversing mountains and rivers,
never separating again ♪
He saved my life,
raised me,
and educated me with great care.
♪ No regrets in this life ♪
That's why
I can't take his kindness for granted
♪ Seeking a lifetime side by side ♪
and act like a spoiled kid.
♪ Eternity in a moment ♪
♪ Braving life and death to fulfill
the vow of growing old together ♪
♪ Staying close even through partings,
never straying far ♪
So you don't
remember your birthday.
♪ United as a song of promise ♪
Likewise, I've been a drifter,
so I don't know mine either.
♪ Encircling you and me ♪
Why don't we make today
our shared birthday?
♪ Endless longing
that cannot be expressed ♪
But birthdays are sacred;
not up to us.
What's wrong with this?
In those biographies you love,
they always say,
"We may not have been
born on the same day,"
"but I wish to
die on the same day as you."
This way,
we would be
born together,
as we'll die together.
♪ Don't ask how long the journey is ♪
♪ What fear is there
if black hair turns to grey? ♪
After we get through
these difficult times,
the sky will clear again.
♪ In other words,
my heart is complete with you ♪
And every year after,
we must celebrate our birthday
to the fullest.
Every year,
♪ The transient days go on without cease ♪
we will keep
traveling hand in hand to many places
♪ We'll always be together and watch
the fireworks in the mortal world ♪
and enjoy all the beautiful landscapes.
♪ Though past days fade like dreams,
do not forget them ♪
Year after year,
for an eternity.
♪ No regrets in this life ♪
♪ Seeking a lifetime side by side ♪
♪ Eternity in a moment ♪
♪ Braving life and death to fulfill
the vow of growing old together ♪
♪ Staying close even through partings,
never straying far ♪
♪ Our fate in this lifetime ♪
♪ Unforgettable and everlasting ♪
♪ No regrets in this life ♪
♪ Seeking a lifetime side by side ♪
♪ Eternity in a moment ♪
♪ Braving life and death to fulfill
the vow of growing old together ♪
♪ Only one person can hear my promise ♪
♪ It echoes for thousands of years ♪
♪ I hope this love will never change ♪
♪ I'll stay by your side ♪