Are you that
old man who sells books?
Am I that ugly?
Lu Sinian,
long time no see.
You've seen it.
Don't you like it?
That recurring dream of mine,
is it your doing?
And,
after coming here,
the dream changed.
Why is that?
Both dreams
are memories of your past life.
Do you not believe me,
or do you not believe that Yuyao would kill you?
Whether I believe it or not is my business.
First, tell me,
who are you?
I forgot to introduce myself.
My name is Xuanqing.
We
are old acquaintances.
Old acquaintances?
You lured me here.
What is your purpose?
What do you want?
Lu Sinian.
Lu Sinian!
Bo Peak reflects the snow's glow.
The Jade Pool ripples gently.
Lotuses bloom with a millennial love.
An endless affection that never fades.
Sinian!
I just saw an anomaly in the sky.
Did you see anyone?
Are you hurt?
No.
You scared me to death.
I thought it was some anomaly.
An anomaly?
Yes,
an anomaly.
I
know how to read the stars.
The celestial signs I just saw
were a bit unusual.
There might be a bloody disaster.
So I rushed to pick you up.
Let's go down the mountain.
Xuanqing
left because he was afraid
of running into Yuyao.
Why did he run away?
I seem to have just remembered something.
I think I saw at the bottom of the water
a mass of
something black.
Is that
what you called
an anomaly?
Then we really need to go down the mountain!
It's your first time here, so you don't know.
Around here,
there's a legend that's been passed down.
In that water,
there is a terrifying,
inherently brutal water monster.
The kind that kills
and eats people.
I'd rather believe she is just the way she looks now.
If she's been pretending all along,
then she's acting a little too well.
Maybe she
isn't that scheming.
Yueyue,
can't you be a little understanding?
I'm busy with work right now,
and the project is under a lot of pressure.
Didn't I bring you to Tianchi?
Do you call this keeping me company?
You've been answering and making calls the whole time.
You are always working.
I want someone
who can keep me company and care for me,
not a
workaholic who is always busy.
My career is on the rise right now.
I have to deal with these things.
Career on the rise.
Then when will things settle down?
When can we actually live a normal life?
Who says I don't want to live our lives?
Don't I have to pay the car loan and mortgage?
Don't I have to pay for water, electricity, and heating?
Stop guilt-tripping me.
You say the same things every day.
What's the point?
There is no point.
Then let's break up.
Who's afraid of who?
Fine, let's break up.
Don't regret it.
Listen up, whatever's in the water.
No matter what monster you are,
tonight,
I will stand guard here.
Let's see what moves you make.
Yuyao,
long time no see.
Oh no,
I should say,
it's been 98 lifetimes.
Xuanqing.
I didn't expect it to be you.
There's a lot you didn't expect.
You're so obsessed with love,
your magic progresses too slowly.
You couldn't find Lu Sinian,
so I found him for you,
and lured him here.
Shouldn't you
thank me properly?
What did you do to Lu Sinian?
Don't worry.
I am helping you.
He has reincarnated for 98 lifetimes,
and you still can't forget him.
This 99th lifetime
is your last chance.
Whether it's the last chance or not
is not up to you.
The love and hate in this world,
who dictates it?
The Queen Mother?
Couples in this world...
Some are childhood sweethearts
who grow old together.
Some fall in love at first sight
and stay together like birds on the wing.
Others
love each other deeply
and make eternal vows.
Of course,
there are also some
who cast off the old for the new,
change their minds,
and fall for someone else.
Tell me,
shouldn't they be punished?
Under this Sea-Calming Needle you guard,
lie the love spirits
of so many couples.
If I borrow a little,
what's the harm?
Don't even think about it!
Yuyao.
Time is running out for you.
Why is there no breakfast today?
Boss.
Yuyao.
I'll go get something to eat myself.
Thank you.
Here you go.
I actually didn't have that dream again last night.
So where did this dream come from?
Young man, come here.
Where is that pretty girl with you?
Why didn't she come with you?
Ma'am,
are you talking about...
The boss of the clothing store.
To meet you,
she was picking and choosing here.
In our Kazakh legends,
the snow lotus
represents pure love.
The girls
will take that whip
and chase their lovers.
Come here.
Take a look at this.
Look at this hairpin.
Look at its tassel,
doesn't it look like a whip?
Young man.
Don't be shy.
My eyes are not wrong.
This girl treats you very well.
You must hold on to her.
Ma'am,
we just met not long ago.
But,
it feels like we've known each other for a long time.
Right.
It's good to grow fond of each other over time.
Buy a gift for the girl.
I'll get one for you.
Let me show you our intangible cultural heritage crafts.
Kazakh embroidery.
Take a look at these embroidered bags.
What about this person?
This doll.
Hello.
Is boss Yu Yao here?
Our boss went to Dinghai Shenzhen to fix something.
Fix something?
Fix what?
Practicing cultivation.
Thanks.