Now, only the Queen Mother can save you.
As long as we pass these 99 steps of the heavenly ladder,
we still have a chance.
Did you hear me?
Husband.
These characters are too difficult to write.
I might as well go practice the zither and pipa.
Writing Han clerical script on bamboo slips
is different from writing it on Xuan paper.
As the saying goes,
a rope saws through wood,
and dripping water pierces a stone.
Where there is a will,
there is a way.
You're such a bookworm.
Seeing you look so serious and anxious
is actually quite cute.
Yuyao.
The broad peaks
reflect the snow's brilliance.
The jade pool
ripples with gentle green.
The blooming lotus holds a millennium of love,
never to be broken.
What a beautiful poem.
M-My lady.
Who are you?
You...
It is improper for men and women to touch.
You don't remember me.
Miss,
please behave yourself.
It's fine.
It doesn't matter if you don't remember.
Missing this lifetime won't make a difference.
Sinian.
This is the only lifetime left.
We've survived 98 lifetimes.
In this lifetime,
we can't have any regrets.
Yuyao.
You are so foolish.
Why make yourself suffer like this?
It's the 49th level, Sinian.
Sinian, hold on a little longer, Sinian.
Sinian, just hold on.
You're here.
Sinian.
Young Master Lu.
I have never met you before, Miss.
What can I do for you?
You have come from afar.
As the evening drum sounds,
would you do me the honor
of sharing a cup of tea?
Thank you.
I received a letter from home.
The situation is unstable, and war is raging.
I have studied for ten years.
Now it's time to serve in the army.
I
wish to emulate Ban Chao of the Eastern Han,
and cast aside the pen to join the army.
I must hurry on my journey.
I will take my leave now.
Sinian.
War is merciless.
You must return safely.
Lu Sinian,
will you leave me in this life?
I won't.
That day,
I saw you clearly,
and decided
never to leave your side.
I saw you clearly too.
Yuyao.
If one day I really leave,
just crack the whip,
and I will return.
Okay.
Hiyah!
Sinian.
What exactly did we do wrong?
Would the best beginning
have been never meeting at all?
You stay in the Heavenly Realm
and be a good divine official.
I will stay in the mortal realm and guard the Jade Pool well.
That way, we can both live well.
Sinian.
I tried my best.
I really tried my best.
Yuyao.
Your Highness,
please save Sinian.
Yuyao,
for him,
you trespassed on the Heavenly Ladder,
violating the Heavenly Laws.
Is it really worth it?
I owe him.
I will repay him with ninety-nine lifetimes.
I have no regrets.
Your Highness.
You promised me that
as long as we pass these 99 trials,
you would let us be together forever.
In this world,
is there anything that can be eternal?
Like you,
I once met someone.
At first,
I also thought it was love.
But
he lied to me.