(Hello, everyone.)
(I'm the one leading you on
the front line)
(to uncover shady plots as a
real-time reporter,)
(Li Feizhang.)
(Do you know where I am?)
(That's right.)
(I'm at the famous Yuyuan Biotechnology)
(which was founded single-handedly)
(by the tycoon, Xu Yongyu.)
(This is)
(a very open company.)
(There are no locks and security guards.)
(Anyone can enter and leave the building.)
(But actually,)
(Xu Yongyu has built an
underground world which)
(is the reason that)
(I'm risking my life)
(to come here and reveal it.)
(Let's look for)
(the underground world.)
(Let's see how Xu Yongyu)
(turned from a gangster)
(into a billionaire.)
(It seems that)
(our security system)
(really needs some upgrades.)
(Since you're here,)
(you can't leave empty-handed.)
=Love of Replica=
=Episode 14=
(No wonder Li Feizhang
keeps targeting Xu Xixi.)
(There are old grudges
between him and Xu Yongyu.)
(The popular singer, Xu Xixi,
surprises all.)
(Is she using her twin sister to debut
or a stand-in singer?)
Remove all reports immediately.
Don't let more people come
across it again.
Sweep everything
under the carpet soonest.
Compatibility?
Indeed, there're many news reports about
parents having another child
because of their currently sick child.
But An Yue and Xu Xixi are twins.
Xu Yongyu wouldn't give up
a healthy child for
a sick one, would he?
The video given to An Yue by her mom
mentions that, too.
I don't understand that, too.
That doesn't make sense.
An Yue is his daughter.
However biassed he is,
he wouldn't have been so cruel, right?
But the possibility is there.
Xu Yongyu's fatherly love for Xu Xixi
has become too extreme.
To him, An Yue is a stranger
whom he hasn't
spent time with.
If he wants to kill An Yue
to save Xu Xixi,
indeed,
I won't be surprised.
But we're just speculating.
I don't understand
why my mom doesn't want me to see him.
She'd rather die
than reveal who I am.
What're we waiting for?
Let's run
or we'll be dead.
Xu Yongyu's power
is beyond your imagination.
We can't escape.
Our only choice
is to get into Xu family to
gather criminal evidence
and hand it to the right party.
Did he know about you
after reading the news?
I'll get someone to remove it
for you to keep swapping identities
for Xu family's investigation.
(That's unnecessary.)
(The report is in An Yue's favour.)
(She's safer because of the exposure.)
I think
we can't do without him.
He has just undergone a surgery.
Tiancheng, go and rest.
Don't worry about me.
The doctor says my wound
is healing very well.
After the blood clots
in the brain were cleared,
I'm suddenly relaxed quite a bit.
(Let's return to the subject.)
(When the news was released,)
(I immediately removed it.)
(But I realised that)
(another party)
(was doing the same thing.)
He didn't want to act rashly
and put us on our guard.
But undeniably,
the news saved me.
Could you find out who wrote it?
(It's Li Feizhang.)
(But)
(he's currently not contactable.)
I doubt if
Xu Yongyu has done something to him.
Tiancheng, save your energy
and go to rest.
Don't remove the news.
But
we have to trouble your agency
to spread the news to everyone.
Let's make sure everyone knows that
An Yue and Xu Xixi are twins.
Do you think that...
He will reach me soon.
We may face the same.
We're not safe.
Yes.
Our capability
is too limited
to handle Xu Yongyu.
The best way forward
is using public opinion and publicity
to protect An Yue
and us better.
The report mentions
'See you on Monday'.
It means more future updates.
Monday...
That's tomorrow.
Although we don't know what he's up to,
apparently, Xu Xixi has a
live stream on Monday.
Not only she does that.
There's also Xu Mengyun.
I think the news report
was most probably created by
her and Li Feizhang.
She's so stubborn.
This time around,
we'll use Xu Mengyun
to our advantage.
Since the computer with administrator account
is not in Yuyuan Biotechnology,
it's most probably in
Xu Yongyu's study.
So we have to figure out how
to get into his house
to get authorised access.
The security level of
the hidden base exceeds that of labs.
It may be about
our parents' past research.
The cause of my dad's accident
and the truth your mom
doesn't want us to find out
should all be there.
An Yue,
before we access the hidden base,
don't overthink.
Dayu, go in with Xixi.
Okay, Mr. Xu.
Hello.
(Sir, we searched the hotel)
(but couldn't find him.)
I checked the surveillance camera
and saw him leave early.
Lu Jinyan knows I'm looking for them.
He's been working for me
and knows how I manage things.
He knows he can't escape.
To him,
the safest place
is anywhere within my control.
Do you mean that
he has gone to the venue?
Go back to the venue now.
Step up the security there.
If you see Lu Jinyan,
don't spare him.
Who's that? Does he even know
how to drive?
Oh hell!
Xu Xixi?
I'm An Yue.
She can't sing.
She let me be the ghost singer.
I solve the problems
without any recognition.
I have to hide behind the scenes.
And Tian Sui
always uses me to find
sources for Xu Xixi.
I really don't wish
to continue bearing it.
I don't want to be
her substitute anymore.
So please help me.
Help me expose their true colours.
Fear not.
The live stream today
is a chance to ruin their reputation.
Take a look here again.
Okay.
Ms. Chen,
regarding the script today,
Xixi and I have new ideas that we'd like
to discuss with you.
Tian Sui,
I've told you before.
For your sake,
I exceptionally
let Mr. Xu
avoid mentioning in the interview
anything about the news report.
Do you think I haven't done enough?
Now if Ms. Xu demands
anything further,
let's just cancel the programme.
Ms. Chen,
I think you've misunderstood.
I'm here to
tip you off big time.
The viewership will surely skyrocket.
What's the tip-off?
It's something like
Xu Xixi's twin sister's surprising
appearance on set of
'Star Colleagues' or
live-streamed reunion between
tycoon and long-lost daughter.
Are you serious?
The supervisor arrived early, right?
It's a big opportunity.
It's a rare opportunity.
Yes.
Xu Yongyu rarely shows up.
Will he be in the headlines?
Yeah, will he?
Stop!
Catch the girl!
What are you doing?
Don't you dare touch me!
I'm going to live-stream.
Go after her!
Hello.
(The girl's at the venue.)
(We're chasing her.)
Okay.
Dayu,
they were spotted nearby.
Go and check it out.
Okay.
Let's go.
Don't be nervous and do your best.
Get ready to live-stream.
Three.
Two.
One.
Go!
Let's go!
♪I think about you all the time,
you never know how I feel♪
♪Whenever I open my eyes,
they're already full with tears♪
♪Don't know what to do
with my heartache♪
♪I can never go to you♪
♪Is it true love or are they tears♪
♪Wouldn't mind longing for your love♪
♪Can you tell me if I'm wrong♪
♪Cause I don't want to get hurt♪
♪Don't leave me alone in the dark.
You're the one I love♪
♪Tell me you feel the same way I do♪
♪And don't make me wait too long♪
♪Say you love me♪
♪Wish I can hear
you say this word to me♪
♪Can you tell me if I'm wrong,
cause I don't want to get hurt♪
♪Come to my arms and I will tell you♪
♪You're the one I love♪
♪My love is you♪
Hello, my lovely audience.
I'm the host, Chen Xin.
Welcome to this episode
of 'Star Colleagues'.
(Today's guests - Xu Yongyu and Xu Xixi)
Today,
I have the privilege to introduce
(Today's guests - Xu Yongyu and Xu Xixi)
two special guests who are
the founder of Yongyu Capital,
Mr. Xu Yongyu,
and his celebrity daughter,
Xu Xixi.
Welcome them with applause.
Hello, Xixi.
Our netizens had known about
your scheduled appearance
on my programme.
They reacted excitedly
by leaving your comments
asking about your latest plans
for the near future.
For example,
will you organise any concert?
I'm sorry that
due to my personal plans,
I'm quitting the entertainment
industry infinitely.
Oh, why?
That's so sudden!
You sing so well.
You're doing so well.
Why are you quitting suddenly?
Today
marks Xixi's last filming
before she suspends work.
Her father, Mr. Xu Yongyu,
has been by her side.
We can feel
the father-and-daughter bond
that is really harmonious
and touching.
I think Mr. Xu has
the qualities of a good father that
all children anticipate.
As a token of appreciation to
Xixi and her father
for being our guest stars,
our crew have specially
prepared a surprise
for them.
The surprise is the news
about twins.
Another guest star is
the long-lost twin sister of Xixi's,
An Yue.
She's coming from behind.
Really?
They really look the same.
They mirror each other.
Indeed.
How come they look exactly the same?
They're really twins, then.
They look exactly the same.
It turns out she has a twin.
So, Xu Yongyu has two daughters?
Exactly.
Dad.
Are you An Yue?
That's great!
I've finally found you!
Li Feizhang is not contactable.
Who's the mastermind?
Do you think
he will spare you?
Congratulations, Mr. Xu, for being
reunited with your daughter.
Xixi and An Yue look identical.
By her looks, people know
she's your daughter.
When I first saw An Yue,
I was shocked
especially when she showed
the DNA report.
The crew really racked their brains
for the surprise.
Indeed.
I was very surprised, too.
This is a memorable moment.
Let's take a photo.
Good.
Okay.
Where is Xu Xixi?
Is that An Yue?
Mr. Xu.
Sir,
do you want to avoid them?
I'll get the press dispersed.
No. Stay beside Xixi.
Mr. Xu,
could you answer our questions?
Everyone knows
you only have a daughter, Xu Xixi.
Is Ms. An Yue standing by your side here
also your daughter?
Were you hiding her identity
purposely or
do you have other explanations?
Could you answer us?
Is the one beside you Xu Xixi or An Yue
that you've just got reunited with?
Okay, everyone.
An Yue
is my daughter.
She was kidnapped when she was little.
For years
I've been searching for her.
The kidnapper is the one
who took Xu Xixi hostage.
So it's the kidnapper!
Luckily,
the kidnapper faced the music.
An Yue has found
two loving family members.
I wish to tell everyone concerned
about this matter
and the press to stop worrying.
I'll treat An Yue well.
She's my daughter, after all.
I should make it up to her,
after the years when we were apart.
Ah,
An Yue
isn't well.
The three of us have just
been reunited.
Wonderful time feels short.
We don't want too much
attention and disturbance
from the public.
I hope you understand.
Yueyue,
let's go home.
Thank you, dad.
Thank you for your concern, everyone.
In the future, I'll try
my best to integrate into my new family.
For easy access
to future updates and
your convenience,
I've decided to accept
the programme crew's invitation
to live-stream my new family
life for seven days.
So, everyone can see how the three of us
get along in our daily lives.
Right.
Good.
Sir,
you were treating An Yue so well today.
Have you changed your mind
to accept her?
Accept her?
What do you think the daily live stream
starting tomorrow is for?
It's to ensure An Yue
appears in the videos throughout
so that I don't get to target her.
In that case,
they'll have it their own way.
From tomorrow onwards,
they'll see what they want,
a loving father and a filial daughter.
Let everyone see
how biassed I am towards
my sick daughter.
As for Lu Jinyan,
let him stay.
Instead of letting him stir up trouble,
let him stay within my control.
(I'll treat An Yue well.)
(She's my daughter, after all.)
(I should make up for)
(the years when we were apart.)
(Ah,)
(An Yue)
(isn't well.)
(The three of us)
(have just been reunited.)
People
may take that to mean that
An Yue is ill.
It's his self-fulfilling prophecy
if An Yue disappears.
Don't worry.
Once An Yue joins the family,
the real-time reporting crew
will immediately live-stream.
Tian Sui will be watching.
Live stream
makes Xu Yongyu think twice.
I think
besides taking care of me,
you're busy with An Yue's case.
Tian Sui and you aren't making progress.
You're so quiet.
You're not your real self, Ding Beifan.
Didn't I promise to wait for
your discharge?
I'll fulfil my promise.
Let's eat.
I'm ready for the discharge.
I'll confess to Tian Sui.
Today?
Yes.
Uncle Jiang said I'm recovering well.
What about you?
You want me to go all out.
I wouldn't let you down.
Why? Are you scared?
No.
Why would I be scared?
Jiang Tiancheng,
I've long known that
she likes you more.
But I like her.
If our relationship isn't successful,
it means I don't love her enough.
I'm not scared.
I'll only work harder.
Okay.
We'll see if you have time
to work harder.
Where will you confess?
I'll send you there.
Do you remember the place?
Of course.
We gave Tian Sui flowers together here
for the first time
and agreed to compete fairly.
Now that I recall,
it was wonderful.
You looked confident and sincere.
You don't know how I envied you.
I envied you
for being able to confess your love to her
freely and fearlessly.
But because of my health,
I wasn't even brave enough to do that.
Now everything is better.
The biggest obstacle
between her and me is removed.
Do you think
my confession will be successful?
Maybe.
She...
Tian Sui.
Why are you guys here?
Weren't you just discharged today?
I had Ding Beifan send me here.
There's something
I want to tell you in person.
Let's go there.
Ah,
if there's nothing else, you may leave.
If I go back later,
you don't have to send me.
I know
it's wrong timing for me to be here.
But I need to tell you something.
I assure you that after this,
I'll never disturb you.
Tian Sui,
I like you.
I...
Don't say anything.
Please let me finish.
Since I met you,
my life has become colourful.
I want to hold you.
I want to enter your life.
I know that
you have someone you like.
I'm not up to your expectations.
But I've never given up and
chickened out.
Maybe
I don't know about love
but I do know that
I want to be with you
for the rest of my life.
I may have said too much
because I think
if I don't say it now,
there won't be another chance.
In fact,
I indeed used to have a long list of
detailed criteria for a suitor.
I hoped my future partner would be
gentle, tall, caring,
ambitious, proactive,
and most importantly,
we'd share some common ground.
In short,
you don't fit in with
all the criteria.
But
I've still fallen for you.
Ding Beifan,
let's give it a try.
No. Wait a minute.
I...
Didn't you make any confession?
I wanted to confess to her
that I came to bid farewell.
That's right.
Jiang Tiancheng just told me
he's leaving Lancheng.
So you...
Did you do it purposely?
Nonsense.
My only intention was to
bid farewell to her.
You misunderstood me.
Okay. You're right.
The surgery's done.
It was successful.
I'm relieved so much.
I thought of
travelling the world
after An Yue's case is settled.
I want to make up for all the
wonderful time
I've lost.
I've just
wished him a happy journey.
Okay.
I'm making a move.
Three's a crowd.
I'll drive you.
No, I'm fine.
I told you I don't need
you to send me home.
Bye.
Calm down. Don't stir up trouble.
Let me do it.
We've infiltrated into Xu family.
Next, distract Xu Yongyu.
I'll figure out in the study
the authorised access
to Yuyuan Biotechnology base.
I'll delay as much as possible.
Xu Yongyu and An Yue are
live-streaming at the garden.
Enter the study quickly.
Access the computer to get authority.
Tiancheng, let's start.
(System user can't be changed
but can be added.)
(Your palm vein patterns
need to be entered.)
(The palm vein authentication device
should be)
(at the bottom of the table.)
(Left hand inputting)
How long does it take?
Around ten minutes.
(Left hand inputting)
Yueyue,
how does the new home
feel?
It feels good.
I like the place.
It's your home now.
Feel free.
And feel free to talk with daddy.
The family has never felt
so joyful before.
I have to leave for work.
I have to go to the study.
I'll be right back.
(Left hand inputting.)
♪I'm in the darkness all by myself♪
♪Trying to look for you
Wherever you are♪
♪Did you know? I'm standing on this
empty road, don’t know where to go♪
♪I'm calling your name♪
♪If I had a chance
to do this over again♪
♪I know for sure
it wouldn't be the same♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪I can't stop love for you♪
♪My heart is saying it is very true♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪I can't stop love for you♪
♪Even though I know
that you don't feel the same♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪I can't stop love for you♪
♪My heart is saying it is very true♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪I can't stop love for you♪
♪Even though I know
that you don't feel the same♪
♪I'll let you go♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪I can't stop love for you♪
♪My heart is saying it is very true♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪I can't stop love for you♪
♪Even though I know
that you don't feel the same♪
♪I'll let you go♪