Dad, Dad, are you okay?
Other hospitals also refused us.
Then where can we go?
I'm begging you, please help him.
We have nowhere else to call.
No, no.
Dad, Dad!
A man will come to a certain moment.
Dad.
Dad. Dad.
A moment where they wish to receive the help of divinities.
Oh, no.
It's the abdominal artery rupture patient we just told you over the phone.
We don't have a doctor who can do the operation.
Didn't I just tell you that?
What are we gonna do about him?
He's in the state of hypovolemic shock.
Now we can hardly maintain his vital signs.
He'll die if you don't do the operation now.
We can't. Please leave.
Go.
Dr. Ha?
Yes.
Let's go.
Doctor.
Please save my father.
I'm begging you, please.
Send them away.
If the divinities have too much to tend to,
the man wouldn't mind if a ghost could help.
Get out.
No!
Don't do that!
Please reconsider.
If we send the patient away like this,
he might die on the way.
Are you crazy?
You are just an intern, how dare you speak up like this?
Hurry up and send him away, what are you waiting for?
No!
Stop!
Isn't this a hospital?
Aren't we doctors?
If doctors abandon patients,
then who will...
You fool, think you are a doctor now.
Hey, why don't you do the surgery on him then?
Dad, no!
(Ghost Doctor)
What happened next?
Did the ghost save the patient?
(Episode 1)
You want to know?
Well...
(Episode 1)
It's a secret.
If people in this world know it,
something disastrous is going to happen.
Do that kind of ghosts really exist?
Of course, they should be here, in this hospital, too.
The guardians of the sick.
You know guardians, right?
So, my little patients,
remember that there are always ghost doctors by your side,
and you should thank them.
Say thank you to them.
Liar!
How can there be such kind ghosts?
- Yeah.
- Liar!
How can a doctor turn into a ghost?
You think ghost is superhero?
She is telling a lie, a big lie.
Let's go.
The children now are really stubborn.
They don't listen to the grown-ups.
If all problems can be solved by the power of the living,
(12 years later)
then that's what is called a lie, a big terrible lie.
(EMC, EunSang University Medical Center)
(Emergency Medical Center)
Gorgeous.
He doesn't let us down today either.
That's Professor Cha Yeong Min of Thoracic Surgery.
What? He's a professor?
Right, you are surprised, too.
With that appearance and that figure,
why did he become a doctor?
More than that, he's mysterious, too.
What is it?
So, the time of CPR?
It took us about 30 minutes to get here.
Without any witness,
we don't know for sure when his heart stopped beating.
Please go this way.
Let Dr. An do it.
No need for ECMO.
Make way please!
Okay, 1, 2, 3.
Measure the blood pressure.
Preparing for intubation.
7.5 milliliter.
Let me do this.
Parrot pose.
Pneumothorax.
Why isn't the ECMO group of Thoracic Surgery here yet?
They'll come in a minute.
Charge to 200. Move!
Ready.
Clear.
Check the blood pressure.
Switch to manual.
Confirm data.
Where are you going?
Hey, O Su Jeong!
(Referral Center)
Professor Cha Yeong Min!
(EunSang University Medical Center)
There is patient in the emergency room who needs ECPR,
(ECPR, external cardiopulmonary resuscitation)
please come with me.
(O Su Jeong)
Intern… O?
I'll do the self-introduction later, please come with me.
Sure enough,
interns often make troubles everywhere though they don't know anything.
It's understandable, I used to be just like you.
It's the privilege of an intern.
Professor, watch out!
I'm sorry, Professor, but we're running out of time.
Hurry, hurry.
What are you doing?
Intern O, let me keep it short.
First,
I don't offer treatment to whoever you toss at me
because I'm not that kind of doctor.
Second,
I don't treat emergency patients because
there will be a few steps till the patients get transferred to me.
Third,
I won't treat that kind of patients.
Patients like the one that just got in there.
This pair of hands is ready for patients with 1% hope of survival.
Professor, watch out.
Crap.
Professor, if you got the time here to...
To do what?
Intern O, please hurry back to the emergency room,
and learn to declare death.
I need to save the ones that really have the chance of survival.
Lunatic.
Name of the patient?
Well...
Name of the patient!
It's Sin Jeong U.
Patient, Sin Jeong U, time of death,
9:31, September 1,
What a mean person.
Who? Don't tell me you went to that man.
Hey, do you know who that is?
Who else can it be? The glamorous gangster doctor.
Gangster? Are you out of your mind?
He is a top doctor that
even the dean dares not to mess up with.
(EunSang University Medical Center)
He is a top doctor that
even the dean dares not to mess up with.
He performed an operation during his internship,
which saved an emergency patient.
The whole hospital was shocked, and people thought it's outrageous.
But there have been similar things before.
And now, any patient he touches lives.
Rumor says that he's being possessed by a ghost.
What did you just say?
What? He performed an operation during his internship?
You cannot believe that, either, right?
Back then, he was about your age,
even a genius...
No, the possessed-by-a-ghost thing.
It's just a metaphor, describing his great medical skills.
How can it be a real ghost?
Female, 33 years old. Patient of Behcet syndrome.
(EunSang University Medical Center)
According to AR, her colon ulcer
showed inflammation, after three surgeries,
(EunSang University Medical Center)
According to AR, her colon ulcer
showed inflammation, after three surgeries,
it developed into an aneurysm. Professor Cha will perform quadrido this afternoon.
(Quadrido: the fourth surgery)
Quadrido?
The fourth, not the fifth?
(Quadrido: the fourth surgery)
Well, it's the fifth surgery.
Technically, it's a reoperation of the fourth surgery.
Professor Cha knows that very well.
It's a disease that comes back often.
When it happens, you have a surgery.
Over time, the connection becomes severe and there are adhesions everywhere.
The blood vessels in the chest burst.
It's a tricky and difficult surgery.
Why did you do it since it's tricky and difficult, Chief?
That's because all the other doctors said they couldn't do it.
Then you should do the reoperation too, Chief.
Well... Professor...
What?
The patient said he didn't trust the chief.
He wants to change the surgeon.
Then we have no choice. Prepare for the operation.
Next.
The 70-year-old male patient
with chronic diabetes and hypertension
suffered from a stroke two years ago.
Cardiac sarcoma was found one month ago
during an examination due to breathing difficulties.
(Cardiac Sarcoma, a type of rarely occurring primary malignant cardiac tumor)
That's the one I diagnosed and treated.
The son asked if his father could have a surgery.
So, what, are you going to do it?
I can't do it.
How can I do that?
Can Professor Cha do it?
It cannot be done.
Well, Professor Cha...
Don't jump to conclusions. Please think about it.
Take the son's filial piety into consideration.
A hematoma or tumor tissue that falls out of the heart
may go to the brain, and cause a worse stroke.
There is also the possibility of reoccurrence due to unstable removal.
He has one year left without a surgery.
If he doesn't want to make that even shorter,
a filial son
would let him spend the rest of his life in peace.
Tell the son that.
Professor Cha, don't do this.
Next!
He knew it and he did it to make me look bad.
He treated me, a department chief, like garbage.
When young people think they are capable,
they become aggressive and arrogant.
Go on and see what that will lead you to.
Heaven, please don't just observe out there.
That's right, today's the day.
All right, you brat, meet your opponent.
Relax and be gentle.
He dared not say a word back in there, but he...
But what did he mean?
What opponent?
OK, it's over. Unplugging.
How many are there?
What is wrong with him?
Like one of his screws is loose.
Today is the day to meet the newcomer.
He's been working so hard on his own, of course he's happy
to see a newcomer.
Ah, is it today?
With the Specialist Physicians' Law, how hard could it be?
Why hasn't he shown himself yet?
Being absent on his first day.
Bring him to me when he's here.
I will.
But what's with the look on your face?
What, because you had to declare a patient's death in the morning?
It's not that.
But how do you know?
I saw it on the way in.
The patient suffered from an unwitnessed cardiac arrest.
(Unwitnessed arrest: Unwitnessed cardiac arrest)
He lost 30 minutes on the way and had no response.
That meant he had no chance, right?
What about ECMO?
We did not use that.
Well done.
ECMO Priming costs 3 million won at a time.
(ECMO Priming: Filling the entire ECMO circuit with fluid)
And it is disposable.
Why waste money when it's useless anyway?
Well done.
You are Professor Cha Yeong Min, right?
I've heard a lot about you.
They say you are the best doctor in our hospital.
Yes, I am, you are?
This is a hand possessed by divinities.
It's unexpectedly beautiful.
I take good care of them.
But... who are you?
A president once said
one genius can feed 100,000 people.
Wait a minute.
Our hospital has 2,000 permanent medical staff
and 5,800 general employees, that is about 8,000 in total.
Wow, Professor Cha could feed 10 hospitals!
Well...
ECMO costs 3 million won a time. That's a general employee's monthly salary.
So if you save ten times, that's the annual salary of an employee.
What's up?
Who are you?
So eminent, but I hear you are a little mean.
You're...
That's the personality, privilege and charm of a genius.
Aristotle said
there is no such thing as a genius without a little bit of arrogance.
It takes a whole hospital to cultivate a genius.
After all, you have the medical skills of divinities.
If you have a problem, you can always come to me.
Hello, bro.
You guys go ahead.
Bro, where's the locker?
It's over there.
By the way,
I will start working with you from today.
I'm Dr. Go Seung Tak.
Thank you.
Oh, please...
Is that the new guy we were talking about?
Who is he?
Hey, who's that guy?
You know him, don't you?
When and where did you know him?
How much do you know about him?
I knew him from school.
I don't know much, only a little.
Did you teach him to be like that?
I wouldn't dare!
I just gave him some information.
Information? What information?
Information about arrogance?
It's not fair!
I'm the biggest victim.
Go Seung Tak.
You don't mean that "they told me" Go Seung Tak, do you?
You know him too, Dr. Lee?
I've only heard of him.
He had an interview when he came as an intern.
It's a legend.
We ask superficial questions at the internship interview.
(EunSang University Medical Center)
Why do you choose to be a doctor?
I want to help suffering patients.
I want to save people's lives.
People would talk about superficial things.
Here's what he said:
Grandpa and Mom told me to be a doctor.
So, his grandpa is the President of our group.
And his mom is the Chairman of the Council.
(Qualified)
Why is there still back-door-dealing in the 21st century?
What dealing?
What if specialists demonstrate?
How dare you do it in modern society?
Withdraw it.
His score ranked first in school.
And he got the best result in the internship evaluation.
If this is a back-door-dealing,
Professor Cha is also a back-door-dealing.
You helped with the internship evaluation.
Since when are specialists selected on the basis of their departmental scores?
What about humanity, sense of mission, sense of life?
When did Professor Cha start to know so well about the qualifications of a doctor?
If that's the case, then send him to another professor.
I don't like him.
He doesn't know enough, does he?
You're here, Vice President of Administration.
Since you're related, you should know very well
that it's not the only thing he lacks.
He is disagreeable and has got no propriety, manners, and humility.
He has so many flaws.
So please take care of him in the future, Professor Cha.
The future of our group is in your hands. Think it that way.
Didn't I tell you?
Dr. Go is the heir to our hospital.
But President didn't want to hand it over to him directly. So, he put forward a condition.
It's kind of a precondition of succession.
It means
that he's here for the certificate for inheriting the Group.
How did it go?
You are asking me?
Why the question?
I can't stand that kind of guy
walking around in front of me.
It smells good.
This is per…
What kind of doctor would wear perfume in the hospital?
Of course it's not for work time.
I want them to get rid of
the smell of disinfectant when dating after work.
Work-life balance.
Don't you understand?
Have you finished showing off your money?
Time to work.
Intern, Go Seung Tak.
What are you doing?
What about the ward inspection?
This is a 65-year-old patient.
She suffered from bicuspid aortic valve
and ascending aorta dilation.
She had the operation of ascending aortic replacement.
Since the extubation at 10 p.m. yesterday,
the day after the operation,
there has been no special problem.
Go Seung Tak.
Tell us about the bicuspid aortic valve.
Bicuspid aortic valve
is a kind of congenital heart disease
with an incidence rate of 1%.
Symptoms vary with ways of aortic dilation.
Young people may also suffer from AR.
According to Aging, it may develop into AS or large artery dilation.
He was famous at school.
Famous for what?
His theoretical knowledge is as rich as a professor.
So what?
He came first in any subject, in any test.
No one knows how he read so many theses.
At school, his tricky questions always got professors stumped.
It was said professors started to learn more because of him.
I heard that you took one-year off.
Looks like that you worked hard.
Go Seung Tak, you take charge of this patient from now on.
What?
Go Seung Tak.
Tell us about Maze OP.
Maze OP
means an operation where arrhythmia transmission pathway which causes an abnormal heartbeat
is changed into normal cardiac conduction
with various of energy sources.
Good.
This patient is also yours.
Excuse me.
This patient's condition is unstable.
I have to continue…
Dr. An,
does a doctor treat patients by sitting at his table?
Leave it to him.
Go Seung Tak.
What medicine can be used during an infectious endocarditis attack?
I don't know very well.
Really?
Vancomycin, gentamycin,
ampicillin, aminoglycosides or ciprofloxacin.
Just choose a suitable antibiotic accordingly.
Do it this way after the discussion with Infection Department.
Me?
Yeah.
Didn't Go Seung Tak say he didn't know?
Why always me?
Because you are my bro.
Hell!
Don't we check these patients over there?
Hey! Those patients…
Gim Jae Won.
Why are these patients still here?
Well…
Their guardians refuse to transfer them.
You think we have sufficient beds?
Ask them to transfer within this week.
Get it.
It turns out that giving up these patients
is right and wise for a doctor.
I learned a great lesson on my first day.
It's meaningful.
Go Seung Tak.
There are two categories of patients in the world.
Patients who can survive after my treatment
and patients who can't.
If my treatment doesn't work,
anyone else can't help them.
These patients fall into the second category.
Didn't you say I need to feed the hospital?
The more patients, the more earnings.
Isn't it the common sense?
How could we put effort into those patients
who have no hope for survival,
but give up those who can survive?
They don't live a good life.
I don't understand why they don't give up.
When time is up, they should let it go.
Shouldn't they?
How ominous!
Right? So ominous.
A doctor is already ominous.
And that genius...
People always say geniuses are crazy.
So, ignore what he said just now.
Don't take it seriously.
Have you eaten yet?
A little.
What's going on?
First, you graduated from the medical university.
And now, you became an intern.
Has your grandpa changed his mind?
Well, the President should be
more cautious.
How does an intern know
such important information?
He upgraded it. He asked me to take the certificate.
Yeah, it must be a big blow for you, isn't it?
Or, it's the destiny of an heir.
A kind of tough test.
I just take it as field inspection.
You actually chose the busiest Thoracic Surgery Department.
Isn't it cool? Heart.
I can't let the doctors who work for me look down upon me.
Since you are here, why not try hard?
Change that attitude first.
Su Jeong.
I have been enjoying special treatment and privilege for 28 years.
How should I change my attitude now?
People should indulge me.
What's more, I don't think it's necessary.
I won't be a doctor forever.
Do I have a proper reason to work hard?
Hello? Who's speaking?
Oh, specialist training doctor.
Operation?
Why must I be there?
I would very much like to go,
but I don't feel…
I haven't finished.
It's Professor Cha's operation.
Why do I have to be there?
Why are there so many people?
Professor Cha, your operation
is the best on-the-spot teaching, isn't it?
It's a rare opportunity to watch.
Moreover, they wouldn't want to miss such a rare case.
Doctors have operations every day. What's there to watch?
You fool around on your first day at work.
Put on your surgical gown and get back quickly.
Stand behind me. Be close.
Let's get started.
I guess that you have heard
this is the fifth operation of this patient.
Adhesion must be very serious.
We must be careful when opening the chest.
Here we go.
Scalpel.
Aspirator.
Electrotome.
Cutter.
All right. Let's swap positions.
Pressure clamp.
Press down.
Hold it.
Insert the tube.
Cut.
Wire guider.
OK, good.
Hello. This is Han Seung Won.
Receive our guests tonight, then.
Don't worry about it.
Now the major operation is over.
Start the esophageal ultrasound.
No bleeding from the aortic valve.
I mean, no after-suture bleeding.
The average pressure difference is less than 1.5.
No narrow blood vessels.
The operation is very successful.
Go Seung Tak.
Explain bio prosthetic aortic valve.
Bio prosthetic aortic valve
is a kind of valve
made of the cardiac membrane
or implanted valve.
But in the end it will get calcified.
Then its side effects may cause problems.
Okay, good.
Very good.
Now we should pull out the tube.
You tie the knot.
Can you do that?
Come on.
Anyway,
on the first day of anatomy practice,
he was responsible for the abdominal incision.
What are you doing?
Don't you know how to do it?
Hey, Go Seung Tak.
I'm not doing it.
After that, he was often absent
with various reasons.
Go Seung Tak, are you…?
Move.
I admire you so much, Professor.
Do you know who are the slowest
in improving speaking of English?
Those who get good grades at school.
They think good performance in tests
stands for good English.
But what's the use of 10 years' good grades?
You are a failure if you cannot speak English.
It's also true in medical skills.
If you only focus on books and theories,
you will become like this senior,
who knows a lot but can't use the scalpel.
You may be born rich. So what?
Your hands are unreliable.
Why not just say his name?
For a patient in a life-or-death situation,
between a bad-tempered but highly skilled doctor
and a cordial, kind but incompetent one,
who do you think he will choose?
The key to saving patients
lies not in here,
but here
and here.
Keep that in mind.
Doctors are not emotion suppliers.
Doctors are professionals with visible skills.
So, if you have no skills
and only want good grades and tags,
don't waste your time here.
Over.
Your hands are unreliable, unreliable, unreliable.
My hands are golden, golden, golden.
I love golden hands.
You know what?
In others' eyes,
I'm a symbol of authority and admiration.
But a strange intern came today.
How dare he show off in front of me?
He thinks he's a prince?
Come on...
Terrible hands.
Cha Bun,
tell me.
Am I a right person he should mess up with?
Of course not.
So, I took him to the operating room,
and then mortified him hard.
Boy, how dare you work against me?
Your hands are so unreliable.
It's all right. I won, anyway.
I don't think that boy will come to work tomorrow.
If he comes,
I'll think of another strategy.
So, I'm thinking that
I can wear my new suit to work tomorrow.
Or I can buy a new car
after I pay the installments.
Good morning, Professor.
You came?
Of course, this is my workplace.
You are tougher than I thought.
That is the basic quality of an heir.
Are we standing too close
considering our social status?
Only the old stubborn cares about it very much.
Equality, justice and fairness are the zeitgeist.
Before learning the qualities of an heir,
why don't you pick up some doctor's qualities first?
For example, knot-tying.
Even a genius needs to be cultivated well.
I happen to be very talented in business.
Then talk to your grandpa.
Who knows?
Maybe he'll change his mind.
He is a fickle man.
I don't need to talk to him.
You go up first.
Why?
Are you asking me a question?
Do you think I'll answer you?
Are we very close?
But he has asked me so many.
Are you very close?
You scared me.
I get it. No discord, no concord.
Enemies become friends.
In the end, I'm the only victim.
What are you talking about?
Shall I buy you coffee?
I must be a bad guy in my previous life.
Hello.
A cup of coffee, please.
He's going to that place again.
Where? What place?
There is a place for him
to drink coffee alone and admire himself.
Thank you.
In my hospital,
there's some place I don't know?
Hey, you are asking for trouble.
Don't go there. He won't like it.
How are you doing?
It's been long.
Great, you look good.
It seems that you've also been drinking coffee here recently.
Hello, this is Cha Yeong Min.
I came to have coffee but came across an unexpected guest.
No, I'm coming now.
Because my mood for coffee is completely ruined.
We've seen it at yesterday's conference.
Well, the patient with cardiac sarcoma.
I didn't tell you that
it was President Jang Gwang Deok of Tianming Group
who was hospitalized here in secret yesterday.
As you know, President Jang is a public figure,
so, he was sent here in secret.
I hope you can understand, Professor Cha.
I've told you my suggestion yesterday.
Yeah, you did.
But his son wants a surgery to be done.
This is his son,
Vice President of Tianming Group.
(EunSang University Medical Center)
I'm Jang Min Ho.
Yesterday you may not know who I am.
(EunSang University Medical Center)
Now that you know it today,
please reconsider your treatment plan.
(EunSang University Medical Center)
Now that you know it today,
please reconsider your treatment plan.
And be careful.
I'm my father's only son.
I can't let him go without even trying.
Professor Cha, you are the best thoracic surgeon.
I'm seriously asking you a favor.
Your father is an elderly patient with diabetes, hypertension and a history of stroke.
It's unlikely for him to make it through the surgery.
Even if he does make it,
it's hard to totally excise the tumors
deep in his left atrium and pulmonary vein.
As a result, he will have a relapse in three months.
It's difficult for him to live long.
But he won't live long either
without surgery, right?
Please, let me fulfill my filial piety as a son.
But I can't bring shame on myself
just to fulfill your filial piety.
Give me today's surgical schedule.
(Emergency Medical Center)
Here.
Go Seung Tak.
Get out of my sight forever.
What?
People say that his foundation is weak
because of a short period of internship.
Then he should start from the emergency room.
What?
Not happy about that?
If so, go tell your grandpa.
Or you can go cry in front of your mother.
You heard him.
(Emergency Medical Center)
Why do I feel so much tension?
You made him mad again?
It was not me this time.
But what can I do in the Emergency Room?
What else can you do?
Pick up calls!
OK.
A call.
Hello, Secretary Gim.
Do you know who I am?
Has it been spread?
Who else can you be?
You are the doctor who can only talk.
It's nice to always be inquisitive to me.
But there's a problem of time and place.
Who can compare with you?
You had better clear these up while I am speaking gently.
Why clear up?
Not at all, take them.
You know it's a famous brand, yeah?
This young man still has not waked up yet.
Sir.
Can I take charge of Dr. Go Seung Tak?
What? Yes, of course.
I guess it is OK.
Although… we are classmates in the student numbers,
but you're an intern now due to
frequent suspension of schooling.
Maybe you have not known that
there is a strict hierarchy in the hospital.
Follow me before I get angry.
You will be sorry.
What?
That hierarchy.
Ah, it hurts! It hurts!
It hurts!
Get out the way!
Sorry.
How dare you keep me waiting?
Do you know who I am?
Mr. Patient, do you know who I am?
You think you are funny? OK.
Get the Chief out, the Chief.
Get the Dean out, now!
My position is higher than all of them.
You can talk to me.
Are you kidding me?
Are you messing up with me, brat?
Are you messing up with me?
Brat, wet behind the ears.
Dad,
this is Professor Cha from Thoracic Surgery Department.
Hello.
I am Cha Yeong Min.
OK, Professor Cha.
I have heard that,
you are the best thoracic surgeon in Korea.
You flatter me.
This is my little daughter.
I am Jang Se Jin.
Actually, my daughter is a doctor, too.
She works in a famous hospital in Seattle, USA.
She came back from so far because I am ill.
Leaving such reliable son and daughter behind,
I feel complicated in heart.
My son said I can still receive a surgery.
I'd like to hear your honest opinion as an expert.
So I invited you to come here during busy work.
I heard your story.
You found your powerful biological father and changed your life.
You are more decisive than I imagined, Jang Se Jin.
Yeong Min,
you have become a doctor beyond my imagination.
It's not the time to clear the air
by asking how things are going.
What?
You also want me to operate on the President?
No.
It is the opposite.
I got the President's medical records before coming back.
I discussed with colleagues in the US.
I think your opinion should be
the same with me as a doctor.
I think it's better to let him enjoy the rest of his life
than to do a risky operation on him.
That's what's best for him.
Who said it was a risky operation?
If you're doing this because you hate me...
Jang Se Jin,
in your eyes,
am I still that intern 12 years ago?
What? Didn't he write a will?
Or do you feel unsatisfied with that will?
What do you want me to do?
Kill him?
Or save him?
I didn't expect you to become a doctor like this.
I need to talk to you.
I think today is our last chance.
Se Jin.
I will wait for you there.
Gim Se Jin.
She went to America for further study.
She should be on the plane by now.
It is said that her biological father is a millionaire.
Her life has changed greatly.
Of course… a completely different life.
That must be the man she was dating.
You can tell immediately.
He has been dumped obviously.
Just a poor intern.
She may not even give a straight look at him now.
I didn't expect you to become a doctor like this.
No…
You will never understand
what kind of doctor I am now.
I am Cha Yeong Min.
Have you adjusted the operation schedule?
I have.
But… do you have to do this operation?
Don't worry.
It is hopeful with Auto Transplantation.
(Auto Transplantation)
But we were supposed to have another surgery at that time.
That surgery wasn't an emergency.
It's okay to postpone it for a day or two.
This is a high-risk operation.
The likelihood of recurrence is high.
Professor, you would never do this kind of surgery before.
An Tae Hyeon,
how long have you been a specialist training doctor?
4 years.
I remember the appointments for professors
are reviewed in each March.
The review will begin soon.
The patient's son told me that
as long as I do this surgery,
a bright future is guaranteed for me.
Wouldn't it be nice if you could share in the glory?
That's why you worked for me
for so many years, isn't it?
Well, I'll go get ready.
Very good.
(EunSang University Medical Center)
Start the operation.
Scalpel!
Suction!
Now we'll take out the heart.
Everybody needs to concentrate.
Yes!
Pull!
Hey!
Pull gently!
If there's any bleeding because of you,
can you undertake the responsibility?
Focus!
OK, sorry…
I'll take care of it, you can take a rest.
How can I leave before the patient wakes up?
Who is it?
(I want to see you now, could you come out?
I will go back to America by air tomorrow morning.
There's something I really need to talk to you before I leave.
I will be waiting for you at the place we used to go a lot.)
I'll be back soon.
Stay with the patient.
Call me if anything happens.
- Is there anyone in the car?
- Really?
- What should we do?
- Why hasn't the ambulance come yet?
There's so much blood.
It was that car that hit it from the side.
Still not here? He is dying. Come on.
Oh, no…
What should we do?
I am a doctor, let me have a look.
Why isn't the ambulance here yet?
Hey, sir, can you hear me?
Step aside, everyone!
Step out of the way!
What the…
Here, here!
Sir, can you hear me?
(Rescue Team)
It's cardiac arrest.
There is a cardiac defibrillator in the ambulance, right?
Bring it to me.
Hello?
Please step aside.
Doctor, someone is injured here.
Get the tools here.
(Be back in 60 seconds)
Well… Brother Jae Won.
Go Seung Tak, where are you now?
Where else? The Emergency Room of course.
Didn't I ask you for a favor earlier?
(VIP Room for Critical Patients)
I… I can't hear you clearly.
What am I doing right now?
Now patients are being brought in one after another.
Oh, they are really coming in.
Hello? Go Seung Tak.
Why is it so noisy?
Oh, what a pain!
(Rescue Team)
(Emergency Medical Center)
It's a traffic accident victim.
He was knocked down by a car while riding his motorcycle.
Follow me.
(EunSang University Medical Center)
He is the driver of the car that collided with the motorcycle.
Professor Cha Yeong Min.
- What?
- Is he a doctor in this hospital?
Yes.
Come this way, be quick!
(Emergency Medical Center)
(EunSang University Medical Center)
The patient is Professor Cha Yeong Min.
- Professor.
- One, two, three.
What's wrong with him?
His chest bumped into the steering wheel.
Blood pressure is 80/40.
Pulse is 120.
Yeah, my chest bumped into the steering wheel.
(Cardiac tamponade refers to the phenomenon of excessive fluid accumulation in the pericardium compressing the heart. RV rupture - Right ventricular rupture)
RV rupture is also possible.
Transfer me to the operating room now.
(Cardiac tamponade refers to the phenomenon of excessive fluid accumulation in the pericardium compressing the heart. RV rupture - Right ventricular rupture)
Tell the operating room to get ready first.
There's no time for a CT scan.
What are you waiting for?
Find an empty operating room and call Thoracic Surgery Department.
Yeah, take a look at the heart now.
No one's answering the phone in Thoracic Surgery Department.
Why? Who's the doctor on duty today?
Go Seung Tak.
Dr. Go, why aren't you answering the phone?
Aren't you the doctor on duty today?
Is Go Seung Tak on duty today?
No.
You can't give me to him.
Yes, call An Tae Hyeon.
Come on!
It's Professor Cha Yeong Min. Please check him.
What can he check?
He'd only read about cardiac tamponade in textbook.
You don't know anything about cardiac ultrasound.
Cardiac ultrasound.
Do a cardiac ultrasound. Hurry up!
Don't do it on me if you don't know how.
Do you know how to read it?
You…
actually know that.
Go Seung Tak.
Do you see the hematocele here?
It's a cardiac tamponade in the right ventricle.
A surgery is needed to plug it up.
Right here.
You see that? Here.
There's hematocele in the heart.
It looks like a cardiac tamponade.
We're gonna do surgery to find the rupture and plug it up.
What are you waiting for? Send me to the operating room!
O Su Jeong, come on, to the operating room.
Yeah, to the operating room.
Find someone who can do the surgery.
Hurry up.
What are they doing? Why aren't they here yet?
90/110
Yeah, it's fine.
Hold on, Cha Yeong Min.
You'll make it.
Answer the phone.
I'm going crazy.
His blood pressure is falling.
He will die if it goes on like this.
Why is nobody coming?
Please, just this once.
Please.
Till now,
I have saved so many lives with operations.
Is it fair that no one in this operating room can save me?
Him out of so many doctors! Why him!
There's no time! Call the Emergency Room now!
Hand me the scalpel.
What are you doing?
Don't tell me you...
Just give me the scalpel.
It is just your first year.
What do you want to do?
Didn't you just say he was going to die?
Are we just gonna let him die?
Go Seung Tak.
There's no time. Give it to me.
I can't take responsibility for that.
What are you talking about?
Dr. O, you have to stop him.
He knows the theory, but he's awful with the scalpel.
You're putting my life in the hands of a brat like him?
His blood pressure went down again.
If we wait any longer...
Wait.
Okay. I know you're trying to do something to save me.
That's nice.
But have you ever used a scalpel?
Fine. I know there's no other way right now.
Calm down.
Just calm down and take a deep breath.
Inhale, exhale, inhale, exhale.
Good. I've been through this before.
I know you're scared.
You've never done it before. Of course you're scared.
But you know…
When I was an intern…
I know you can do it too.
Not everyone can do it, though.
Anyway, I mean…
You have to believe you can do it.
Go through the procedure in your head first.
Your theoretical knowledge is as rich as a professor!
Not there, brat.
Do you have a problem with me?
Probably.
But not now.
Save me first.
You can't take your revenge here.
I told you not there!
Dr. Go, what are you doing?
Will you do it or not?
What's going on?
How is that possible...
Ah-ah.
Hey! Go Seung Tak!
Let's start.
O Su Jeong, come and be my assistant.
Wake up!
Come on!
Drill!
Saw!
Retractor!
My…
My heart.
-=Preview of the next episode=-
Now, my hidden talent has been revealed.
I can't even loaf on the job anymore.
Doesn't he know what's happening to him?
Come with me.
Come on. Go Seung Tak.
Nurse Jeong, be careful!
Nurse Jeong, can you be serious?
Comatose ghosts can't possess.
But you actually can...
Dr. An, where's that guy?
Who is this guy?
My surgery was perfect.
I bet you took the oath before you joined Thoracic Surgery Department.
When you took up the scalpel in the operating room that day,
you weren't trying to save me, but to kill me!