[The World I Love - Liu Yuning]
♫ Dark night, wet moon, and cold blood ♫
♫ Made the naked pupils in my eyes afraid of the light ♫
♫ Is it bright and warm? ♫
♫ I can only guess based on intuition ♫
♫ Ah, love pouring over the world like jade, granting me good luck ♫
♫ Ah, the thread of love is coiled strongly around me ♫
♫ I do not fear  ♫
♫ How people treat me in this world ♫
♫ Breaking through, struggling to escape ♫
♫ How to differentiate between good and bad ♫
♫  There are times when I'm fragile ♫
♫  To heal wounds with a kiss of love ♫
♫ My existence ♫
♫ Thorns won't break my wings ♫
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 27]
You've been standing here all night, Your Majesty.
Your injuries haven't healed yet.
Would she have died if Pianran and Ye Qingyu arrived a little later?
The imperial physician said she had been so close to death.
I ask her to live well,
she should do as she's told.
Her life belongs to me. Without my permission,
she is not allowed to die.
Your Majesty, someone asks to see you.
Ask him to go.
It's Pang Yizhi. He said he had to see you, Your Majesty.
Scholar Pang, what did you come for?
Your Majesty, you've addressed me wrongly. Sheng Kingdom has been conquered,
so I'm not the Sheng Kindom's Scholar of the Ministry of Ceremonies but a disciple of Xiaoyao Sect.
I came to make a divination for you to exchange for one thing.
What's the thing?
Don't you want to know what the divination is about?
No.
Emperor Jin, I can't hold anything back, so I have to say it
whether it's good or ill luck, or I'll go crazy.
From the divination image,
you'll suddenly lose your love
and live in pain and regret the rest of your life.
Cannot reclaim your love and be trapped in the underworld.
It seems you don't want your tongue anymore.
Emperor Jin, be patient. I haven't finished my words.
There are two chances showed in the divination image.
One is in thunder. The other is in water.
What do you mean?
You know, I'm not proficient.
Sorry, I can't explain it.
What do you want to exchange it for?
I want a bottle of your heart blood.
Scholar Pang, what makes you think I would give it to you
after hearing your nonsense?
You have the whole world under you.
Of course, I was not fully confident that you would give it.
However, I have a thunder-series artifact.
If you give me your heart blood, I'll repay you with it.
What is it?
This is Yin-Yang Twin Bracelets, made from thunder iron. It's an artifact of Xiaoyao Sect.
When two people wear one of the bracelets, the owner of Ying bracelet won't die
if the owner of Yang bracelet is alive.
The reason is that the lifespan of the owner of Yang bracelet
has offset the disasters of the owner of Ying bracelet.
Yet, once you put on the bracelet,
you can't take it off.
Offset disaster.
I'm willing to offer the artifact in return for your heart blood.
Pang Yizhi, what do you want the blood for?
It has nothing to do with you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
We don't know his purpose. Besides, your heart has been injured.
I beg you to think well.
Nian Baiyu. Dagger.
Thank you.
Martial Nephew, I've been practicing martial arts
and learning divination for many years. What is it for?
I can't change what has happened or save my friends.
You're my friend.
Now, I'll make divination for you.
Xiao Lin, if you were still alive,
you would certainly admonish me from doing this.
Now that you're in the underworld, you can't stop me.
Just let me do what I want to.
From now on, our fates have become one.
Are you all right, Your Majesty?
Take her pulse again.
Your Majesty, her pulse is recovering quickly.
She'll wake up in a few hours.
You can all leave.
Yes.
Your Majesty, are you okay?
When Ye Xiwu wakes up, lock her up in the Cold Palace.
No one is allowed to visit.
She's now my weakness. If she's killed,
my life span will be reduced.
Yes.
Remember, don't talk about the bracelets to anyone,
including Ye Xiwu.
Yes.
Your Majesty, how do you want to deal with Ye Bingchang?
Have you found why she tried to kill Ye Xiwu?
She said Ye Xiwu caused Xiao Lin's death.
As Xiao Lin's widow, she wanted to avenge his death.
The person who killed Xiao Lin was not Ye Xiwu
but me.
Don't kill her.
Put her in the dungeon. Don't let her go unless she dies.
Yes.
Your Majesty, why does Pang Yizhi want your heart blood?
I think he's up to no good.
And I'm afraid it will be detrimental to you.
Your Majesty, I beg you. Please take care of your health.
I don't care about it.
What did you put in there?
Dry mylabris.
One tiny sip...
is lethal.
Did you cook this porridge for me specifically?
No, Tantai Jin. I didn't want to kill you.
It's all wrong...
Li Susu, are you giving up?
This is...
Barren Abyss.
Li Susu.
Senior Jize.
I failed to kill the Devil Lord.
I've let down your trust.
I'm sorry.
You not only feel guilty to me, but also feel guilty to Tantai Jin.
Right?
Guilty?
I'm surprised that despite being convinced I wanted to fatally poison him,
he was still willing to marry me...
and be with me forever.
Senior, whether he is a demon or a god, since he loves me deeply,
how can I not be guilty?
Silly...
Let me tell you. Even if you and Tantai Jin didn't have such chaotic lives,
this would be how you and Tantai Jin end.
Li Susu, in this lifetime,
the fate of you two has already been written.
Whatever you do will have the same ending.
If you don't want to owe him, you have to owe the world.
In Barren Abyss, I mentioned
a dream, a teardrop, and a thread.
Have you understood them?
The tear is Soul-slaying Teardrop.
The silk is Tantai Jin's love thread.
The dream...
Was it Enlightened Life?
Since you've guessed right,
why haven't you woken up yet?
What do you mean?
What are you doing?
Sang Jiu, I'll take the punishment for you.
When my immortal body vanishes,
my divine essence will replace your devil bone.
Mingye, let go of me!
My divine essence will replace your devil bone.
Everything happens for a reason.
Don't indulge in foolishness.
Seize the chance.
My divine essence will replace your devil bone.
If he loses the evil bone, Devil Lord won't return to life.
With the power of the lightning punishment,
Mingye replaced my demon bone with his divine essence.
So similarly, I can replace the evil bone with my divine essence.
But now my body has no power,
let alone divine essence.
What should I do?
That hurts.
With my weak body,
how can I build divine essence and trigger the lightning punishment?
It's a gem that I forged with the divine essence of the entire Flying Serpent clan.
This tiny piece contains the powers of immortals.
It's capable of overturning Heaven and Earth.
Why don't I call it World-alluring Jade?
World-alluring Jade!
That explains it.
This is the succession of cause and effect.
What is this place?
This place looks so familiar.
I feel I've been here.
This is where Tantai Jin lived when he was little.
This is the Cold Palace.
Have you ever seen your mom?
I haven't either.
They say I don't have a mom.
Yue Ruanruan.
You're awake.
How are you feeling?
Here. Eat the medicine.
What's this bracelet for? Why can't I take it off?
I don't know it. It looks like a divine weapon or artifact.
Did Tantai Jin put it on you to stop you from escaping?
I won't escape.
Then, eat the medicine and get well.
Being alive is the most important thing.
They said you didn't eat or drink.
I thought you didn't want medicine but wanted to die.
How can it be?
Good. I've lived for so long
and have known that where there is life, there is hope.
Cheer up.
If I go all out to absorb power from World-alluring Jade,
I'll definitely be devoured completely.
Even if I die, I mustn't die before completing this thing.
Jize's barrier won't last long. I have to hurry.
Your Majesty, this is the elixir refined by the warlocks today.
Your life was reduced for Ye Xiwu.
I'll make the warlocks refine elixirs day and night to extend your life.
This is a drop in the bucket.
But it might be good.
If I'm still alive, Ye Xiwu won't die.
She mustn't die.
I'm not done with her.
Your Majesty, it seems Ye Xiwu doesn't want to kill herself anymore.
She ate the meals we sent today.
Did she?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Why don't you go see her?
Ask her about the origin of the spikes,
so that we can find out how to pull them out.
Nian Baiyu.
As long as she's alive,
I don't want to know if she has meals or anything trivial like that.
I'm not interested.
Yes.
What a pity.
When I'm devoured by the World-overturning Jade,
I won't see the stars clearly.
Will I...
not be able to see Tantai Jin's face clearly too?
Tantai Jin, I owe you in the lifetime.
But now my life doesn't belong only to me anymore.
I will repay you with my life.
As expected, with World-alluring Jade,
my cultivation has advanced considerably.
If I speed it up, the divine essence should be completed soon.
It was almost there.
His Majesty has been working diligently lately.
Old guys like us can't keep up with him, huh?
But isn't His Majesty too harsh with regulating us officials lately?
[Chenming Hall]
I'm afraid His Majesty has been in a terrible mood lately.
It's more than a bad mood.
His Majesty seems to have health issues these days.
Could the rumor be true that His Majesty's meridians are badly injured and will die soon?
Don't say that. Stop talking nonsense. Let's go.
This puppetry spell is recorded in the Yiyue Tribe's ancient books.
But it usually can only control one person.
After I improve it with Chixiao Sect's instrument forging methods,
you will be able to control thousands.
Mighty Ruo Water,
control the souls.
Wake up.
These civilians King Sheng sent us
will be your soldiers to fight for you and listen to your commands.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
With the ten thousand Nether Soldiers, our great plan will definitely succeed.
Your Majesty, recently in the southern borders,
suspicious people have been seen again.
They turn civilians into puppet demonic soldiers and wreak havoc everywhere.
They are large in number and are no longer small groups like before.
Did you find out who's behind this?
According to the scouts, the southern borders are covered by miasma.
The source of these demonic soldiers seems to be deep in the poisonous miasma.
They can't probe deeper since only Sheng civilians are involved,
so most ministers think this can be ignored.
Although they are remnants of Sheng, they're people of Jing now.
Go investigate immediately.
Yes.
Your Majesty, there's another thing.
What is it?
Ye Xiwu was found unconscious on the ground this morning.
Now she is awake.
We couldn't find out the cause.
We can only presume it's due to her weak body.
Also, her hearing seems to have declined.
And she has poor eyesight.
It could be due to her being kept inside for a long time.
Your Majesty, please send a doctor to treat her.
No need to report
as long as she's not dead.
Why is the water filled?
When did this happen?
Congratulations, Your Highness, your spell has been completed.
Now with the Ruo Water Puppets to fight for you, you can devour the demonic energy without limit.
You can definitely kill Tantai Jin and get back to the throne.
You don't need to comfort me.
I'm perfectly aware.
Swallowing demonic cores and devouring the demonic energy
is the cause of this appearance of being between life and death.
My days are numbered. I'll die soon.
All this is because I won't accept my fate.
I'll do anything...
to fulfill my ambition.
But you... You've been following me since I was young.
I must thank you.
I've been following you since you were young and weren't made the crown prince.
I'm willing to follow you till the end.
Spread the news that I'm on the southern border.
When Tantai Jin knows, he'll definitely come personally.
I'll drag him into hell with me.
This fight between us won't stop till death.
It can never be reconciled.
Since you have such a resolution, you'll definitely succeed.
I'm willing to assist you with my life.
My men, listen! Let's go to war!
Your Majesty, we've found that the mastermind behind the demonic soldiers is indeed Tantai Minglang.
Now he's hiding on the southern border and controlling civilians with demonic spells.
He gathered ten thousand puppets and has a demonic woman cultivator with him.
According to the chamberlains of Sheng Palace,
it was this woman who advised King Sheng to hold rituals with your mother's bones.
I shall...
personally...
fight this war.
Wise decision!
[Jing Capital]
With the World-alluring Jade's side effects,
my body can't last for too long.
I'm about to forge the divine essence.
With it, I'll be able to trigger the lightning punishment.
I hope there's still time.
Your Majesty, according to the refugees who got out,
thick fog started to appear a few days ago.
And the people in it will lose contact with the outside world.
This should be...
Tantai Minglang's place of demonic cultivation.
Your Majesty, there should be a lot of trapped civilians inside.
I've sent men go probe in there first.
The troops will pass after safety is confirmed.
- What is going on?
- What's that?
Have them come out now. Something's not right.
- This fog is poisonous.
- I'll go rescue them.
The poisonous miasma is too dangerous to go in.
Oh my, Third Brother, you're so alert.
But the entire southern border has been turned into a poisonous fortress.
I guarantee that anyone who enters shall not return.
Your abilities to control little animals won't be of use here.
Let this place be your
burial ground.
This terrain is quite dangerous.
I'm afraid Tantai Minglang has troops waiting in ambush.
I must first clear the poisonous miasma to reduce our casualties.
What? What's going on?
- What happened?
- Look! What's that?
- It's the miasma.
- It has dispersed!
- Your Majesty.
- Looks like the rumor is true. His heart and meridians are truly injured.
Let me see how long your injured heart can last.
Spread my order. Whoever kills Tantai Jin shall be a marquis.
Kill Tantai Jin!
We mustn't fight a protracted war. The southern border is full of danger.
We have to keep our morale up by fighting a quick battle.
Baiyu, follow me closely.
Yes. Go.
Protect His Majesty.
Charge!
Tantai Jin is eager to save his people.
He's forcing out his power.
Let's just let him show off for now.
When his power runs out,
my preparations should be finished.
Fu Yu, I'll go first.
You come later.
Tantai Jin,
let's see how much longer you can hide.
You'll regret it
after you occupied the poisonous fortress.
Why isn't General Ye at the battle ground?
His Majesty already secured multiple victories.
But you're here wielding your weapon.
Does His Majesty not trust you?
That's not true.
His Majesty told me to guard the capital in case the rebels launch a sneak attack.
Tantai Minglang is a treacherous one.
His Majesty gives this important mission to me.
It means he trusts me.
It seems General Ye takes the idiom sleeping with your weapon literally.
(To be prepared for battle)
Well, I'm different.
I just want to stay in the capital and shy away from work.
Chief Pianran, how do you know
if I'm sleeping with my weapon or not?
Ye Qingyu,
you've been corrupted.
Focus on your practice.
I'll go check on the city gates.
Look at those dark clouds.
How unusual.
There's thunder.
The lightning punishment is coming.
Ye Xiwu, you must hang on.
- The sky looks weird.
- No, it's not.
This seems like an ominous sign.
Is His Majesty suffering a defeat in the war?
We've only lived a few peaceful days.
- Don't tell me...
- News of victory!
News of victory!
With His Majesty taking the lead,
our troops smashed into enemy territory.
We will conquer the poisonous fortress soon.
We've captured more than 3,000 rebels and saved over 10,000 civilians.
Is today some kind of festival?
Why's everybody so excited?
Don't you know it yet?
The rebel Tantai Minglang has been defeated.
Your Highness, I've found a side door to the old city
at the northwest corner of the Jing capital.
Since it's recently being renovated, few people go through it
and there aren't many guards there.
What's your business?
Material delivery.
Stop for a routine inspection.
You don't look familiar.
Are you carrying any prohibited goods?
Enemy attack!
Tantai Jin, I didn't expect there would be someone you actually care for in this world.
I'm surprised.
It's the thunder.
I'm about to succeed.
What happened?
Run!
Tantai Jin, I'm coming.
Your Highness, the gate to the Jing capital is open.
You'll achieve your ambition very soon.
Well done.
Where do these burglars come from? How dare you trespass my territory?
A fox demon wants to guard Tantai Jin's city?
I like eating black-hearted demons the most.
A mixture of human and demon like you perfectly suits my taste.
Your Highness, the Ruo Water Puppets are ready.
Mighty Ruo Water, control her soul.
Please enter the palace first.
Leave this fox demon to me.
Try your best.
Yes.
Go.
Slay our way in!
Attack!
Don't hurt innocent civilians!
Are you being serious with me?
Demon-hunting Crossbow!
Fu Yu!
Ye Qingyu!
Pianran, look at me.
I have something to say to you.
I've failed my kingdom and family.
Now I die for protecting the civilians
and protecting my loved one.
This death is worth it.
What are you talking about? You won't die.
I won't let you die.
Ye Qingyu.
I thought I would never be as good as Jiang Rao.
Because he's already dead.
He'll live in your heart forever.
I didn't expect that now I'm also...
Ye Qingyu, you're not Jiang Rao.
And don't even think about becoming Jiang Rao.
You are Ye Qingyu.
♫ Ingenuine affection is also enough ♫
♫ Sincerity makes flirtation hard ♫
Pianran,
if only I could have met you
earlier.
♫ Although fireworks are short-lived, they are easily enjoyed ♫
♫ But this time, who will be the one ♫
So I could have fallen in love with you earlier.
To dote on you.
Pianran, demons live much longer than humans.
Will you still remember me
after a few hundred years?
You jerk!
If you dare to die,
I'll forget everything about you!
Just forget about me.
Don't feel sad for me.
After living the best days of my life with you,
there's nothing I regret...
when I leave the world.
What a shame.
We...
can't leave the world together.
♫ I no longer take the passing of time seriously ♫
♫ But I never forget your utterance, "No regrets" ♫
Ye Qingyu!
You fool.
You think I'd make the same mistake twice about the same thing?
Losing Jiang Rao made me suffer so much.
I can't lose you again.
Please forgive my selfishness.
If fate has a plan for us,
we will meet again someday.
Let me,
let your Pianran,
leave the world first.
Qingyu.
In the past, I couldn't see my heart
because I lost my love thread.
Now, my heart belongs to you.
It only belongs to you.
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Black Moonlight - Zhang Bichen and Mao Buyi]
♫  Mortal desires are like gazing upon the sudden disappearance of the moon  ♫
♫  The mortal world is like three thousand flowers in the midst of a snowstorm  ♫
♫  Compassion is embracing a butterfly during times of ruin and pain  ♫
♫  Realization is washing away our memories in turbid water and rain  ♫
♫  We'll never meet again  ♫
♫  I've seen the flowers bloom from soft-spoken words  ♫
♫  Teary-eyed till all that's left was nonsense  ♫
♫  Love intertwines around the fragile titled roof  ♫
♫  Embracing the endless lingering fear  ♫
♫  I've admired you through the myriad of years  ♫
♫  I believed I have been loved for a moment  ♫
♫  I plucked the dark feathers that shrouded my body in evil  ♫
♫  And become devout like the flawless moonlight  ♫
♫  Listen to the breathing of the flowers ♫
♫  and how they are just like any other creature  ♫
♫  No matter how far we walk, through the dust, wind, and stars  ♫
♫  The moonlight is my armor  ♫
♫  I'd admire your arrival when you came covered in scars  ♫
♫  And willingness to live a life in peace  ♫
♫  You plucked the dark feathers that shrouded your body in evil  ♫
♫  And learned to love what you used to resent  ♫
♫  Despite living insignificant lives, our dreams are as big as the sky  ♫
♫  And we'll make it something to remember us by ♫