[The World I Love - Liu Yuning]
♫ Dark night, wet moon, and cold blood ♫
♫ Made the naked pupils in my eyes afraid of the light ♫
♫ Is it bright and warm? I can only guess based on intuition ♫
♫ Ah, the thread of love is coiled strongly around me ♫
♫ I do not fear how people treat me in this world ♫
♫ Breaking through, struggling to escape  ♫
♫ How to differentiate between good and bad  ♫
♫  There are times when I'm fragile, to heal wounds with a kiss of love ♫
♫ My existence ♫
♫ Thorns won't break my wings ♫
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 14]
It hurts badly.
It's not right.
If my injury is healed, will the demonic energy come back?
Forget it, I can't hold back Mingye.
But will Mingye care about my sincerity?
The two gods wanted to test the king's sincerity.
One transformed into a small white dove and the other transformed into a hawk.
The hawk chased the white dove and the dove pounced into the arms of the king.
The white dove pleaded with the king, "Please save me, save me quickly."
The king, being a sincere person, said to the hawk, "You can eat my flesh."
The hawk said, "I can eat your flesh,
but I want to eat the amount of flesh that is the same weight as the dove.
Otherwise, won't I get the short end of the stick?"
The king agreed, so he had someone bring a scale.
He put the dove on one end of the scale and cut a piece of flesh
from his leg and placed it on the other end.
Guess what happened?
The weight of the flesh was not enough.
So the king cut another piece of flesh from his leg and placed it on the scale. But it was still not enough.
He cut all the flesh from both legs, but it was still not enough.
Why? I have seen doves before.
Doves are much smaller than the herring in our river.
That's because these two gods wanted to test the king's sincerity.
However, what they didn't expect was that the king stood up with difficulty
and threw his entire body onto the scale to exchange the dove's life.
As a result, it was the king's sincerity that moved the gods.
The king's body was completely restored, and he ascended to become a god.
However, I still don't understand why someone's sincerity needs to be tested by cutting their flesh and blood.
So many people pray to the gods, claiming that they are sincere.
If he is not faced with unbearable suffering,
how can we know if he is truly sincere?
I can't give in.
I can't let Mingye worry about me.
I haven't seen Sang Jiu these days.
Where is she?
Could it be true, as Tian Huan said?
No. I have to go and ask her.
Mingye, I'm going back to the Mo River for a few days.
No need to worry about me.
Is she avoiding me?
♫ I want to borrow the setting moon that hangs at the edge of the sky ♫
Wars have been frequent recently.
I wonder if Sang Jiu has returned from the Mo River.
Why can't I meet her?
I miss Mingye so much, but I can't go to him.
♫ I want to suspend a dream where I can exchange my tears for your return; My heart's in flames ♫
♫ Otherwise, we will spend ten thousand years like this ♫
Mingye, I heard that you went to battle again.
I pray for your safety.
I have had feelings for you for a very long time.
♫ And the saltiness of my tears ♫
♫ be your repayment and my debt ♫
♫ Did you know even the wisest soul ♫
♫ lightly hesitated before crossing into the territory of their enemy? ♫
♫ A heart ravaged by love and hate refuses to fly away ♫
♫ Did you know one glance from your hardened heart is like piercing my bone with a sword ♫
♫ If fate is a calamity, I cannot help but want to resolve it ♫
♫ but want to resolve it ♫
Mingye, when can you see my sincerity?
Before, my nanny always said when she couldn't sleep at night,
she had to gather demonic energy to make pearls so as to pass the time.
She actually accumulated a full bag of pearls.
I once made fun of her,
but I didn't expect that I am doing the same so soon.
When my shift is over, I must go back and find Sang Jiu.
Even if she is really avoiding me, I must see her.
Report! The traces of a demon group have been found 300 miles away, but they don't have any intention to attack.
They are gathering towards the Demon Realm.
Towards the Demon Realm?
Yes.
Follow me.
Let's go spy on them.
Yes.
All gods arrive.
Mingye, did you find any information during your search in the Demon Realm?
The Devil Lord did take action and has sinister intentions.
Therefore, I have summoned everyone to discuss a solution.
This time, I sneaked into Barren Abyss
and discovered that the Devil Lord is practicing am array called All-in-Distress Way.
It seems that this array can devour all pure energy in the world,
causing all living beings to die and demons to thrive.
If he succeeds, wouldn't this world become purgatory?
We mustn't allow him to open the All-in-Distress Way!
But now, it seems that the Devil Lord is like an arrow on the bow, ready to be released.
How can we stop him?
Is there no way to kill the Devil Lord?
Mingye, since you called us here, do you have any good ideas?
Yes.
When the Devil God practices the array, he will extract the evil bone
and personally guide the foul energy of Heaven and Earth.
As long as the evil bone is not destroyed, the Devil Lord won't die.
So, when the evil bone leaves his body, the Devil Lord can be killed.
This will be the only chance.
But the evil bone connects the Devil Lord and the All-in-Distress Way.
How can we get it?
That's right, Mingye.
How should we assist you?
And what do you plan to do?
We can set up an ambush near the Devil Palace.
When the array is activated, the Devil Lord has to defend the center of the array.
At that time, I will do my best to force him away from the center and stop the array.
Then I will go with you.
There are many demon soldiers in the palace, but I can use the power of the God of the Cosmos to freeze time
and separate the demon soldiers with the Time Freeze Trap.
This way, you only need to deal with the Devil Lord alone.
I'm the God of the Universe.
I can be anywhere in the universe, so I can take advantage of the Devil Lord's unpreparedness
to take the evil bone away from the Devil Palace and seal it in the Heavenly Pillar.
The Heavenly Pillar is the supreme place in the universe, where the spiritual veins of Heaven and Earth converge.
It is indeed capable of sealing the evil bone.
The God of the Sun, please grant the Nine Celestial Bodies and Big Dipper Array.
It seems that it's time to use this array.
Indeed. To trap the Devil Lord, we can only use this array.
The Nine Celestial Bodies and Big Dipper Array are granted by the heavens.
This array was created to imprison demons. Once it is activated, both gods and demons will be trapped
and unable to escape, except for Chuhuang who can control space.
Mingye, are you sure about this?
The Devil Lord was born from the foul energy of Heaven and Earth.
What nurtures him is the endless pain, sadness, and hatred in this world.
As long as there is pain and sorrow in this world, the Devil Lord will be immortal.
Even as gods like us, we cannot match him.
Now we can only gamble on this last chance.
When Jize and Chuhuang leave,
I will use my true form to hold the Devil Lord, trapping myself with him in the array.
I won't give up until death.
You don't have to worry about me. Even if I'm trapped in the array, it's nothing.
I can just risk my divine body to fight until death.
It's not a big deal to me.
Since you are so brave and risking your lives, why should we save our divine power?
If necessary, we can burn up all of our divine power.
When the nine celestial bodies are in alignment, I will move them
and rain down celestial punishment to assist you in killing the Devil Lord.
Under the punishment, everything will be destroyed and the Devil Lord will not be able to escape.
Even if we exhaust all gods' divine power, we can only activate the celestial punishment once,
so we must aim carefully.
I might not come back from this journey.
I bid my farewell.
From now on, the survival of all living beings in the Three Realms will depend on you.
Little Mingye, you can go.
Don't worry, we will take this responsibility.
I, Jize, am honored to know you all.
I have lived a fulfilling life in the Shangqing God Realm for tens of thousands of years.
Now, I have no regrets.
After seeing you off this time, I don't know how many of you will return.
Maybe after this battle, there will be no more gods in the world.
It will be a new start.
Everyone, hopefully, we will meet again.
I heard that someone is assisting her in dual-cultivation outside.
So, she probably doesn't need you anymore.
I might not come back from this journey.
I bid my farewell.
From now on, the survival of all living beings in the Three Realms will depend on you.
So be it.
I will die and my soul will be destroyed on this journey.
If Sang Jiu has found the person she loves and stays with,
it's better than being alone in Yuqing Palace for the rest of her life.
[Divorce Letter]
Sang Jiu, I'll let you go.
After I kill the Devil Lord,
and then you can live with the one you love safely and happily ever after.
Did Mingye ask you to give it to me?
Yes, Lady.
Lady!
Ruby.
Goddess.
Send it to Lady Sang now.
Yes.
Mingye.
Mingye!
Mingye. Mingye!
What's the point of sending a piece of paper?
If you really don't want to see me again, just tell me face-to-face.
Mingye. Mingye.
Mingye!
Mingye, say something!
Sang Jiu, you have 24 hours to pack up and leave the Yuqing Palace.
Leave Shangqing God Realm.
What are you talking about? Are you crazy?
What did I do to piss you off?
For so many days, I dare not say or do anything.
I was even afraid to look at you and talk to you for a few moments.
And now you don't even want to look at me. Are you planning to use a piece of paper to drive me away?
From the beginning, it was your father who forced me.
I didn't have any affection for you.
The safety and stability of the Four Continents and Three Realms rely on me,
but you won't stop pestering me.
You asked me to teach you swordsmanship and clear your foul energy.
I'm already tired of these things.
Now, I can only abandon you.
Because I...
bothered you?
Yes.
I did not expect...
♫ Seeing all the colors of the wind, being drowned by the sea of clouds ♫
I tried to avoid you...
and not to bother you, but things still ended up like this.
♫ Tides are outlined by the waxes and wanes of the moon ♫
My dad once told me a story about a king saving a white dove.
♫ Waiting to speak, but thoughts only remain in silence ♫
He told me that the king cut off his flesh to feed the hawk in order to save the dove.
But it was still not enough.
The gods are so unreasonable.
However, I still don't understand why someone's sincerity needs to be tested by cutting their flesh and blood.
That's because these two gods wanted to test the king's sincerity.
However, what they didn't expect was that
the king stood up with difficulty and threw his entire body
onto the scale to exchange the dove's life.
As long as you have sincerity, the gods will definitely be moved.
I thought I had enough sincerity, but the god never turned his head towards me.
Mingye,
I will go back to pack my luggage.
And I will leave...
before the sun is out.
Sang…
♫ I still remember your figure is outlined by the stars ♫
Mingye...
♫ It shines so brightly that I am not able to touch ♫
♫ My crush is frozen by streamers of light ♫
Mingye...
I want to ask you one thing.
Have you ever,
♫ With one glance, my soul was fettered ♫
...even a little bit,
for even one second,
♫ I pray that the rest of my life is only for this moment ♫
had any feelings for me?
♫ I cannot escape fate's rules ♫
Sang Jiu,
♫ I ached and loved before ♫
♫ Actually, the sun and moon can be side by side. Light and darkness can overlap ♫
♫ Love and hatred can have blurry boundaries ♫
♫ The most irreconcilable wish is worthy of the most cultivation ♫
From the moment you and I arrived in the Shangqing God Realm on our wedding carriage...
♫ Maybe, the only way to solve a catastrophe is to make my love into a sword and break the connection between the sky and the water ♫
Why don't you have one, too?
Why are you eating everything you see?
...to the moment you ate the untouched divine fruit,
♫ It can be seen that I travel across wind and snow to be by your side vigorously in the name of love ♫
...and to your each and every move when we were together…
♫ Only to reach this distant farewell ♫
♫ If living is the boundary of good and evil, ♫
Never.
♫ I wish to exchange my thoughts ♫
I've never loved you.
♫ To hate bravely for courageous fulfillment ♫
♫ To love bravely ♫
♫ and then bid farewell courageously ♫
Sang Jiu, you must forget me.
I wish you happiness.
♫  Mortal desires are like gazing upon the sudden disappearance of the moon  ♫
♫ The mortal world is like three thousand flowers in the midst of a snowstorm ♫
♫ Compassion is embracing a butterfly during times of ruin and pain ♫
♫  Realization is washing away our memories in turbid water and rain  ♫
♫ We'll never meet again ♫
♫  I've seen the flowers bloom from soft-spoken words  ♫
♫ Teary-eyed till all that's left was nonsense ♫
♫ Love intertwines around the fragile titled roof ♫
♫ Embracing the endless lingering fear ♫
♫ I've admired you through the myriad of years ♫
♫ I believed I have been loved for a moment ♫
♫  I plucked the dark feathers that shrouded my body in evil  ♫
♫  And become devout like the flawless moonlight  ♫
♫  Despite living insignificant lives, our dreams are as big as the sky  ♫
♫  And we'll make it something to remember us by ♫
Sang Jiu, it's you.
I'm leaving.
I'm here to say goodbye to you.
All right.
I didn't know you could drink.
Okay, it's just what I want.
Sang Jiu, you have something you want to say to me?
No.
Before I go,
I just want to get what you owe me.
What?
You owe me...
a wedding night.
Relax.
I created this toxic orb myself.
It weakens a person momentarily
but not lethal.
Sang…
Sang Jiu…
Oh, it also takes away your voice.
After tonight,
we let go of our grievances...
and go our separate ways.
Sang Jiu,
you and I did not bid farewell properly.
After all, I let you down.
Today...
Right, it is this very day…
We pay a huge price
and prepare for so long.
It's all…
for this fight today.
The Devil's Army has gathered near the Devil Palace.
The Devil Lord is planning to cast All-in-Distress Way over all three realms.
If his plan works, it causes the destruction of all lives.
A complete annihilation.
Are you willing to join me to kill devils?
We will gladly join the fight!
We will gladly join the fight! We will gladly join the fight!
Lord of Monsters! Lord of Monsters! Lord of Monsters!
Lord of Monsters, you have control over 100,000 evil cultivators.
That's a crazy number of followers.
We are all at the Devil Lord's disposal.
You two do not need to call me Lord of Monsters.
Please, call me Dimian.
Oh, you truly care about your own kind, don't you?
Now I see why you fell out with your wife to cross over to the Devil Lord.
I can't imagine what it would be if you ran into her in the battle.
Right now, we have bigger fish to fry.
We need to think of a way to complete our mission.
Greetings, My Lord.
Today, I will unite all three realms.
The array of All-in-Distress Way will suck all the pure energy out of the universe.
and fill the world with foul energy.
Before long, all living things will turn evil.
We will come together to share the everlasting desolateness.
Siying, Jingmie, Dimian, offer your devil energy.
Use the devil artifact as a medium and assist me to create the array.
So that's the Devil Lord's ultimate weapon of mass destruction, huh?
It is your great honor to protect the initiation of the All-in-Distress Way.
Let all things be desolate.
Chuhuang, I'll leave it to you.
Mingye, how are you holding up?
Where are you now?
What have you been up to since we parted ways?
The war must be still occupying your time, I guess?
I cannot help myself from thinking about you sometimes.
I'm worried that you might be injured.
I just hope you live well.
Mingye.
You're still alive.
I dare not to die since demons are not yet destroyed.
We have to stop the Devil Lord before the array is successfully executed.
Time is of the essence.
I'll be off to the Demon Realm first.
The Devil Lord isn't our only problem there.
There are also three other Devils and tens of millions of soldiers.
You're hopelessly outnumbered.
You cannot stop the Devil Lord if you go by yourself first.
That's all the more reason for me to go first.
I can lure away those three sidekicks of his, leaving him all alone.
This is outrageous.
Jingmie, step aside.
Mingye did manage to keep them off the offering altar.
Let's just hope everything goes as planned.
Mingye, I'm ready.
Devil Lord, your turn.
- How dare you disrespect His Lordship?
- Kill him.
This is the Cage of Time Freeze.
If you want to go back in time and lose your powers, by all means, go ahead.
- Attention, heavenly soldiers.
- Yes.
Today, follow me to kill all demons.
We will purge the Demon Realm. No retreat until death!
No retreat until death!
Devil Lord, you actually created such an evil array against Heaven.
If the array is activated, it will lead to the annihilation of all three realms.
With everything gone, so are all sins.
And I will return to nothingness.
Such a shame your followers are under the wrong impression that you'll be ruling the realms with them.
Turns out it's a suicide mission for them.
Jingmie, ignore their soldiers. Break the Cage of Time Freeze.
The truth is, your hands are tied, whatever my real intention is.
The God of the Cosmos' Cage of Time Freeze isn't strong enough to take on my demon soldiers.
Not to mention your divine power.
It can't harm me one bit.
I cannot harm you but our combined powers can.
A portal?
Very good.
I indeed did not expect that blow.
The God of the Universe?
You see, to me,
it doesn't make a difference how many of them die for my cause.
The All-in-Distress Way has been broken and the foul energy has cleared.
Everyone, send in a backup to support heavenly soldiers quickly.
You can stop the All-in-Distress Way.
I see you people came prepared.
Little flood dragon, what else do you want to do?
Oh, I didn't think the Devil Lord felt fear, too.
Aren't you full of surprises?
I'm not letting you get away with it this time.
Today, whether I live or die.
I will kill you.
Oh, yeah?
Well then, show me
what else you're capable of.
I knew it. Removing the evil bone from his body makes him vulnerable.
And once this bone is sealed, we'll be able to take him out, once and for all.
Chuhuang, it's almost time.
I got you.
No, I got you.
It is not over yet.
It's time.
Nine Celestial Bodies and Big Dipper Array, initiate!
Initiate!
What's that?
It's the Nine Celestial Bodies and Big Dipper Array.
As long as it stays intact, no one, not even Lord, can get out of here.
Chuhuang, the evil bone's all yours!
Oh no, my evil bone.
Catch up with His Lordship. Kill all the heavenly soldiers.
The Devil Lord is trying to break through the array. Hold on.
No, he's trapped.
We did it.
Mingye, are you okay?
I'm fine.
The barrier of the array has been cast. Nobody leaves the Demon Realm.
Together, you and I can finish off the Devil Lord.
Stripping him of the evil bone didn't seem to do enough damage to slow him down.
This is going to be a fierce battle.
Fortunately, with the barrier of the array being cast, once the evil bone is sealed,
it's only a matter of time before we eliminate the Devil Lord.
Damn it. I'm stuck in here.
What am I going to do?
That's the trace of Chuhuang's divine power.
Where'd Dimian go?
I thought we couldn't get out of this array.
Follow His Lordship.
What's going on?
Jize, your divine power is drying up because of freezing time.
You have to stop or you're going to burn out of divine essence.
The Devil Lord is gone. What are you waiting for?
- But you…
- Mingye, don't be silly. We both bear a heavy burden.
If one of us has to stay, it'll be me in the limelight. All right?
Trust me.
Jize!
Jize…
I want you to have this phoenix feather. It holds all my divine powers.
No matter where you are, if you want to see me, it will bring you to me at once.
Give me the evil bone.
Unless you walk over my dead body. Don't even think about it.
Chuhuang, hand over the evil bone.
With it, I will become the Devil Lord.
And when I become the lord of all three realms, I can rule the whole universe with you.
Dimian, I thought you were deceived by the Devil Lord, making you untrue to yourself.
But now you're telling me you want the evil bone for your own benefit?
It is for our benefit.
You are the Goddess of the Phoenix Clan.
If I am not the lord of all three realms,
how can I deserve you?
It is absurd.
Don't use me as an excuse to cover up your despicable ambition. It makes me sick.
To my surprise, the dignified God of the Universe
stole from my realm. It was unexpected!
Mingye.
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Black Moonlight - Zhang Bichen and Mao Buyi]
♫  Mortal desires are like gazing upon the sudden disappearance of the moon  ♫
♫  The mortal world is like three thousand flowers in the midst of a snowstorm  ♫
♫  Compassion is embracing a butterfly during times of ruin and pain  ♫
♫  Realization is washing away our memories in turbid water and rain  ♫
♫  We'll never meet again  ♫
♫  I've seen the flowers bloom from soft-spoken words  ♫
♫  Teary-eyed till all that's left was nonsense  ♫
♫  Love intertwines around the fragile titled roof  ♫
♫  Embracing the endless lingering fear  ♫
♫  I've admired you through the myriad of years  ♫
♫  I believed I have been loved for a moment  ♫
♫  I plucked the dark feathers that shrouded my body in evil  ♫
♫  And become devout like the flawless moonlight  ♫
♫  Listen to the breathing of the flowers ♫
♫  and how they are just like any other creature  ♫
♫  No matter how far we walk, through the dust, wind, and stars  ♫
♫  The moonlight is my armor  ♫
♫  I'd admire your arrival when you came covered in scars  ♫
♫  And willingness to live a life in peace  ♫
♫  You plucked the dark feathers that shrouded your body in evil  ♫
♫  And learned to love what you used to resent  ♫
♫  Despite living insignificant lives, our dreams are as big as the sky  ♫
♫  And we'll make it something to remember us by ♫