Timing and Subtitles brought to you by ðŸ‰ Dragon in a Clam ðŸš Team@Viki.com
♫  Dark night, wet moon, and cold blood  ♫
♫  Made the naked pupils in my eyes afraid of the light  ♫
♫  Is it bright and warm?   ♫
♫   I can only guess based on intuition  ♫
♫  Ah, love pouring over the world like jade, granting me good luck  ♫
♫  Ah, the thread of love is coiled strongly around me  ♫
♫  I do not fear how people treat me in this world  ♫
♫  Breaking through, struggling to escape   ♫
♫  How to differentiate between good and bad   ♫
♫   There are times when I'm fragile, heal wounds with a kiss of love  ♫
♫  My existence  ♫
♫  Thorns won't break my wings  ♫
I heard the surviving followers of the Devil Lord,
Siying and Jingmie, lost the demon fetus a while back at the Battle of the Barren Abyss.
That's why they wreaked havoc.
They're trying to find the fetus through the guidance of the devil artifacts.
It doesn't matter if she's Ye Xiwu or Li Susu,
the Devil Lord's threat will always be the biggest obstacle between her and me.
We can't start over until I find a way
to stop the return of the Devil Lord.
Right now, I know nothing about him.
How am I supposed to handle him?
Since he has put Siying and Jingmie in charge of reviving him,
they must have information about the demon fetus.
If I could break free from the Devil Lord's control
then I might stand a chance of stopping his return.
This is the Barren Abyss.
It looks exactly the same as it did in Enlightened Life.
If I want to learn about the Devil Lord,
the quickest way is to venture into the devil's lair
and find Siying and Jingmie.
This place is like a confusing maze.
How do I find them?
Xiaoyao Swordplay.
Find them!
Devil energy is dense in the air
where those two are.
If I use it as a guide, I'll surely be able to find them.
The devil energy here is thick.
It must be that way.
I shall pay them a visit.
That geezer, Dimian, actually ran away.
How did he manage to break free from
His Lordship's Decamillennium Demonic Seal?
Wait!
Maybe he tampered with the charm that he gave us.
I knew this would happen. Why else would he agree to help us so easily?
If I ever see him again,
I will rip him to pieces.
What is that?
It has been 10,000 years.
Siying and Jingmie, do you two remember me?
It's our lord.
During these ten thousand years, how has your mission progressed, Siying?
My apologies for my incompetence, My Lord. It took me 500 human years...
to pinpoint the location of your demon fetus.
He's now hiding in an immortal sect.
I need more time.
As soon as I awaken the evil bone within him, you'll be reborn, My Lord.
I've been trapped in the Barren Abyss for 10,000 years.
How are you so sure he still has the evil bone?
What if it's destroyed?
Can I still return?
I can assure you that the evil bone is indestructible, My Lord.
It carries your will.
It will remain indestructible as all lives across all the Three Realms remain alive
and suffering continues.
The evil bone is all that's left of me.
I can't control the demon fetus's mind with only that.
No one can resist the will of the evil bone.
Nor can one stop your return.
If he goes against me, what do you suggest I do then?
Regardless of whether he's willing or not,
the evil bone will make him suffer
and eventually sacrifice himself for the Devil Lord.
You seem very certain about it.
Rest assured, My Lord.
Except for you,
no one knows the flaw in your plan.
I knew it was you disguising yourself.
What would a demon fetus of 500 years of age
know about His Lordship's resurrection plan devised 10,000 years ago?
Is this how you talk to the Devil Lord?
You're just a mortal lucky enough to be chosen
as His Lordship's demon fetus.
You're not as important as you think you are.
We will collect all three devil artifacts and activate the All-in-Distress Path.
Whether you like it or not,
our real Devil Lord will be brought back to life.
However, if you stay here in the Barren Abyss, I'll play nice with you.
You are, after all, the demon fetus of His Lordship.
You should feel honored.
Honored?
You're wrong there.
I'm not your lord.
Not now and especially not in the future.
You don't get to come and go as you please!
He has joined an immortal sect and is determined to pursue what's good.
He won't listen to our words no matter what we say.
So are we supposed to just let him go that easily?
He is His Lordship's demon fetus, after all.
How can a wolf remain hidden amongst a herd of sheep?
Father.
Susu, you…
I was just roaming around, and I don't know how I ended up here.
Now that you're back, you should go and get some rest.
Father, come inside and have a cup of tea.
I'll go boil some water.
Lord of Monsters?
Dimian?
What is he doing here?
Does he intend to hurt Susu?
Are you the Devil Lord?
No. The Devil Lord has not yet been resurrected.
You're the demon fetus the Devil Lord left behind, aren't you?
It's pretty bold of you to show your face here.
Are you not afraid of the immortal sect disciples seeing you
and eliminating you?
It seems like he doesn't know that I'm a member of the sect.
I guess he didn't come for me.
Is he after Susu then?
You can stop pretending to be a man of virtue, Lord of Monsters.
If I hadn't known you were once the leader of the Demon Clan,
a loyal follower of the Devil Lord who massacred thousands of deities, one of which was Chuhuang,
I would have thought you were someone else.
Who are you?
If he's just a demon fetus,
how could he know what happened ten thousand years ago?
I can't put Susu in danger.
I'll test and find out who he is.
The techniques he's using are from the immortal sect.
But he clearly is a demon fetus.
He should be able to do more than this. I'll try again.
Father!
Susu, don't come over.
You don't know this.
- He is a…
- I know.
I know what you're thinking, Father,
but this man in front of us is Cang Jiumin,
a Xiaoyao Sect disciple, not someone else.
I'm sorry that I can't tell you the reason why.
However, Father, please trust me.
Okay, Susu. Don't worry.
I won't hurt him today.
However, you also have to trust me.
This man's background is far more complicated than you can imagine.
You should stay away from him.
Don't be fooled by him.
I promise you.
As long as he doesn't hurt you, I won't touch him.
I'll also keep this a secret for you.
I see.
It turns out that Lord of Monsters is your biological father.
Only Dad and Uncle Zhaoyou know about this.
Just pretend as if you know nothing in front of others.
Don't blame him.
He is just someone who once degraded to a devil and has a blood feud with the Devil Lord
and had momentarily mistaken you for him.
After all, he's just a repented poor man who is lost and trying to make amends.
Ye Xiwu.
That isn't my name.
The person I know is named Ye Xiwu.
That's not me.
The person you know has never been me.
Tantai Jin, haven't you been lied to by me enough?
But I've never lied to you.
I've always been Tantai Jin and not what you dread that I'll become.
Ye Xiwu, every day
in the past 500 years, I've been carefully recalling every moment I was with you.
Besides, I've stayed in the immortal sect for a while now.
I roughly know what you're worried about.
I'm not the Devil Lord.
Whether you'll tell me the truth or not, I'll never turn into that.
I'll forever keep this a secret for you.
It's better for everyone not to know.
I'll also not breathe a word about Bone-Refining Seal.
There's one more thing.
Bone-Refining Seal isn't the first devil artifact I came into contact with.
There's also a devil crossbow.
I told you I'd been looking for you in the Nether River for 500 years.
There, I discovered
and merged with the God-Slaying Crossbow by accident.
And that force delivered me out of the Nether River.
That's how my master found me.
I don't know how to take it out.
When I woke up, I was already in Xiaoyao Sect.
If you don't believe me, you can ask my master, Sect Leader Zhaoyou.
No need.
Have you recovered?
I just suffered some minor injuries when Bone-Refining Seal backfired.
I'm fine now.
I mean,
the burns you got...
in the Nether River.
They were healed by my master.
Good.
You said Ye Xiwu is just a dream.
However,
in Shangqing God Realm,
I saw the Red Immortal Fruit tree that was cut down...
ten thousand years ago sprout again.
Dimian, the once Lord of Monsters, also has a chance to start afresh.
Do you think there's a chance for Cang Jiumin...
and Li Susu to start over again?
Junior Brother Jiumin, isn't it a good thing that we're in the same sect now?
Why do we have to go back to the past?
♫  Every pair of stars from the east and the west  ♫
♫  were lonely souls in the beginning  ♫
I'm sorry, Tantai Jin. I can't say yes to you now.
Maybe I should leave you
and leave this place for a while
to take my mind off this
and avoid seeing you.
It'll be better for both of us.
Ye Xiwu, do you really believe in Dimian's words
that I'm the Devil Lord?
♫  Don't ask about the right and wrongs  ♫
I've been looking for you for 500 years.
I won't let go of the past easily.
Moreover, I can decide who I am
and who I'm going to be.
I'll prove to you that I'm not the Devil Lord.
You broke into my life in the past.
From now on,
it's my turn to pester you.
You're often in a daze lately, Younger Sister. Is something bothering you?
You're right.
I'm concerned about a defiant demon fetus.
Isn't it the person
who fought against us on the Divine Platform a few days ago?
I know him.
He was my enemy when I went through my tribulations.
Then he really is the demon fetus Yiyue tribe lost 500 years ago.
He should have possessed the supreme power of the Devil Lord.
However, he's deceiving himself in the immortal sect.
This demon fetus keeps disobeying His Lordship.
Unexpectedly, he's your enemy.
This man is insidious, cunning, and full of schemes.
You must not trust him.
When I was facing tribulations in the mortal world, he made me suffer a lot.
It would be hard to achieve our goal by force.
Why don't you let me help you to make it work?
With your help, we'll surely be able to revive His Lordship.
Everyone is worried that the Devil Lord will resurrect.
If they find out the demon fetus is living among them...
Immortal sects will be thrown into chaos,
pushing the blame on each other.
And the demon fetus will have no place to stay
and only be able to return to Barren Abyss.
Brilliant.
This is his past.
We should be able to find his weakness there.
He's also there.
Who?
The man standing next to Cang Jiumin is from the Yiyue tribe.
He's working for Jingmie now.
Are you saying that Nian Baiyu is also in Barren Abyss?
That's right.
Let's do something nice then.
I'll do as you say, Sister.
Sect Leader Qu.
Master.
Your Majesty.
Nian Baiyu?
Jiumin, you know this devil cultivator?
Yes.
He was my attendant in the Jing Kingdom 500 years ago.
When we got separated, I hadn't turned to the devil path.
I went astray later on, and it had nothing to do with him.
In that case, you're turning from evil to good
and coming to Hengyang Sect to look for your old master?
Yes.
Nian Baiyu is loyal and kind.
I believe that becoming a devil isn't in his nature.
I hope you can give him a chance to start over
on account of our years of friendship.
Your Majesty.
Since you've interceded for him, well,
I'll let you stay.
Thank you, Sect Leader Qu.
Thank you, Sect Leader.
Get up.
Your Majesty.
Get up quickly.
Your Majesty, I…
I'm no longer a king
or anyone's master.
Get up.
Baiyu, no matter what happened in the past, you can start
all over again now.
You don't have to stay by my side.
It's up to you whether you want to stay in Hengyang Sect
or go back to the Yiyue tribe.
I want to stay.
Good. It's not easy for us brothers to reunite with each other after centuries.
You should settle down first.
Why are you here?
Yue Ya.
Sect Leader told me to show a devil cultivator to his room.
I didn't expect it to be you.
Why did a disciple from Zixiu Isles become a devil cultivator?
Miss Yue Ya, sorry, I…
Sect Leader asked me to settle you in.
Don't worry. I will do my best to take good care of you.
Come with me, you liar.
This immortal is incredible.
Yes.
Senior Brother, I don't want to deceive you.
There is no room for anyone else in my heart.
I understand now.
Thank you for helping us fight off the monster.
Sister, look.
This is so pretty.
- This is for you.
- Let me have a look.
Mistress Mo Nv, opening a silk workshop is indeed a great idea.
Not only can we help Mistress Siying accomplish the task
but we can also attract some lecherous and arrogant disciples over
to suck their vitality.
No one will suspect us.
I've gone through cycles of reincarnation,
so I'm disillusioned with the world.
I've left Barren Abyss.
It's a charitable deed if I could find you a place to stay.
- Thank you, Mistress Mo Nv.
Someone from the immortal sect is here.
- The immortal sect?
Is anyone there?
Sir, what brings you to my silk workshop?
Bingchang, I liked you
not because of that strand of Love Threads,
but because of who you are.
Unfortunately, I never got the chance to tell you these things,
and our fate has come to an end.
Xiao Lin.
Why are you not saying anything?
Turns out it's a handsome man.
Nothing unusual from the Devil-Detecting Lantern.
I'm Gongye Jiwu, a disciple of the Hengyang Sect on Mount Changze.
I was supposed to go to the capital of Jing Kingdom. I entered here by accident.
My apologies.
It turns out that he has become an immortal sect disciple.
My last name is Mo. You can just call me Mo Nv.
I'm the owner of this silk workshop.
They are all embroiderers.
Miss Mo, there's demonic energy around here.
I worry that there's a demon wandering around.
I don't know if you've run into it.
Sir, I heard there is a demon in the capital of Jing.
Could it have come here?
Don't panic. The Demon-Detecting Lantern in my hand didn't respond.
It shouldn't be somewhere near here.
This is an Exorcising Talisman. Demons are afraid of it.
Paste it on the door for protection.
I'll thank you on behalf of my girls.
By the way, are you going to the capital of Jing?
I can give you a ride in my carriage.
There's no need. It's too much trouble.
Not at all. Fate has brought us together.
I'm going to town to buy silk thread.
It's a little scary to travel alone.
Since it's in the same direction, we can go together.
Thank you, Miss.
Nian Baiyu, you should be memorizing mnemonics in the room.
What are you doing here?
I haven't seen Senior Brother Cang Jiumin all day.
I wonder what he's doing.
Cang Jiumin?
Little Martial Aunt said she wanted to take a trip to Jing Kingdom and clear her mind.
I guess Cang Jiumin has gone with her.
Why did they go to the Jing Kingdom?
Have you come to Hengyang Sect to be a spy?
Why are you asking so many questions?
Why are you so nervous?
I'm just joking. You're such a loggerhead.
His Majesty has gone to the Jing Kingdom.
If the demon fetus is born, the Devil Lord is likely to come back to life.
Susu is naive and kind.
If I take chances, it may lead to a disaster.
I can't stand by and do nothing.
Jingmie's Devil-Sound Spell?
What's the matter?
We've got news from Nian Baiyu.
The demon fetus has gone to the capital of Jing.
Surprisingly, he's a romantic type.
Since he cares so much about that girl, why don't we make good use of that?
Let's threaten him with that girl's life.
This is strange.
This should be a bustling street.
Why is there no one here?
Sir, wait.
Who are you? What are you doing here?
I'm passing by this place and want to spend a night here.
However, the inn is closed. I wonder what happened.
You'd better leave.
As night falls, a demon will run rampant.
It has been more than half a month.
Everyone is terrified, and no one dares to go out.
You should stay in another inn.
Why? Why can't I stay in your inn?
The demon targets solo travelers.
My inn is the only one on this street that hasn't been attacked.
However, it'll happen soon.
I'll be doomed if I don't close it.
This demon is so ferocious.
Why don't you get an exorcist to deal with it?
This demon is so powerful.
The feudal government has tried its best but still can't capture it.
Take my advice. Leave here at once to save your life.
Spirit-Nurtured Female Immortal walks so slowly. I've waited for you for a long time.
It's the opposite direction.
Why do you always follow me?
I finally got a chance to go down the mountain to clear my mind.
Can we just walk in a different direction?
Finally, you speak to me.
I was just wondering why you suddenly became mute, as you were still normal
before you came down the mountain.
You shamelessly follow me around.
You're just like a hooligan.
You've wronged me, Spirit-Nurtured Female Immortal.
I'm not following you.
Even after 500 years, the Water-splashing Festival of the capital of Jing is still held annually.
People from all over will join in the festivities.
I'm a native of the Jing Kingdom. Of course, I will be here.
If you ask me, it's you who is following me.
Tantai Jin!
You learned glib-tongued skills a lot when you were in Xiaoyao Sect, didn't you?
You didn't studiously cultivate there. Aren't you afraid of encountering the demon when going out?
It's fine.
You, Spirit-Nurtured Female Immortal, are here.
You have great luck and can protect me.
I can't win against you. Enjoy yourself. I'm leaving.
I wonder if Junior Sister is doing well.
I should go back after being away for so long.
The capital of Jing can be the last stop.
If I still can't forget Susu,
I'm going to tell Master about this.
Are you in a hurry to get to the capital of Jing?
Why are you in a hurry? To slay the demon?
I'm going there to search for an answer,
but I shall slay the evil spirit when meeting one.
Xiao Lin, I'm evil now.
I wonder what your reaction would be if you found out.
I hear that Emperor Jing is offering a reward for the warlock who kills the demon.
The demon in the capital of Jing seems very vicious.
so you must take care.
See? There's a demon now that you have arrived.
It's not good to have you around, isn't it?
Then you have to kill that evil quickly, Spirit-Nurtured Female Immortal.
Don't lose your reputation.
It's you.
Shopkeeper, we want to stay here.
Do you have a death wish?
I came to kill that demon.
Miss, why don't you take my advice?
Don't worry. Just give me one room.
Shopkeeper, I'm going to stay here as well today.
Do you… Do you want one room or two rooms?
- One room, of course.
- Two rooms, of course.
Well…
This…
I came out in a rush, without any money.
Would you like for me to sleep on the street tonight?
It's fine. I have money.
Shopkeeper, give him a room.
The further away from mine, the better.
Sure.
How despicable.
Here you go.
Sir, you woke up so early.
Eldest Senior Brother, what are you doing here?
I was worried about you...
You guys... You guys came to the capital?
Yeah.
Eldest Senior Brother, I'm glad that you are here.
You are adept at evil slaying. Give us some advice.
Sure.
Why do you stare at me?
Because you're beautiful.
So based on the clues provided by the locals
and what we know now,
the demon can change appearances and read minds.
Also, when getting dark, they can also deceive divine artifacts.
So the general warlocks had to give up on her.
You have to know yourself as well as the enemy to take that risk.
I read a book called List of Demons with Pictures in Scripture Hall.
It says there's a demon called Yemei.
She can change her looks and loves consuming human brains.
She especially prefers those who have felt the sting of love being rejected.
She will take advantage of you if you are lovelorn.
I've also read the book that you mentioned.
It recommended a divine artifact which can be used to track down Yemei.
However, I can't recall the name
of the divine artifact now.
That's all right.
I can ask the birds and beasts to send a message to the sect.
Then Nian Baiyu can check it out for us in Scripture Hall
and send the divine artifact for us.
I remember it was on a bookshelf around here.
Look at that.
Isn't it the book they're looking for?
Yemei.
I found it. Yemei has a keen sense of smell.
She can smell the fear and love in one's heart.
She is sharp-nosed, so she fears strong smells.
We can pour spell water along the way to limit the area she can walk.
- You're so careless!
- I'm so sorry.
You can deploy the red silk from Lingting Kingdom
along the path she'll pass by.
The red silk will stick to Yemei's body and can't be gotten rid of.
Then the tracker can follow it to find her.
She prefers well-dressed young people who are alone.
And will become the one they are afraid of or love.
She lures people into the fantasy she creates,
consuming their brain at the peak of their fear.
The one they love?
Don't focus on the meaningless part.
The three of us will split up and wait in the streets where spell water isn't spilled.
There's a three-way road with only one exit in the capital.
I will guard the exit.
- I can make sure she cannot escape.
- Good wine.
That's a good idea.
At least one of us will be able to find Yemei.
A good couple loves each other?
It's not as pleasant as this wine.
Heaven and gods above, bless us.
Please don't let anything go wrong.
That's the only property I've got.
Please don't ruin it all.
Beauty, go to sleep now.
Tell me what you love
and what you fear.
Remember to stall the other two for a while.
I don't want them to spoil our plan.
Don't worry, Mistress Siying. I'll get right on it.
What is this?
Why can't I get it off?
Miss, it's late at night.
Why are you here alone?
Miss?
What are you doing?
Wife, you are here.
What?
It hasn't been that long since we've last seen each other, but you already miss me?
Damn it!
I wonder how the other two are faring?
You're Yemei.
Wait. Don't kill me.
I won't kill you.
You will be handed over to King Jing.
He will judge your guilt.
Senior Brother.
I have seen the girl you love.
Do you want to know about her?
You grew up together.
It's you who took care of her and read and cultivated with her.
You've waited for her for ten years.
Even your master thinks you're a man worthy of his daughter.
You and your demonic words.
I love her, and this has nothing to do with anyone.
I don't care who she loves and who loves her.
Seize!
Gongye Jiwu, are you really not curious about it at all?
Cang Jiumin had married her,
slept with her.
Your sect sister who you love is married.
She doesn't love you. She loves someone else.
She's married to someone else.
She doesn't belong to you.
She doesn't belong to you!
Gongye Jiwu, you're lucky this time.
How did this happen?
It's you.
There are signs of a fight here.
This is bad. Susu.
Mistress Siying, I underestimated the power of the demon fetus.
Also, Mistress Mo Nv suddenly…
You are such a disappointment to me.
You can't handle the demon fetus.
You can't even control Gongye Jiwu.
Get up.
Listen. Our target today is the demon fetus.
Nothing else matters.
I need you...
to go back to his immortal sect lover's dream and see what his weakness is.
It's the Water-splashing Festival.
What place is this?
Why are we here?
You brought me here.
Look. How lively it is.
Me?
Bravo!
Why are they wearing masks?
So today is the Water-splashing Festival.
Where is he?
Tantai Jin?
It's…
me.
This is the irresistible weakness of the demon fetus.
Just convince the demon fetus to believe
that Devil Lord is his inescapable destiny.
Mistress Siying, you will get what you want
and control the demon fetus as you wish.
Finally something interesting.
Go and give a big present to the demon fetus.
How could I be here?
This is Barren Abyss.
Why am I back here again?
Devil Lord, it's you again.
What do you want to do by bringing me here?
What do I want?
I want to ask you.
Born as a demon fetus,
yet you think you are the God of War, Mingye.
Keep my look in mind.
This is the only look you'll ever be in the future.
You're wrong!
I used to be a demon fetus.
But now, I'm Cang Jiumin, a disciple of the immortal sect.
If you didn't mention it,
I would have forgotten about that.
Will your fellow disciples
accept you in the immortal sect?
What does this have anything to do with you?
How stupid.
You are clearly a wolf wanting to wear sheep's clothing and
hide among the sheep herd.
Are you joining the immortal sect because of her?
Look. There she is.
Tantai Jin.
It's all over.
You can take off your mask now.
You didn't expect it, right?
It's me.
Tantai Jin.
- All-in-Distress Path lasts forever.
Do you think by tricking my affection,
you can save the lives of the Three Realms?
How ridiculous.
Have you seen it?
Remember the face that scares you.
That's who I am.
No, this isn't real.
This is a dream created by the Devil Lord.
Tantai Jin, you can only be me.
Susu is in danger. I have to go to save her.
It turns out...
that you...
always...
fear me.
Jingmie, why are you hiding here for?
Did you get ready for the thing I asked you to do?
I walked around just now.
It's a lively place here during the Water-splashing Festival.
It's a pity to ruin it.
A pity?
The festival means a lot to the demon fetus.
Only this place can make him realize who he is.
Yes, you're right.
What's this?
This one is me.
The other one is you.
Legend has it that by burning the doll of us together,
evil spirits and disasters can be warded off.
Isn't the earthly custom interesting?
Don't tell me you've developed unnecessary emotions like those mortals.
Remember. Our only task is about the demon fetus.
After 500 years, the Water-splashing Festival looks as lively as ever.
Don't worry. The nightmare is over.
The Devil Lord won't appear at the festival.
The demon yesterday…
So I'm still the one you're most afraid of.
No. I believe what you say.
You're not him.
You will never become that awful look.
How do you know for sure that it wasn't me?
You would never hurt me.
You wouldn't do it before and it's even less likely now.
You used to be Tantai Jin.
Now you are Cang Jiumin, the most kindhearted disciple of Xiaoyao Sect.
You are not him.
Nor will you become him.
I believe in you.
I know now.
What?
I've seen the appearance of the Devil Lord...
the demon made before.
That was the one you showed me from your memory
when it was over the gate tower and in the thunder of the suffering.
♫   My regrets   ♫
♫   In a bird cage, where does karma strike in the next life?   ♫
♫   In the abyss, my heart cries in the rotation of time and space  ♫
♫   In the dark, only you light the way for me   ♫
He's the Devil Lord.
So you know?
Have you known since you arrived at the Xiaoyao Sect?
♫   How did you get so far away?   ♫
Yes.
Ever since I joined the immortal sect, I've always heard
everyone talking about and discussing the Devil Lord.
I'm worried the one they talk about,
the one in their prophecy, is all me.
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid of being exposed one day.
I fear they will discover...
that I'm the demon fetus that everyone
in the immortal sect wants to eradicate so badly.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by ðŸ‰ Dragon in a Clam ðŸš Team@Viki.com
♫  Mortal desires are like gazing upon the sudden disappearance of the moon  ♫
♫  The mortal world is like three thousand flowers in the midst of a snowstorm  ♫
♫  Compassion is embracing a butterfly during times of ruin and pain  ♫
♫  Realization is washing away our memories in turbid water and rain  ♫
♫  We'll never meet again  ♫
♫  I've seen the flowers bloom from soft-spoken words  ♫
♫  Teary-eyed till all that's left was nonsense  ♫
♫  Love intertwines around the fragile titled roof  ♫
♫  Embracing the endless lingering fear  ♫
♫  I've admired you through the myriad of years  ♫
♫  I believed I have been loved for a moment  ♫
♫  I plucked the dark feathers that shrouded my body in evil  ♫
♫  And become devout like the flawless moonlight  ♫
♫  Listen to the breathing of the flowers  ♫
♫  and how they are just like any other creature  ♫
♫  No matter how far we walk, through the dust, wind, and stars  ♫
♫  The moonlight is my armor  ♫
♫  I'd admire your arrival when you came covered in scars  ♫
♫  And willingness to live a life in peace  ♫
♫  You plucked the dark feathers that shrouded your body in evil  ♫
♫  And learned to love what you used to resent  ♫
♫  Despite living insignificant lives, our dreams are as big as the sky  ♫
♫  And we'll make it something to remember us by  ♫