Timing and Subtitles brought to you by ðŸ‰ Dragon in a Clam ðŸš Team@Viki.com
♫  Dark night, wet moon, and cold blood  ♫
♫  Made the naked pupils in my eyes afraid of the light  ♫
♫  Is it bright and warm? I can only guess based on intuition  ♫
♫  Ah, love pouring over the world like jade, granting me good luck  ♫
♫  Ah, the thread of love is coiled strongly around me  ♫
♫  I am not afraid of how the world treats me  ♫
♫  Breaking through, struggling to escape.   ♫
♫  How to differentiate between good and bad   ♫
♫  There are times when I'm fragile, heal wounds with a kiss of love  ♫
♫  My existence  ♫
♫  Thorns won't break my wings  ♫
Here.
What's wrong?
Feeling unwell?
Mozhu, if a friend of yours left you and could never make it back,
what would you do?
What if he died instead of refusing to come back?
If you have a spare moment today,
could you buy some wine for me from the town?
You have not fully recovered. You can't drink.
It's not what you thought. I want it to commemorate my friends.
I heard when a mortal's relatives or friends died,
they would evoke the dead with wine to commemorate and console their souls.
Some of my friends, who were very important to me,
passed away before me.
Where do you think mortals will end up after they die?
Their souls will wander
until they get to the Nether River
and float down the river to the end of the world.
What about gods?
Gods have no souls.
When gods fall,
they'll be completely gone in this world
and can't be seen anywhere.
But when they're remembered, they won't be completely gone.
A new prescription?
Yes. Maybe this one will work.
If I can't recover, don't force it.
Just let it be.
What are you talking about?
Good medicine usually tastes bad. Just take it.
Or what? Never get back your sight and stay here forever for free food?
I don't know where else I can go.
I don't have relatives.
All my friends have died.
My wife…
No.
I have nothing to do with her now.
She hates me.
I'm afraid we won't ever meet again.
How…
How do you feel about her?
I made it clear at the beginning
that we will go our own way. Do not disturb each other.
Mingye, remember to tell me
when you feel any better with your eyes.
Even if you can see a little bit of light.
I have to be prepared.
Prepared for what?
I must get ready
to leave here.
Don't be so nosy.
Just let me know.
Will you always be living here?
Why do you ask?
Now, in this world, you're my only friend.
May I visit you occasionally?
You can't.
After you get your sight back, I'll leave immediately.
Where will you go?
I don't know yet. It could be anywhere.
I'll just travel around, leading a free and happy life.
If you knew it was me,
I'm afraid you wouldn't want to visit me again.
Be careful on the stairs. Come on.
It is a sunny day!
Sit down and let me comb your hair.
- What?
- Just sit down.
It's the jasmine fragrance I made yesterday.
You're lucky to have some.
What… What's wrong?
♫  Flip through the written fabulous years in books  ♫
♫  Dream in circles the remaining flashy and vivid regret  ♫
♫  I would rather not wake up and dreams would not vanish  ♫
♫  A bond of marriage entwined for thousands of years  ♫
I'm fine.
Why are your eyes red?
Nothing. Maybe the fragrance irritates my eyes.
You should have told me. Let me check.
♫  My heartlessness ebbed and flowed like seasons  ♫
♫  My affection ebbed and flowed like seasons  ♫
♫  I couldn't experience endless sorrows or worries  ♫
♫  A fair complexion was not afraid of being soaked in tears  ♫
♫  I only wish to exchange this life with eternity  ♫
♫  Ingenuine affection is also enough  ♫
♫  Sincerity makes flirtation hard  ♫
♫  I still believe in the touched feelings that you gave me  ♫
Do you feel better?
♫  Although fireworks are short-lived, they are easily enjoyed  ♫
♫  But this time, who will be the one  ♫
♫  Waiting for a long while?  ♫
What?
Nothing.
I thought your eyes recovered.
Don't be too sad. Your eyes will recover.
These herbs are very efficacious.
It turns out that the heaven treats me well.
I thought our paths would not cross again.
I did not expect that I could meet you again.
Sang Jiu, if I don't recover,
can we always stay together in this forest?
When I get the chance to tell Sang Jiu the truth,
I'll take her back to Shangqing God Realm.
I then will think of a way to purify her demonic energy and cleanse her essence.
I almost forgot.
My senior brother is coming in a few days.
I totally forgot my lessons lately.
I've nearly recovered.
How about we switch places?
Come and sleep in the bed.
No way. Your eyes haven't recovered.
Then you come up on the bed.
We can squeeze up.
Don't worry. I'm a good sleeper.
I won't disturb you.
All right. Go to sleep.
Fine.
How come he hasn't got his sight back yet?
Tomorrow, I'll go up the mountain for another kind of herb.
It's said to be very efficacious.
Sang Jiu, don't blame me for lying.
I just want us to stay together like this longer.
Even longer.
Mingye.
Here. Take the decoction before it gets cold.
Open your mouth.
So sweet. Is it honey?
Yes. Because you hate the bitter decoction.
Come over.
You got a bee sting when stealing some honey?
Closer.
Even closer.
All right. It no longer hurts.
Report. Goddess!
In a bamboo forest, we found Lord Immortal's trace!
Come on.
Sit here in the sun.
I'll be back before noon.
I'll bring back some bamboo shoots for soup.
Okay.
Oh. If you're thirsty, the water is on the table in front of you.
There are some leftovers in the kitchen.
If the wind rises, you have to put on your cloak.
Yeah, right beside you.
Okay.
I should go.
Mingye!
What are you doing in this place?
You're safe.
But why didn't you return to Yuqing Palace and let me know you are well?
I was badly wounded.
I retreated here and recuperated for some peace.
I am sorry to keep you worried.
You've recovered, right?
Mingye, how much longer will you stay here?
You go back without me. The scenery here is great.
I want to stay longer.
But you've just recovered. You need someone to take care of you.
- How about I stay here?
- No need.
Someone takes care of me here.
If nothing else, I'm going back for some rest.
I have to tell you an urgent matter
concerning a lot of people.
What is it?
Yesterday, heavenly soldiers reported
they found the Devil Lord's Bone-refining Seal in a valley.
That's why I hurried to you.
If the devil's energy overflows, I'm afraid…
The Bone-refining Seal has great devil energy.
If the land or water is polluted,
the consequences can be catastrophic.
We must not delay a single moment.
Let's go.
You two lead the way.
- Yes.
Hold on a minute.
Here we go.
Mingye, you leave with heavenly soldiers first.
I'll fetch a weapon from Yuqing Palace and then catch up with you.
Fine.
Sang Jiu, I'm hurrying to leave for an urgent matter.
Hearing that a devil artifact appeared, I have to go take care of it immediately.
In one to ten days, I will come back
and explain everything to you.
I am sorry to leave without saying goodbye.
I'll always miss you and think of you.
Mingye.
The Bone-refining Seal is there in the center.
Even this crater was made by the Bone-refining Seal.
After the Devil Lord was gone,
I had our soldiers search everywhere
and finally, they found this devil artifact.
Thank you.
Finding the Bone-refining Seal consumed time and manpower only.
Mingye, your complete disappearance for days
was the matter that exhausted me.
Now, the Devil Lord is dead.
Without a master, the Three Devil Artifacts are less powerful.
But their devil energy still pervades for miles.
If we don't stop it,
I'm afraid soon this place will be a shelter for demons.
My father told me the Bone-refining Seal has the most inscrutable functions
among the Three Devil Artifacts.
It can enhance the devil energy
and also make a seal or barrier.
When the heavenly soldiers were captured,
they were deprived of their divine essence, infused with devil energy,
and then became demons.
I really didn't dare to act rashly.
I had our men guard here until I found you.
Deprived of their divine essence?
Sang Jiu is my only daughter and the princess of the Mo River!
For you, she extracted her divine essence and can never become an immortal!
Now, you think you can move on just by saying thank you?
My demonic energy backlashes.
If it can deprive someone of his divine essence,
maybe it can also help Sang Jiu rebuild her divine essence.
I'll go check it out.
Mingye!
This artifact appears to be evil but is moderate inside.
If the artifact is cleansed without devil energy, maybe it can mend its ways
and it can be put into good use.
The devil energy is temporarily held back.
I have to get it out as soon as possible.
The Bone-Refining Seal has huge devil energy
and has gradually infiltrated into the earth.
Powerful as I am, I still can't easily get it out.
It seems that I can only do this.
Heart-guarding Scale.
This is the hardest scale of a flood dragon like me.
Once the scale is injected with my divine power, it can serve as a shield to temporarily isolate the devil energy in the seal.
Mingye, how did it go?
The seal crashed against the earth here.
They're nearly integrating.
To get the Bone-refining Seal, I had to exchange something.
I then exchanged my Heart-guarding Scale for it.
The Heart-guarding Scale was in your flesh.
How could you just pull it out?
The bodily pain wasn't much of a thing.
My father died in the fight against the Devil Lord.
Now, you sacrificed your Heart-guarding Scale
to exchange the devil artifact to grace this region.
You deserve to be the God of War.
If Father knew about this,
he would be gratified, too.
I conjured heavenly rain.
With the protection of my Heart-guarding Scale,
it won't be long before this place has abundant spiritual energy.
Surrounded by mountains,
there's no light in the valley.
Let's call it Mount Buzhao.
(Buzhao means no sun lights.)
It's quite considerate of you, Mingye.
Father had many subordinates and disciples.
Only you followed in his steps
and knew his wishes best.
So, you would also protect
what my father had protected. Right?
Let's go.
Back to Shangqing God Realm first.
So, this is the Sun Quadripod.
Before the world came into being, the Sun Quadripod's four legs represented four seasons.
The fire in it was the sun.
Burning fiercely.
When Tian Hao was alive, he used it to purify demons.
Unfortunately, it would cost the user's energy and shorten his life.
Since then, it has been sealed here.
Purifying the Bone-refining Seal with the Sun Quadripod would really be perfect.
If it works, the purification can be done in four days and nights.
Then, I can use it to cure Sang Jiu.
In the Sun Quadripod, there are spring, summer, fall, and winter.
The four seasons in the quadripod can purify everything.
When I burn my divine essence,
I can wash the devil energy off the seal.
In the future, nature may take its course and lead to something.
Sang Jiu and I can start all over again.
God of War, Mingye.
You can call me Mingye.
Why don't you try one?
Just try one. It's super sweet.
♫  I want to borrow the setting moon that hangs at the edge of the sky  ♫
♫  Suspending the firefly and butterfly until the wind and snow arrive  ♫
♫  I want to suspend them at an inappropriate time to forget everything that's occurred  ♫
Look at the sword, not me.
Are you willing to try dual-cultivation with me?
What?
♫  Otherwise, we will spend ten thousand years like this  ♫
♫  Let's stop time before we say farewell  ♫
♫  Let the sweetness of your slight smile and the saltiness of my tears  ♫
I will die and my soul will be destroyed on this journey.
Sang Jiu,
I will let you go.
It's better than being alone in Yuqing Palace for the rest of her life.
For so many days,
I dare not to say
or do anything.
I was even afraid to look at you and talk to you for a few moments.
Now, you don't even want to look at me.
Are you planning to use a piece of paper to drive me away?
Have you ever... even a little bit
for even one second,
had any feelings for me?
Never.
Sang Jiu.
Now, the Devil Lord has been killed.
Stability has been achieved in Three Realms.
Heaven grants mercy on me.
I will gradually make it up for...
what I owe you.
Wait for my return.
Even if I have to go all out,
I will purify the Bone-refining Seal
and remove the devil energy from you.
Mingye, how could you try to use the Bone-refining Seal
to cure that clam demon who lost her divine essence?
For her, you even take the risk of being possessed to use the Sun Quadripod.
Fine.
Goddess, soldiers have assembled.
Thank you. I lost my parents and made no achievements in battles.
But you still take orders from me,
which scares me.
Don't say that, Goddess.
I and everyone else here followed
your father Tian Hao to settle in Shangqing God Realm.
Though you're young, you're the goddess of flying serpents
and owner of Yuqing Palace.
We don't dare to forget that.
Glad to hear that.
Mingye will have entered a strict meditation retreat for days.
To find the devil artifacts is concerned with people's lives.
It can't be suspended.
I just received the information
the Unionidae Tribe picked up a devil artifact.
Please go with me to search for it.
Yes.
Try to fight with me for Mingye?
Sang Jiu, can you even survive?
Where on earth has Mingye gone?
I've been looking for him in the woods all day.
Without his vision, he couldn't have gone too far.
Did somebody take him?
By order of Lord Immortal, you shall kill the clam demon on sight.
Search the place.
Yes.
It's Tian Huan.
Mingye has already returned to the Shangqing God Realm.
Kill me on sight?
Mingye, is that you trying to kill me?
Goddess Tian Huan, there's nobody here.
Goddess Tian Huan, there's no one outside, either.
Report, there's no trace of the clam demon.
Looks like she is one step ahead of me.
She escaped.
What a pity. She can run,
but she can't hide.
Let's go.
No. I need to find out what that was all about.
What happened here?
These are new faces.
Halt.
Who are you and why are you here?
I…
I'm a low-ranking immortal from the Lower Realm.
And I'm here to see Lord Immortal Mingye.
But you don't even have divine essence.
You are not so much an immortal as an imp.
What do you want to see the God of War about?
I have an urgent matter. Would you please get word to him?
Just give this to him…
What is this bead?
I'm not passing it on to the God of War.
You should just leave.
I wish I could help you, but the God of War is in a 4-day strict meditation retreat.
He's not taking any visitors.
A strict meditation retreat? Why?
Is he not feeling well?
It's an important matter about the Four Continents and Three Realms.
He carries the peace of the world on his shoulder.
If something happened to him in the meditation retreat, who could take responsibility?
What has Goddess Tian Huan been up to?
Being on the same page with the God of War,
Goddess Tian Huan is leading the hunt for devil weapons scattered around the universe.
and evil beings roaming the Four Continents and Three Realms.
If any one of you demons is connected to the Devil Lord,
well, you might want to watch your back.
Mm, be careful.
Since Mingye is tied up with his cultivation these days,
I'll just wait for him.
I have to get to the bottom of it all.
Charge.
If you want to hurt my people,
you'll have to go through me first.
How come this river produces troublemakers?
You should ask yourself if you can take me.
Who are you to fight with me?
Go. Protect Father.
Yes.
Seize him.
You old clam demon, with thousands of years of cultivating,
yet you couldn't even take 100 blows dealt from my Fog Silk Brocade.
And you even call yourself a king?
That's funny.
Your son, on the other hand, was a handful.
But he, too, was defeated by me.
Tian Huan, what do you want?
To wipe evil demons off the map.
I am told the Water Tribe of the Mo River
is in cahoots with the Devil Lord and possesses a devil artifact.
Do you know it's a crime punishable by the extermination of a tribe?
But if you hand over the devil artifact, only the culprit gets punished.
The rest of you will be off the hook.
Nonsense!
We people in Mo River have always lived in peace and stayed in our own lanes.
How can we collude with the Devil Lord?
Is this the way the Gods of the Shangqing God Realm do things?
Framing people for crimes they didn't commit?
We offer protection to the three realms.
I don't need some lowly demon like you to tell me what to do.
So keep your opinions to yourself.
Why are you doing this to us in Mo River?
Have you forgotten the kindness we once showed you and Mingye?
You're right.
I do not have bad blood with people in Mo River.
Do you think I covet your poverty,
your demonic energy,
or these
crappy pearls of yours?
Goddess, should we run this by the God of War?
What do you mean?
Well, he is… he's the son-in-law of the Mo River.
The son-in-law of the Mo River...
This bunch of clam demons forced Mingye into marrying that smelly little clam demon.
He doesn't even like her. He had already divorced her.
How shameless they are to claim kindship with Mingye?
But... But there's no sign of a devil artifact.
That's because you're stupid to find a devil artifact.
It doesn't mean they aren't the Devil Lord's allies.
What?
Found your conscience after killing so many of the Water Tribe members?
Listen to me. They are in league with the Devil Lord.
We may not have found the weapon, but they fought back, which was suspicious.
Anyway, this demon is cunning.
Our heavenly soldiers fought back in an act of self-defense.
Don't worry. Mingye won't blame me for this.
We do not possess any devil artifacts.
But one thing's for sure. You have your demon.
You're jealous because my daughter married Mingye.
That's why you set her up.
I'm jealous of her?
A flying serpent is born to be a spirit beast.
Why would I, the flying serpent goddess,
be envious of an annoying and unsophisticated clam demon?
Do you know?
When her demonic energy flared up, I pretended to look after her.
I added some Ruo Water to the spring.
And I told her that was Essence-Cleansing Spring.
That dumb woman took my word for it and soaked in the water despite the pain.
Tian Huan, how could you be so vicious?
Whatever you do will come back to you.
Old clam demon, you and your Water Tribe will be wiped out today.
All thanks to your good daughter.
Getting involved with my Mingye,
she's bitten off more than she can chew.
Sang Jiu, this is what you get for being against me.
By order of Lord Immortal, you shall kill the clam demon on sight.
Search the place.
Yes.
Why isn't this Image Reflection Pearl working anymore?
It runs on Senior Brother's demonic power.
Is it possible...
Did something happen to Senior Brother?
You're still new to demonic cultivation.
Your demonic energy isn't stable yet.
You need to avoid mood swings,
or you could slip into madness.
No one else in the Mo River is fairer than you, Princess.
You'll surely marry the right man someday.
Oh, you. You have the nerve to say it.
Mingye has divine essence.
And you do, too.
He is the God of War.
But what about you? You follow your brother and me everywhere and do nothing all day.
Have you no shame?
Remember, as long as you are sincere,
Gods will be moved.
It will.
All right, it is time for bed.
I'll read you stories tomorrow.
I am told the Water Tribe of the Mo River
is in cahoots with the Devil Lord and possesses a devil artifact.
Do you know it's a crime punishable by the extermination of a tribe?
We do not possess any devil artifacts.
But one thing's for sure. You have your demon.
You're jealous because my daughter married Mingye.
That's why you set her up.
I'm jealous of her?
Do you know?
When her demonic energy flared up, I pretended to look after her.
I added some Ruo Water to the spring.
And I told her that was Essence-Cleansing Spring.
That dumb woman took my word for it
and soaked in the water despite the pain.
Old clam demon, you and your Water Tribe will be wiped out today.
All thanks to your good daughter.
Getting involved with my Mingye,
she's bitten off more than she can chew.
I'm sorry. This is all my fault.
I shouldn't have fallen for him.
I shouldn't have saved him
and then even married him.
It is all because of my big mistake.
I should've known better,
I regretted.
I'm unworthy to be called your daughter
or Princess of Mo River.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by ðŸ‰ Dragon in a Clam ðŸš Team@Viki.com
♫  Mortal desires are like gazing upon the sudden disappearance of the moon  ♫
♫  The mortal world is like three thousand flowers in the midst of a snowstorm  ♫
♫  Compassion is embracing a butterfly during times of ruin and pain  ♫
♫  Realization is washing away our memories in turbid water and rain  ♫
♫  We'll never meet again  ♫
♫  I've seen the flowers bloom from soft-spoken words  ♫
♫  Teary-eyed till all that's left was nonsense  ♫
♫  Love intertwines around the fragile titled roof  ♫
♫  Embracing the endless lingering fear  ♫
♫  I've admired you through the myriad of years  ♫
♫  I believed I have been loved for a moment  ♫
♫  I plucked the dark feathers that shrouded my body in evil  ♫
♫  And become devout like the flawless moonlight  ♫
♫  Listen to the breathing of the flowers  ♫
♫  and how they are just like any other creature  ♫
♫  No matter how far we walk, through the dust, wind, and stars  ♫
♫  The moonlight is my armor  ♫
♫  I'd admire your arrival when you came covered in scars  ♫
♫  And willingness to live a life in peace  ♫
♫  You plucked the dark feathers that shrouded your body in evil  ♫
♫  And learned to love what you used to resent  ♫
♫  Despite living insignificant lives, our dreams are as big as the sky  ♫
♫  And we'll make it something to remember us by  ♫