[The World I Love - Liu Yuning]
♫ Dark night, wet moon, and cold blood ♫
♫ Made the naked pupils in my eyes afraid of the light ♫
♫ Is it bright and warm? I can only guess based on intuition ♫
♫ Ah, love pouring over the world like jade, granting me good luck ♫
♫ Ah, the thread of love is coiled strongly around me ♫
♫ I do not fear how people treat me in this world ♫
♫ Breaking through, struggling to escape  ♫
♫ How to differentiate between good and bad  ♫
♫  There are times when I'm fragile, heal wounds with a kiss of love ♫
♫ My existence ♫
♫ Thorns won't break my wings ♫
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 9]
Father. Senior Brother. I'm so useless.
I couldn't save the Four Continents and Three Realms. And I didn't stop Devil Lord from resurging.
This is…
The ancient divine artifact, World-Alluring Jade?
Martial Uncle once told me, it's an ominous object lost tens of thousands of years ago.
It was forged by a female devil with tens of thousands of immortal bones.
Why is it at the bottom of the Mo River?
And why would it save me?
Forget it. I'll just keep it and get out of here first.
Congratulations, Your Highness!
This time we wiped out Tantai Jin because of Your Highness's leadership.
I'm willing to die for Your Highness without hesitation!
What's your name?
Qi Shuang. I used to be the deputy leader of the Moonshadow Guard.
The demon core Tantai Jin consumed was arranged by me.
Qi Shuang. I will remember this name.
And you just said you're really willing to…
I'm willing to die for Your Highness without hesitation!
Good.
Your Highness, what are you…
Someone, take him away.
Feed him to my pets.
- Yes, Your Highness.
No, Your Highness!
Your Highness! At least I worked hard for you, Your Highness!
- I won't raise a dog that bites its master.
- Your Highness!
Wise decision, Your Highness!
Those freshly caught demon creatures are starving right now.
By the way, you must raise them properly.
Someday they'll be of great use.
I shall do my best.
If Tantai Jin can manipulate demon power,
I should be able to, as well.
- Wise decision, Your Highness!
Leader, I heard this Tantai Minglang enjoys torturing people.
Just now, Qi Shuang was dragged out.
He's probably been executed.
His Highness needs some Yiyue girls.
- Yes.
All of you, raise your heads!
It's your blessing to be selected by His Highness.
This one and that one. Take them.
Get up!
- Get up!
- Come on. Faster.
Move!
Move! Come on!
Faster!
Go!
Come on!
Sister.
Baiyu.
You two, go save the other girls.
You go find our weapons.
Go.
Let's go.
We've been running for a night.
Everyone, get some rest.
Go.
Leader, the high priestess betrayed us and His Highness is missing.
What should we do?
I have sworn to serve His Highness with my life. I will not go back on my word.
I'm going to find him.
We'll follow you. We'll go wherever you go.
- Yes!
My good brothers!
Sister, you take them back to Yiyue tribe first.
Leave the rest to the Moonshadow Guard.
I guess there's no other way.
Baiyu, you must stay safe.
- Moonshadow Guard, listen!
- Yes!
You four escort the girls back to the Yiyue tribe.
The rest of you, come with me to find His Highness!
- Yes!
I'm freezing.
Tantai Jin, just wait.
But where should I go next?
Back to the Sheng Kingdom?
No.
Tantai Jin has clearly gone astray.
I have to stop him from becoming a devil.
If he goes to the Jing Kingdom, I must follow him there to watch him.
Dear Grandmother and Father, wish you are well.
I am safe.
I have been doing well.
I have enough food and money.
Grandmother, don't worry about me.
Jing Kingdom is a beautiful place.
When I finish sightseeing, I'll go back home.
From Xiwu.
Hi, mister. How long does it take to transport goods to the capital of Sheng?
Less than three days. Rest assured. I'll deliver it personally to your mansion.
Thank you.
My father will reward you when he gets it.
Little girl, why are you hanging around all alone?
Why don't you go home?
There's something important that I must do.
Another hundred miles along the river, and then I'll be in the Jing Kingdom.
The evil bone is still in Tantai Jin's body.
If he degenerates into a devil or dies accidentally, everything will be in vain.
Someone's there.
Hello.
Are you all right?
Tantai Jin?
Stop playing dead. Don't try and play this trick.
No matter how pitiful you look, I won't fall for it!
Tantai Jin?
He's so cold. Tantai Jin!
Tantai Jin, wake up!
Tantai Jin!
You can't die.
Tantai Jin, you mustn't die!
Tantai Jin!
Wake up, Tantai Jin!
Karma comes so quickly.
You were alive and kicking when you tried to capture me.
Only a few hours later, you're in my hands half-dead.
What are you looking at?
If not for the sake of my father and my family, I would just slap you to death and bury you right here.
You'd better move as little as possible.
When pressing water out of you,
I accidentally broke a few of your ribs.
How come it's you?
Why did you save me?
None of your business.
Tantai Jin, I'm telling you. Now you're in my hands.
I can save you and I can also kill you.
If you let yourself die without my permission, I'll tear you to pieces and throw you into the wilderness.
As expected, I can't see.
All right, now it's my turn.
Whether you like it or not, you must answer my questions honestly.
What questions?
We've only been apart for a few hours.
What exactly happened on the ship?
Why have you washed ashore and lost one eye?
Are you going to answer or not?
I was ambushed by Tantai Minglang.
Tantai Minglang?
Your elder brother from the Jing Kingdom?
Why would he do that?
You should ask him about it.
Fine, next question.
did only you escape from there?
Where's Jing Lan'an? Isn't she with you?
She's dead.
Tantai Minglang killed her?
I killed her.
Tantai Jin, this punch is for those who died because of you.
This is both for Jing Lan'an and me.
I tried to treat you sincerely, save and protect you, but now I really regret it.
Jing Lan'an saved your life. She brought you up.
You drank her blood and were taught by her. But you killed her!
Auntie,
let me ask you. Do you regret betraying me?
My child,
I don't regret it.
Yes, I killed her.
You've gone insane.
You're right.
She brought me up. She gave me life.
On that New Year's Eve, when she came for me,
I really wished...
she didn't abandon me.
What?
Of all the things she did, she shouldn't have returned after leaving.
She gave me hope but then discarded me like trash.
What did Jing Lan'an do?
Nothing.
It's just betrayal.
She and Yingxin did the same.
She betrayed me.
Turns out she let me go in order to kill Tantai Jin.
Did she collude with Tantai Minglang?
Tantai Jin, I'm going to escort you back to the Sheng Kingdom.
And then put you in prison to keep you from the outside world.
I'll be watching you every second of every day.
As long as I'm alive, don't ever think of devouring demon cores or killing people.
What are you laughing at?
Ye Xiwu, your stupid words were both strange and funny.
Why don't you just kill me?
Why do you try to be bound with me forever?
Your life and death are not up to you now.
What are you doing?
Roasting fish.
Found it!
There's blood!
Tantai Jin really survived.
He's such a pain in my neck, just like that female demon.
Your Highness, although Tantai Jin isn't dead, he's already a spent force.
Please let me tie up this loose end.
Your Highness may return to the capital and wait for my good news.
No. I must see Tantai Jin dead with my own eyes.
Search further away.
Even if we have to dig three feet deep, we must find Tantai Jin!
Your Highness, we'll be entering the Jing territory ahead.
Is there still no news about Tantai Jin?
Your Highness, we have a visual on the Jing soldiers.
Are you sure?
From both their clothes and weapons, they're absolutely soldiers from the Jing Kingdom.
But we're not sure why they are here in large numbers.
Lead the way.
Yes, Sir.
I didn't expect you to be a little helpful.
You have so many schemes, but you're a good cook.
I've been doing this since I was little.
Didn't you grow up in the palace?
You roasted fish in the palace?
Red fish from the Taiye Pond.
Sparrows from the imperial woods.
Rats from the imperial gutters.
All these can be my food.
You just need a few grains of rice.
They'll bite the hook and get themselves killed.
This is Tantai Jin. Both pitiable and detestable.
Fate has been cruel to him.
He also fought back with cruelty.
Li Susu, you have to see clearly.
This is the Devil Lord.
Eat.
You eat it. When you finish, we'll hit the road.
We don't have time for you to heal.
It's not poisonous.
I know that. Otherwise, why would I let you eat it?
Ye Xiwu, why are you so persistent in not letting me die?
Don't worry.
One day I will tell you.
You'd better pray that day comes later.
When I destroy the evil bone and kill you, I will tell you.
What's wrong?
Without the antidote, it won't be long till the poison kicks in and kills me.
Nothing.
Tantai Jin.
We have company.
Hurry!
They haven't gone far. Split up and chase!
- Yes!
They can't run far.
Search carefully!
Anyone who captures Tantai Jin will be rewarded!
- Yes!
They are Tantai Minglang's men.
Just hand me over to them.
You can both live and get rewards.
Shut up.
Go in the opposite direction. Don't get caught.
Ye Xiwu.
Over there! After them!
After them!
Come on!
Tantai Jin, I really must have owed you in my last life.
I'm surrounded.
No.
I haven't found the way to destroy the evil bone yet.
I can't die here.
- Split up.
- Yes.
Damn. How come it's a woman?
You must have seen Tantai Jin.
Where is he? Say it!
Oh, that dead man is named Tantai Jin?
He's dead.
Dead?
Then, why were you running?
I stole something from him.
I thought you were here to catch me.
For a damn woman like you, I chased half a day for nothing!
Go die!
This way! After her!
Don't let her get away!
Be quiet.
All of you split up and go search.
- Yes!
Didn't I tell you to run in the opposite direction? Are you looking to get killed?
I'm worried that if you get caught, you'll sell me out.
Now, it's perfect. Neither of us can get away now.
What's that noise?
Go now!
If you tell me honestly why you came here, I'll spare your lives.
We're here...
to hunt down Tantai Jin.
By whose order? Is it Tantai Minglang? Where is he?
His…
They're all dead.
Your Highness, since they're here for Tantai Jin, he should be around here.
- Please give orders to Secret Dragon Guards to…
- Go back.
Your Highness, Tantai Jin is…
Get on the horse.
Take these bodies back to the city.
No one saw Tantai Jin today. Understand?
- Understand!
Tantai Jin, this is as far as I can help you.
This place is concealed enough.
Let's spend the night here.
Why didn't you leave just now?
Why did you distract the soldiers and save me?
That's just because…
Better to talk about it when we're safe.
No soldiers are chasing us for now.
Give me back my charms.
If we run into them again, at least I have something to defend us.
You drew so many Sketch Charms?
You only taught me this type.
These are useless for the current situation.
And they were soaked in water for too long.
There's no magic on them.
Meeting you is the unluckiest thing.
Tantai Jin, why is your blood black?
What exactly happened to you?
Once the poison in your left eye spreads throughout your meridians,
you'll spit blood three times and die.
What's going on? Just tell me!
I was poisoned by Tantai Minglang.
Maybe in a bit, it will kick in and I'll be dead.
You scoundrel! Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Would it help if I did?
Are you a doctor? Do you have the antidote?
There must be a way to save you.
Wait here. I'll be back soon.
Ye Xiwu!
Ye Xiwu! Where are you going?
Report!
The men we sent out to search haven't found Tantai Jin yet.
Useless!
Your Highness, urgent news from the capital.
Something happened in the palace. They need you to handle it, Your Highness.
Please return to the capital first. I'll take care of this.
Fine. I've been out for too long this time.
My third brother, when I find you,
I'll crush the bones of you and Yue Ruanruan into powder.
I'll make you disappear for good.
Let's go.
Tantai Jin, you can't hide much longer.
You must be eliminated.
You're awake.
You're back.
Of course. Did you think I'd leave you alone here?
You're badly injured and slept for hours.
I gave you some simple treatment.
Have some fruit first.
You're in luck. I picked up some herbs and came back. They can stop the poison from spreading.
I'll apply them to you in a second.
You should not try to run around out there. You have so many injuries and almost died.
You really scared me. I must owe you in my previous life.
Ye Xiwu, you don't need to try so hard to save me.
You have to live on.
Are you injured somewhere else, too?
Come on.
What are you doing?
You still mind this when you're dying?
What's more, we're already married. There's nothing to be shy about.
Ye Xiwu, you said it on the ship.
From now on, we will have nothing to do with each other.
When we get out of here, I will settle scores with you properly.
But now your life is in my hands.
I will decide whether you live or not.
Understand, Tantai Jin?
Okay.
What is this?
Give it back!
It looks like some kind of treasure.
Why haven't I seen it before?
I found it on the road.
I don't know what it is, either. It's probably worthless.
Give it back to me.
Since you found it, technically, it's not yours.
Since it's in my hand, it's mine now.
No! You can't hold it.
Ye Xiwu, be honest with me.
What exactly is this?
It's a lost divine artifact from ancient times.
It's called World-Alluring Jade.
World-Alluring Jade?
You'd better not have any funny ideas about it!
This jade was forged by a female devil ten thousand years ago.
She killed tens of thousands of immortals, and withdrew their immortal bones.
Making this jade was an evil deed.
That's why its users were doomed to end badly.
They'll be short-lived and die violently.
Bad endings… Violent death?
Guess you are thinking if you devour it, it'll be more useful than devouring demon cores?
You'd better give up this idea, or you'll die a horrible death.
I'm already deeply poisoned.
The poison might kick in any second.
I can't even keep my life now.
Why would I be afraid of death?
Why would I be afraid of some curse?
There's no difference for me...
whether to die now or later.
I won't let you die here.
Time to apply your medicine.
Don't move. Okay? Otherwise, I might break some more ribs.
Done. Time to sleep.
I'll take you back to the Sheng Kingdom tomorrow morning.
There must be a way to save you.
♫  Mortal desires are like gazing upon ♫
♫  The sudden disappearance of the moon  ♫
♫  The mortal world is like three thousand flowers  ♫
♫  in the midst of a snowstorm  ♫
♫  Compassion is embracing a butterfly during times of ruin and pain  ♫
You saved me because of love?
What is love exactly?
Love is you don't want him to die.
You want to stay with him.
You'll be worried if you don't see him.
You'll be happy if you do.
♫  Teary-eyed till all that's left was nonsense  ♫
♫  Love intertwines around the fragile tiled roof  ♫
♫  Embracing the endless lingering fear  ♫
♫  I've admired you through the myriad of years  ♫
♫  I believed I have been loved for a moment  ♫
♫  I plucked the dark feathers that shrouded my body in evil  ♫
♫  And become devout like the flawless moonlight  ♫
Almost there. When we go through the woods ahead, we'll find somewhere to rest.
Tantai Jin, you indeed have not died.
Seems like you also made up with Second Young Miss Ye.
- Who's this?
- Tantai Minglang's subordinate.
She's able to use demonic hexes. Be careful.
Tantai Jin is too weak to take any risk.
If he dies, everything will be in vain.
Tantai Jin, her target is you.
Find a good chance to run first. I'll think of a way to stall her.
What? Are you so deeply poisoned that you don't have energy to fight back?
Seeing me means you two lovebirds' tragic ending has come.
What are you going to fight her with?
Just leave it to me.
Shatter!
Tantai Jin!
Are you okay?
Tantai Jin, you can even kill Jing Lan'an who brought you up, but care so much about this woman?
You're dying anyway.
I'll catch you back alive for His Highness to vent his hatred.
Ye Xiwu.
Ye Xiwu! Ye Xiwu!
Ye Xiwu!
She was hit by my Heart-Gnawing Curse. She'll be dead in no time.
Undo this curse right now! Or I'm gonna crush your bones into scattered dust!
You can barely keep standing.
You are barely surviving. How can you afford to save her?
You might as well just surrender.
Ye Xiwu, we have a lot of unfinished scores to settle.
I can't just let you die here.
The World-Alluring Jade.
This jade was forged by a female devil ten thousand years ago.
Its users were doomed to end badly.
They'll be short-lived and die violently.
As long as I can live now, why should I fear death afterward?
You demon.
I'll eliminate you for His Highness to spare all trouble later!
Tantai Minglang can't kill me.
One day, I'll go to him!
Ye Xiwu!
What happened to me?
Did Tantai Jin save me?
Tantai Jin!
This glow?
It's the World-Alluring Jade!
You scoundrel! You devoured the World-Alluring Jade!
You'll die violently! Don't you know?
Chongyu Harp, help me. I must take the jade out.
Come out!
Do you want to save this man...
who tried to possess the World-Alluring Jade?
Who are you?
You're the female devil who forged this jade?
Do you want to save this man?
I have to save him. He can't die!
But the World-Alluring Jade has chosen him.
Misfortune will fall upon him very soon.
He will have a violent death in a foreign land.
No!
I'll help him get the jade out. Whatever method I must use!
Well, there is one.
But is this man worth it?
Take a good look at what kind of person he is.
You are a monster.
You will bring disaster to anyone close to you.
Look! This kind of person…
You were born unworthy of the most common human emotions.
He isn't worth your sacrifice.
If someone had to die, I'm sure anyone would choose you.
That's not true!
He can't die. If there must be someone to carry his curse, let it be me!
But before the curse lands upon me, there's one task I must complete.
Do you know how to destroy the evil bone?
I know what you are after.
Maybe you can find the answer in Barren Abyss.
But now the power of the World-Alluring Jade has condensed into his eye.
If you want to take it back, you have to trade it with one of your eyes.
Fine.
I'll do it.
How ridiculous.
In this world, someone's actually willing to die for others.
Tantai Jin,
you won't die.
Only if you're alive,
more people will be able to live.
You two, go check over there!
It's Nian Baiyu.
Your Highness!
He's still breathing.
They're indeed theMoonshadow Guard. It seems like they won't hurt him.
Someone! Take His Highness to the camp for treatment!
Yes, Sir!
I couldn't go to Barren Abyss with Tantai Jin heavily injured.
I can only leave Young Devil Lord to you.
Tantai Jin, when I find the way to destroy the evil bone, I'll be back for you.
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Black Moonlight - Zhang Bichen and Mao Buyi]
♫  Mortal desires are like gazing upon the sudden disappearance of the moon  ♫
♫  The mortal world is like three thousand flowers in the midst of a snowstorm  ♫
♫  Compassion is embracing a butterfly during times of ruin and pain  ♫
♫  Realization is washing away our memories in turbid water and rain  ♫
♫  We'll never meet again  ♫
♫  I've seen the flowers bloom from soft-spoken words  ♫
♫  Teary-eyed till all that's left was nonsense  ♫
♫  Love intertwines around the fragile titled roof  ♫
♫  Embracing the endless lingering fear  ♫
♫  I've admired you through the myriad of years  ♫
♫  I believed I have been loved for a moment  ♫
♫  I plucked the dark feathers that shrouded my body in evil  ♫
♫  And become devout like the flawless moonlight  ♫
♫  Listen to the breathing of the flowers ♫
♫  and how they are just like any other creature  ♫
♫  No matter how far we walk, through the dust, wind, and stars  ♫
♫  The moonlight is my armor  ♫
♫  I'd admire your arrival when you came covered in scars  ♫
♫  And willingness to live a life in peace  ♫
♫  You plucked the dark feathers that shrouded your body in evil  ♫
♫  And learned to love what you used to resent  ♫
♫  Despite living insignificant lives, our dreams are as big as the sky  ♫
♫  And we'll make it something to remember us by  ♫