[The World I Love - Liu Yuning]
♫ Dark night, wet moon, and cold blood ♫
♫ Made the naked pupils in my eyes afraid of the light ♫
♫ Is it bright and warm? I can only guess based on intuition ♫
♫ Ah, love pouring over the world like jade, granting me good luck ♫
♫ Ah, the thread of love is coiled strongly around me ♫
♫ I do not fear how people treat me in this world ♫
♫ Breaking through, struggling to escape  ♫
♫ How to differentiate between good and bad  ♫
♫  There are times when I'm fragile, heal wounds with a kiss of love ♫
♫ My existence ♫
♫ Thorns won't break my wings ♫
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 3]
[Ye Mansion]
He talks to birds?
Yeah. And flies and mosquitoes!
When he passed by the lake the other day, a toad was sitting on the shore, and they chatted for a while.
Mr. Tantai is so weird.
He can hold a conversation with a toad.
Is he talking to himself?
- The servants passing by the lake were all snickering at him.
- Indeed.
You, stop being naughty!
What is this nonsense?
Haven't I told you?
Forget about supervising him to find faults, your only job is to watch Tantai Jin.
If he does anything suspicious, especially if he is up to any tricks, report it right back.
Also, keep a close eye on him.
Don't let him freeze, starve, or get beaten up.
He's not allowed to leave Ye Mansion.
His every movement is being watched.
It's utterly impossible for him to play any tricks.
He also talks to sparrows, butterflies, and whatnot.
Basically, he talks to all animals except humans.
Miss, do you think he can actually talk to animals?
You must've overworked yourself.
Why don't you take a few days off?
Miss, I really saw them talking!
Maybe it's because no one in this mansion ever talks to him.
Anyone would go crazy without someone to talk to all year round.
Now that I think about it, Mr. Tantai is quite pitiful.
Could it be that he became a devil god because he was isolated for too long?
This won't do. I need to get information from him.
Second Young Miss.
You've followed me around for days.
Do you have something to say to me?
You guessed right.
I've been so bored lately. So I wanted to have someone to chat with.
Go ahead.
Nice weather today, huh?
It's freezing!
Tantai Jin.
Tantai Jin!
You're always getting bullied. How does that make you feel?
I don't.
No way.
Anyone who gets insulted would be angry or feel resentful.
Haven't you thought of doing something about it?
Like… killing me?
You want me to kill you?
No.
That's not what I meant.
I just wanted to know what you're thinking.
It doesn't matter what I think.
You all insult me not because of what I've done, but simply because you enjoy it.
I can't change all of you.
As for whether I hold resentment or grudges, none of it matters.
I'm just a hostage prince from Jing Kingdom.
To be alive is exhausting enough.
I don't have the energy to think about anything else.
This was five hundred years ago.
The young devil god truly hasn't done anything bad.
Or should I say, he hasn't had his chance yet.
Instead, others were the ones doing bad things to him.
Maybe he only became a devil god due to the series of tragedies.
If someone was willing to help him, to show him kindness, and cared about him
would he have fallen on this devilish path?
Tantai Jin, life is indeed tough, but you still have to live on.
Come find me if you ever feel bored.
Not socializing for too long can turn you into a psychopath!
Like you?
You looked good when you smiled just now.
There're so many people in the mansion.
I'm sure someone would like you and want to talk to you.
No one will ever like me.
And I don't need to be liked.
Miss!
Miss, look!
I visited all the clothing stores in the captial and got some nice and thick winter clothes.
Pick one for Mr. Tantai.
This one's too thin.
This works.
The color looks good, too.
But it's too big. He can't wear this.
How am I supposed to know his size?
Go fetch me some sewing tools.
Miss, I'm not sure if I should ask you this…
Then don't.
Why are you being so nice to Mr. Tantai now?
Because I'm afraid.
Afraid? Of what?
I'm afraid one day when Mr. Tantai freezes to death, he'll drag us along to hell.
And what if after all the constant ill-treatment, he finally snaps one day,
decides he's done being a punching bag, turns into a big tiger donned in a black robe, and eats us all!
Why would a big tiger be wearing a black robe?
[Don't freeze to death]
This coat is for me?
A kept man who lives off a woman can actually afford a new coat?
Stop right there.
Tantai Jin? What is it?
You just slit my coat.
Slit?
Now that's a slit.
Are you getting mad?
Are you starting to have a temper because Second Sister hasn't beaten you lately?
How dare you glare at me?
Our Ye family has given you such a good life...
that you've gotten brash with your masters now?
I'm going to beat you up right now!
Why are you getting violent?
Wait! Why did you pull me away?
I just helped you slit that kept man's coat.
Look at him showing off.
Ye Zeyu, pay for it.
Hasn't Father taught you an eye for an eye, a coat for a coat?
What?
What's wrong with you, Xiwu?
You paying or not?
Don't make me go to Father.
I'll pay.
Here!
What happened to your loyalty after falling in love?
Just ignore him.
This slit is too big to be patched.
You can't wear this anymore.
I'll get a new one.
You gave this to me.
It's mine now.
All right. You keep it.
I'll have Chuntao buy you a new one.
Miss! It's a royal edict!
Mr. Tantai is to have an audience with the king.
This young devil god still has ties within the palace?
I must follow him to find out.
In case something fishy is going on.
I'll come with you.
Tantai Jin is here to meet His Majesty!
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Second Young Miss Ye, His Majesty will only meet Prince Tantai alone.
If you have nothing to do, how about having a chat with the Queen Dowager?
It's okay. I'm pretty familiar with the palace.
I'll just take a walk.
Sure.
Devil Lord was raised in this palace.
What on earth did Tantai Jin go through?
How did he spend his youth?
Why choose him to become a devil god?
If I saw the place he lived in before, maybe I can find some clues.
You there.
Second Young Miss Ye.
Do you know where Tantai Jin used to live?
Tantai Jin, here's a letter from the Jing Kingdom.
It was sent from the palace.
Do you want to read it?
No.
Any normal person would want to hear from his family. When you say no, it sounds like a lie.
For me, the Jing Kingdom is a thousand miles away, to which I shall never return.
Emperor Jing is someone I knew twenty years ago, whom I will never reunite with.
He is but a foreigner in a foreign land.
I don't care.
Nor do I need to care.
Do you mean that?
Do you know the king of Jing Tantai Wuji is about to die of an illness?
Your elder brother Tantai Minglang has been made crown prince.
I see.
Noted.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Tantai Minglang is an ambitious one.
He's been waging wars against us and never bothered to care about you, his younger brother's wellbeing.
Are you truly not afraid that I might cut your head off as a sacrifice?
Tantai Minglang and I are just strangers who share the same blood.
He wouldn't care if I lived or died.
If you were to behead me as a sacrifice, I'm afraid that may be exactly what he wishes.
He shows no mercy for you.
Have you never thought of going back to the Jing Kingdom and taking back all that belongs to you?
I see he's trying to play me against my own brother.
Your Majesty, I'd left my country over a decade ago.
I am but a wanderer.
The people of Jing Kingdom only acknowledge Tantai Minglang.
There's no place for me back there.
Besides, fate has a plan for us all.
The throne, the mortal land, I'll leave these for others to compete.
This is my fate.
To be able to live is enough for me.
It seems I was overconcerned.
You may leave.
This man has a heart of stone.
He baffles me every time I see him.
No wonder his old man does not care for him.
Since he refuses to work for me, he's useless now.
Have someone keep an eye on him.
He'll cause trouble as long as he's alive.
About what I mentioned before, get it done quickly.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I've already made arrangements.
Do be careful. Find someone of similar appearance and age.
Don't make any mistakes.
When the time comes, I can weaken the Ye family and disrupt the Jing Kingdom as well.
Wise move, Your Majesty.
Second Young Miss, we've arrived.
This was where Prince Tantai had lived before being sent to the Ye family.
You guys want to harm His Highness!
You guys want to harm His Highness! They want to harm His Highness.
Ma'am, it's a cold day. Why are you on the ground?
Second Young Miss, this is Nanny Yingxin.
I heard she's the one who brought up Prince Tantai.
She followed His Highness here from the Jing Kingdom.
You want to harm His Highness!
Do you mean Tantai Jin? Who wants to harm him?
I'd never cause him harm.
Your Highness, please hold on.
Steward Wu.
I haven't had the chance to congratulate you on your marriage.
Congratulations.
Steward Wu, let's drop the pleasantries.
I heard that although you married Miss Ye Xiwu, the one you love is Miss Bingchang.
As we all know, Miss Bingchang and our Prince Lin have reciprocated feelings for each other.
And General Ye has long regarded him as his son-in-law.
Since you're now at the Ye Mansion, this is rather convenient.
Could you keep an eye out for me?
What do you mean?
For proof of their collusion, of course!
Collusion?
You want me to help you frame Xiao Lin and Ye Xiao?
What a poor choice of words.
I'm His Majesty's close attendant.
Certainly, I should share his worries.
If you're willing to help, not only can I guarantee you'll live long,
but I may also help you marry your one true love.
In this vast capital, Xiao Lin is the only one who has been sincere to me.
We're not close enough to meddle in each other's affairs,
but there's no reason for me to harm him.
I'm afraid I won't be able to help you do that.
Don't ask for the hard way.
Don't forget what happened to Yue Yingxin.
How did she become like this?
This cold palace has few visitors all year round.
We don't know when she went crazy either.
I just heard that she's been like this ever since Prince Tantai left for Ye Mansion.
I didn't harm His Highness. I didn't harm His Highness.
It's not me. No. I didn't harm His Highness.
I didn't harm His Highness.
Don't you forget where you are right now.
Don't forget I'm in control of her fate.
It's up to me whether she lives or dies.
Don't think you can live in peace by being a docile son-in-law with no say in the Ye family.
I'll kill Yingxin if you don't comply.
But I won't let her die so quickly.
I thought you were just Xiao Liang's loyal dog.
I didn't expect you to be a talkative one, too.
Tantai Jin, you…
His Highness is summoning you.
I'll be right there.
Hostage Prince Tantai, as for what I just said…
Steward Wu, you were just catching up with me.
You're getting better at this, huh?
All right, listen.
If you dare tell anyone else about what I said, I will make you regret being born.
A lowly son of a lowly mother!
That Steward Wu talks too much.
That Tantai Jin thinks too highly of himself!
Godfather, don't let anger consume your health.
About the one you told me to find, I've got him.
It'll surely be enough to fool those of the Jing Kingdom.
No. I just shared too many secrets with him.
If he is of no use to me, I can't let him live any longer!
Tantai Jin must be killed tonight!
If he won't listen, replace him with someone who will!
Godfather! Godfather!
Godfather!
He's dead!
Lin'er, you said you had something important to discuss.
What is it?
Royal Father, many civilians of late have gone missing in their sleep.
I suspect a demon has entered the capital.
I sent Chen Xian to lead the Secret Dragon Guards
to investigate the missing civilians as soon as I heard the report.
I've arranged day-and-night patrols in and out of the capital to look out for the demon.
Royal Father, please be careful in the palace too, in case the demon causes trouble.
Of all the princes and nobles we sent to Mount Buzhao, you're the most promising one.
You excelled the fastest in your cultivation.
You've made great progress in just three years.
But faced with demons like this, I'm afraid success isn't guaranteed with just three years of cultivation.
Sorry to let you down.
It's fine.
I happen to have someone who can be of use to you.
Sixth Prince, we meet again.
Junior Martial Uncle!
So, Master sent you here?
My senior brother said the opportunity of my lifetime would be in the capital.
He told me to spend a few years here before returning.
What opportunity is that?
Well, I don't have a clue.
But at least I can help while I'm here.
The Barren Abyss Barrier has weakened recently,
and demons are slipping through, wreaking havoc in the mortal world.
You also know that our Xiaoyao Sect loves minding irrelevant things like this.
This is not irrelevant.
It's a big deal concerning people's lives.
Since Royal Father appointed you as Scholar of the Ministry of Ceremonies, as an official, you ought to protect your people.
Now that we are under attack by demons, please help me subdue them right away.
Look how the tables have turned.
Back in Mount Buzhao, I was your Martial Uncle.
Now that I'm in the Sheng Kingdom, I've become your subordinate!
But the salary of a Sheng official is simply too low.
I can't even feed my own mouth. Let alone, my family members.
Junior Martial Uncle, you're adopting cats again.
You know me best.
Young Devil Lord had a hard life in the palace,
that's why he's so pessimistic and hopeless.
The evil bone feeds on hatred and pain to accumulate strength.
That's why Tantai Jin suffered so much.
Is this the fate of a devil god?
Little one.
It's late. Why are you out on this windy night?
Aren't you cold?
Father, why are you home so late?
You have worked hard.
You have learned to worry about me?
You've really grown up.
By the way, if you have nothing important to do, don't hang around outside.
- Why?
- The capital isn't safe.
Some civilians have disappeared in their sleep.
It seems it's a demon's doing.
And another strange thing happened in the palace.
His Majesty's loyal advisor Steward Wu had an accident.
He chatted a little with Tantai Jin and died soon after going back.
His ear canal was bleeding.
The way he died was bizarre.
A wasp even crawled out of his ear.
- A wasp?
- He talks to birds?
Yeah, and flies and mosquitoes. They chatted for a while.
I won't say more, in case my darling daughter becomes too frightened to sleep.
Go to bed.
Miss, are there really demons in this world?
Not only demons, but also devils.
Even when I left the palace and hid in Ye Mansion, they still wouldn't let me go.
I must find a way to get out of Sheng Kingdom.
Steward Wu, you've lived long enough.
Go.
With my current abilities, controlling a couple of small creatures is the best I can do.
I barely got out of danger this time.
Next time, might be more challenging.
How do I know if he has awakened?
Young Devil Lord doesn't have much power now.
If it was him who did it, he must have used a curse or a charm.
If you murdered someone, you'll definitely leave traces behind.
Second Young Miss?
There's nothing on him.
What are you dissatisfied with, Second Young Miss?
I'll just have to trick it out of him.
Steward Wu from the palace suddenly died today.
Did you know that?
I heard that he stopped you before you left the palace.
What did he say to you?
Nothing.
So calm.
Is he really innocent?
From today on, I'm going to search you before you go to bed.
I'm warning you! Don't even think about playing tricks on me.
Second Young Miss's interests are getting more and more interesting.
Don't you start with me.
Who knows if you might have told one of those wasps or bugs to kill for you.
I don't want to end up like Steward Wu, dying a mysterious death.
How did she find out?
In this case, searching my body doesn't seem enough.
How about...
I take off all my clothes so that you may be rest assured?
Go ahead. Not my loss.
We're husband and wife after all. I've already seen it all.
Go on.
You're not going to do it?
Shall I do it instead?
When did she become so much smarter?
Be wary of your candles during this hot summer!
Grudge, hatred,
fear, remorse…
You're the one!
Help!
[East Capital Gate]
As expected, nowhere else has more nightmares
than this palace does.
With the aid of these nightmares, I can cultivate more nightmare blossoms.
The red string is up to your neck.
It seems you've had a miserable life.
Why don't you leave here with me?
I sense a unique scent outside of these palace walls.
It's not yet dawn anyway. I'll go take a look.
[Ye Mansion]
It's right here. It was worth the trip.
This scent is truly unique.
It was mine, to begin with.
Your Highness, don't go.
Little beauty, you're obviously a mortal,
but there's something demonic in you.
How very interesting.
What a fruitful night I got.
Why don't you come back with me, too?
With the nourishment of these miserable souls,
the nightmare blossoms will soon cover this mountain.
As long as they bloom all over the forest,
I can evolve from a demon to a devil!
[Ye Mansion]
A demon in the capital…
Steward Wu's violent death…
Do they have anything to do with Young Devil Lord?
What are you looking at?
There better not be leftovers. Finish them.
Ye Xiwu, you're so capricious.
Yeah. Lately, I find myself enjoying watching people eat.
Is there a problem?
When this month ends and you don't put on three pounds, I'll give you a good beating!
Her psychopathic ways are becoming more unpredictable.
Miss! Miss!
- Bad news! Eldest Young Miss is missing!
- What?
She was perfectly fine last night, but she was suddenly gone this morning.
I'm afraid… it's t-t-that… demon His Lordship mentioned.
What should we do?
Calm down. Tell me in detail.
His Lordship sent for the Scholar of Ceremonies to exorcise demons in the mansion.
I hear Sixth Prince is here, too.
I'll go take a look.
She's still interested in Xiao Lin.
Good. This way, no one will care about Steward Wu's death.
Butler Liu, bring Jiahui back to have a good rest.
Yes.
Elder Brother, who's this guy?
He's the new Scholar of Ceremonies, Pang Yizhi.
I heard he's the direct disciple of the Xiaoyao Sect, and also the sect uncle of Sixth Prince.
Identifying devils and catching demons is his specialty.
Then, do you know who his master is?
I heard it's Immortal Qingxu from Mount Buzhao.
Never heard of him.
Could he be Uncle Zhaoyou's great-grand master.
No demon or devil can escape from his eyes.
He can identify one in an instant.
When he strikes, every demon and devil dies in his hands.
Oh, no. He's a senior disciple of Xiaoyao Sect.
If he finds out Tantai Jin's evil bone and executes him, that would be bad.
What do I do?
Scholar Pang, anything I can help you with?
Junior Martial Uncle, what's wrong with him?
- Scholar Pang, he…
- This young master...
has a charming face.
He's bound to be rich and famous.
When you're rich, don't forget me. Don't forget me, yeah?
Thank you for your blessing.
The Xiaoyao Sect five hundred years ago must've been lenient with admissions.
Scholar Pang, you've walked in circles for a while. Have you found anything?
General, for now I haven't seen anything yet, but everyone in your mansion should be fine.
Please allow me to cast an array in your mansion
to search for that demon's traces, and get Eldest Young Miss back.
Sure. Thank you, Scholar Pang.
You mean that well-cultivated demon took them to Mount Banzhen in the southern outskirts
and used these people...
to plant flowers?
Yes. Ye Bingchang and Yingxin were both taken by that demon.
But it seems like that demon doesn't plan on killing these people yet.
Why don't we share these clues with them and have them rescue the kidnapped?
Got it.
You go check what Ye Xiwu is doing.
Ye Xiwu has been very perceptive lately.
She has suspected me of controlling animals.
If I tell her these, it's no different from pleading guilty.
Forget it. Why bother getting into trouble?
[Demon-Locking Array]
Demon-Locking Array.
It's here.
Next step…
What's the next step again?
Where should this flag be planted?
The white flag corresponds to the metal element.
I've tried this spot. That one's wrong, too.
This doesn't make sense. It's not here.
Will this poorly constructed array work?
Never mind. I'll do it myself.
Thankfully, Father forced me to learn how to draw spells for a few years.
Since I don't have any powers, I can use this for desperate times like now.
Scholar Pang, I'll borrow some of your incantation slips.
It's for the good of everybody. Surely you wouldn't mind.
The misery in the mortal world is indeed nightmare blossoms' best fertilizer.
Traveling thousands of miles from Barren Abyss was certainly worth it.
Aren't these two the ones I brought back just last night?
Their nightmare blossoms have bloomed so quickly.
My judgment was right.
Let me see what's special about your experiences.
So you're a maid from Jing Kingdom.
You followed a hostage prince to Sheng Kingdom.
Let go of me. Your Highness!
Let go of me!
Who is this?
There's someone with such a twisted fate?
He hasn't had a hint of warmth or a glimmer of light in his life.
If I plant a nightmare blossom with him, it'll definitely be the best of its kind.
It can surely help me become a devil.
[Order]
This demon-locking array is like guarding by a tree stump for a hare.
(Idiom, waiting for a windfall)
If the hare doesn't show up, he won't catch a thing in ten thousand years.
Shoo!
Second Young Miss, are you all right?
I'm okay. I was just startled by this bird.
I think if you don't tell them where the demon is, they won't find a trace till dawn.
Who'd have thought Ye Xiwu who fears nothing and no one,
would be afraid of a bird?
Please keep a distance from her.
Fine.
This woman is usually so vicious yet she somehow fears me.
Nighttime is the best time.
I smell it. Right there.
He's the one.
I've never smelled such a sweet scent.
He can definitely grow the most beautiful nightmare blossom.
Someone from Xiaoyao Sect is here.
I better be cautious.
What was that?
The edict of the Heavenly Lord reveals all hidden evil.
Demon-Binding flag, purge all darkness!
Seize!
Sixth Prince, we caught it, didn't we?
Oh, no. This black fog was a smokescreen.
It was a distraction!
That's… Tantai Jin's chamber!
[Ye Bingchang is in the southern outskirts on Mount Banzhen]
Now they can't tell who wrote it.
I have to think of a way to slip this note to Xiao Lin.
Let him play the hero.
I can't arouse Ye Xiwu's suspicion again.
You're the one I've been looking for.
You will allow me to flourish the most beautiful nightmare blossom.
By the light and power of the mystic thunder, strike!
You've overestimated yourself.
Tantai Jin, hold on to me.
Ye Xiwu, are you a fool? You'll get yourself killed!
I can't let you die!
What a pair of lovebirds.
Then you can come along.
Second Young Miss!
I'm doomed.
She is General Ye's precious daughter.
He's going to rip my head off!
Sixth Prince, nothing must happen to Second Young Miss!
Second Young Miss was kidnapped by the demon.
[Ye Bingchang is in the southern outskirts on Mount Banzhen]
"Ye Bingchang is in the southern outskirts of Mount Banzhen."
I'm going to save her.
Could this scribble be some kind of trap?
It's our last resort. I have to give it a try.
Bring the Secret Dragon Guards. Let's go.
Okay.
What is this place?
Susu, that devil god came like a storm.
You must stay and guard the gate.
I'll help the sect leader.
What? Why is Senior Brother here?
- And why am…
- Listen to me.
Hengyang Sect's mantle must be passed down.
Hengyang Sect… But it's clearly…
Susu, wake up!
-  clearly…
-  Tantai Jin has been killed by the dream demon.
The devil god has awakened. You're about to fail.
Susu, wake up!
Tantai Jin has been killed by the dream demon.
-  Susu, wake up!
Father.
-  Junior Sister, wake up!
-  Junior Sister…
Devil God… Tantai Jin…
Dream demon…
-  Junior Sister, wake up!
-  Junior Sister…
Where is this place? The demon's den.
What was that dream I just had?
Tantai Jin! Thank goodness, you're not dead!
Why are you still standing there?
Help me get down!
Nightmare blossoms.
It all makes sense now.
What's a nightmare blossom?
I've read about it in books.
The dream demon brings people to her den, then uses their dark memories or fear as seeds
that grow into vines and bind them in place.
Trapping them in endless nightmares flourishing the nightmare blossoms that she feeds on.
It's like raising livestock.
Ye Xiwu,
you've been reading?
Have you seen my elder sister?
She should be here, too.
Over there.
Let's go.
Here she is.
Yingxin?
Why is she also here?
How do you know her?
I saw her when I was in the palace.
You were investigating me?
No, I wasn't.
I was just…
Passing by a remote and cold palace, and saw a crazy woman.
So what if I investigated you?
You're always being so mysterious.
Have you seen the demon?
The night's still young.
I guess she's still hunting.
She captured so many people. And she's got her own barrier.
She's quite a mighty one.
No wonder Pang Yizhi couldn't catch her.
The deeper you sleep, the tighter the vines will twine.
Tantai Jin, why weren't you bound?
Because I never dream.
Let's rescue them.
Be careful.
This is the land of the Yiyue Tribe.
But we were just in the woods.
This…
This isn't reality.
Tantai Jin?
Greetings from Yingxin, Princess.
♫  My empty heart has nothing to yearn for  ♫
I see. Thanks for telling me.
But I'm the princess of Yiyue Tribe.
For the tribe, I have to go.
Let's go.
♫ My regret ♫
Princess, Yingxin and Lan'an were born to serve you.
Wherever you go, we will follow.
It seems like this is Yingxin's dream.
- Which means Yiyue Tribe's princess…
Yiyue Tribe has pledged their allegiance to the Jing Kingdom.
is Tantai Jin's mother.
Princess Yue Ruanruan, known for her gentleness and virtues,
is hereby granted the title of Consort Rou.
She will be welcomed and greeted with a grand wedding ceremony.
A nationwide celebration.
May Your Majesty and Her Highness love each other forever,
and may your descendants thrive on and on!
♫  Broken, rebuild; destroy, reconstruct  ♫
♫  I shed meaningless tears of sorrow ♫
♫  The destined path is one I won't follow  ♫
♫  Who is the mystic bird that returns?  ♫
♫ Die bored, not mine ♫
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Black Moonlight - Zhang Bichen and Mao Buyi]
♫  Mortal desires are like gazing upon the sudden disappearance of the moon  ♫
♫  The mortal world is like three thousand flowers in the midst of a snowstorm  ♫
♫  Compassion is embracing a butterfly during times of ruin and pain  ♫
♫  Realization is washing away our memories in turbid water and rain  ♫
♫  We'll never meet again  ♫
♫  I've seen the flowers bloom from soft-spoken words  ♫
♫  Teary-eyed till all that's left was nonsense  ♫
♫  Love intertwines around the fragile titled roof  ♫
♫  Embracing the endless lingering fear  ♫
♫  I've admired you through the myriad of years  ♫
♫  I believed I have been loved for a moment  ♫
♫  I plucked the dark feathers that shrouded my body in evil  ♫
♫  And become devout like the flawless moonlight  ♫
♫  Listen to the breathing of the flowers ♫
♫  and how they are just like any other creature  ♫
♫  No matter how far we walk, through the dust, wind, and stars  ♫
♫  The moonlight is my armor  ♫
♫  I'd admire your arrival when you came covered in scars  ♫
♫  And willingness to live a life in peace  ♫
♫  You plucked the dark feathers that shrouded your body in evil  ♫
♫  And learned to love what you used to resent  ♫
♫  Despite living insignificant lives, our dreams are as big as the sky  ♫
♫  And we'll make it something to remember us by  ♫