[The World I Love - Liu Yuning]
♫ Dark night, wet moon, and cold blood ♫
♫ Made the naked pupils in my eyes afraid of the light ♫
♫ Is it bright and warm? I can only guess based on intuition ♫
♫ Ah, love pouring over the world like jade, granting me good luck ♫
♫ Ah, the thread of love is coiled strongly around me ♫
♫ I do not fear how people treat me in this world ♫
♫ Breaking through, struggling to escape  ♫
♫ How to differentiate between good and bad  ♫
♫  There are times when I'm fragile, heal wounds with a kiss of love ♫
♫ My existence ♫
♫ Thorns won't break my wings ♫
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 6]
Teach me.
What should I teach you…
The one you used to repel the crows at Xiao Lin's mansion that day.
Not that one. That spell is too dangerous.
You're just an amateur, and if you mess the charm up, you might blow up the house.
It's always wise to play it safe.
Because you are Tantai Jin, I will never teach you spells that can kill.
Then, what are you going to teach me?
I got one. Watch this.
I'll teach you this today.
Okay. That's it.
A charm is finished.
But you need the right incantation to make it work.
Is it nice?
What's this charm for?
This charm is called "Sketch".
When I was little, I was always clamoring to go out to play.
My father…
An immortal taught me this spell
so that my mind could wander around the world even when I was stuck in a small room.
Also, every time I scribe the charm, I get to see different sceneries.
These cultivators are extremely boring.
Instead of improving their cultivation, they choose to waste their time on such useless things.
That's not true.
The immortals say that the body, heart, and mind are three different parts.
When the three parts are unified, the golden elixir is formed.
Empty thy heart to unite soul and character,
Calm thy body to silence energy and emotions,
Steady thy mind then all three merge into one.
Unite the body, heart, and mind, and the golden elixir will be cultivated.
But how to unify them?
Turn your energy into Qi and your body won't move.
Turn Qi into a soul, and your heart won't move.
Make your soul empty, and your mind won't move.
Destroy your desire for romantic love, and then you can understand the universe and all lives.
This is the one and only way of Heartless Way.
♫ Dream in circles the remaining flashy and vivid regret ♫
♫ I would rather not wake up and dreams would not vanish ♫
♫ A bond of marriage entwined for thousands of years ♫
♫ To smooth the frivolous face ♫
♫ I was already tired of bidding farewell ♫
♫ I would send ashes and brightness to the moon ♫
But I've gotten carried away.
All roads lead to the right way, and Heartless Way is just one of them.
♫ My affection ebbed and flowed like seasons ♫
Okay, I will learn it.
♫ A fair complexion was not afraid of being soaked in tears ♫
♫ I only wish to exchange this life with eternity ♫
It is a pity. I've looked into it.
The Young Devil Lord doesn't have an immortal bone.
No matter how hard he works, there's no way he can achieve immortality in this life.
But as long as he doesn't turn to the dark side, staying a mortal might not be a bad thing for him.
♫ Although fireworks are short-lived, they are easily enjoyed ♫
♫ But this time, who will be the one ♫
♫ Waiting for a long while? ♫
Ye Xiwu, did I draw this charm correctly?
But why is it not working?
Well, you can't guarantee to succeed every time you scribe a charm.
This is your first time. Getting the pattern right is impressive enough.
Also, the Sketch charm will show you the purest and most beautiful things.
You must clear your mind of all thoughts when chanting the spell, especially no evil thoughts.
Only by doing that can you make it work.
Take your time. Don't waste the materials.
Remember, clear your mind.
As a teacher, you fell asleep right in front of your student.
You are really something.
Wake up!
Make sure I've learned it before you go to sleep. Wake up.
Why are you so unreasonable?
I haven't learned it yet.
This is not the Sketch charm.
I'm teaching you a new one.
Are you not happy?
Ye Xiwu, what are you doing?
Let go of me.
Once you started drawing, you haven't taken any breaks.
- What do you want to do?
- If you practice all night, you might die from exhaustion.
Come on.
Ye Xiwu!
- You…
- Be good. Let's resume the study tomorrow.
Ye Xiwu, let go of me.
Be quiet.
Ye Xiwu.
Because I love you, all right?
When you love someone, you want to keep them alive and spend time with them.
You get anxious when they're not around, and feel happy when you see them.
The universe manifests in an inch of land. The soul follows the mind.
Rise!
Tri-foot crow is the royal totem of the Jing Kingdom.
Were there any people from Jing at the wedding that day?
The hostage prince Tantai Jin was also there.
It's said that the Yiyue tribe can communicate with birds and control them.
This matter…
This child has been lurking for many years.
He is extremely scheming.
Keeping him alive will lead to disaster sooner or later.
Your Majesty, means...?
I want him dead.
Hide the traces well.
I got it.
Your Majesty, Ye Xiao's second son, Ye Qingyu, is coming back from the border today.
I remember he was smart from a young age, and very organized when doing anything.
He is a young talent no less gifted than Lin.
Yes.
I heard people lining the streets to welcome him.
The Pillar of the State Great General's hard work rendered great merits.
The army is full of his supporters. And this son of his excels him.
I think this son's reputation is even better than his father's.
What's going on?
They both came from the same dad,
but the firstborn is hopeless, while the second son is young and promising.
He outshines his father.
It doesn't matter!
Even your ten fingers are different lengths.
[Ye Mansion]
Who is missing me?
My Second Younger Brother will be back soon. Right?
Our house has been in turmoil since early in the morning.
None of us can get a moment of peace.
I-I can't stand any longer.
I'm exhausted.
I'm still injured.
Second Young Master is home.
Greetings, Second Young Master.
Grandma. Father. I'm back.
Thanks to God's blessing, you are home safe and sound.
It was unfilial of me to leave Grandma and Father for so long.
Please punish me, Father.
Why would I punish you? You were guarding the country.
Is there anything more honorable than that?
Although you couldn't stay home to keep us company,
our ancestors would be very proud of you, and the people of Sheng admire you.
As your father, I'm very proud of you.
Stand up now.
Up.
Come, let's start eating.
We waited so long for you to come home.
- Come on.
- Don't bring up "punishment" the moment you get back.
Why isn't my second eldest sister here?
You mean Xiwu?
She was busy with something in the attic last night.
Qingyu, your Second Elder Sister has been studying so hard these days, forgetting to eat and sleep.
She probably forgot the meal time again.
Let's just bring her some food later.
Yes.
That's not appropriate.
Grandma and Father are both waiting here.
How could a junior be absent?
Qingyu,
Xiwu... Xiwu is still a child.
She is in her 20s and a married woman.
Xiwu has married into another family anyway…
Married or not, everything she says and does represent our family tradition.
Well…
Though having been at the border these years, I have also heard of Xiwu's infamous behaviors.
She maltreated our servants, pushed the eldest sister into the water,
got drunk and lost her virginity in the imperial palace, and even got married muddleheadedly.
That's right, Qingyu. You should discipline Ye Xiwu.
Look at my injuries!
On the wedding day of the Sixth Prince, evil birds made a ruckus in his palace.
Xiwu left us outside and rushed back to save her husband, protecting outsiders.
She's not worthy of her last name Ye!
Eldest Brother, as a man of the Ye family,
you failed to help someone in need and protect your sisters. Yet you have the nerve to criticize Second Elder Sister.
At least, Second Elder Sister was trying to save someone.
Who were you trying to protect when getting these wounds?
I'm starving.
I feel so dizzy. I can't hear anything clearly.
Xiwu has always been naughty.
I'm afraid after I left, no one here has taught her how to behave. I need to go check on her.
Qingyu! Chuntao, go and help your miss out!
Ye Xiwu, get up. We have company.
Let me sleep a little longer.
Someone is coming here. Time for lunch.
Let me sleep.
Tell Chuntao to save some food for me.
This is ridiculous!
Miss! Miss, you…
Why are you yelling?
Who was here?
Your younger brother, Ye Qingyu.
Yes, Miss. Why are you still sleeping here?
Second Young Master came home today!
What does Second Young Master's return have to do with me?
I had my palms beaten after all.
One can get off today, but not tomorrow.
It is bad.
How come this Second Younger Brother is even meaner than Ye Xiwu?
Ye Xiwu, Grandma and Father were waiting in the dining room today. But you were absent for no reason.
That was unfilial.
Your brother came back from thousands of miles away,
and Father and Grandma were there to welcome me home, yet only you weren't.
That was disrespectful of your sibling.
You are married, but you were doing… doing licentious acts in broad daylight.
That was shameless.
I was away from home for three years and neglected to discipline you.
How could you become such a rascal?
I am unworthy of the Ye family.
I've realized my mistakes.
Since you've realized your mistakes and I just got home, I won't punish you too harshly.
Kneel here for half an hour and introspect on your behavior.
Miss, you should kneel down.
If Second Young Master sees you like this, he will make you kneel for another half an hour.
There is no such thing as he, as the younger brother, teaching me a lesson.
Even the eldest brother is scared of me in the family.
But he has the authority.
He is the warden of the Ye family.
I thought the warden was my dad.
Yes, it used to be him, but he doesn't like too much red tape,
so when dealing with a lot of things, he always muddles through them.
But people in the Sheng Kingdom take clans and etiquette very seriously.
Then one year, Old Master found it too much work, so he gave all the worship ceremony work to Second Young Master.
[Clan Patriarchs]
Unexpectedly, Second Young Master did a great job, more reliable than Master.
Ever since then, Second Young Master was voted to be the warden by all the Ye family members.
[Clan Patriarchs]
Some became prime ministers at the age of 12,
but just how unreliable was my dad that had the whole clan approve of this brat becoming the family warden?
Don't say that about Old Master. Second Young Master will punish you again.
When is Second Young Brother going to leave?
After the Spring Festival, the earliest.
Miss. Miss.
Miss.
Who is the family warden beating this time?
Second Young Master went to your husband.
Ye Qingyu is so fierce.
If he finds out that Tantai Jin is evil, my brother will get rid of him immediately.
Miss...
Miss, be careful.
The universe manifests in an inch of land. The soul follows the mind.
Prince Tantai.
I've heard a lot about you.
Whatever you heard about is probably not something good.
Slanders and rumors can ruin a person, but I believe in seeing with my own eyes.
You came here not to chitchat with me. Right?
First, I want to apologize for Second Elder Sister's misbehavior.
Second, I want to invite you to have meals with the family from now on.
Last, my sister is ignorant and unruly, so please don't let her mess around in the future.
For example, her shameful act earlier today.
If word gets out about it, the Ye family's and your reputation will be stained.
Shameful act?
Why don't you be straight and tell me exactly what we were doing?
I can just let it go.
I shouldn't interfere in your private matters.
But there is another thing I want to ask you about.
What is it?
Earlier, were you chanting a spell?
You misheard.
I cultivated in Xiaoyao Sect for three years.
Although not a master, I can tell when one is chanting a spell.
Does Second Elder Sister know about this?
Does my father know about it?
You want to know if Ye Xiwu knows, then why don't you go ask her yourself?
I grew up with Second Elder Sister.
Although naughty and mischievous, she is careless.
She can be easily deceived.
Prince Tantai, I've heard that there have been frequent disturbances
and rampant demonic activity in the capital recently.
What does it have to do with me?
The Xuancheng Palace suffered a disaster on their wedding day.
Many places still urgently need repair and my eldest brother's injuries have not yet healed.
Even my father, Pillar of the State Great General, has been injured.
I heard you were there too, but you were unscathed.
So what?
I was just lucky.
Jing Kingdom's royal symbol is a three-eye crow.
The beast that broke into Xuanchen Palace that day happened to be crows.
What a coincidence!
General Ye, considering your amazing imagination,
it's an awful waste of your talent to have you defend the border as a general.
Prince Tantai, I have a spell called Bone Inspect, which can tell one's nature.
Would you care to try it?
Do you have to do this?
If you are innocent, what's there to be scared about?
Second Younger Brother, you misunderstood him.
Is half an hour over so fast?
Not yet.
I'll soon go back to the ancestral hall to make up for it.
Second Younger Brother, when the monsters were rampaging, I was with Tantai Jin the whole time.
He almost died. It wasn't him. Really.
Let me ask you for the last time. Have you been secretly studying spells?
I thought you were mad over some big deal.
Yes, he is practicing spells.
I learned some simple spells recently.
I thought it was boring to practice alone, so I had Tantai Jin practice with me.
But he is so dumb that he can't grasp them at all.
That's why he was secretly practicing in the room.
So that's what you are worried about.
What's so secretive about it? Why couldn't you just tell him?
Learning spells?
Who did you learn spells from?
Remember there were demons in the capital?
I had Scholar Pang teach me a few tricks.
Prince Tantai, I was rude to you just now. My apologies.
Second Elder Sister, I just told Prince Tantai. Since we are a family, he shouldn't eat alone at a single table.
Starting tomorrow, he may dine with us.
Great. I agree.
You made a very wise decision.
You only care about eating.
Just now if it weren't for me, you might've been killed.
Qingyu.
Speaking of spells, do you know immortal arts as well?
The Bone Inspect spell you were talking about…
Fake, just to intimidate him.
I was scared to death.
Oh, well, Tantai Jin. Ignorance is bliss.
You... Fortune favors fools.
Second Young Master.
Second Young Master, Prince Xuanchen sent people to invite you over.
His Highness said that after being long parted from you, he misses you very much.
He invited you to his palace to catch up.
- Get the horse ready.
- Yes.
[Xiao Mansion]
General Ye, it turns out you are also a disciple from our Mount Buzhao.
I wouldn't have figured it out if Your Highness didn't say anything.
Descendants from Sheng's official families are most likely sent to immortal sects
for a few years of cultivation, no matter whether they are talented or not.
It's something of a tradition now.
It's normal that Scholar Pang can't tell.
Unlike His Highness, I don't have his talent in making elixirs and cultivating.
I only fit in armies, playing with weapons.
You are joking, General Ye.
A talent like you can even be humble about your gift,
then I would be a parasite of your kingdom.
I heard the emperor of Jing has died suddenly.
If the news is true, I don't know what kind of disturbance the world will suffer.
You don't need to worry.
Tantai Wuji died of a severe illness, and his throne will fall into Tantai Minglang's hands.
I heard this man is paranoid and bad-tempered.
If he succeeds to the throne, I'm afraid the Jing Kingdom itself will be in trouble.
As the saying goes, "The rise brings suffering to the people, and the fall also brings suffering to the people."
It has been like this since ancient times.
Your Highness, although the Jing Kingdom is an enemy, their soldiers and civilians are all flesh and blood,
no different from us.
General Ye, you are very broad-minded.
I feel ashamed of my shallowness.
As the guardian general of the borders, I receive a salary from the court.
I am duty-bound to protect the Sheng Kingdom with all my heart and strength.
However, deep down in my heart, I hope there will be no more wars in the world,
and one day the countries can be reunified.
But the hostility between the two kingdoms has been there for years.
I wonder which powerful lord will have such courage, and in which year and month this will happen.
Your Highness, if someday you become the emperor of Sheng,
I…
General Ye, my father is in his prime.
You should not have said such things.
I spoke out of turn. Please punish me, Your Highness.
Don't be like this.
The general trend of the world is that what has been divided must be united, and vice versa.
You mortals should accept this reality.
How about this?
I'll conduct fortune-telling for you guys.
What fortune?
What's the matter?
According to the divination result, the person who can end the chaos, pacify the empire,
and bring happiness to the people is now in Sheng's capital city.
Let me check again.
That day, I devoured the dream demon. It gave me temporary power, but it ran out very quickly.
My body's yearning for demonic powers seems to be insatiable.
Why is this happening?
Ye Qingyu suspects me,
and Ye Xiwu follows me around every day.
I have to figure out another way...
to find new demonic power.
- Second Young Master.
- Chuntao, have you seen Eldest Young Master?
Eldest Young Master… He went out early in the morning after borrowing thirty taels from Miss.
He probably went again to the…
How dare you, Ye Zeyu!
Big!
[2 + 2]
Another round?
Yes.
For each round you lose, you have to take off a piece of clothing.
Eldest Young Master Ye, you have just taken off one.
If you lose one more time, you'll be stripped naked.
So what about taking off clothes?
You, a lady, can watch me without feeling shy, then why would I flinch? Let's start.
Another round, then.
Sir, please stop. Who are you looking for?
Ye Zeyu. Is he inside?
What is it you want to see him about? Tell me so I can inform him for you.
I'm here to break his legs.
[Gamble House]
My ancestors, please bless me.
I need to win once!
You don't want to see me become a laughing stock, do you?
Big! Big! Big! Big! Big! Big! Big! Big!
Open it! Open It! Open it!
Big!
[2 + 2]
My ancestors, you guys are unbelievably iron-hearted!
Strip! Strip! Strip!
I haven't lost yet. You go!
Go!
Eldest Young Master Ye, are you quite unlucky today?
Small! Small! Small! Small! Small!
- Small!
- Open! Bless me.
Open! Open! Open!
Small! Small! Small!
Small!
[1 + 1]
It's small!
It's your turn to undress!
Undress! Undress! Undress!
Go ahead! Undress!
Undress! Undress! Undress! Undress! Undress!
Undress! Undress! Undress!
Who the hell dared to hit me?
You did well.
Second Younger Brother, you are here.
Put on your clothes and go to the Ancestral Hall.
Kneel there according to domestic discipline.
Yes. I'll go right now.
Make way. Make way for me.
What are you looking at? Look away.
Ye Qingyu really seems quite powerful. I have to guard against him.
My spell skills is progressing slowly, and can be found out easily.
It's not nearly as useful as demonic elixirs.
It happens to be Spring Festival, and the streets are full of the hustle and bustle,
suitable for going out and hunting.
But Ye Xiwu definitely won't let me out.
Tantai Jin, let's go Spring Festival shopping.
You are looking for trouble yourself.
Why are you dragging me along?
It's not like I'm asking you to draw a carriage. Why are you rejecting me?
Everyone should bathe in the sun more.
In this way, you can get stronger. Being confined in that little attic all day long, you'll become a freak.
This is just what I want.
Let's go. Come on.
Festivals in the mortal world are so lively.
There are more people on this street than the whole of Mount Changze.
Chuntao, let's get off and walk around.
- Miss, that's delicious, too!
- You only think about food!
As Spring Festival approaches, people come and go on the streets.
If I look carefully, I should be able to find a monster or two pretending to be people.
Wait a moment, Young Master.
You forgot your cloak.
You can keep it as a compensation. I apologize for my brother.
You are not him.
He owes me. Why are you paying back on his behalf?
He owes me a piece of clothing.
Are you, as his brother, going to strip on his behalf in front of me?
Also, the money he owes me is far more than the value of a dress.
It's sweet. You want some?
Then I'll eat all of it.
So many people here.
I can distinctly sense the demonic power nearby.
But where is it hiding exactly?
Delicious chestnuts. Take a look here.
Chestnuts! Let's go!
Miss, would you like some chestnuts?
- I'll have some, please. I'll have some.
- All right.
- Bravo!
- Yeah!
Hey!
Where are you going?
Let's watch this.
Here, have a taste.
Have a try!
Okay.
Look at you. Hiding in that little attic all day long,
you look as if you will melt in the sun.
You should come out for a stroll more often, enjoying some good food to lift your mood.
Great!
Are you saying I can come out whenever I want?
Of course.
But I should come with you, lest you get lost.
This woman is not dumb. She is still guarded with me.
Miss, there are still so many things to buy.
If we keep hanging around like this, we won't be done even when it gets dark.
Good point.
I'll leave the carriage to you.
You can go back home after you get everything. I'll walk around a little longer.
Let's go.
- Good!
- Great!
Awesome!
- You got rid of all of them?
- Yes.
That Second Young Miss Ye is inseparable from His Highness.
Those people probably won't have another chance to harm His Highness.
If you want to meet him under the Ye family's nose, you have to be cautious.
High Priestess, although His Highness is the princess's son, he is not so close with the Yiyue tribe.
Also, you had been gone for so long.
What if he refuses to recognize you?
It's not only for the Yiyue tribe,
but also for himself.
Let's go and find a place to stay the night first.
Yes.
Tantai Jin. Tantai Jin, what's this?
I don't know.
This is a mud whistle.
Every kid has played with one of these.
Could it be that you two are immortals who have descended to earth and not partake in the pleasures of mortal life?
I did come to earth, but I didn't expect Young Devil Lord to not recognize this thing.
He has been living like a prisoner since he was a child. Who would buy him toys?
Here.
Seeing as how he's looking around with an inexperienced look,
I think he is probably just like me, coming to a temple fair for the first time.
Tantai Jin, how about I buy you one?
Ye Xiwu, are you a little child? Using me as an excuse to buy toys for yourself.
I will buy it.
Hide!
I didn't expect Second Younger Brother, who is usually serious, to come out shopping.
We shopped for half a day. I think I have paid off what my brother owes you.
Let me calculate.
The principal has almost been paid off, but you also need to pay me some interest.
- That's a lot of interest.
- Of course.
Which color is the prettiest?
All good.
Buy lipstick for me, and the debt you owe me is cleared.
Okay.
- Put it on for me, then.
- I…
Hurry up.
I'll close my eyes and spare you the embarrassment. Okay?
Gosh.
Did you see that?
Am I pretty?
Am I hallucinating?
Is that really our family warden?
Have you had enough fun?
He turned around to us.
- I'll buy these two.
- These two. Okay.
Have a good one.
Tantai Jin, do you smell something strange?
No, not a smell. I can't tell what it is.
No.
This is the source of that demonic energy.
I've finally found her.
If I can take her demonic elixir…
Pian Ran, where are you from?
I'm not a Sheng citizen.
My hometown is remote, and you probably haven't heard of it even if I told you.
So you come from afar.
Do you have any relatives in the capital?
No.
I live by myself.
Alone and nowhere to belong. If I encounter any trouble in the future, I might have to go to you for help.
No problem. You may come to me whenever you need help.
My home is just across the bridge ahead.
Young Master Ye, you have been running around all day with me.
Would you like to come to my place for a cup of tea?
Today is the New Year's Eve. My grandmother is at home, and I shouldn't stay out for too long.
All right. No need to ramble on.
I can let you go today.
Young Master Ye, remember to retrieve the cloak when you have time.
Goodbye.
Young Master Ye.
Don't forget, now you owe me a cup of tea.
This man is likable.
Never mind. I'm not in a hurry now.
[Ready-Made Clothing Store]
This dress is perfect for Grandma. This one is for Father.
I'll take this one, too. It fits Chuntao perfectly.
Shopkeeper, please pack them for me. Let's see what else I need.
Oh, Ye Zeyu! Come in!
- What's wrong?
- Try it on for me.
My size is different from Eldest Young Master's.
I think it fits.
Sir, I will take this one too. You don't need to pack it. We will put it on.
Right, pick several sets of clothes in this size for each season.
Choose them based on his body measurements. Pack them all and send them to General Ye's manor.
Okay.
Ye Xiwu, is it for me?
Didn't I promise to buy you a new one before?
I forgot for many days. I'm sorry.
What are you standing here for? Put it on. It's getting dark.
Father and the others will worry about us.
Go.
Go, go, go!
Change into it.
Finally, we've finished shopping.
We can go home to have New Year's Eve dinner.
It seems taking you with me was a pretty wise decision.
Firecrackers. Who wants some firecrackers?
Firecrackers!
She is selling firecrackers.
Chuntao has bought some.
Buy some firecrackers!
There's no harm in buying a few more.
Ye Xiwu.
Miss, please buy some firecrackers.
Sister, I'll buy all the firecrackers in your basket.
I made these firecrackers with my own hands.
I'm afraid they are not very good-looking.
Don't worry. I like ones like that. How much do I owe you?
You can pay me 30 pennies. No, no...
pay me 20. Twenty is enough.
Here.
No, you shouldn't have. But…
- Miss…
- You can have this too.
- Happy New Year, sister.
- Miss, you don't have to…
I met a goddess today.
Why did you buy so many firecrackers?
I like setting them off. You got a problem with that?
It's so cold. The sooner she sells all of them, the earlier she can go home to celebrate New Year's Eve.
You bought all of them today, but tomorrow... she will still be out in the cold to sell them.
Maybe she'll meet another fool like me tomorrow.
Ye Xiwu, your small bag of money can't do much for her.
You are right.
There's no way to rid this world of misery, and there's nothing I can do to make a difference.
But, at least, she gets to go home earlier to celebrate New Year's Eve today.
[Till The End of The Moon]
Black Moonlight  sung by Zhang Bichen and Mao Buyi
♫  Mortal desires are like gazing upon the sudden disappearance of the moon  ♫
♫  The mortal world is like three thousand flowers in the midst of a snowstorm  ♫
♫  Compassion is embracing a butterfly during times of ruin and pain  ♫
♫  Realization is washing away our memories in turbid water and rain  ♫
♫  We'll never meet again  ♫
♫  I've seen the flowers bloom from soft-spoken words  ♫
♫  Teary-eyed till all that's left was nonsense  ♫
♫  Love intertwines around the fragile titled roof  ♫
♫  Embracing the endless lingering fear  ♫
♫  I've admired you through the myriad of years  ♫
♫  I believed I have been loved for a moment  ♫
♫  I plucked the dark feathers that shrouded my body in evil  ♫
♫  And become devout like the flawless moonlight  ♫
♫  Listen to the breathing of the flowers ♫
♫  and how they are just like any other creature  ♫
♫  No matter how far we walk, through the dust, wind, and stars  ♫
♫  The moonlight is my armor  ♫
♫  I'd admire your arrival when you came covered in scars  ♫
♫  And willingness to live a life in peace  ♫
♫  You plucked the dark feathers that shrouded your body in evil  ♫
♫  And learned to love what you used to resent  ♫
♫  Despite living insignificant lives, our dreams are as big as the sky  ♫
♫  And we'll make it something to remember us by  ♫