♪Hush now, don't disturb
the moonlight on the pond♪
♪A shattered heart
rests pillowed in my chest♪
♪I would shield you♪
♪From this cruel wind and frost♪
♪The russet cloth
brushes against my heart♪
♪Like sunset
draping over your shoulders♪
♪This lingering afterglow♪
♪Holds the image
of our very first glance♪
♪I borrow a thousand-year wind
to caress your gauze window♪
♪Tailoring moonlight
into your luminous gown♪
♪Severing the past,
weaving a thousand yards of splendor♪
♪With a thousand-year dream,
I seek the fragrance of your hair♪
♪Pouring a lifetime of passion
into the silk you wear♪
♪In this splendid world,
wherever you are is paradise♪
=The Silk Master from the Future=
=Episode 7=
(This story is entirely fictional.)
Prefect,
he is deceiving the public
with wicked words.
He should be arrested and punished!
You're right.
Li Yunhe,
is this your plan?
Hold on!
What are you doing here?
Go back, now.
Prefect,
Li Yunhe is the Zhou live-in son-in-law.
When you inquired
about strategies, Prefect,
he was merely proposing a response.
Even if his words were incorrect,
it hardly amounts to a crime.
Why must he be thrown into prison?
Moreover,
the matter of Li Yunhe tearing down
the proclamation
is already full of doubtful points.
That is indeed a questionable matter.
Wait.
And who might you be?
I'm...
She's my personal maid.
Her words don't count.
Guards!
Seize these two
who are disrupting the court!
Hold it.
Prefect,
I believe Li Yunhe's method is feasible.
Well, well,
you again?
Just now,
you were exchanging glances
with the Zhous' maid right here.
Now you jump out to help Li Yunhe?
Who the hell are you?
Prefect,
recently, the areas around Feng City
have been flooded.
Refugees are pouring in ceaselessly.
The grain price issue is already
a thorn in our side.
Why not try Li Yunhe's method first?
What's the harm
in making a last-ditch effort?
Better than sitting around
awaiting our doom.
That's absurd.
How can matters of people's livelihood
be treated as a game?
He's just a live-in son-in-law
of the Zhou household.
What does he know about statecraft?
Could it be that you already
have a good plan to deal with this?
I...
I don't know
whether Li Yunhe tore down
the proclamation willingly,
but since he remains calm
in the face of crisis,
presumably,
he's quite confident
in the strategy he proposed.
If it doesn't work,
and public unrest brews,
who will bear the consequences?
Originally,
I had the people in my heart,
but unfortunately,
you're all too foolish.
Forget it then.
It seems I must
visit the prison after all.
Guards!
Put the shackles on me, then.
Hold on!
Prefect,
I think
we should follow
Li Yunhe's method to proceed.
What's going on?
My lord,
what is your view on this matter?
I don't really understand statecraft,
but Chen is right.
There's no better way now.
Then let's try it as he said.
(So what if it incites a rebellion?)
(They're just
a bunch of lowlifes anyway.)
(At worst, I'll have Father
send troops to suppress them.)
(By then,
the people's anger and resentment)
(will all be pinned
on Li Yunhe and the Zhous.)
(Let's see if he survives that.)
We'll do this
dragon boat race
and implement
work relief.
The government will help post notices
to raise grain prices.
Yes.
Li Yunhe.
Prefect.
You go back and rest well.
I'll summon you if there's any matter.
Understood.
I take my leave then.
(Zhou Manor)
Hey,
what are you busy with?
I don't have time to explain now.
I'll help you pack first.
You need to hurry up
and flee
before the city gates close.
Why should I flee?
I'm doing just fine.
Besides,
I don't want to leave you.
How can you be so foolish?
Why did you have to
tear down that government proclamation?
Anyone can see
that Lu Qifeng and the Feng City Prefect
set it up to frame you.
You also said
once the disaster relief fails
and stirs public anger,
you'll be the first one
to be beheaded!
What are you panicking about?
If they dare
put my name out there,
before long,
my name
will be known throughout the land.
Yeah, you'll be wanted by everyone,
infamous for eternity.
No.
My good reputation will spread
across the world.
Where on earth
do you get this confidence?
Don't worry.
I have a life principle, which is
that a gentleman
never stands beneath a crumbling wall.
Besides, if there was real danger,
I'd have fled long ago.
Yeah, keep boasting.
Never mind.
If you won't leave, then don't.
At worst,
I'll just think of ways
to pull some strings
and work my connections.
(She's merely a hired hand
from the Zhou Manor.)
(Why does her manner of speaking)
(sound so much like the Zhou heiress?)
(Xianquan Tavern)
Yunzhuo.
Your incognito visit this time
is way too low-key.
That idiot Prefect from earlier
was clearly in cahoots
with the Marquis House.
Why didn't you just chop his head off?
Nonsense.
A court minister
can't be beheaded on a whim.
He holds the position
and performs his duties.
Moreover,
he did heed Li Yunhe's advice.
That shows he can still be redeemed.
Li Yunhe
really has some substance.
It's one thing
to be good at selling goods,
but he can also match verses.
He really is
a man of true talent and learning.
Just matching a line
counts as true talent and learning?
Your standard of judgment
is a bit too low, isn't it?
You were at the scene today,
and you couldn't match it either.
Moreover, Li Yunhe
answered the Prefect's questions
with clear logic
and a sharp mind.
Even you were full of praise.
Zhao Ziyao,
the longer you're out here,
the more insolent you become.
Fine, I'm sorry.
I truly think
Li Yunhe's potential
goes far beyond that.
How about we castrate him
and bring him into the palace,
so he can keep me company and amuse me?
That's enough.
Go back and rest.
You're a young lady,
yet you keep roaming around every day
without even changing your clothes?
It's just that
I don't have any comfortable clothes.
Well, Li Yunhe is to blame.
He sells Gambiered Silk,
and he's still being so stingy,
doing that pre-sale nonsense.
It's truly infuriating.
But on the other hand,
the quality
of this batch of Gambiered Silk
is indeed quite good.
I almost regret
revoking their imperial supplier status.
Send men
to keep a close watch on Li Yunhe
and the Marquis House.
Report to me at once
if there's any news.
Yes, Your Majesty.
The Prefect actually
went through with it?
Absolutely true.
The Prefect is now
sending people everywhere
to post notices,
raising the grain prices.
Interesting.
Truly interesting.
My lord,
now the Prefect
not only has people
posting notices everywhere,
but also says that Li Yunhe,
the folk talent, proposed the strategy.
And now,
many of the city's commoners
are cursing
this conscienceless scoundrel.
Good.
Very good.
Li Yunhe
likes raising grain prices, huh?
Send men out.
Have the neighboring
prefectures and counties
ship all their grain in.
Have them ship in as much as they have.
We'll sell it all to the government.
That's brilliant, my lord.
Right now, grain prices
in the surrounding areas are low.
We buy low
and sell high to the government.
All this gleaming silver
is money for the taking.
Once Li Yunhe's reputation
stinks to high heaven,
even if the Zhou family
wants to protect him,
they'll have to think twice
about the consequences.
I take my leave then, my lord.
My lord.
The situation now
is all under your control.
I shall take my leave as well.
Take care, Xie.
With the situation as it is,
don't you plan to make a big profit?
It's blood money.
I disdain to earn it.
Oh, Xie,
don't take this the wrong way,
but your family
is the wealthiest in Feng City.
In the way of business,
no one ever complains
about having too much money?
As long as your family
cooperates with my Marquis House,
I guarantee
you'll rake it in hand over fist.
My father entrusted the business to me,
teaching me to take benevolence
and righteousness as my foundation.
For me to hype grain prices with you
and frame Li Yunhe,
this must absolutely not be done.
It's the government buying
at a high price.
As they say, the people
shouldn't fight the officials.
Not to mention
that my Marquis House is backing it.
As long as you don't
come forward
to lower the grain prices...
Fine.
I agree then.
Alright.
Farewell.
The money?
My Marquis House earns it.
As for the infamy,
Li Yunhe will have to shoulder it.
(Today's grain price:
180 coins per hodful)
(Xinfeng Grain Shop)
Grain price is 180 coins per hodful.
It's all because
of that worthless Li Yunhe's idea!
Yeah!
Let's get Li Yunhe!
Where is your conscience?
- Let's beat him up!
- Get him!
(Zhou Manor)
Li Yunhe, come out now!
- Li Yunhe, get out here!
Li Yunhe,
with things as they are now,
how can you still be in the mood
to be drinking tea here?
Hey.
Why can't I enjoy some tea?
The front gate of the Zhou Manor
is packed with people,
and they're all cursing you.
After the government notice went out,
this afternoon, the grain price
has already risen
to 200 coins per hodful.
How could it have risen so much?
How?
How am I supposed to know?
Chunxiang, what does the Prefect say?
Mr. Li,
the steward
just inquired with the Prefect.
The Prefect says
we can continue posting notices
and continue raising prices,
but the government
will no longer buy grain.
Because they have no money.
No money?
Wait.
Feng City may have flooding this year,
but it's still a fertile land.
How can the government
be out of money so quickly?
Hey, Mr. Li,
where are you going so late at night?
Chunxiang.
I'm going out to discuss some matters.
Can't you see what's going on?
He's messed up
and is preparing to flee.
Go tell Xingyu about it
and have her sign the divorce letter
right away.
Bad news, Your Majesty.
The grain on the market
has been completely bought out.
Grain prices are still rising.
The common people
simply cannot buy any grain.
Those profiteering merchants
are utterly outrageous.
I originally intended
to attract grain merchants
from surrounding areas
to come sell grain quickly
by raising grain prices.
As grain prices increased
along with the supply,
those commoners who had money
could buy grain.
I never expected
it would turn out like this.
Could it be
that someone is meddling
behind the scenes?
Have you found anything?
Your Majesty,
the Marquis House
has seemingly dispatched many men
to procure grain from other regions.
The Marquis House
is clearly disregarding
people's livelihoods,
seeking to exploit this chance
to amass wealth.
You're absolutely right, Yunzhuo.
The Marquis House
has no regard for its reputation.
Their greed is truly despicable.
We need to find an opportunity
to give them a proper warning.
Any news from Li Yunhe?
Mr. Li had the Zhous' steward
deliver a letter to the Prefect,
asking the Prefect
to widely post notices
to raise grain prices.
But the Prefect's Office responded
that the government
already has no money to buy grain.
That shouldn't be.
Feng City is a fertile land,
so the city government's silver
should be able to last
for quite a while.
Your Highness,
I don't know about that.
A revolving door of Feng City Prefects
and an ironclad Marquis House...
The Marquis title
is hereditary and permanent,
entrenched in Feng City for many years.
They're already deeply rooted.
If the Feng City government coffers
were full of silver,
that would be the strange thing.
Your Majesty,
Li Yunhe requests an audience.
Li Yunhe? What's he doing here?
Summon him.
- Yes.
(Xianquan Tavern)
Mr. Li, what brings you here
so late at night?
My apologies for disturbing you
at this late hour.
Firstly, I came to thank you
for speaking up righteously
in the government office today.
Secondly,
there's a tremendous
opportunity for wealth.
I wonder if you
might be interested.
Tremendous wealth?
Li Yunhe,
you're not planning a rebellion,
are you?
Mr. Li, please don't take offense.
When my sister was little,
she suffered a fright once.
She's not quite hinged.
I...
I see.
But sir,
about your sister's tendency
to speak without thinking,
it's best
to keep her from going out too much
lest a careless remark be taken
seriously by someone with ill intentions
and bring a prison calamity upon you.
Don't you agree?
You're absolutely right, Li.
Well, after some time,
I'll find my sister
a suitable husband
and marry her off.
♪Fine rain falls outside the pavilion♪
♪With honors won, an old friend returns♪
♪Who took the March rain♪
♪To dye the silk against the skin♪
♪Yam juice enriches the silk threads♪
♪Weaving the Milky Way
down to the mortal world♪
♪Needle and thread
stitch away the marks of time♪
♪Cutting a yard of the misty rain♪
♪Embroidering half a scroll
of earthly verses♪
♪Where the golden honors hang high♪
♪The clouds dance in the air♪
♪Brewing wine, we speak of legends♪
♪In fine liquor,
true feelings are revealed♪
♪In this life I'd be a cloud-tailor♪
♪Never failing the stars,
nor failing you♪
♪Fine rain falls outside the pavilion♪
♪With honors won, an old friend returns♪
♪Who took the March rain♪
♪To dye the silk against the skin♪
♪Yam juice enriches the silk threads♪
♪Weaving the Milky Way
down to the mortal world♪
♪Warp and weft entwine,
one shuttle, one dream♪
♪As seasons change♪
♪Cutting a yard of the misty rain♪
♪Embroidering half a scroll
of earthly verses♪
♪Where the golden honors hang high♪
♪The clouds dance in the air♪
♪Brewing wine, we speak of legends♪
♪In fine liquor,
true feelings are revealed♪
♪Washing away
a lifetime of wear and tear♪
♪Only for you♪
♪On the street of golden honors,
the music rises♪
♪The moon moves west
beyond the pavilion♪
♪Wine runs dry, yet the revelry lingers♪
♪In silk, I seek a kindred soul♪
♪The rain has ceased,
clouds begin to clear♪
♪The fragrant silk billows
under the low-hung stars♪
♪I'd cut the clouds and morning glow
to drape over you♪
♪A single bolt of silk becomes♪
♪Your wedding gown♪