- Hello, Sir.
- Hi, there.
[Keep Out]
Someone has been barricading oneself in the building for ten hours.
I heard about this news online.
Apparently, the perpetrator has taken a hostage.
What? That's insane.
Ever since I was young,
I was always hit by small bouts of bad luck.
So I'm used to getting my usual bad luck, but...
it's a bit different this time.
Come on, isn't this too crazy?
[Good morning.]
[Nice weather today.]
[See you soon.]
[Breaking News: Male taken hostage by armed robber]
A bank robber has hid himself in this apartment complex.
The robber has taken a male resident hostage.
As 15 hours have already passed, there are concerns for the hostage.
♫ During the day, things aren't looking up,
and you're discouraged. Yeah! ♫
♫ No matter how tough things may be...
You can overcome them, keep it up! ♫
♫ Let's go! I'm right here within your reach ♫
♫ I'll catch you when you fall into despair ♫
♫ I'm here for you. Never leave you ♫
♫ The vast world ♫
♫ Could bewilder us from time to time ♫
♫ I hope you'd never change because you're
perfect the way you are ♫
[Mr. Unlucky Has No Choice but to Kiss!]
[Episode 8: Mr. Unlucky Has No Choice but to Be Happy!]
I've had all kinds of bad luck ever since I was born.
I guess my unlucky life ends here...
But in my final hours...
Watch out!
I'm glad I was able to meet him.
For a constantly unlucky guy like me, meeting him
may have been the only good thing in my life.
I had so much fun.
We promised, didn't we?
And I wanted to see you as soon as I could.
I was so happy.
Wow! When your life is about to end,
all your happy memories really do flash before your eyes.
You got mad earlier for my sake, right? Thanks.
Dating is the only option.
Eating like this every morning will be normal for us now, huh?
I wanted to live longer...
together with Naoya.
- It's scary.
- Please stay back.
- Did something happen here?
- Yes, there is an incident.
You over there, please stay back.
Please stay back. It's dangerous.
Everyone, please stay back.
Please open the door!
Kota!
Naoya?
Kota, are you okay?
Please!
Take me as your hostage instead.
Please open the door.
Kota.
Please.
Kota!
The bank robber is still in the building with the hostage...
Oh, someone came out.
I wonder who the victim and the robber is.
Come out after you've done your time.
Yes, I'll atone for what I've done.
Officers, please take her away.
And by the way,
this is a toy.
Oh, that woman seems to be the culprit.
Let's go.
The police officers are escorting the bank robber to the police station.
Please let them through.
Stay back. Make a way for them.
Passing through. Please let them pass.
I can't believe this guy.
What? You looked like her first love?
Apparently, we look exactly alike.
You shouldn't do this.
You can always start over.
I know you can.
See, you're shaking so much.
You're not the type to do something like this.
I fell hard for a pop star and wanted to support him.
So I needed money.
Okay, so the robber listened to Naoya just like that?
Yeah.
That's amazing.
You've really got something.
Yeah.
Kota, it was a mishap for you.
But I'm glad you're okay.
It could've been so much worse.
Yeah. I guess so.
Hey, Naoya, can we talk about next week's seminar?
Sure.
Thanks.
I'll be right back.
- See you.
You sure are loved, Kota.
What? Are you flustered?
No, not at all.
Kota, over here.
I've been called over. I'll be back soon.
You know, Naoya,
when I was taken hostage, I thought my life was over.
And at the same time, I really wanted to live more.
Since I was a kid,
I always had small instances of bad luck everywhere.
I caused a lot of trouble for people.
I was worried that my bad luck would continue forever.
I really hated it at one point.
But ever since I met you,
I realized that I can enjoy my life
for the first time.
Hey.
Move in with me.
What's this all of a sudden?
Well, I'm worried about you.
If I'm nearby, you can live a normal life. Right?
I don't want you to be in danger like that when I'm not around.
So...
Oh, don't worry about that.
I mean, think about it.
Do you plan on being with me 24/7?
It's obviously impossible.
I know, but...
I'm really happy you're caring for me.
But I'm not with you to get rid of my bad luck.
And I've been thinking lately
that having bad luck isn't bad.
It's thanks to my bad luck that I got to meet you.
I'm truly grateful for that.
What? Stop staring at me.
Well, there's something I've been keeping from you.
What?
You know...
I knew about you before we met.
What? Since when?
The entrance ceremony.
Seriously?
To be more exact, on the way home after the ceremony.
- We have the same major.
- Let's hang out one day.
Okay! Of course, let's hang out.
What a breath of fresh air.
At first, you caught my attention because I liked your face.
You liked my face?
But that wasn't all.
Be more careful!
Okay, I will! I'm sorry!
Who the hell are you telling to be careful?
Don't you know the law, you bastard?
That sudden change in your attitude made me fall hard for you.
Then I got more and more curious about you.
You were always cautious and stayed at a distance from others.
You kept shallow relationships
to avoid getting too involved with people.
It reminded me of myself.
What? How does that remind you of yourself?
You have super good luck and I have bad luck.
We're complete opposites.
People always wanted something from me because of my good luck.
Some even tried to use me.
I mean, Naoya is guaranteed to get the tickets.
You're only interested in his good luck.
You always manage to get the tickets, so they used you
for a profit.
After seeing you,
I realized that I avoided deep relationships with people, too.
You and I are the same.
That's why I was happy
when you called me out.
Excuse me...
Hey, it's you, Kota.
Can I talk to Naoya for a second?
- Naoya?
- Sure.
So, at that point, you already...
Of course, I knew your real personality.
I was wondering if we could tour the place together.
Sure thing.
Really? I'm so glad.
You were happy just being with me.
It broke evenly!
And even the smallest things brightened up your eyes.
Really?
When I saw you like that, your happiness spread to me.
And you looked for me...
Naoya!
I'm so glad I found you.
Nobody had ever looked at me with such eyes before.
So I was certain that you'd never stand me up.
I got worried that something happened.
Hello? Do you know where Kota lives?
So when you showed up at the meeting place...
I'm really sorry.
I was relieved that you were okay.
Then, you were looking for me that whole time?
The time we spent together made me like you even more,
so I was fine with whatever reason you had for approaching me.
But then you said that...
Naoya, I have something else I want to talk about.
I was hoping we could stay together always.
I was really happy.
Even as fake boyfriends,
I was content with just seeing your happy face.
No, we aren't fake boyfriends.
I told you, my bad luck isn't why I'm with you.
I'm with you because I really like you.
So just stay with me and be my boyfriend like you wanted.
Oh, I, um...
Hey, I told you it's not funny!
Hey, don't laugh.
- Don't laugh.
- Say it again.
- No way!
- Just say it!
- I don't want to. You say it then.
- Why do I have to?
- I won't say it.
- Just smile for me then.
Hey, Naoya, what is this?
You didn't win the ticket? For real?
[Sorry, you did not win the ticket.]
Wow, that's rare.
You were so famous for your 100% success rate.
This has been happening a lot lately.
Maybe you did something to make your luck disappear.
- Didn't you?
- What happened?
Could it be... my fault?
Tell us what happened. Don't you find it too odd?
- Nothing happened.
- Are you sure?
Kota, do you want to go on a date again?
Sure.
Oh, but if you're with me...
Remember earlier?
Maybe your luck is disappearing because you're with me.
Sorry, if that's the case.
Don't apologize.
Rather than something invisible like luck,
being with you is far more important to me.
Thank you.
Yeah. Then let's spend the night somewhere next time.
Sure.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah, see you tomorrow.
I'm a bit lonely going home alone without Naoya.
But I want to move in
only when we really want to live together one day.
Until then, no matter what bad luck comes my way,
I think I can be optimistic and overcome it all.
After all, I have Naoya now.
Hey, there.
I heard your breaker exploded. Sounds awful.
This is so exhausting.
Well, I'm glad you're not hurt.
And you can stay here until it's fixed.
Oh, I'm just staying one night.
What? Really?
I thought you were coming back.
Oh, I wasn't thinking it at all
when I called Naoya.
Oh, I didn't want to rely too much on you.
I've already told you this.
It makes me happy when you rely on me.
Then... Then please...
let me stay at your place for a while.
Of course.
It's heavy, right? Come in.
Okay, thanks for letting me stay.
Even though I was experiencing bad luck at the moment,
I felt lucky.
Hey, where's your air mattress from last time?
Oh, I punctured a hole when I folded it up,
so we can't use it anymore.
Wait! Is it because I used it?
But thanks to that, we can sleep together like this.
So close.
Don't worry, I won't do anything.
You won't?
What? Can I?
No, that's not what I...
Good night, Kota.
Good night.
No way, I can't believe we're sleeping in the same bed.
Are you asleep?
Yeah.
You're awake. Why are you lying?
Just because...
And why the hell would you ask if I'm sleeping?
How am I supposed to sleep?
And I woke up that morning after an uneventful night.
It seems Naoya will wait until I feel more comfortable.
But I do feel a bit unsatisfied.
Channel Manager: taijitu_09
Chief Segmenter: bjohnsonwong
Translation Editor: ta2gal
General Editor: cerejacult
Chief Editor: kakashiandme
He's not waking up.
Why won't you do that when I'm awake?
You... were awake?
You just woke me up.
Hey, why won't you do that when I'm awake?
Hey, stop that.
I'm sorry.
- Rai-kun, help me!
- You're sneaky.
- Sorry.
- I won't let you go!
Let go of me. Let go, Naoya.
What the hell?
- I'm going to tickle you.
- No.
♫ Together while holding hands ♫
♫ Let's get to know each other entirely ♫
♫ Till the day we die ♫
[THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION.]