A mafia can't kill another mafia.
Fuck.
You know what happens if you break the rules, right?
If you kill me,
you'll die, too.
Fuck. Hey!
I'll kill you, you fuckking bitch.
Where are you? Where are you?
Hey! Open the door!
Hey!
Open the door, I said! Fuck!
Just give up.
Everything will be over in thirty minutes, anyway.
Fuck. What are you saying?
Where... Where did this go? Why?
We're a team. You can't do this to me.
It's almost over. Why are you doing this? Please...
Get it together!
There's no point saving Lee Yun Seo and Kim Jun Hui.
They're civilians, and you're a mafia. You can't live together!
Fuck. Oh Jeong Won.
When people die...
hearing is the last sense you lose. You know that, right?
Listen carefully.
Fuck. Lee Yun Seo. You die, too.
Fuck...
Ahn Na Hui?
Check if she died after thirty minutes and message me.
It's so cold.
The blanket. The blanket...
Shit.
Fuck.
What? What's going on?
Why did it turn off?
Why...
Who's this?
Who's there!
Shit...
What are you doing? Don't do it. Don't do it.
Shit.
Shit, who's this?
Why are you doing this to me?
Fuck!
Don't come. Don't come, you bastard!
Fuck. Why? Why...
Why are you doing this even in death!
You were going to kill me if I didn't kill you!
Hey! Get lost!
Fuck! Get lost!
Im Eun Chan and Choi Mi Na were executed by the mafia overnight.
Im Eun Chan and Choi Mi Na were civilians.
All participants, please find the mafia and begin voting.
You should've killed me, too, if you were going to do this.
Why did you let me live?
I need to die if you want this to end the way you guys want.
So why did you let me live?
Why did you let me live?
What are you thinking, exactly?
I can't talk for long right now.
Let me take care of Jin Da Beom first.
What...
are you talking about?
Did you kill them?
Answer me.
Hey.
Say something!
Hey. Please calm down.
Let's talk later.
Hey, Oh Jeong Won.
Hey!
Jun Hui.
How could she do this to us?
Jin Da Beom will try to kill you guys if he runs into you. Be careful.
Why do you think...
Jeong Won didn't kill us?
Whatever. Don't think about that anymore.
We can't trust either of them anymore, anyway.
Let's vote for Jin Da Beom for now and think about what to do.
What do you mean?
He won't just sit still if we vote for him, too.
He'll do whatever he can.
And even if he dies, there will be Oh Jeong Won.
We'll be in danger at night.
We need to take care of things before that.
What...
are you thinking of doing?
If necessary,
we will have to kill her to stop her.
I'll go to the storage in case something might happen.
I'll come with you.
No. Get some rest.
- Why? I'll go, too.
- Please listen to me.
You know they're on the second floor.
I'll be right back. Keep the door locked.
Okay.
♪  Happy birthday to you  ♪
What's this?
It's a birthday present.
Put it on me.
- Thank you.
- Do you like it?
I like it a lot.
Jeong Won isn't here.
But why did you let me live?
Why did you let me live?
I can't talk for long right now.
No way.
Jin Da Beom is missing.
I'll look for him. Stay with Yun Seo–
That's enough.
I won't be fooled by you guys anymore.
He's really planning to kill us all.
- He's dangerous.
- That's enough, I said!
Hey.
I heard you guys are the mafia.
You and Jin Da Beom are the same to me and Yun Seo.
Come to the rooftop if you want to save Lee Yun Seo.
Shit...
Yun Seo!
What the hell? I thought I'd seen it all.
Don't come.
Don't do that, you crazy bastard.
That's enough. Let go of Yun Seo.
Did you kill Go Gyeong Jun and Shin Seung Bin, too?
Are you happy you ended up just like them?
Shut up, you fucking bitch.
You don't have to go this far.
How does it feel to see me again?
- Happy to see me, right?
- I'm the one you want to kill.
Let go of Yun Seo.
I wish I could.
But what can I do?
I can't fucking stab you, you know.
- So what do you want?
- What else?
I should finish what I couldn't do yesterday.
Go upstairs.
- Do you want me to jump?
- Yes.
You have to die if I can't kill you.
No. No–
Shut your mouth!
Fuck! That's enough. You son of a bitch.
Hey. Do that to me instead.
Fuck. You stay out of this.
Shut up and just watch!
By the way,
what will you do after I die?
- Will you let go of Yun Seo?
- No...
As for that...
it depends on how you behave.
You won't let her live even if I die.
You don't want to jump? Should I kill her right now?
It's not that!
I wish I could do it, too, but...
I can't do it because this is against the rule, too.
What are you saying?
A mafia can't commit suicide.
They can't kill themselves.
Why not? What about Choi Ju Won then?
He got executed because he broke the rules.
This is a different situation.
Don't fucking come, I said.
I'd be dying because you threatened me, so you'd be killing me.
Shut up and jump!
Don't you remember my warning at the freezer last night?
Do you want to die together?
Don't come, fuck! Just jump!
Son of a bitch!
Die, you son of a bitch!
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Let go, you son of a bitch.
Fuck!
Let's...
just die together.
Yun Seo.
Yun Seo!
Hey, you crazy son of a bitch!
You son of a bitch!
Fuck.
Jin Da Beom has died.
Jin Da Beom was a mafia.
Hang in there.
You need to stay awake.
Did you get hurt at all?
I'm okay.
It hurts! It hurts!
Okay...
- Don't talk.
- Yes.
- I'm okay. I'm okay.
- Don't talk.
I was going to take care of it.
Why did you do that? Why?
I'm sorry.
I think I know who you are now.
I missed you...
Se Eun.
But...
please stop now.
I'm sorry.
I...
I had no choice, either.
I know.
It's okay.
So...
please stop now.
Yun Seo. Yun Seo!
Wake up! Wake up, Yun Seo!
Yun Seo!
Hang in there for a bit.
I'll let you get out of here.
No.
Jeong Won.
No...
Yun Seo.
Yun Seo!
Hey, Yun Seo! Yun Seo!
Hey! Yun Seo!
Oh Jeong Won has died.
Oh Jeong Won was a mafia.
The mafia game has ended with the civilian team's victory.
Jun Hui. Jun Hui.
Wake up.
Kim Jun Hui!
Just leave him!
He might end up in a coma if you interrupt him while connected to the server.
Do you...
remember us?
You're Se Eun's parents.
What...
What is all this?
How was the game?
Was the dying experience scary and painful enough?
What did you say?
What happened to everyone?
What did you do?
Don't worry.
They're only asleep.
They're unconscious,
but the pain is real.
Was all of this a game?
You came here only recently,
but you've played the game dozens of times already.
Time moves at a different pace in the game.
But Jeong Won is supposed to be the sole winner in all games.
You guys won for the first time.
What did you do to Jeong Won that she helped you?
Tell me.
We need to know so we can fix it.
I woke you up to ask you that.
Why...
Why are you doing this? Why?
In the world my daughter created,
you all need to pay for your sins.
What sins?
Did you really ask "what sins" just now?
The sin of bullying Se Eun, who was innocent.
The sin of putting her in hell by believing in the baseless rumor!
Those are your sins.
Hey, get out of here.
Wh-Wh-What? What is it?
- What are you doing?
- Do you still collect porn?
Give it back! Give it back to me.
- Give it back to me, I said.
- Hold on, hold on.
Look what he's into.
Give me my phone back!
Wow, it's sexy. So sexy.
She's like a celebrity. A celebrity.
Where are you going?
Se Eun.
Park Se Eun!
Hey, did something happen to her?
I don't know.
Thanks to our CM: damiechan
Your classmate died.
But why...
did no one try to take responsibility?
Everyone's afraid they'd be in trouble.
You say it was a joke, a misunderstanding, that you didn't know. They're all excuses.
No one owned up to their fault.
No one did.
That's why we created this game.
I wanted you to feel the pain
just like how our Se Eun felt.
To teach you what you've done.
Yes.
I know you were a special friend to Se Eun.
You should've saved her, then!
Why did you leave her to die?
You're just like the rest of them.
The memories get erased every time.
So you'll never get used to the pain.
It'll feel new every time.
Live in this game forever.
Wait...
I also...
miss...
Se Eun a lot.
I want to tell her...
she suffered so much alone.
I want to apologize for not knowing.
If someone has to be responsible,
I will.
So please let the rest of them go home. Please?
You're not entirely back to normal now.
It might hurt if you strain yourself.
I...
don't care about being in pain at all.
So just choose me.
Please let everyone go...
Everyone...
Let everyone go. Please...
Please...
She got her memories back because Jeong Won helped her.
She changed the setting as a birthday present, so she could get her memories back.
What are you trying to say?
Committing suicide wasn't one of the options.
Jeong Won took action, believing she was Se Eun.
She chose to save them.
Get it together!
That's not our daughter!
It's just an error caused by the setting.
- Let go.
- That wasn't a simple error! It was Jeong Won's will!
What if Se Eun doesn't want to play this game like Jeong Won?
What if we're taking revenge just for ourselves?
No.
We aren't even close.
We aren't even close yet.
She bet her life to save her friend.
Not everyone did, but some of them felt guilty toward Se Eun.
We could give them another chance at this point.
Let's have all of them go and keep an eye on them.
No, I can't do that.
Move.
Move, I said!
Our Se Eun...
is dead and gone now.
Thanks to our chief segmenters: manganese, iamsolyne, damiechan
Thanks to our segmenters: teufelchen_netty_266
Thanks to our TE: abythe
Thanks to our general editors: anna_vos and daiemyllygunnarsen_878
Thanks to our chief editors: damiechan and oriannanixy_957
Thank you for watching!
Shit! I lost again!
You scared me.
What's this?
Yes, Ms. Kim.
Where?
The bus stopped?
H-Hello? Hello?
No.