Kim Dong Hyeon was a civilian.
They're here.
What happened to Dong Hyeon?
H-Hey, say something.
Where is Dong Hyeon? What on earth happened?
He thought…
the white line had disappeared…
and he went to check on it...
but he slipped.
What about the village?
How far did you go?
You said you were going to find people and ask for help! Did you?
We can't go.
Everything is blocked by the lines.
We're completely trapped.
Then...
we are really…
trapped here until we finish this game?
Yes.
Are you crying?
If I hadn't
suggested…
that we go to the mountains...
they wouldn't have died.
If I had just kept quiet…
Dong Hyeon died because of me.
It's not like you forced anyone.
They volunteered.
No one knew there was no path.
No one knew. What could we have done?
So…
what will you do now?
We can't leave here until the game is over.
Are you going to stay like this?
No.
I will find another way.
Hello? Hello?
Hello? Hey. Hey!
Where are you going?
Gyeong Jun and the others called me.
If you don't want to go, then don't go.
I think I should go anyway.
Shit!
Damn it!
Hey, Kim Jun Hui!
What are you doing?
Isn't that a phone call?
What's wrong?
Hello?
Just leave it.
What's wrong?
It's all fake.
What?
The wire wasn't even connected.
What the heck?
Look at this.
It's empty.
You love sesame.
Yes, thank you.
The only thing we have in common is our love of ramen.
Then do you have a different kind of taste in music?
Fuck! Do you want to die?
How dare you force a pervert's music on me?
All right! I won't.
Hey, Otaku.
Games are your area of expertise.
Did this game exist before?
No, I've never seen it before, either.
And I'm not an Otaku.
All right, sorry about that.
Anyway, what do we need to do to win this game?
It's the same as the mafia game.
Have you never played it before?
Who doesn't know that, you fucker?
You're the only one who knows if you're a civilian or a mafia until you die.
You need to find out who plays what role on the other team.
Doctors and Police Officers are on the same side as Civilians.
The team that kills the other team first wins.
Fuck, when will we find all the mafia members?
Hey,
what if we just kill whoever we want?
Then the game will end.
You said you're also a civilian.
We only need to kill all the mafia. Why kill everyone?
It says to kill everyone, you fool.
Why would you kill your own team?
You can't even kill anyone. You're just bluffing.
You were scared to death when others died…
You fucker! When was I ever scared–
Shit! Shut up, would you?
Choi Ju Won!
Why did he die if he was the mafia?
I don't really know, either.
He says that the mafia has to kill someone.
There must have been a reason why Ju Won was killed instead of a civilian.
What happens when a civilian kills a member of the mafia?
Is that allowed?
It's not in the rules, so I don't know.
Let's just gather all the mafia members and tell them to kill their own teammates.
- Good idea.
- Isn't it? I'm a genius.
- That sounds good, doesn't it?
- It does.
Gosh, you morons.
What part of that sounds good to you?
Do you think this will work?
What if someone like Choi Ju Won dies today?
We will have to hide and lock the doors or something.
Are you going to vote?
We have to.
How many of us are Mafia?
I don't know. It doesn't say.
Oh, yes. The police officer!
The message this morning said that the police officer used his power. He should know!
Are you all really civilians?
Aren't there any police officers here?
Hold on! Things are getting hectic.
If we're really going to vote, let's call Jun Hui as well.
Go and get Jun Hui.
She should get him herself.
What about Na Hui?
Who knows? She's probably asleep in the infirmary.
Hey, Park Wu Ram! Get Na Hui, too!
When I got hurt,
I should have said it was painful and convinced them to come back.
This wouldn't have happened if we had returned immediately.
No.
Even if you asked them to come back,
they could've just kept going.
It's not your fault.
Even so…
Everyone is to blame.
Even when I saw Dong Hyeon die right before my eyes,
I couldn't do anything.
Hyeon Ho,
let's survive and get out of here.
I'll protect you, no matter what.
Will you?
Once we escape,
I want to watch your game.
Don't fall for me after you've watched the game.
Why on earth do you think
the person who created the Mafia game is doing this?
First, we need to find out who created this game and why.
Where do you think the creator of this game is?
We are the only ones here right now.
What if they come when we fall asleep?
That's when they killed Ju Won, too.
They said the mafia killed Ju Won,
but our class is the only one on the list of participants.
Any other participants would've been on the list.
You're right.
The mafia would have been selected when the roles were assigned.
Then…
does this mean that someone among us killed Ju Won?
If it's according to the rules,
I guess so.
Who do you think is the mafia?
Seeing as how Choi Ju Won died, wouldn't it be Go Gyeong Jun's group?
She's right. They harassed Choi Ju Won all the time.
I think Jin Ha and Seung Bin even borrowed a lot of money from Choi Ju Won.
I don't know about Choi Ju Won,
but mafia members usually try to kill civilians.
We might be able to tell from yesterday's votes.
Let's kill Heo Yul first.
Wait, why are you looking at me?
Well, Eun Ha, you're the one who suggested that we all vote for Heo Yul yesterday.
I just listened to you and voted.
Hey, Choi Mi Na!
Are you saying I'm the mafia?
Eun Ha,
why exactly did you accuse Yul of being Mafia?
It's not me.
Are you saying that I killed Yul on purpose?
Yul got all the votes under your guidance!
It's true!
That is true.
What's wrong with you guys?
Hey, Kim So Mi.
Then why did you do that?
Me?
Do what?
I saw how you pushed Dong Hyeon in the mountains.
He died because of you!
Are you crazy?
Did I push him?
Hey, that's not true!
I almost died trying to grab Kim Dong Hyeon as he fell!
Everyone else saw it happen. Stop bullshitting!
Guys, I honestly had no idea. It was just a joke.
She knew he was going to die, and she pushed him anyway!
I told you I didn't.
Hey, call Jun Hui and the others.
Ask the other guys!
Hey! Both of you, that's enough.
Nice!
What are you doing?
We can eat with you once we've confirmed whether you're an ally or foe.
What are you saying? Give me my phone!
Is this good?
Fucking shit!
Stay the fuck still!
You're dead if you make me spill it.
One hit per drop. Understood?
Shit.
It's the same as ours. The role doesn't show up.
Fuck! You son of a bitch, I got something on me!
G-Give it back now.
Hold on. I still need to check something.
Check what?
If I can use someone else's phone to vote,
I can target the votes as I please.
Kneel!
Let go! Let go of me! Let go!
Hey,
choose someone. I'll press it for you.
I don't want to.
Then I'll vote for you.
Hey, stop it. S-Stop it!
I said, stop it! Stop it!
I said, stop it! Seriously, stop it—
Shit, I guess you can't vote on someone's behalf.
Hey, I have been looking for you everywhere.
Let's go. Everyone's about to vote.
Are they going to vote again after Yul's death?
The game has to end so we can go.
We have no choice.
Still, how can we do it again?
We have to stop them.
We shouldn't vote.
How can we stop them?
We need a plan to convince them.
I'll convince them. Are they all gathered?
No, they are in different rooms.
First, let's get everybody together.
I'm going to help you, too.
Where's Da Beom?
Go Gyeong Jun's group called him earlier.
Geez, those damn bastards.
They really get on my nerves.
I said, let go!
Hold on, will you?
Okay. Stay still.
Fuck, it doesn't work.
Hey!
That's enough.
What are you guys doing?
What the fuck?
- Da Beom, get up.
- Get up.
Stand up.
One against three?
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
Where do you think you're going?
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, that's enough.
Come with us. We need to discuss something.
Why should I listen to you? Hey, you!
Damn it! Hey.
You motherfucker.
Why should I listen to you, you son of a bitch? Come here.
Fucking bastards.
Words don't get through to you, right?
You need a beating.
You son of a bitch!
Son of a bitch!
Let the fuck go! Let go, you son of a bitch.
Will you listen?
Will you do as we say?
All right, you motherf*cker!
Let's go.
Hey, hey, hey!
Let him go. Come here!
Hey! Just stop it, will you?
Should I tell everyone what you guys just did?
What will everyone think?
Get it together.
Why are you wasting your breath?
I think they'll all start voting once we give them the go-ahead.
How about it?
Should I click your name?
You fucking bitch.
Put this down.
We won't tell anyone, so put this down.
Just stop it now, please.
F***.
There will be a meeting in the auditorium.
I think you should come as well.
Keep the snack bar open for everyone.
The reason we gathered everyone
isn't to choose whom to vote for.
It's to convince you not to vote at all.
"Not to vote at all"?
Can we do that?
If we vote, someone will die, no matter what,
but if no one votes, everyone can live.
What if someone votes secretly after everyone agrees not to?
What happens then?
She's right. How can we trust everyone?
We have to get everyone to trust one another.
We can collect all the phones. Then no one can vote.
Yes, if we collect all the phones, no one will be able to vote.
We can do it.
Who will be in charge of the phones?
This person may change his or her mind.
We can collect them and leave them in the center of the room for all to see.
Yes, we can all keep an eye on them at all times.
What if someone steals them?
I don't want to. I'm not giving you mine.
This sounds like a good idea. Let's hand in ours.
Are you crazy?
Who would steal your phone? Just hand it over!
- I said, I don't want to!
- Are you a phone addict?
- Don't.
- What?
Why the fuck are you giving me all this shit?
No one will die if we hand them in.
You guys are fucking noisy.
The Class President is saying something right for once.
Why aren't you all cooperating?
You have to hand in your phone so no one can vote.
Every one of you better hand them in.
Hand it in while I say it nicely.
What are you waiting for? Hurry.
Come on, hurry!
Hurry. We're running out of time.
One minute left until voting ends.
Gosh…
Seriously, fuck!
Hey, Class President! Are you sure this is okay?
Let's wait for now.
It's not even midnight yet.
Hey…
Hey, hey! It's past midnight, and there's no announcement.
Did… Did it work?
We're fine now, right?
We did it!
- We did it!
- We're okay!
We're okay!
We're okay now, right?
Participants must vote to track down the mafia.
Hey! What are you doing?
What do you think?
If I do nothing and die, will you take the responsibility?
She's right.
Guys, hold on! Hold on!
We don't know that yet.
Know about what?
The game will simply continue as before.
If we die because of you, will you take responsibility?
Hey, hey!
Don't accuse Jun Hui for no reason. Calm down.
Lee Su Bin and Park Ji Hun will be executed for violating the rules.
Lee Su Bin and Park Ji Hun were civilians.
Everyone handed in their phones, right?
Participants must vote to locate Mafia members.
What the are you doing?
Find your phone unless you want to die.
Fuck!
We must vote! If we don't, we'll die!
Oh Jin Seo will be executed for violating the rules.
Kim Jun Hui, hurry!
Jun Hui.
What are you doing?
Kim Jun Hui!
Oh Jin Seo was a civilian.
Idiots.