(Lee Je Hoon)
(Kim Dae Myeong)
(Sung Dong Il)
(Jang Hyun Sung)
(Oh Man Seok)
(Ahn Hyun Ho)
(Cha Kang Yoon)
(The Art of Negotiation)
- Have you tried it a lot? - My gosh.
- Really? - Wait.
- You've been here often? - This is so good.
- Hey, we're going to line up. - Why isn't the line moving?
- I should lose weight. - Seriously.
- We should get some for to-go. - You stay out.
Mr. Lee.
Oh, my.
How have you been?
Well, you know...
Are you still working for the same company?
Well...
What was the name of the company?
- It's GOGO Consulting. - Right.
- That's the one. GOGO. - Yes.
Why don't we talk?
Sure. Well...
Excuse me for a second. Get me suyuk, will you?
Seriously? The name of the company is GOGO?
Is it a nightclub?
I don't think you can show your face around Yeouido.
What?
This town is filled with con artists.
I'm considered a straight guy in this town.
Even so, you got caught.
Exactly.
I shouldn't have gotten caught like you.
Word is...
you're still running your game.
My gosh. You must have lost your mind.
Who told you that?
Yet, you're not denying it.
Hey.
I can bankroll it.
Do you want to play a hand together?
You're unbelievable.
- You haven't learned your lesson. - Right.
I made so much money that I can't come to my senses.
How much do you have?
Well,
I've got some.
(Episode 12: The Game)
All right.
Mr. Yoon.
You're also admitting that you own JUMBO Pharma's shares, correct?
Yes,
I am.
I was trying to do you a favor.
But you turned it down.
(Sanin)
You must not know what I'm holding in my hand.
I know exactly what it is.
And you must have more evidence.
Mr. Yoon.
That's enough.
Let me tell you.
This proves that Yoon Joo No was...
directly involved in manipulating JUMBO's stock price.
He owned ten times the number of shares his brother did.
With that many shares, he did more than just participate.
He was the leader of this operation.
Director Ha.
Mr. Chair.
It's too soon to jump to conclusions.
Then what?
Should we hand him over to the FSS?
Or the prosecution? Should we ask them for a second opinion?
Listen.
This isn't the time for you to protect your pride.
You must accept your mistake and bow down.
We're just trying to help you with good intentions.
I'm simply answering the questions I've been asked.
Please continue.
We're not here...
to determine whether or not you committed a crime.
The purpose of our meeting is to decide the disciplinary action.
Accept the disciplinary action.
If you disagree with our decision, you can seek legal representation.
Let's take a short recess.
A short recess for what?
We should just finish the meeting. And we'll be free to rest then.
Let's take a break.
Fine. All right. Let's all have a cup of coffee.
Okay.
(Sanin)
What's gotten into him?
He must be out of it.
- You think so? - Yes. That's quite common.
Yoon Joo No rarely loses it.
My gosh, everyone loses it at meetings like this.
Everyone pleads and begs us to believe them.
They demand our help to uncover the truth...
while claiming to be innocent.
They kneel on the floor and beg in tears.
I've fallen for it several times.
But once we present evidence and press hard on them,
they all crumble.
There hasn't been an exception ever. Not even once in my career.
Then shouldn't he plead at least?
I bet he wants to.
He probably wants to get down on his knees right now.
But as you know, he likes to save face.
He doesn't know when to bow down.
Well, it only takes one shot to take down guys like him.
Precisely.
(Sanin)
Is it going according to your plan?
Not exactly.
Then admitting to your actions could be a viable option too.
This could end with your dismissal.
Just like I told you when I first came back to Korea,
I have nothing to lose.
So the severity of the disciplinary action...
doesn't matter either.
Why doesn't it matter?
You don't know what you're in for.
Will I go to prison?
That's why...
you want me to agree to dismissal, right?
Let's say this ends with my dismissal. What then?
What's next?
Sanin Group can file a civil lawsuit against me, right?
It will cost a fortune to compensate for the damage.
Even so, why play a hand that will backfire?
If you keep this up, it will cost more than your job.
When they file a lawsuit, it will be an emotional move.
How will you benefit from that?
I came back here because...
I wanted to find out the truth about my brother.
So...
I'm only speaking the truth now.
So you don't care...
if you end up in prison...
or get sued as long as you find out the truth?
Yes.
(Sanin)
- Bring us coffee. - Yes, sir.
- Hear me out. - Sure.
There's no way Yoon doesn't know about the company's situation.
Could it be a suicide mission?
A suicide mission?
"Sanin manipulates stock prices."
He might be planning to expose us and ruin us completely.
By causing our stock price to crash?
So he could be trying to drag us down with him.
How will he handle the consequences?
My gosh.
Why would a man who has nothing to lose worry about that?
Come in.
Gosh, later.
If that's the case,
we must make our move first.
How?
We must get ahead of him and expose that he manipulated the stock price.
My gosh. I told you that wasn't an option.
That's what he wants right now.
No.
"Sanin Group was able to stop..."
"the corporate raider, Yoon Joo No, from manipulating the stock price."
That's the angle we should play.
"Sanin Group is capable of weeding out internal risks."
That will be our stance.
How will we convince the chairman?
We can't convince him.
The articles would be published without our knowledge.
I see. So...
Sanin Group is facing difficulties because of Yoon Joo No.
Since he was removed, things will only improve for Sanin?
What?
Yes. We can roll with that.
That's good.
But here's the thing.
For a reporter to put out a decent news article,
the story must sound convincing.
- With facts, it will be better. - Right.
Do you think Yoon Joo No will give us any?
You see, when people get chatty,
they're bound to make a mistake.
Mr. Yoon.
Do you need anything?
No. I'm good.
Someone will come to see me.
Could you let me know then?
- Who? - Excuse me.
(Sanin)
Were you able to rest a bit?
I just became curious...
after listening to you earlier.
So tell me. How does this so-called game go?
Could you explain it to us?
The stock price manipulation is often called the game.
Right.
But I doubt one person can run the game alone.
No.
You will need other players to help you for the game.
Among the players, there's the mastermind. The one...
who designs the entire operation and reaps the largest profit.
And...
This way.
Then there's the figurehead to keep the mastermind hidden.
Let me serve it based on age. You ordered jujube tea, right?
Safe.
- Driving. - The bankroll provides the funds...
- to manipulate the market. - I hope we can get along, sir.
I ordered the tea.
- Could you give her the tea? - Yes, sure. Here you go.
Let us be humble.
Then there's the painter who manipulates the stock charts.
I'm going to paint on the charts.
- And... - As for this guy...
Right.
My name is...
Jang Won Seok.
A long time ago, I used to work in Yeouido as a finance guy.
I'm a freelancer now.
Exchanging names, are we? What is this, a blind date?
Oh, right. Okay.
He was a technician.
But he got caught and lost his hand.
But you're back?
Yes.
I'm back with a new hand.
He ought to come back.
There's no better business than this.
Exactly.
It's not like I can work as a delivery man at my age.
My gosh.
Anyway, we're going to play this game...
solely based on trust.
You all know that, right?
That's why this is a tough job.
Right on.
No matter how hard or lonely it gets,
- let's trust our team. - Yes.
We should rely on each other.
- Let's take it all the way. - Yes.
- Okay. - Okay.
They're a group of con artists, to begin with.
- Let's drink. - So they don't trust one another.
In many instances, names aren't exchanged...
and faces remain hidden.
Given the nature of this group,
to join this family,
you must be introduced by an existing player.
My gosh. Where are you going?
By the way, he's clueless that he was duped.
That's why he's back.
The mastermind must've done a great job driving the car.
It was a hit-and-run,
- but he has no idea what happened. - Right.
- Okay. - Great.
All right.
I invited all of you to the group chat.
Let's make a fortune and never see each other again.
- That's the goal. - That's the goal.
- Bye. - I look forward to it.
Take care.
The mastermind, also known as...
the biggest player and the architect,
rarely shows up.
Yes, Doctor. The meeting is over.
Yes. I'll tell you in person.
(Yeouido Boutique, Banker, Jujube Tea, Doctor)
I'll be back soon.
Hey. So the Doctor is the mastermind?
Why are you curious about that?
Well,
the mastermind didn't show up today.
But he's in the group chat. Am I wrong?
Then just let that be.
Why should the identity of the mastermind matter to you?
Seriously.
That punk.
Listen. I have one million dollars at stake in this game.
I ought to know how this game is going to play out.
Listen up.
I'll only explain it once.
There's a company named Seono Technologies.
- What kind of company is it? - I don't know. And who cares?
I guess it has some kind of technology.
When the players get together,
they settle on a company for their game.
Usually, they choose companies worth around 100 million dollars.
Why is that?
Shouldn't they pick a big company to have a bigger profit?
And it will be easier to go unnoticed.
Because they can't freely control the price with big companies.
To be able to move ten million dollars,
companies worth around 100 million dollars are suitable.
The company is worth around 100 million dollars.
Which means we need 100 big ones.
You said you were good for ten, right?
Yes. Ten million dollars.
Then we need exactly 100.
Their stock price is between 1.2 and 1.3 dollars.
Okay.
We're going to drive the stock price below a dollar.
That's when you come in.
I see. Okay.
Don't buy them without the green light.
I'll let you know...
- when it's your turn. - Okay.
Keep the group chat notification on.
Okay.
They will gradually drive the stock price up and down...
as the players buy the stock.
Then when individual investors join them,
they purposely drive the stock price down.
To raid the retail investors, so to say?
Correct.
It refers to their attempt...
to force individual investors to sell their shares,
so they can buy them.
Once they have done the market sweep,
as the players sell and buy the shares,
they drive up the stock price.
As the players must be the only ones buying and selling,
they sell and buy...
an agreed-upon number of shares at a scheduled time.
This is called...
a matched order.
Usually, the transaction goes down during lunchtime.
Why is that?
The market activity is at its lowest...
and is the least monitored period around lunchtime.
The people at the FSS must have lunch too.
The devil is in the details.
Once we've gathered enough shares, I'm going to...
drive it up.
Up to five dollars.
That high?
I'll have to publish news articles and so on.
Tabloids will be part of it too.
I know a few YouTubers too.
I see. Yes.
I hear finance YouTube channels are quite influential now.
Great idea. Nice.
So how does the order go?
Remember the order the drinks were served?
That's the order.
I see.
Then I'm last.
Did you think you'd go first?
Once the stock price skyrockets,
the players sell the shares in the order they agreed upon...
and slowly pull out without getting noticed.
When they do, the stock price doesn't plummet right away.
Due to the influx of individual investors...
misled by the fabricated news from the players,
the stock price often goes up, which is contrary to expectations.
That's why the stock charts from the game often show two spikes,
resembling the camels' humps.
But as JUMBO was a failed game,
the chart didn't resemble the camels' humps.
I barely made any money because the last one was a flop.
So I'm trying to come up with a great game this time.
Seriously, Won Seok.
You have no idea how hard I'm working.
I got it. Thank you for your hard work.
- Okay. - So don't worry. You just wait.
Okay.
Let's not...
see each other for a while.
Sure. Okay. Bye.
Why did it fail?
Someone broke the agreement first,
sold off the shares, and pulled out.
A betrayal after a betrayal.
That's the kind of skill set...
the industry requires.
In a failed game like this,
a large number of shares would be available in the market,
so the stock price would plummet.
By the time individual investors figure it out,
it's probably too late.
When it hits the lower limit,
you can't sell the shares even if you want to.
How do you know that?
I think I've been a victim too although I have no evidence.
So...
what was your role in this game?
The architect?
The one who designed and led...
the stock price manipulation of JUMBO was Dr. Ko Byung Soo.
He held the largest number of shares as well.
Is that so?
What happened to that guy?
Did he go to prison?
As you know, it was a failed game.
Therefore, it must have been difficult...
to prove the direct involvement of the players in the game.
Let's say what you're telling us is the truth.
Then don't you want...
to catch this doctor guy?
I must.
That punk. He wants me to clean up the mess.
He's practically putting rubber gloves on my hands.
Darn him.
I think you can talk to them.
What?
My gosh.
Darn it. Where did that jerk go?
Come on.
(CW Co-working Space)
Okay.
- How may I help you? - Pardon?
If you're here as a visitor, please sign in.
Okay.
You should get your revenge.
Because of that guy,
your brother died.
You haven't caught the culprit yet?
No.
Not yet.
"Not yet?"
Mr. Yoon will be okay, right?
I'm not sure.
He wanted to handle the disciplinary hearing alone.
But why?
If we help him,
we could be reprimanded too.
He said someone would be here. Do you know who it might be?
(Daejin Delivery)
Hey, you!
Take this upstairs! You can't leave this here.
Oh, okay.
- Take it upstairs. - Will do. Thank you.
(CW Co-working Space)
Oh, thank you.
I'm in.
GOGO.
Darn it.
- Who are you? - Water delivery.
Who ordered them?
Hold on. Let me see.
Mr. Lee Seung Soo.
- Doesn't he work here? - He does. Leave them inside.
Sure.
- Hey. - Yes.
Please excuse me.
Why do you always eat alone?
I'm sick of the food.
Spicy stir-fried pork and pork cutlets. All of it.
So, which desk?
That must be it.
What's this?
Who left bottled water here?
So, you're looking for Dr. Ko?
Yes.
That's why I came back to Korea.
Didn't you come back to conceal the evidence...
that you manipulated the stock price?
I never partook in stock price manipulation of any sort,
so I have nothing to hide.
Is that so?
The way you explained it to us earlier...
showed us that you know an awful lot about it.
You don't need to participate...
in stock price manipulation to know the things I told you earlier.
Mr. Yoon.
Please just admit what you did so we can move on.
Nothing good will come out of letting this drag on.
But I can't admit...
to doing something I never did.
All right, fine.
Let's talk about everything one by one then.
First, this report.
I submitted that report prior to visiting the site.
After conducting due diligence, I informed you...
that we should not invest in JUMBO.
Right, you did say that.
(Due Diligence Report on JUMBO Pharma)
(Prepared by Yoon Joo No, M and A Team)
(JUMBO Pharma, Sales Performance and Analysis Report)
(ULTRA FOCUS Quarterly Sales Performance)
(JUMBO Pharma)
Sir.
Many retail investors are selling and exiting.
I think we can shoot it today.
(I haven't bought enough shares yet.)
I haven't bought enough shares yet.
I'll give you my 25,000 shares.
At 12:10pm, like last time.
Okay.
Director Ha is probably involved too, right?
He was acting out of character.
Yes, he was.
At 12:10pm, 20 dollars.
Go for 25,000 shares.
Okay.
(Price: 20 Dollars)
(Quantity)
(Quantity: 25,000)
(Stock Purchase Order)
(Your purchase has been successfully processed.)
You got them, right?
Then I'll hit the gas today.
Buckle up.
Yes.
Sir.
I need to talk to you.
Okay, what is it?
We shouldn't invest in JUMBO Pharma.
Why not?
It doesn't look like JUMBO Pharma...
developed ULTRA FOCUS on their own.
I think they're importing the drug from the US.
What? What are you talking about?
JUMBO's sales numbers have been going up...
since the launch of ULTRA FOCUS,
but their net profit is in the red.
What? That's...
Isn't it because the new drug is costing them a lot of money?
JUMBO Pharma...
doesn't even have a proper lab.
They don't have the capacity or equipment...
to manufacture a copycat drug.
Did you visit their factory?
Yes.
Well...
Let me look into it, then.
Wait for now.
The due diligence report I submitted was based on their documents...
Yes, I heard you.
It was strictly based on the documents they gave us.
It doesn't reflect their actual situation.
This new report will show you...
Yes, I heard you.
You guys...
You guys should go for lunch.
He seemed flustered.
His pride must be hurt too.
He'll decide against the investment, right?
Isn't that what you're hoping for?
(Restroom)
But what if he already got a rebate?
That means he's already in the same boat as them.
Then it won't be easy for him to cancel the plan to invest in them.
Well, that is true.
If he already received a kickback,
the fact that JUMBO is a scam...
will put him in a difficult position too.
Yes, exactly. If he decides to cancel the investment now,
JUMBO might say they'll reveal everything.
(Dr. Ko)
Darn it.
He should've never gotten involved, to begin with.
He won't be the only one losing money.
Exactly.
What about the people who already bought in?
Sorry, I need to make a quick call.
Sure.
(JUMBO Pharma)
Darn it.
(Joo No)
What's up?
Hey.
You sold it, right?
What?
Your JUMBO shares. Did you sell them?
Hey, I heard you. How many times must I tell you?
Hey.
Have you not sold them yet?
Well...
They're saying it'll go up again.
Who said that?
I've done my research too.
It goes down after two spikes.
Like the camels' humps.
This is not that. Sell them right away.
(Joo No)
(Sell all)
(Confirm)
- I sold them. - You're sure, right?
Did you really sell all your shares?
Yes, I sold them all!
Do you not believe me?
I just blew my entire yearly salary.
All right.
How may I help you?
I'm here to take out a loan for my company.
I was told to bring a certificate of my registered seal again.
Sir, this is only valid for three months.
That's why I got a new one.
I see. I'll go ahead and process the application, then.
- For one million dollars, right? - Yes.
When will the money be deposited?
It'll be deposited right away.
You had already started the process.
I see.
- Have a good day. - Thank you.
(JUMBO Pharma)
(20.20 Dollars)
(20.30 Dollars)
Wait, sir.
Yes?
Just a moment, sir.
Well, I just remembered...
that we're experiencing a backlog of loan applications to review.
I think...
it'll actually take about a week.
Then could my application be denied?
No, I'm sure it'll be approved. It's just that...
it'll take some time. That's all.
My gosh.
A week?
Yes, just one week.
I'm sorry.
(Authorized Personnel Only)
Please...
Let me just recover my losses.
A million dollars. Even if it's just four percent,
I can recover all my losses.
Please.
Please...
Nice.
Thank goodness.
(JUMBO Pharma, 20.45 Dollars)
Please keep going up. A little more...
Please...
(Restroom)
These jerks.
Did they think I was a total pushover?
(JUMBO Pharma, 20.45 Dollars)
(Sell all)
Darn it.
A hundred thousand shares? Shoot.
Hold on.
What is this? They're developing a new drug?
Darn, should I buy more?
Should I buy more or not?
Shoot. What should I do?
(JUMBO Pharma, Discussion Forum)
("What's Next for JUMBO, Developer of Korea's Only ADHD Drug?")
(JUMBO Pharma, 20.45 Dollars)
(Sell all)
(JUMBO Pharma, 20.50 Dollars)
(Transaction successfully completed)
(Confirm)
Darn it.
Did you sell your shares?
(Dr. Ko)
What are you talking about? It wasn't me.
You scamming jerks.
You guys can clean up the mess.
(Buy at current price, complete)
(JUMBO Pharma, 20.50 Dollars)
(JUMBO Pharma, 20.60 Dollars)
(JUMBO Pharma, 20.75 Dollars)
What is this?
Someone bought them?
Seventy-five.
Ninety.
Yes.
Someone bought them right away.
So?
Are you suspecting me?
Yes.
Mr. Yoon.
We're here to discuss how you should be reprimanded.
No, it's fine.
Let's have an open conversation and move on.
All right.
Your brother was holding 100,000 dollars worth of JUMBO stock...
because of the information he obtained from you.
That you admit, right?
Yes.
And you had ten times more.
But you're saying...
I manipulated the stock price?
Not you?
On top of that,
in the report you submitted to me,
you wrote that we should invest in JUMBO.
As I explained earlier, I submitted another report that said...
we should not invest in JUMBO.
Fine.
Let's say you actually advised me against investing in JUMBO.
But...
isn't that what you had to do to commit the perfect crime?
We didn't have to actually invest in it to make the stock go up.
It was enough to have rumors go around about our investment.
The stock would still go up.
Then you could just sell them all and exit.
In other words,
you said we shouldn't buy JUMBO...
to create an alibi for yourself.
What do you say now? Am I wrong?
I guess I could've done that.
But...
that's not what happened.
What?
Hold on. What do you mean?
My brother couldn't sell his shares and exit.
That's why...
the evidence still remains.
I see.
He didn't sell his shares.
You didn't profit from them, so you did nothing wrong?
Hey, Mr. Yoon.
Do you really not know? Or are you just acting dumb?
Just the fact that you had those shares...
makes you a criminal.
That's not what he's saying.
Okay, go ahead and explain. What does he mean?
What's he talking about?
He's talking about his brother.
His brother couldn't sell his shares...
and died.
That too!
He keeps putting the blame on his late brother to weasel out of it.
How could you pin everything on your late brother?
Have you no sense of decency?
Director Ha!
Fine.
All right, then.
Then explain this.
Why did you invest in JUMBO shares?
Fifty thousand shares, at that.
They...
aren't mine.
What?
Come on, Mr. Yoon.
You shouldn't lie to us.
This letter states that you own 50,000 shares...
and that you should attend their general meeting of shareholders.
We can't talk if you're going to deny this.
You should admit this, at least.
I'm trying to help you here.
The ones at eye level are part of our Gold Line Package.
They're the best ones.
Each niche costs 7,000 dollars.
The ones right above the Gold Line cost 6,000 dollars,
but most people go for the Gold Line.
Otherwise, you'd either have to look up...
or down as they aren't at eye level.
The ones on top are also quite popular.
I'll go with that one.
Are you a Buddhist by any chance?
If so, there's an event we're organizing.
I'm not interested.
Well, you know...
In Buddhism, taking one's own life...
is seen as a harmful action that also hurts...
the people around you.
- So... - I'm not a Buddhist.
Oh, I see.
I heard his brother took his own life in his stead.
What is this nonsense now?
High-ranking executives from Sanin were here.
That's what they said.
What exactly did they say?
That he and Joo No invested in some stock together.
- Goodness. - I see. That must be the reason.
What is it?
Earlier, one worker felt bad about the brother...
and wanted to give him her prayers. But Joo No rejected her,
saying he's not a Buddhist.
How can he do that? Oh Woon is an orphan now.
Well...
- Gosh. - Good grief.
Who will take care of her? She doesn't even have a mom.
Isn't your child around the same age as her?
Raising them together will be easy.
Nonsense.
Raising a stranger's child is not easy at all.
You shouldn't say such things even if we're at a funeral.
- Oh, right. You have it tough. - Hey.
I'm fine.
Oh Woon.
Why don't we...
live together?
Call me...
Dad from now on.
Okay?
Mr. Yoon.
Yes?
I looked into what you asked.
- The inheritance? - Yes.
Before your brother passed away,
he pocketed one million dollars.
He didn't have many assets.
If you inherit,
it'll also include the liability for compensation.
You'll end up with far more debt.
So...
Is Oh Woon the inheritor?
Yes.
The first in order is your niece.
But she's a minor.
You, the second in order, must inherit on her behalf.
Both you and Oh Woon should give up the inheritance.
No.
I will inherit it.
You will...
have to pay the debt in his stead.
I know.
I inherited both...
a one million dollar liability to the bank...
and 50,000 shares of JUMBO Pharma.
In other words,
the 50,000 shares printed...
on the shareholders'meeting invitation you're holding...
are not mine...
but what I inherited from my brother.
Is it true?
Did you inherit his debt?
Of one million dollars?
- Do you have proof? - How is that important right now?
Even from what we've heard so far,
you can be charged with insider trading,
nominee trading,
direct stock price manipulation, and...
Right?
Those can lead to corporate image damage...
and charges of breach of duty.
That's why you're fired. Got it?
I request a chance to explain myself.
Save it. Write your resignation letter and get lost.
Is that an official order?
No, it's not.
(Sanin)
Could I be granted some time to think?
How much do you need?
About two hours.
Is that enough?
Yes.
Okay. Get some fresh air for two hours.
It's already time for lunch.
Let's all have lunch.
We'll take a break.
Great.
Gosh.
Could he really have inherited his brother's debt?
Director Lee.
Did he?
Who knows?
How could you...
give Yoon Joo No time because he asked?
Director Cho. Are you starving or something?
No.
Let me explain, Director Ha.
Disciplining him without hearing his side of the story...
might cause issues later.
What issues?
The disciplinaryproceedings...
clearly state that one gets the chance to show cause.
Ignore that and discipline him,
and he might take legal action...
for not following the proceedings.
Could that result in the nullification of the discipline?
Someone like Yoon Joo No can make that happen.
I get it now.
Two hours can get him nothing.
If you ask me,
not sticking to the proceedings is all Yoon Joo No has...
against us.
I see.
So this punk is playing his last card?
Yes.
I didn't do Mr. Yoon any favors.
It was me making sure he had no way out of this, Director Ha.
All right. What's left now?
You can discipline him once he returns in two hours.
Okay.
That jerk.
He earned money just to buy that?
Goodness.
My legs are killing me.
(Daejin Delivery)
(Ko Byung Soo)
Darn it.
Whatever.
I'll end up behind bars now.
Mr. Yoon.
How did it go? Did they decide on disciplinary action?
Not yet.
By any chance, did anyone come by for me?
No, no one.
Yes?
Hey. I found Dr. Ko's laptop.
I did, but it's password-locked.
Did you unlock it?
No, I couldn't.
Didn't you find it?
I found his laptop.
I don't know the password to unlock it.
I'll bring the laptop to you.
Okay. Make your way here.
Okay.
Do you know how to crack a password?
Of a laptop.
No.
Do we have to hack into it?
Can you do it?
Me?
Won't CEO Cha Ho Jin be able to do it?
CHACHA Games?
What?
Nice pass.
You can't.
- No! - No!
Shoot.
What's up?
Why isn't CEO Cha answering his phone?
He's busy at the moment,
pivoting.
I have an urgent favor to ask.
Right now?
Okay. We're on our way.
CEO Cha.
No more basketball.
We need to head to Sanin right now.
To where?
Sanin?
- He's my senior. - I see.
- Hi. - Hi.
Here.
- Did you get caught? - No.
But I soon will. His laptop is missing, after all.
But how will you unlock it?
I don't know.
I need to head back.
Okay. We'll call you as soon as it's unlocked.
Thank you.
- Let's go. - Okay.
- Excuse me. - Sure.
I'm done with my job.
You are. Great work.
I'll get in touch.
Don't. Take care of yourself.
We will now resume the meeting.
It was short,
but could we take it that it was enough time for you...
to prepare an explanation?
Yes.
Go ahead.
My brother realized Sanin had plans to invest in JUMBO through me.
He bought 100,000 dollars worth of JUMBO shares and then sold them.
In the process, he had lost a great deal of money.
To make up for it,
he must've unlawfully used one million dollars of bank money...
to purchase 50,000 shares again.
So what?
You had nothing to do with those 50,000 shares?
You had no idea?
It wasn't until the inheritance...
that I learned my brother owned that many shares.
We've heard that already.
- If there's nothing new... - However,
with that amount,
I suspect it belonged to a manipulative force.
Timing-wise, when my brother bought one million dollars...
worth of JUMBO shares, only wash trades...
In other words,
only the forces were trading the shares.
What do you mean by that?
Are you implying that your brother was a member?
No.
I'm saying one of the forces...
betrayed by selling 50,000 shares,
and...
my brother happened to buy them.
Come on.
Isn't that too big of a coincidence?
Yes. You may think so.
- That's why... - That's why...
you continue to suspect me.
Director Lee. Remember?
I advised you not to buy JUMBO shares.
I do.
Who took my shares?
(JUMBO Pharma)
That jerk.
(Junior Managing Director's Office)
Director Lee. We need to publish an article right now.
What's wrong?
Sanin might...
get caught up in share price manipulation.
We must issue an article that Sanin has nothing to do with it...
and won't investigate.
I don't understand.
Just get on with the article at once.
The one...
who stopped that was me.
You remember, yes?
I do.
Good. Thanks to me,
Sanin avoided suffering damage.
Had I been involved,
would I have told you we shouldn't buy the shares?
Like you suspected me,
couldn't you have done so to create an alibi?
What?
So? Do you have evidence or something?
We have more than enough evidence against you.
I'm asking if there's any against me.
Hi.
- Hi. - Hi.
What password were you talking about?
It's this laptop.
This laptop belongs to a man...
suspected of manipulating stock prices.
The documents on here can clear up the misunderstanding about Mr. Yoon.
You're an expert in this area, right, CEO Cha?
And you have experience in hacking.
Instead of hacking, I got hacked into.
Right. You were the victim.
And...
It's only in movies that you can easily hack into laptops.
I can't do it. Plus, it'll take too long.
You must do it, CEO Cha.
- Is it an urgent matter? - Yes.
Let's see.
- Do you have a screwdriver? - A screwdriver...
- Yes, I do. It should be here. - Great.
I do have evidence.
As I explained, forces don't trust each other.
As a result, they keep a record...
of the amount of money traded, the date,
and the transaction details.
They even save not only calls...
but also every text message.
So the forces leave a record of their crimes?
Correct.
After all, they can't go down alone.
True.
It's the same as the old days when people...
bribed politicians with slush funds and kept a ledger.
Yes.
That's why they keep a record of everything.
And?
Where's that evidence?
This is what Do Han Chul did to me.
You know, DC.
We know.
Can you hand me that laptop?
Sure.
Here.
Okay.
(Golf Club Data, External Vendor Orders)
To think...
it works like this.
- What were you looking for? - Ha Tae Soo.
(Ha Tae Soo)
Did my name pop up in their files?
My apologies. I have something to hand over.
(Sanin)
What is that?
It's a record of Director Ha's...
JUMBO share purchases using insider information.
From April 26 to April 29, 2021,
Director Ha bought 25,000 shares in the 4-day period.
On May 3 at 12:10pm,
he bought an additional 25,000 shares,
which totaled up to 50,000 shares.
It was worth about one million dollars at that time.
And 27 minutes later, at 12:37pm,
he sold everything.
No, listen.
He made that up.
I swear I'm innocent.
Seriously.
Being wrongly accused is making me tear up.
And here are...
the transaction details of my brother, Yoon Joo Seok.
On April 29, 2021, at 9:10am.
He bought shares worth 100,000 dollars...
and then sold everything four days later.
But...
he bought 50,000 shares again 30 minutes later.
Worth one million dollars at that point.
It was...
one minute later after Director Ha sold...
the whole 50,000 shares.
In short,
my brother Yoon Joo Seok...
bought the shares Director Ha sold.
That night, Sanin issued an article...
stating it would not invest in JUMBO.
And the next day, the stock price crashed...
as soon as the market opened.
The stock price kept falling to the floor.
My brother...
couldn't sell his shares until the very end.
So what?
Are you blaming me...
for your brother's death?
That's not what I think.
Darn it.
Because of me...
Because of me, Joo Seok...
No.
Don't say that.
It's my fault.
I simply...
wanted to know the truth.
And now I know what they are.
The record indicates...
Director Ha took part in the stock price manipulation.
After hearing my report on JUMBO,
he sold all the shares to run away...
behind the forces' backs.
But those shares...
ended up with my brother.
I sold them off after a short while.
I didn't make any money off of it!
You must've made a profit,
though not as much as you'd planned.
But even if you hadn't earned any money,
the fact that you were in possession of JUMBO's shares proves your guilt.
That is what you, yourself, told me today.
Bring that here.
You should come here instead.
It is where the subject of the disciplinary hearing...
sits.
You punk, get over here!
- Director. - Yoon Joo No!
- Director. - Move!
- You can't do this. - You punk!
I'm a founding member of Sanin, you fool!
- Director. - Move.
I won't take this from kids like you.
When I first started out at Sanin,
you were still in your diapers!
You. Get off me. Stop holding me back.
Yoon Joo No!
Step aside. Move.
Then,
it was Director Ha all along.
Mr. Yoon...
did leak inside information to his brother,
but it wasn't intentional.
And...
his brother died.
It'd be heartless...
to find fault with him.
Then,
what should be done...
about Director Ha?
You can't park your car there. Goodness, sir.
- I won't be long. - Sure thing.
(Sanin)
Director Ha did a lot of work around here.
He was even in charge of Constructions.
Generating all that funding was no small feat.
How old is he again?
He won't be turning 60 any time soon.
I guess he put in too many hours...
for someone of his relatively young age.
The man must be worn out.
Tell him to take a break.
At the disciplinary hearing for Yoon Joo No,
Director Ha was dismissed from his position.
Really? Director Ha was terminated?
Yes. He packed up all of his things at night.
He wasn't even offered severance pay.
Second-in-command was cut overnight.
Won't Director Ha sue the company...
for wrongful termination?
As if that's an option for executives.
He probably was let go for a reason.
By the way,
you've got to hand it to Yoon Joo No.
Maybe he really is the chairman's son.
I told you he wasn't.
Do you see a resemblance?
The chairman's son is in the US.
Hold on. Mr. Yoon...
flew in from Hawaii.
That's in the US.
Wait. Is that how it is?
(The Late Yoon Joo Seok)
I'll take ten dollars' worth.
- With random numbers? - Yes.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
- Have a good day. - You too.
In my dream last night,
stars turned into numbers and rained down upon me.
Sweet, right?
What if this becomes a winning ticket?
When will you stop this wishful thinking?
When I win the lottery.
I will someday.
What will you do with the money?
Buy a house.
An apartment unit?
No.
I'm going to buy a house with a huge yard.
Like the ones in movies.
With basement levels.
I have it all mapped out.
You, me, Oh Woon, and your wife will live together.
I'd rather not.
Is that so? Then give it back.
You don't want to, so give it back.
After that sweet dream you had?
You weren't sold on my vision though.
Hey.
I thought you'd express your gratitude...
with a beef steak.
- I'll have the beef sandwich. - Sure.
There's your beef.
- Are you sure that's beef? - It is.
Hey.
Why did you put your trust in me?
I didn't.
Yet, you gave me a task that important?
It seemed as though...
you felt wronged.
A robber can't whine...
after tripping during a robbery.
Why didn't you file for bankruptcy?
I thought that was your expertise.
You've been trying...
to pay off your debt.
Says who?
You've been working as a delivery man to do so.
How far have you gotten?
Not far...
which is all the more reason to work harder.
What about you?
How much of your brother's debt were you able to pay off?
Me?
Well, I make good money.
You annoying brat.
What's this?
Why do we need bottled water?
We have a water dispenser. Did you put in the order?
I thought you did.
Hold on.
- Who... - Are you Lee Seung Soo?
Yes?
We're from Gangnam Police Station.
I see.
Lee Seung Soo is with the chairman...
- Hold on. - You're coming with us.
- Wait. - Don't.
- I'll... Hey! - Hold on.
What is the meaning of this?
(Korea Securities Depository)
(Shareholder meeting notice)
Who sent this?
I have no idea.
Jin Soo, good morning.
Good morning, Mr. Oh.
Gosh, Ms. Kwak.
- This is unexpected. - Morning, Jin Soo.
Doors closing.
Good morning.
Mr. Yoon, did you stay here all night?
No, I just got in early.
You should've gotten some rest.
I will once my work is done.
Can we gather to talk?
Sure.
This is next year's business plan requested by Samoel.
It includes how Sanin will pay the remaining debt...
and the direction of business...
the group will be taking in the foreseeable future.
I know Samoel is the creditor,
but can they request such things?
When they lent Sanin three billion dollars? Yes.
The interest rate is nine percent.
That's right. Once we renegotiate the terms,
the conversion price will go down 30 percent.
Then that'll make someone else the largest shareholder of Sanin.
Right.
Then today's briefing needs to go well.
Hey, I'm glad you're here.
Get over here and lend me a hand.
But I'm on the M and A Team.
Why you...
Hey! Where are you going?
Lend me a hand.
Get in here.
Jin Soo, watch me.
Take one...
and place it like so.
Goodness.
Hey, you know...
how you said Yoon Joo No was...
I mean, Mr. Yoon.
Who told you Mr. Yoon was the chairman's son?
I don't know.
I think I stumbled upon it.
Why do you ask?
Didn't you say he was the son-in-law?
Did I?
Word has been traveling among the employees.
As you know, Yoon Joo No had Director Ha dismissed.
A team manager had the CFO removed.
The company's second-in-command.
That wasn't exactly Mr. Yoon's doing.
Director Ha's corruption scandal caught up with him.
Still. What happened is unusual and unprecedented.
So?
So, Yoon Joo No...
I mean, Mr. Yoon. That's why people are wondering...
if he's the chairman's son.
Hold on.
Did you just scoff at me?
But that's absurd.
They have different surnames.
He could've been born out of wedlock.
That's not true.
Really?
Hey. What about this, then?
Yoon Joo No... I mean, Mr. Yoon.
The White Snake.
I hear his nickname is actually the White Thread.
Because of his gray hair.
- Is that true? - Sure. If you say so.
Why do I get the feeling that you're looking down on me?
Did you sense that?
Get over here.
Do you think being on Yoon's team gives you some sort of authority?
Hello, everyone.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
Jin Soo, shall we put up the slides?
Sure.
- The chairman will be here too. - Sure.
Are you saying I need to be present at this meeting?
They wanted to greet you since it's been a while.
Who are they sending?
Mr. David, sir.
Let's go.
Who will deliver the presentation?
Mr. Yoon Joo No, sir.
When will the chairman be here?
I'd like for him to be here before those from Samoel arrive.
Who do they think they are...
to demand the chairman's presence?
You know how these funds think they have all the power.
They wanted to know our business plan moving forward,
and the loan we took out will soon reach maturity.
We'll be in trouble if they don't grant an extension.
Of course.
Won't they be taking over the company?
Are you ready for today?
Yes.
The chairman is here.
Sit.
I heard they wanted to see me in person.
Greeting you is one of the reasons they're attending this meeting.
It'd be lovely to exchange some kind words.
Those from Samoel Fund are here.
Goodness. What a pleasure, Chairman Song.
Mr. David, it's you I owe this pleasure to.
- Please have a seat. - Sure.
Shall we begin?
Sure.
Just a moment.
My director hasn't arrived yet.
We should wait.
I was wondering why you came alone today.
Sorry? Goodness.
Actually, the company hired a new executive.
I see.
We came here today so that he could greet you.
He'll be here soon.
- There he is. - Goodness.
Chairman Song, hello.
Hurry into your seat.
Allow me to greet you.
Right.
Director Ha.
Yes?
Is this your new gig?
Yes, I'm a director at Samoel Fund.
It's a small world, isn't it?
This wasn't one of my cases,
but Mr. David put me in charge.
No one knows Sanin better than I do,
and I have a soft spot for the company.
It's been a while.
Yes, sir.
Allow me to present the business plan...
for the upcoming year.
Unbelievable.
As if a team manager would know anything.
Who are you to dare talk about the future of a company?
And in front of the chairman, no less.
You should know...
that Chairman Song is a man of great insight.
I learned a lot while working under him.
Go on, Chairman Song. Show us how it's done.
Are you suggesting I present it?
What's wrong? Don't you want to?
Fine. Whatever.
Then, go ahead.
(2025 Sanin Business Plan Report)
Allow me to present Sanin's business plan...
for the upcoming year.
(The Art of Negotiation)
(Thank you for watching The Art of Negotiation.)
Dr. Park, you might want to consider...
blue onesies.
Is it a boy?
The dad must also be thrilled.
Well...
Sure.
I appreciate the beef steak.
Don't mention it.
Then, is my work done?
No.
That meal wasn't for free.