Tingting.
Actually,
I was the one who kissed you
that day.
=Who Stole My Kiss=
=Episode 4=
I...
Tingting,
are you sleepy?
I can finally take it off.
It's stuffy.
Do you normally come out
wearing like this?
I need to be careful today.
If someone sees us,
we can't date properly.
Mochi.
He's not!
It's okay.
Why are you here?
Helen, why are you here?
I'm just walking around.
I was watching a movie with my friend.
Let me introduce.
This is the planner of
Zhuoyuan Gaming Company,
Han Tingting.
This is my manager,
Helen.
She's your manager.
Hello.
You're such a pretty planner.
Mochi, since when
have you started dating?
Why didn't you tell me?
We're not dating.
Qin Mochi?
It's him.
I'm the reporter from Reap What You Sow.
You're not famous lately.
Have you thought about
changing your field?
Girls.
- Is she your girlfriend?
- Stop taking photos.
Is she your girlfriend?
Are you so focusing on dating
that you've neglected your career?
- Stop taking photos.
- You've misunderstood.
She's Mochi's assistant.
She's not his girlfriend.
An assistant won't dress up like her.
This gossip is shocked.
Let me take a photo.
Stop taking photos.
We'll report the truth as it is.
Trust us.
We just need one photo.
Just one photo.
Stop taking photos.
Exclusive interview.
Why not I let you do
an exclusive interview with Bingbing
next month?
Really? Don't lie to us.
Why should I lie to you?
Leave now.
No, you're alone here.
It's fine.
Listen to me. Go now.
No.
Hurry. I'll call you.
Hurry. Okay.
Mochi.
(Tingting.)
(It's Helen.)
(Were you frightened just now?)
I'm okay.
Are you okay?
(We're okay.)
Well, is your company aware that
you two are dating?
No worries.
I don't disclose it.
Only my two best friends know.
That's great.
After all, he's the candidate
for your ambassador.
If they found out about
your relationship,
they might hold prejudice against him.
It won't happen.
No worries.
The staff in my company
like Mochi very much.
We all think that
his image and personality
suit our game very well.
Really?
So, you'll support him?
Of course!
I've liked him
since his debut.
As his manager,
I've been worried about him every day.
Okay.
Go back and rest.
(Record)
(When will the game proposal
be amended?)
(Qin Mochi)
(I still owe you supper.)
(Are you free tonight?)
(Are we dating again tonight?)
(Han Tingting)
(Yes!)
(Wechat
You've got a Weixin message.)
(How do you plan to
celebrate your birthday this year?)
(Qin Mochi)
(I still owe you supper.)
(Touch up your make-up.)
(Use the colour that will seduce a man.)
(You and He Rang...)
(No worries.)
(I'll make sure He Rang)
(won't disturb you.)
Ting,
happy birthday.
That's so nice of you.
Thank you.
Mr. Lu is here.
(So, master knows
it's my birthday today)
(and he's here to give me a present?)
Tingting,
I've sent you the proposal feedback.
Amend and send it to me tonight.
Tingting, thank you.
Master.
You're revengeful.
Although I tore your shirt
in the restaurant
and it's my fault,
you don't have to
make me work overtime alone
on my birthday.
(Qin Mochi)
Qin Mochi?
Hello.
You're here to pick me up?
Are you two close?
No.
We're friends.
Keep the boundary with the celebrities.
Don't put your guard down just because
he treats you well.
Tingting.
Mr. Lu, you're here.
Hello.
I'm here to pick up Tingting.
♪Does he like you?♪
♪Don't rush to interrupt♪
♪You're being silent♪
♪I lost the courage to talk♪
♪That day was a suitable timing♪
♪I wanted to tell you♪
♪Because you're gentle♪
♪Like printed in my heart♪
♪Wanted to♪
♪Embrace your breath♪
♪Only you can♪
♪Solve the cute riddle♪
♪I like your♪
♪Silly face♪
♪So happiness is always mentioned♪
♪It's in the bottom of my heart♪
♪There are wind, rain and you♪
♪Every day♪
♪You've slowly become♪
♪The best weather in my eyes♪
♪Holding me in your arms♪
♪I like♪
♪Being with you♪