I'm counting on you for
becoming the game ambassador.
The game ambassador?
Yes.
Have you forgotten?
From now on,
your business is my business.
You're my brother.
You're my sister from now on.
Can you help me become
the game ambassador?
What are you talking about?
I'll design the male protagonist
based on your image.
Bottoms up!
I'll finish the drink!
So, you approached me
for the endorsement?
Of course not.
I really want to be your friend,
Tingting.
But, shouldn't friends
be helping each other?
I'm sorry to make you misunderstand.
I don't have the authority
to decide that.
Tingting,
that's what you promised me.
So, it's just
a deal to you,
isn't it?
This is not a deal.
Time is precious.
No one will treat you well
for no reason.
Isn't this
the way of engagement
of the adults?
Let me put it this way.
I'm willing to spend time and effort
to sustain our relationship
because you can give me the chance
to endorse the game.
If I become the game ambassador,
I'll make the game
more popular.
It's a win-win situation to us.
It's a win-win situation,
do you understand?
A win-win situation.
Yes.
I think there's misunderstanding
between us.
I don't have the authority
to decide about the endorsement.
I shouldn't be biased either.
You've got the wrong person.
=Who Stole My Kiss=
=Episode 6=
That's why I said
a handsome guy who came to you
is either a playboy or a scammer.
I just want to find the person
who kissed me.
Why is it so hard?
When one is in love,
it's easy to be tricked.
That's why I advise you
to just listen to music, pursue
a celebrity and watch a series
when you're lonely.
Stop looking for a handsome guy.
What do you mean?
Are you cursing me to be single forever?
Isn't that great?
That room is yours forever.
You can stay there alone
when you're old.
You're...
The rental...
Going to be alone when you're old.
He Rang, what are you talking about?
(Zhuoyuan Gaming Company)
Ting,
I believe you're not like that.
What are you talking about?
Didn't you look at Weibo?
Take a look.
See?
What's going on?
You can't enter! This is our office!
Get out!
You can't enter!
I'm an entertainment reporter.
Can I interview Han Tingting?
You've been working here.
Did you see Qin Mochi
pick up or drop off Han Tingting here?
She is there!
Han Tingting is there!
You can't enter!
Hello, can you tell us about
your relationship with Qin Mochi?
Don't listen to the rumour.
He and I are not dating.
Many netizens think that
you're using your authority at work
to help Qin Mochi.
Is that true?
Stop recording. Stop taking photos.
Stop taking photos.
Han Tingting is embarrassed and upset.
She's using violence
to stop the interview, isn't she?
I...
I didn't do it on purpose,
but please stop taking photos
and stop recording.
Are you agitated
because what I said was correct?
Please answer the question.
- Please answer the question.
- Was I right?
Please answer the question.
We just want to interview you.
Ting.
Were you frightened?
I'm okay.
Why are you injured?
I think they scratched me just now.
I'll be fine in a few days.
I'm sorry
to have troubled you.
I'm a man.
The scar is my badge.
Tingting.
Mr. Lu wants you to
meet him in the office.
(Apology press conference)
First of all,
I'd like to apologise to all my fans.
What happened
has made you worried.
(We got to know each other)
(during a meal half a month ago.)
(I thought)
she was a pure and innocent girl,
but I didn't expect that
she kept asking to meet me
with the condition
of making me the game ambassador.
I rejected her the first few times
(because I didn't like that.)
(We went to the cinema)
(because I wanted to
tell her in person,)
(but I didn't know it'd be recorded.)
(It won't happen.)
(His image and personality)
(suit our game very well.)
(Really?)
(So, you'll support him?)
(Of course!)
(I've liked him)
(since his debut.)
This matter
has badly influenced the company image.
The credit reload rate for the new game
has dropped by 80%.
Lu Bai,
you're her team leader.
What do you have to say?
Mr. Chen.
The netizens were
emotionally manipulated.
The rumour spread fast
in a short period of time.
It shows that the matter
was sensationalised maliciously.
I suggest
we should collect evidence and
investigate the matter first.
Well,
this is Han Tingting's personal issue.
It has nothing to do with the company.
We just have to fire Han Tingting
to make our stand
to protect the company image.
Master.
Master, do you trust me?
Master,
I didn't do anything.
(Suspension agreement)
♪Does he like you?♪
♪Don't rush to interrupt♪
♪You're being silent♪
♪I lost the courage to talk♪
♪That day was a suitable timing♪
♪I wanted to tell you♪
♪Because you're gentle♪
♪Like printed in my heart♪
♪Wanted to♪
♪Embrace your breath♪
♪Only you can♪
♪Solve the cute riddle♪
♪I like your♪
♪Silly face♪
♪So happiness is always mentioned♪
♪It's in the bottom of my heart♪
♪There are wind, rain and you♪
♪Every day♪
♪You've slowly become♪
♪The best weather in my eyes♪
♪Holding me in your arms♪
♪I like♪
♪Being with you♪