The volume
You are a descendant of the Kun family
You must remember
-Quick -The Kun army never admits defeat
Bless me
Father
Your Excellency State Preceptor
The Kun family has been completely besieged and eliminated
Are they all dead?
What about Kun Ze's son and daughter?
There is still a young boy
He jumped into the river during the pursuit
Rest assured
He certainly couldn’t have survived
State Preceptor
There is also a little girl here
This
Isn’t this Su Ying’s daughter?
The little saintess of the Su family?
Heaven really helps me
I survived a great disaster
Washed ashore by the river
From then on, I concealed my identity
And was reduced to slavery
On the day I left Zhongli
I learned that the envoy from Shangshan
Proclaimed to the world
That my father intended to rebel
And killed my mother in the Zhongli palace
Also said he went mad
Killed the entire Kun family
Such crimes brought divine punishment
Turning everyone in the Kun family into monsters
The Kun clan thus fell into decline
From then on
The Kun army
Became the shame of Zhongli
With the death of the saintess
The You Su clan
Seemed to have vanished as well
You just said
The You Su clan
Possess illusory powers
The saintess lineage
Is bestowed with heavenly illusory forms
What does that mean?
The You Su clan
Has had since ancient times
The custom of practicing illusion arts
Only
Nowadays, the Su people
only know some juggling tricks
Only the Saintess lineage
inherits the orthodox tradition
It is said that after the bloodline awakens
they excel greatly in illusion arts
able to bewitch people's minds
and create illusions
Su Qingqing possesses this ability
so why all these years
has she not tried to escape
She has long been controlled by Xian Xuanji with drugs
unable to use her illusion arts
Therefore
the only one in this world who can save her
is me
It seems
you have no choice but to take this risk
Right
Have you ever thought
if we fail
even if it means death
I must go
You are not afraid of death
but is Marquis Nanbo afraid
Is Zhen E afraid or not?
If your identity is exposed
How will the Marquis of Nanbo's estate handle itself?
The Marquis of Nanbo's estate is using you
You may not care about their life or death
What about the Shizi Camp?
Have you ever considered
That your actions
Might implicate the Shizi Camp?
Your Majesty
The secret envoy from Gui Fang
Has sent us a secret letter
Is the heir of the Marquis of Nanbo
Truly, as the secret letter says
Connected to the Kun Family Army from back then?
Zhongli and Nan Du are thousands of miles apart
We have never heard of any connection between the Kun Family and the Marquis of Nanbo
What kind of association could there be?
The information provided by this person
Cannot be wrong
What we need to determine now is
This heir of the Marquis of Nanbo
After all, it's the old troops of the Kun family.
Or the son of Kun Ze
One
Lord E Shun
Has he ever been to Zhongli?
Never.
This matter is suspicious.
We must be cautious.
Go.
Summon someone here.
It seems our plan needs to change.
Yes.
Someone who should have died seven years ago.
This time,
We must
Eliminate the root of the problem.
All of this
I have thought about.
I have let all of you down.
Once,
I had lost
All hope.
Living
For me,
Was a luxury.
Until one day,
I met you at the slave market.
That day, you saved me.
He also said that in the future
he would surely train me to become
the fiercest warrior in Donglu
so I would no longer have to kneel in servitude
At that moment
I finally realized
that I myself
had already knelt for far too long
and had long forgotten
how to be
a dignified member of the Kun family
- So - So you deceived us
It wasn’t like that
I
I gave you a chance
didn’t I
But you still
chose to go alone
to Zhongli Palace
But Qingqing is my last family
I promised my father
I would protect her
The one who made that promise to Father
was Kunwu
But who are you now
It is E Shun from the Prince's Camp.
He is the little slave
I picked up from the streets
Who exactly are you
You're right
Who am I
One
E Shun
True feelings
Or false pretenses
I can no longer tell myself
Brother Jiang
They have already apologized
Besides
For such a long time
He hasn't done anything
That would betray the Prince's Camp
It must have been forced by circumstances
If he had done
Anything to betray the Prince's Camp
Would I have let him live until now
From now on
What should we call you
E Shun
Or Kun
You can call me Kun Wu
E Shun
From now on
My Crown Prince's Camp
Only the heir of the
Marquis of Nanbo, E Shun
There has never been
None have Kunwu
Camp of the Heir
Apparent, heed the command
The sovereign's decree
Open the door quickly
What kind of order is being delivered in the middle of the night
Could it be that they
Found out E Shun's true
identity, haven't you?
If that is truly the case
Then it has nothing to do with the rest of you
You were deceived by me
I definitely will not drag you down with me
What dragging down or not dragging down
Let me tell you
We can deal with them together
Matters between brothers
Can be discussed later
Wait a moment
If they really knew
E Shun's identity
They would have barged in long ago
The Crown Prince's camp awaits orders.
By the decree of the King
Open the gate quickly
What are you doing in the middle of the night?
What brings you here so late at night?
What is the matter?
Young master, you're awake so late at night
What are you doing in this courtyard with weapons?
My brother simply enjoys practicing martial arts late at night
Is that not allowed?
Just like how your Kingdom of Zhongli
enjoys delivering decrees in the middle of the night
What of it?
Is there a problem?
Well, no
You must be joking, young master
What arrangements has the Grand Preceptor made this time?
The King sent me to inform everyone
The Sacred Wedding Ceremony
will be held tomorrow ahead of schedule
I am here under orders to deliver the invitation
Moved forward
Intruders broke into the palace tonight
The King was alarmed
The condition has worsened
To prevent any complications
We hope all the young masters
will be present tomorrow without fail
Withdraw
Your Majesty
The invitation has been delivered
Any findings?
On the Southern Bo Marquis's heir
There was indeed a scent of blood
I boldly speculate
that the one who stormed the palace tonight
must be him
It seems
this remnant of the Kun family
has grown ambitious
Unexpectedly, he has transformed
into the esteemed Southern Bo Marquis's heir
Good
No matter who you disguise yourself as
I
will tear off that mask of yours
At tomorrow's sacred wedding ceremony
Arrange ambushes and archers
all around
Your Majesty intends to
Like catching a turtle in a jar
The current evidence is insufficient
It's not advisable to act rashly and alert the enemy
Wait until the Sacred Wedding ceremony tomorrow
If that Lord E Shun does not come
The Sacred Wedding will proceed as scheduled
We’ll first eliminate that troublesome Saintess
But if that Lord E Shun dares to come and rescue her
I can expose him on the spot
As the last remnant of the Kun family
And execute him right then and there
Wipe out the Kun family
Completely exterminated
Yes
Who
How
Planning to stand there like a door god?
This cup
To you, for time and again
Saving me from dire straits
This cup
To you, for your sincerity
Treating me like a brother
This cup
To you, for believing in me
And understanding me
Protect me
I was a slave for seven years
Treating me as a dignified person
You are the first
Between you and me
I owe you a great deal
I have sent a carrier pigeon to Donglu
Explaining my background
All my actions
Stem from personal vengeance
Unrelated to the Shizi Camp
I will definitely not implicate you all
If I can return safely tomorrow
What I owe you
I will slowly repay
If I do not return
A few cups of plain wine
To express my apology
This stupid pigeon
I plucked its feathers and fed it to the cats
Wanting to send a message to Donglu
Without even asking me, the heir of Donglu
Whether I agree or not
You know
You can't stop me
Then try stepping out of this room.
Sorry.
No matter what.
I cannot let you take the risk.
It's useless.
Brother Jiang's skill in tying people up.
is quite practiced.
What time is it?
Don't worry about the time.
Just stay put.
Brother Jiang said.
As long as you can stay put for a day.
Both the heir's camp and you.
can be kept safe.
Let me go.
Don't waste your energy.
Brother when.
Young Master Chong.
Second Young Master Chong.
My life or death.
you certainly wouldn't care about.
Letting me go.
won't do you any harm.
Brother Chong.
If his identity is exposed.
it would mean annihilation for the clan in the Southern Capital.
Help him
Is to help your brother
I don't care if you live or die
But if you die
That person won't survive either
Where is Jiang WenHuan
Jiang WenHuan
The medicine in the bottle
Is the antidote I extracted yesterday
From your medicinal dregs
This medicine is brewed
Send it to the Holy Maiden
But time is limited
The antidote made by my sister Yi Yao
Can only sustain you
For half the time it takes an incense stick to burn during spellcasting
After half an incense stick, your energy will be exhausted
Last night I already scouted the altar
From the alley entrance to the altar
Is a total of fifty steps
I will be among the crowd
Creating chaos
To divert the priest's attention
Retreat to the end of the alley
As long as you can use illusion techniques
To make everyone lose their senses
For the time it takes half an incense stick to burn
Someone will naturally come to take you away
Brother Xin Jia
You must release me
Before Brother Jiang left
He repeatedly urged and said
-Just cannot -Jiang Wenhuan wants to rescue them himself
I'll untie you first
Wait a moment
Brother Chong is right at the door
Later, act according to my signal
It begins
Her time of death has come
No matter how you scheme
Anything you do now is futile
Fate
Cannot be changed
Go back
Brother Chong, don’t be impulsive
Your matter
Will naturally be handled by Jiang Wenhuan’s planning
Go back
Don't think I don't dare to kill you
Precisely because of this
I cannot let him take the risk for me
Can't be bothered to waste words on you
We are all brothers here
Brother Chong
Brother E Shun
How about
You go back first
Run quickly
I will be there soon
Let go
You let go
Xin Jia, you
Let go
Only the great God
bestow favor upon the common people, sincerely I pray
Admiring the sage virtue of heaven
The saintly maiden is without blemish, worthy to match that heaven
Jiang Wen Huan
Offers sacrifice to her sacred bones
Why have you come
Reverently accepting heaven's decree
Why did you take the risk to save people for me
For them to go is to seek death innocently
I am the leader
of the heir's camp
I promised to protect you all
and return unscathed
A promise must be kept
Heaven bestows grace upon the people below
Your Majesty
Has anyone arrived
Not yet seen
Worthy to match that heaven
Pass down the order
The Sacred Nuptials shall commence early
May the spirits enjoy this offering
What time is it
Oh no
Could the ceremony have started early
Make way
Qingqing
Brother
Young Master Jiang
What's going on
What happened
What occurred
Why has everyone fainted
I don't know
Look quickly
The Saintly Maiden has ascended to heaven, the Saintly Maiden has ascended to heaven
Quick, quick, kneel and pray for blessings
The Saintly Maiden ascends, Heaven protects Zhongli
Where is Qingqing?
Don't panic yet.
There is still one person who can save her.
The saintess ascends to heaven, heaven protects Zhongli.
The saintess ascends to heaven.
Ascend to what heaven?
Everyone, snap out of it.
Issue a city-wide warrant for that fake heir apparent and the saintess.
Dig three feet into the ground.
But you must find them and bring them back to me.
Alive or dead.
Yes.
Impersonating the heir apparent, abducting the saintess.
ku ku ku .
This time, you will not escape my grasp.
Su Qingqing's fate has changed.
How could that be?
Fate.
Can it truly be changed?
Stop!
After her!
Don't let her get away!
Stop!
Fake.
Sister Yiyao.
How is it you?
you
Yiyao little sister
Are you okay?
It was you who saved the saint.
What about the little saintess?
Hey you guys
Go over there and take a look
Search over here
You few
Come with me this way
is
Strange
He was right here
just a moment ago.
I see a figure there!
green
Kunwu gege
Are you okay
I'm fine
Go
You go first
I'll lure them away
What about you
Don't worry
It's easier for one person than for three
to shake them off
Later
we'll meet outside the city
But
No buts
After all
this is someone you must protect
no matter what
Isn't it
Go check that alley over there
Yes
Hurry up
Thank you
See you soon
Over here
Is it you
So it is because of you
Who are you
You
are my destined one
You are my destined person.
What is a destined person.
This point.
Should be told by you.
Who exactly are you.
Why can't I see your fate clearly.
I don't know.
And why can you change the future.
What is a destined person.
Young Master Jiang.
I wonder how Young Master Jiang's injuries are.
Although Young Master Jiang was not fundamentally harmed.
He still needs to rest and recover properly.
I am injured.
And is unable to perform formal greetings.
I hope the State Preceptor will understand.
Young Master Jiang is injured.
Naturally, there's no need to worry about these formalities.
However.
There is one thing I do not understand.
Young Master Jiang was perfectly fine.
How did you end up near the sacrificial platform?
Being hurt by someone
At that time
I saw the holy maiden being kidnapped
I originally intended to step forward
to capture that villain
But unexpectedly
my skills were inferior
and I ended up being injured by them instead
However
fortunately, the chaste one appeared in time
scaring those people away
and saving me, Jiang
Here, I, Jiang, must also express gratitude
for the chaste one's life-saving grace
I wonder
how I should repay the chaste one
This subordinate's actions
merely follow the master's orders
If you wish to express thanks, Lord Jiang
then thank the Grand Preceptor
Lord Jiang is an envoy of Mount Shang
Ensuring your safety
is my duty
Lord jiang
there is no need to stand on ceremony
Since that is the case
That Young Master Jiang
should focus on recovering from his injuries
Remember
those who stabbed you today
were two villains who abducted the Holy Maiden
Is this chaste one friend or foe?
Could it be that she stabbed me
truly to clear my suspicion?
We've arrived
The carriage arranged by Young Master Jiang
is right there
Good
This is the direction away from Zhongli
Where are we going?
Where is Brother Jiang?
Qingqing
You're hiding something from me
I'm sorry
Brothers Konu
What do you mean?
This
was given to me by Young Master Jiang to pass to you
By the time you see this letter
you should have accomplished your wish
rescuing the Holy Maiden
Since that is the case
Please leave Zhongli quickly
to avoid further trouble
Between you and me
there is no need for debt or obligation
The road ahead is long
take care of yourself
In this life, to have known you
is my great fortune
How much for this little slave
This young master will take them
Fifty coins
This kid really isn't cheap
E'shun
Take care
So
from the very beginning
he never intended to let me stay
That's right
Staying behind
would only hold everyone back
Well then
still leaving?