Miss Asi has had too much to drink
We should send her back
I haven't finished this wine yet
If you're still not satisfied
Just continue
I'll take her home first
I
I can still drink
I'm not drunk
Quick, someone
Not drunk at all
Thank you, young master
For bringing our eldest young lady back
Miss Asi drank too much
Take good care of her
That guy
Could he still be drinking?
Here, for you
Young master
Where is your residence?
Do you need
Someone to escort you home?
Residence
Go home?
They all left me behind and went away
I'm not going back
You, go, go, go
At such a young age
Why drown your sorrows in alcohol?
Go back early
Sleep it off and forget everything
Even if I go back, he ignores me
All along
We were the closest of friends
Promised to trust each other in life and death
In the blink of an eye, he won't even speak to me
Cheat
Then it must be that you did something
That let your friend down
I shouldn't have been suspicious of him
When people meet each other
It's fate, and it should be cherished
The world is unpredictable
Having one true friend in life is enough
Especially
The companions made in youth
Are even more precious
Rare and precious
A little misunderstanding doesn't matter
The two brothers just need to have an open conversation.
Close friends
I really want to
continue being friends with him
Brother Tao
Brother Jiang, here
How is it
Just picked
Brother Xin
Hmm
How did I get back last night
Brother E Shun brought you back
I'm telling you
If you're going to drink in the future, have some good wine
Don’t always go to those taverns
and drink that cheap liquor
The next day, your head is splitting with pain
It’s the worst for your health
Really?
But he wasn’t—
He was the one who brought you back
late last night
Let’s go
Last night, you were the one who brought me back
Sorry
I drank too much
Don't remember anything
Thank you
No need
If something happens to you
We all get punished
I'm doing this for myself too
Good
Good, very good
Brother Chong is impressive
Good
Not good
Not good, not good
What's wrong
Tomorrow's Gaomei sacrificial wine feast
Chong of Libei
The Crown Prince Chong and his wife
Are also coming
The Crown Prince Chong is coming
Why are they coming
I heard the relationship between the two brothers
Isn't very good
The Gaomei Sacrifice is just
An old minor ritual in the Eastern Realm to worship the ancestral founder
Although every year we invite the heirs of the various feudal lords
often those who come to the banquet
are merely envoys
This time, the heir of the Northern Bo Marquis
has come in person
I wonder what the deeper meaning is
This year, due to the matter of the heir's camp
Donglu is in the spotlight
No matter what
it's better to be cautious
The heir of the Northern Bo Marquis has come from afar
we failed to greet you properly
please do not take offense
General Jiang, you are too polite
We in Libei are not like Donglu
we never stand on such ceremony
The Gaomei Festival ceremony
has always been a minor event in the eastern region
Why trouble the heir
to grace us with your presence in person
On this trip, I have come
not only to congratulate the Gaomei Festival
but also for another matter
There are more important matters to attend to.
Has General Jiang forgotten
my younger brother Chong Yibiao
is still troubling your esteemed territory?
As his older brother,
I naturally wished to pay him a visit.
Could it be that General Jiang
does not welcome this heir?
Of course, you are welcome.
Most welcome indeed.
The Marquis's residence has prepared a banquet
to welcome Your Highness.
Your Highness, please.
Lady about.
Isn't this Lady Asi?
What are you doing here?
What a coincidence, isn't it?
My Li family is assisting the Dongwu Marquis's residence
in co-hosting the Gaomei Festival.
Naturally, I came
at General Jiang's invitation.
Your appearance—
Why is your face all red?
Are you feeling unwell?
But.
Miss but
You are truly elegant and refined today
Exceptionally radiant and magnificent
You flatter me, Lord Eshun
Yes, yes, that is a bit excessive
Right, Eshun?
Look at that expression of yours
Lord Eshun here
Doesn't even want to acknowledge you
Right, Eshun?
Let's go
Li Asi
Stop trying to sow discord
Wait for me
Let go, let go, let go
Run quickly, run quickly
The banquet is about to begin
Let me tell you
This female bandit runs really fast
Run quickly
This woman is really
Chong Yibiao's sister-in-law
The Northern Earl's daughter-in-law
Not bad at all
I, the heir, represent North Li
Respectfully celebrate the
Donglu Gaomei Festival ceremony.
Successfully held
The dance performed by my wife
is precisely the most sublime
If dance of libei
to show respect
The Crown Prince's arrival from afar
is already an honor for our Eastern Lu
I specifically ordered my wife to offer this dance
making our Eastern Wuhou Residence
radiate with splendor
Indeed
The Crown Princess is both talented and beautiful
She can be called
a rare beauty
The Crown Prince did not hesitate
to allow his esteemed wife to dance for us
It was truly a feast for the eyes
Indeed
This dance of the Crown Princess
is something we have never seen before
Yes, yes
Brother
It has been a long time since you last saw your brother and sister-in-law
Have you missed them?
This dance by your sister-in-law
The Crown Princess's performance of the Andai dance
Exotic and enchanting
Wild, unrestrained, and swaying with grace
Truly embodying steadiness, lightness, softness, and beauty
All in one
It is absolutely marvelous, simply marvelous
To have such a beauty
The Crown Prince is truly fortunate
Crown Prince, a toast to you
Thank you for the Crown Prince's offering
The banquet has already begun
Please invite the Crown Princess to take her seat quickly
This Chong Yiwu
Will he really act as we expect?
The hatred between the brothers
Has left no room for reconciliation
As long as the piece named Chong Yiwu remains
He will surely disrupt the Crown Prince's camp and bring them no peace
Are you so certain?
Of course
The first toast of tonight's banquet
Should naturally be offered to
General Jiang's
But this second cup of wine
shall be offered to
my savior from Chong Yiwu
Crown Prince E Shun
If Chong is not good and causes much disturbance
then there is no need to stand on ceremony
What you all may not know
is that back on my wedding day
my younger brother Chong Yibiao
drew his blade against me
Fortunately, my worthy brother E Shun
risked his life to save me
Only then did I, the Crown Prince, escape calamity
Could it be
that the scar on E Shun's chest
was inflicted by Brother Chong?
No wonder Brother Chong repeatedly targets him
So this is the cause and effect
Such deep-seated enmity and hatred
How could Brother E endure it?
Worthy brother E Shun
please, go ahead
Since the Crown Prince is so nostalgic
I wonder if he still remembers
On the day of the grand wedding
My promise to you
Today, you have made an enemy of Brother Chong
In the future, my Marquis of Nanbo's estate
Will surely, for generations to come
Be your enemy
May I ask, Crown Prince
Is the trade route in Libei still unobstructed?
So all these years
It was you who blocked the Libei trade route
It seems my younger brother
Did not strike you hard enough with that blade
Worthy brother E Shun
Still plans so diligently for him even now
I can't help but feel your kindness
Has been mistaken for a dog's liver and lungs
I only do what I wish to do
And fulfill the promises I have made
It has nothing to do with anyone else
As for the Libei trade route
As long as it remains blocked for a single day
I'm afraid you, Crown Prince, will find it difficult to
Truly win the public's
support in Libei, right?
You
are my lifesaver
So why is the heir of Beibo Hou so enraged
Please, return to your seat
Wait
So it is Young Master Jiang
You did remind me of one thing
Since you are my lifesaver
I should treat you with the highest etiquette
of our Libei
Attendants
Change the wine vessel
This dragon-tiger wine vessel is too large
I’ve never heard of such a rule
Using such a large wine cup for drinking
Wouldn’t that make one drunk after just one cup?
This is clearly meant to make things difficult
In our libei
when treating honored guests
we always use this dragon-tiger wine vessel
Three cups must be drank to count
Oh no
With this guy’s physical condition
How can I drink so much
Worthy brother
Please go ahead
How
After taking that stab
Can you not even drink alcohol anymore
I never expected Brother E-Shun
To be quite the drinker
Such a large jug
I might not even be able to finish it all myself
Can Brother E's body handle it
Worthy Brother E-Shun is truly bold and unrestrained
This is the second cup
Please go ahead
Wait
Your Highness
There's no need for that, right
Worthy brother's physique
Is quite robust
The last cup
Please
Wait
Libe's Custom
The third cup can be drunk on someone's behalf
Isn't that right, elder brother
I've also drunk elder brother's wine
This gratitude
I see he received it too.
That's about enough.
Hold on a moment.
You drank the wine from your elder brother.
But the wine from your sister-in-law
You haven't drunk yet.
Xin'er.
Come and propose a toast to your younger brother.
What are you standing there for?
Hurry up and propose the toast.
Second brother, please.
My dear younger brother.
If you don't drink this cup of wine,
You truly would be letting down your sister-in-law.
After all, over all these years,
She has been
Yearning for you day and night.
Xin'er, offer it to him.
Second Young Master.
Please.
Brother Chong's clothes are all wet.
Hurry back and change.
The wine of this family
Can be drunk another day; it's not too late.
Everyone, look here.
Everyone, look.
Everyone, open your eyes wide and look clearly.
What is this?
On this handkerchief,
how could there be Chong Yibiao's name?
Could it be that the uncle and sister-in-law
truly have an illicit affair?
How utterly shameless and scandalous!
Indeed.
Give it back to me.
You bitch.
You worthless thing, unfit for any decent occasion.
You keep embarrassing me and making a scene.
How can you hit a woman?
Prince,
this is a banquet hosted by our Eastern Lu.
Treating your wife like this
is hardly appropriate, is it?
General Jiang,
disciplining my own wife is a family matter.
If General Jiang insists on interfering,
I'm afraid that wouldn't be very appropriate, would it?
Prince,
that's not how it is.
Then what is this?
How dare you use such a filthy thing
to dirty my eyes
Don't think that just because you have some looks
and married into our Beibo Marquis Manor
you can cover up your origins
The number one beauty
is nothing more than
a dancer from our Libei Grassland
Indeed
the spawn of a lowly woman
just loves to engage in this kind of
filthy, despicable behavior
Some things, since you can't escape them
why keep searching endlessly?
For example
you are destined not to marry
the one you love
And another example
you two adulterous dogs
are born lowly scum
Enough
What
Does it hurt?
I'm hitting my own woman
You bastard, how dare you block my way
Say that again
I said you're a bastard
Well hit
Chong Yibiao
Stop it
Chong Yibiao, you stop right there
Chong Yibiao
Stop right there
Good
After waiting so long, you've finally made a move
My dear brother
Was it a long time ago
That you wanted to kill me
You and that bitch
You both want me dead
Once I'm dead
You can ascend to the heir position
Don't think I don't know
You're colluding with her in secret
Just to seize power and usurp the throne
Chong Yibiao
You, for the sake of power
Constantly plot to harm your own brother
Truly worthy of being that vile woman's bastard
Indeed shameless and lowborn, deserving of divine retribution
You shut your mouth
Chong Yibiao
Chong Yibiao, you stop right there
You'd like me to shut up
But everyone under heaven knows
That mother of yours
Was that disgraceful horse groom
Using those filthy methods
To seduce Father
Otherwise, how would a bastard like you come to be
And now
You use those same filthy methods
To flirt with the wind and moon alongside your brother's wife
You and your birth mother
Truly share the same bloodline
Chong Yibiao
Do you even know
That your very existence
Is a stain upon the North Bo Marquis Estate
You
are an unforgivable sin
You and that bitch of a mother of yours
are both lowly scum
Chong Yi Wu
I won't allow you to insult my mother
Chong Yi Biao
How could he come here
Such a lowly person
The second son is nothing but
the bastard of a horse groom
What are you trying to do
You rebellious son, are you trying to rebel?
Chong Yi Biao, have you gone mad?
Brother Chong
Don't let them
destroy yourself
You're not worth it
What are you here for?
Regarding today's matter
I hope Brother Chong won't take it to heart
Remember, the grass must bend when the wind blows strong
It's not your place to speak.
Uncle Bing has already told me.
Brother Chong, you went to see him.
So the words just now.
Were spoken on behalf of someone else.
A true friend is hard to find.
It's a pity to betray one.
It's raining.
Brother Chong, rest early.
Spring has already arrived.
Why is it still so cold at night?
The rainy night is damp and chilly.
Young master, you should rest early.
I want to listen to the sound of the rain.
You may leave.
Yes.
May I ask the heir,
Is the trade route in Libei
still unobstructed?
In the future, my Nanbo Hou Mansion
will surely, for generations to come,
be your enemy.
For three years,
the heir drank bitter medicine
and suffered immensely,
barely clinging to life.
Now the heir is deficient in both qi and blood.
Constitution yin-cold
Even during the dog days of summer, one must don a great cloak
My house's young master says
Young Master Chong was constrained by others in his youth
Aspirations hard to fulfill
Now that he has left the northern lands
The world is vast and open
He only wishes the young master to let loose his hands and feet
And grandly display his great plans
Even though things have come to this
You still honor your word