Thank you
Go quickly, go quickly, go quickly
Everyone, be careful
What are you all standing around for?
Hurry up and get on with it
Oh no
With just the three of them, can they manage?
Brother Jiang, I'm here
Monster
Look at me
Come on, look at me
You damn bastard
If you have the guts, look at Lord Xin here
Come on
I... I warn you
Don't come any closer
Never thought you, this monster
Would be so obedient at a critical moment
I warn you, don’t come any closer
Ziyu
Father
Get up, child
Are you alright?
I'm fine, Father
But, Father
Why did you call me out in such a hurry?
What for?
Yu'er
You don’t need to ask about this matter
Nor should you get involved
My lord, something has happened
The young masters used some kind of strategy
And have already defeated that evil creature
So quickly?
Come with me, son
This bronze token
Doesn’t seem to be from the East Martial Marquis’s estate
This pattern
Could it be that the people in the carriage
Are really connected to this evil creature?
Brother Tao
Brother Jiang
How are you both?
With them here, we won’t die
What about the monster?
It must have been killed by my sword, of course
Really?
How are things outside?
General Jiang is still evacuating the civilians
Everyone else is here
Go
We're going back to help my brother
Female flying thief
Why is she here
Bury the fallen noble son with full honors
Take the commoners' bodies
Back to their homes for burial
If there are no family members left
Bury them according to military rites
Yes
Does uttering "bury with full honors"
Allow you to shirk responsibility?
General Jiang, you should explain
Why the monsters appeared here
After all, there are many suspicions about this beast fight
Have you seen Brother Jiang?
Where is he?
Why did we lose track of him right here?
Miss
You're looking for me, the Marquis, aren't you?
Who are you?
Why are you following us?
I should be asking who you are
Daring to publicly release evil creatures
And disrupt our Donglu
Quick
Kill her for me
A mighty feudal lord
Openly bullying a young girl
Isn't very appropriate, is it?
Why is it you?
Brother Jiang
This young master
Might I ask if you are Nephew Jiang?
I dare not recklessly claim such relations
Lord Marquis, disrupting the beast fight
Is an act of deceiving the sovereign
Which warrants the execution of your nine clans
You
You refuse a toast only to be forced to drink a forfeit
Then I’d like to see
What forfeit drink Lord Marquis offers me
Why is it you again?
So it was also you who stole the imperial decree
What did I tell you last time?
If I ever see you again
You won’t keep your hands and feet
This time is just perfect
Take your master along with you
Don't move
Or I'll kill her
What are you laughing at
I'm laughing at how stupid you all are, of course
Old man
This girl is a petty thief
Do you think I care
about the life or death of a petty thief
Jiang Wenxuan
You vile man
Something as trivial as sesame seeds and mung beans
and you remember it so clearly
Today
even if I end up in the underworld
I will come back for revenge
What good will seeking revenge on me do
It's them who want to kill you
not me
Without you, would they have taken me hostage
Now you're being unreasonable
Did I ask you to come
Did I tell them to attack you
Was it me who told them to take you hostage?
I don't care, it's because of you.
It really wasn't me.
It was you.
It wasn't me.
Be careful.
Are you alright?
Let's go.
This unforeseen incident.
Is truly heartbreaking.
I will definitely get to the bottom of this.
And give everyone an explanation.
I think we should still report to the king.
And ask His Majesty.
To make the decision.
Right.
We will set off for the capital immediately.
To the capital, to seek justice.
Wait a moment.
Everyone.
Calm down.
You all want to seek justice, right?
Then we have no one else to look for.
We must find.
This person who seized the imperial decree.
And released the monsters—Marquis Ningbo.
What on earth is going on here
Everyone
This
was found inside
the crate used to transport that monster
The emblem on it
is the Ning family crest
Isn't that right
The Marquis's
What is the meaning of all this
Marquis Ning, so it really was him
How could it be Marquis Ning
How is that possible
Why would he do this
Why
Stop asking
So what if this old man did it
The King wants to cut off my descendants
What I did
was all to stop the beast fights
and prevent the reopening of the proton camp
What, reopen the proton camp
Ten days ago, this Marquis received a secret report
The day of the War God Festival's beast fights
is when the proton camp reopens
What plans does the Marquis have?
Father
Must I really go to the capital like my elder brother
to serve as a proton?
The King has already killed one of my sons
I absolutely cannot let the Ning family
be cut off without descendants
The Marquis is indeed decisive in action
Our Guifang will certainly provide full assistance
to express our sincerity
I will offer our Guifang's secret arts
and await the Marquis's commands
Father
All of this is forced upon us by the King
Do not blame this old man
Mount Shang is unkind
The Son of Heaven is without virtue!
Minister Gongsun
Is what Marquis Ningbo said true?
Is the King truly going to reopen the proton camp?
The King
Preparing to establish the Heir Camp
Rather than a Hostage Camp
What is the difference between these two
Indeed
Isn't it about being a hostage
Exactly
Still hostages, aren't they
Everyone, please let me finish speaking
Recently
The King received divine guidance from heaven
Learning that the elixir of immortality
Has reappeared in the world
And the one who can find it
Is among the heirs of the feudal lords
Therefore, the King
Intends to establish the Heir Camp in Eastern Lu
Merely to search for
The long-lost national treasure of Shang Mountain that protects the country
Eastern Lu
You mean the Heir Camp is not in the capital
Correct
This is the King's royal edict
The heirs of the feudal lords may examine it
This
It truly is so
So it is said
If the heir's camp is set up in Donglu
Then the lives of the heirs
will be somewhat secured
If we can retrieve the sacred treasure for the king
Our entire clan will surely be rewarded
Bringing glory to our motherland
This is utterly foolish
How can you believe the nonsense of Old Man Yuanyang
You hypocrites with your false righteousness
Every single one of you
Who doesn't harbor grievances against Shang Mountain
I am different from you
I dare to act and take responsibility
Willing to donate my aged body
Risk my life to fight
Resist the unjust and foolish ruler
Marquis Ningbo, you have a silver tongue
It's a pity that with such eloquence
You don't go to the capital to argue with the king
Instead, you harm the innocent here
Isn't that putting the cart before the horse
Now, based solely on your speculation
you have caused such great chaos
How are you any different
from the tyrannical and foolish ruler you speak of
The lives of your Ning family are lives
while the lives of others are mere weeds and ants
With a narrow mind like yours
so ignorant and petty
you put on an act as if everyone else is corrupt
and you alone are virtuous
When it comes to being a person
being bad is one thing
but what’s worse is being foolish
Jiang Wenhuan
Step back
Ning Bohou
You harm the innocent out of personal vendetta
No excuse justifies
your scheming to harm others
Father
Innocent
As long as I can protect my son’s life
all of you are expendable
Father
Ziyu
All these people are handed over to Father.
Let's go quickly.
Father.
Ziyu.
Heaven wants to destroy me.
My son is innocent!
It is the negligence of our Dongwu Marquis Estate.
Come back to the city with me first.
Wait a moment.
If I had uncovered the truth earlier.
If I hadn't been so arrogant.
If before the beast fight.
I had promptly shared the clues with Big Brother.
All of this.
Would it have been different?
This subordinate general, Jiang Wenfeng, has failed in his duties.
Above, I have failed the King's grace.
Below, I have shamed the Jiang family ancestors.
I am willing to accept punishment.
Stop!
Halt!
Big Brother.
I am the heir of the Dongwu Marquis.
The one who should be punished is me.
Are you deaf?
Try laying another hand on my brother!
I am the eldest son
Eldest brother, hit me
Get out
You have no right to speak here
Let go of me
Stop making a scene
By the king's order
Although the beast fight was initiated by Ning Bohou's rebellion
the Dongwu Hou Mansion is also guilty of negligence
This time, not only will your eldest brother be punished
but the imperially bestowed plaque will also be revoked
as a disciplinary measure
This is already a result of leniency beyond the law
in consideration of the Jiang family's illustrious military achievements by their ancestors
Harming the innocent
Disgrace
Bringing shame upon the ancestors
The glory of the Jiang family
The heroes of Donglu
Will you one day become one of these
As your teacher, I do not know
But there is one thing
I, your master, am very certain
Since the day I met both of you brothers
You
have been your elder brother's pride
I will go prepare some ointment
bandages
for elder brother
I also ask Master
to take good care of elder brother
Please rise quickly
I also ask Master to relay a message to elder brother for me
I will definitely not let him down
I never expected things to turn out like this
The Ning family has actually been wiped out just like that
The incident was sudden, and not something either of us wished for
I've troubled you
It's no trouble at all
Many matters
have been handled through your efforts
Thank you for helping me apply the medicine
Both my and Shi'er's lives were saved by you
Yet you're being so polite with me
This
It was Huan'er who asked me to give this to you
This is
This is from Huan'er
Taken from
that mysterious person who snatched the imperial decree
This object is made from
copper ore unique to Guifang
The State of Guifang
That’s right
The monster that appeared earlier
in the arena
If I recall correctly
should also be crafted through Guifang’s secret arts
the Kui Corpse
Never expected Marquis Ningbo to join forces with Guifang
Guifang is a state surrounding Donglu
not yet subjugated to Shangshan
Due to territorial disputes with Donglu
they have been engaged in war for years
But sixteen years ago
after the great upheaval in Ningzhou
Guifang quieted down for many years
Now they are stirring up trouble again.
Perhaps they learned that I, Donglu,
am about to establish the Heir Camp.
However, Guifang
has always been skilled in witchcraft and mysterious practices.
So it is not surprising
that Kuibashi is associated with them.
The establishment of the Heir Camp in Donglu
will likely bring many troubles in the future.
The camp begins tomorrow.
We can only wait and see how things unfold.
Protect Donglu.
Protect the children.
Alright, no need to see me off.
Go back.
Don’t worry, Father.
Mother, your health is not well.
Please return to your room.
My child, I cannot stop worrying about you.
Brother,
this is for you.
May it keep you safe in Donglu.
Mother’s health is not well.
You must take care of her on my behalf.
Be more filial, you know?
I'm leaving, Father.
Alright, take care, child.
Go back now.
Take good care of yourself.
Don’t worry about me.
Mind your health.
What are you looking at?
Isn’t it true that no one from North Bo Marquis Manor came?
Jealous?
No one came from Xichuan either.
It seems we are both unfortunate souls.
From now on in the Heir's Camp,
we’ll have to keep each other warm.
Let go.
Walking around with a long face all day.
Brother Chong,
we’ll keep each other warm.
After entering the camp,
this old servant will no longer be able
to stay by your side at all times.
Your Heir made a deal with me:
as long as I fight beasts for him,
he will help me find my sister.
You need not worry, young master.
As long as the young master
Stay put in this heir camp.
One day, the wish will be fulfilled.
The matter of the Crown Prince's camp.
He hadn't mentioned it before.
Bringing it up now.
Shouldn't be too late.
What if
I don't want to agree?
Do you think, sir,
you still have a choice?
You are a smart man, sir.
You should understand.
This bait-and-switch scheme.
Once it begins.
There's no turning back.
Otherwise, if the truth comes out.
For you, for my master.
It would be a dead end.
My sister.
How is she now?
Alive or dead?
Your sister is still alive.
But.
Sometimes living.
Is more painful than death.
Don't worry, sir.
As long as you fulfill the agreement.
The master
I will definitely help the young master rescue your sister
My son
Live on
Protect Qingqing well
Father
Alright
I promise you
Dahuang
Come, drink with me
Let's go
Go
Why did you drink so much?
Didn't drink much
Over here
You have a sip too
Brother Jiang
Drink less
I'm drunk
Being drunk is good
Drunk
Then I won't have to regret anymore
What happened in the arena
Was all an accident
Not your fault
I know
Everyone says that
Not my fault
But do you know
I, of the esteemed Dongwu Hou Mansion
the heir Jiang Wenjuan
could not save my beloved dog Da Huang
could not stop the schemes of Ning Bo Hou
In the end
it was my elder brother who took the punishment for me
Tell me
isn't it ridiculous
Tonight
everyone is bidding farewell to their families
I too must bid farewell to someone
Who
Myself
You
From now on
I, Jiang Wenjuan
can no longer act recklessly
can no longer be ignorant of my own limits
and even more, cannot fail to understand my elder brother's苦心 (good intentions)
I must bid farewell
to that guilt-ridden
and helpless
incompetent self
Well then
And toast
to the incompetent self
River lanterns for sale
Selling river lanterns
Wait for me for a moment
Uncle
Do you want a river lantern?
Two river lanterns
Here
Selling river lanterns
River lanterns
In the Southern Capital
If a loved one has passed away
Everyone uses river lanterns
To mourn and express grief
Life is short and unpredictable
The river flows endlessly
People hope that these waters,
whose final destination is unknown,
Can carry their prayers and sorrows
To accompany their loved ones
On their final journey
Then, Brother E, for whom is this lantern
Being released?
For
Those who continue to live
One lantern to honor the living
One lantern to solace the deceased
Very well
Prince's Camp
The camp will be established tomorrow in Donglu
What do you plan to do
It seems Brother Jiang already has plans
That's right
The Crown Prince's camp is being established
It's opened to seek the elixir of immortality for the king
If we successfully obtain the elixir
When the time comes
I will restore the Jiang family's glory
And have that plaque
Representing the Jiang family's generations of merit
Hang once more above the lintel of our house
Furthermore
I will make my eldest brother
Rightfully and legitimately
Become the master of the Eastern Martial Marquis's residence
Brother Jiang has quite a few
Aspirations
What about you
Do you want to achieve great deeds and establish a career
Serve your motherland
Lead troops into battle
Or
I think
I want to survive
Survive
Okay
Then let's toast to us in the Prince's camp
Survive
Okay
You've all drunk me dry
This way
It's this way
Are you sure
I'm sure
Brother E Shun
If you ask me, the drinking capacity of you Southern Capital folks
Is nothing special
Naturally, it can't compare to Brother Jiang's massive capacity
Brother Jiang
It's fine
What is it
Be careful
You see
You and I
Have met a few times
A chance encounter
In a critical moment
You could disregard life and death
Step forward bravely
But honestly
I never expected that in the arena today
It would be you coming to save me
Didn't Brother Jiang say
Do I resemble your childhood friend?
Are you referring to Big Yellow?
I'll call you Big Yellow.
Do you dare to answer?
Big Yellow.
Big Yellow, Big Yellow.
Friends helping each other out
is only natural.
Could it be
Brother Jiang
has never
saved a stranger before?
But it's alright.
Tomorrow
I'll take you home.
Home.
Whiteheads As New.
Covered Chariots As Old.
A chance encounter.
can also be considered a life-and-death bond.
However
today, no matter what, you saved me.
From this moment on, you are my, Jiang Wen Huan's,
sworn brother.
I am deeply honored.
Choosing a day is not as good as meeting the day.
Just take advantage of the beautiful scenery.
Let's swear brotherhood.
Swear
Brotherhood
Yeah.
Swear brotherhood.
Perfect to fill Big Yellow's spot in our family.
You're drunk.
No.
I'm not drunk.
You, if you collapse here again.
I'm leaving, okay?
Don't go.
Big Yellow.
Don't go, ah.
Dad.
Learned to run away from marriage.
And even懂得d how to steal in public.
Leaving aside the matter of running away from marriage for now.
I've only been gone for a few days.
You've actually become so audacious.
To provoke the Marquis of Dongwu's estate.
You've got a death wish, you.
Today
I need to discipline you properly
Otherwise, I'm afraid you'll turn the world upside down in the future
Li Laowu
Go ahead, hit me
All of you, leave us
Yes
How could I bear to hit you, my child
But with that dog-like temper of yours
Look
See how frightened they are
Everything I do is for your own good
If anything were to happen to you in the future
How would I
Go on living
Father
I've told you many times
I don't want to get married
In the future, I still want to enter Qiankun Alley
And become your right-hand man
I've also told you many times
Qiankun Alley
Has its own ways and purposes
Do not bring this up again in the future
Dad.
And also.
In the future, matters of the East Martial侯侯 Residence.
You are not to interfere.
Why.
Those heirs are not so simple.
From now on.
You should spend less time mixing with them.
Silly girl.
How is it.
It's Young Master Ning.
Is he still breathing.
Still alive.
Take him away.
This kid really has nine lives.
The master will surely be satisfied.