I'm going to make a
little bit of a
little bit in the
sink
in the
To love To heal
Episode 05
You're a newbie.
You don't have to come over to thank me.
But,
after you got the job,
you're also responsible for Wanxin Entertainment.
As your leader,
I still want to give you a friendly reminder.
I'll do it.
Look carefully.
I have already told you to stay away from that Mr. Du.
Du Lei,
his goal has always been me behind you.
He and Wan Shan, that old fox,
are a team.
Tang Xin retreated because of him.
Jiang Jun,
you have to understand one thing.
There has never been an idiot lunch in the world.
There has never been a teacher who is a fool.
Really?
Then, is there a house that is free of charge in this world?
What house?
Mr. Landlord,
you are really considerate.
No, Jiang Jun,
don't misunderstand.
I actually think
it was too much to let you enter the M&H.
So,
we have been friends for so many years, right?
I hope you can have a good living environment
to make up for your
unemployment.
I have no other thoughts.
Make up for?
You raised my house price and made me go nowhere.
You let me live in the house you arranged.
You told me to make up for it.
You might as well say that you are used to
being a playboy in other people's lives.
You think it's funny to see me moving in and out by myself, right?
Yes.
Is that what you think?
Isn't my house
a hundred times better than the one you lived in before?
You are a liar!
I don't want to live in a liar's house.
I will move out tonight.
You moved so much stuff over here.
Do you want to live here forever?
What? You are not going to let me live here?
Don't worry.
I have already asked Zhou Jie to find a house.
Find a house?
Do you think it's easy to find a house now?
Last time, Yuan Shuai and Xiaochuan
talked happily.
I thought he had changed his school rules.
I didn't expect him to bully you again.
You are a family.
Why is there such a big difference?
He won't bully our Xiaochuan, right?
Junjuan,
I think you can ask Yuan Shuai to help me.
Are you going to listen to me?
No.
I started to read novels recently.
In their comments, they all said
that my anti-corruption is too much.
I think I can ask Yuan Shuai
to interview him.
Let him tell me about
the story of bullying you.
Oh my god.
For more than ten years,
he has been bullying you alone.
Such a persistent anti-corruption
was actually encountered by me.
I think I can write it well
into my novel
and make it popular.
General.
Brother Yuan Yuan.
General, jump down.
I'm scared.
It's okay.
Jump down.
I'm scared.
Don't be afraid.
Believe me.
I will help you.
Come on.
Come down.
Brother Yuan Yuan.
I'm going to jump.
You have to help me.
Come on.
Ready.
One.
Two.
Three.
Jump.
You fell down, right?
You deserve it.
You said you would help me.
You lied.
I just want to teach you
not to believe what men say easily.
So cruel.
But I still think it's unreasonable.
What's unreasonable?
You lied to me to rent a house.
Or you lied to me to get a house.
I don't think it's reasonable.
I think it's unreasonable.
I think
Yuan Shuai may think
you are a little bit short.
Anyway, you have already entered the company.
At least
you can live better.
Listen to your sister.
You are a little bit short.
Stop your
shameless pity.
This kind of black and white man
will not have a contrast.
And there is no stupid
talent in the world.
It's really sweet
and hurtful.
Oh, my god.
What's wrong?
This question is so boring.
Tell me.
Why does she
think I'm playing with her?
No.
What on earth did you do to her?
She
knows I'm her landlord.
This is the reason
why you come here
to drink at night.
I mean, are you serious?
Do you think
you can get her
around you
and she will react?
You like her.
Shouldn't it be like this?
Naive.
I mean...
For other girls,
they might think so.
But for you,
no.
You
used to bully her.
I heard you were
so sad.
Unless she has
Sdg.
Otherwise,
she will not think
a super villain
in her life
will like her.
Then you tell me.
Will she like me?
Do you think
Lan Jin Ling will like
Ge Ge Wu?
I'm going home
to pack my luggage.
You should thank me
for the earliest
delivery tomorrow.
I'm leaving now.
I'm going out.
Boss.
Xiao Ni.
I have a document
to sign with Mr. Yuan.
Is he coming?
Mr. Yuan is on a business trip
to Beijing.
Your document is very important.
It's okay.
No hurry.
Hello.
Are you free?
I'm near your company.
Can I meet you?
Well...
I'm sorry.
I have a document to sort out.
I quit my job at Ji Yi.
Okay.
Why did you resign?
I met Yuan Shuai.
He suspected that
I was using you
for Wan Xin's business.
And you know
I knew Wan Shan
and I was afraid you would misunderstand.
So I resigned.
You resigned because of this?
Actually,
I didn't...
Ji Yi
has been very concerned
about this project.
And Wan Shan and my father
are old acquaintances.
They have been looking for me many times.
But I went to find them.
Then why didn't you just say it?
After all,
our company has a competitive relationship.
Besides,
we have promised each other
that we will not interfere with each other's work.
I'm sorry, Mr. Yuan.
It's okay.
It doesn't matter.
To be honest,
I'm quite relaxed now.
I have helped others
for so long.
Finally, I have a chance
to do what I want to do.
What are you going to do in the future?
I haven't thought about it completely.
I will be a speech therapist
in some financial training classes.
I may develop in this field in the future.
Maybe.
Then you won't be
my teacher anymore.
Four seven
four eight
four nine
Why don't you get off work?
What are you counting?
If I pass fifty people,
my love hasn't come yet.
I will get off work.
Then your love
is too magical.
I'm going to go now.
Did I use too much strength
to get off work?
It's been less than a week.
The network signal is also very good.
Is it
faster than our network speed?
Xu Li.
There is a delivery order.
Can you please
send it to me when you go back?
Okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Ren Shuai.
You're a bad guy.
You ordered so many things.
I will kill you.
You're a bad guy.
I...
No.
Why are you
here?
My cousin is on a business trip.
He asked me to help him raise a dog.
So...
On a business trip?
You want to raise a dog for him?
Then
you're home alone.
He's so cute.
What does he mean?
Fang Cai.
Well...
I...
You bought a lot of vegetarian food.
Are you not going out?
These are very important
to me.
Because I'm running
the last test.
So I'm very busy recently.
But a dog
needs exercise.
Yes.
It's a good idea to let him exercise.
Fang Cai.
Let's go.
So this is what you said
to let him exercise?
Does he eat dog food?
He eats it every day.
This is what
my cousin told me.
You're so sweet.
But actually,
a dog needs...
What?
It's a dog.
It's going to the bathroom?
Xi Ya, you're so busy.
How about
I help you raise a dog?
Okay.
Thank you.
It's the first time
it's thanked me.
I'm so happy.
Then...
I'll...
I'll help you raise a dog.
Fang Cai, let's go.
Where's the rope?
Over there.
Fang Cai, come here.
We're leaving.
Fang Cai.
Come on.
I lost a hair!
You lost a hair?
I'll leave now.
Back to work, okay?
Bye
I'm leaving
You're going to drive a night car again, right?
Here
I bought it for you
Take care of your health
Thank you
You're welcome
Help me turn off the light when you leave
Okay, bye
Bye
I'm leaving
This is the financial report and the account of Hu Di Group
Within two days
a complete asset evaluation report will be issued
Am I doing it alone?
Or I'll do it with you
Okay, Mr. Ma
Bye
Are you still fighting?
You're really good at it
Don't sit down all the time
It's useful to stand up and do a jump
Hello
Can you order?
I didn't order
General, right?
This is yours
Five thousand good comments
Thank you
Did you receive the business dog food?
I received the business dog food
Thank you for your vote
I can't finish my work
I'll go home after eating
I'll just pass by
I'll go to the restaurant
I'll go home
Go home
I don't have a home to go back to
Don't bother
I have a lot of things to do
I'll stay in the company today
Don't worry, it's safe
Brother, how did you shoot this car?
I'm really sorry
I was in a hurry
I didn't notice
Look at you
You've knocked down the pole
Brother, you
Let's talk privately
Brother, can you?
Or you can drive
Okay?
Brother, this
I've already taken it
Can't I pay the full price?
You don't have to worry about me
I'm shooting Liu Gening
You two continue
I'm leaving
I'll go home
I'll get back to work
I'm leaving
I'll go home
You two continue
Okay, boss
What do you say?
I'm being chased
Like
Why is it a like?
I'm in a car accident
Liar
What does it have to do with me?
I'm not a liar
What's the matter with me?
No
You don't even give me a like
So petty
What do you mean, General?
I'll answer the phone
You see how much you are
Hello
Baby, are you asleep?
I'm working overtime
I have good news for you
I can go back to China in the last semester
We don't have to live separately
Really?
That's great
I'll pick you up later
Are you done?
You're in a hurry to go to work
Baby, I'm sorry
Boss is urging me
I'm hanging up
If you keep doing this
Don't take the year-end award
during your working hours
Boss, I didn't take the year-end award
I have a call
He's going abroad to study
and will be back soon
Are you trying to irritate me?
No
I want to tell you
We are childhood friends
We have been together for many years
We never broke up
There is a trick in it
Trick
No
I had a car accident
I sent a friend a car
She gave me a like
What does she mean?
Boss
I think
you need a sincere apology
Apologize
I didn't order food
I'll help you walk the dog
This is the compensation for her
I brought you some strawberries
blueberries
bread and milk
I washed them all for you
And coffee
It's for you
Seriously
You are so handsome
Oliver
I did it!
You are the first person to witness my western world.
Let me tell you. I used a method.
It's a simple method.
I used all my data simulation machines to do a division experiment.
The result...
Do you know?
My matching method is very accurate.
It's a huge breakthrough!
Congratulations.
What method did you say you used?
I... I can't tell you right now.
But when I'm done with everything, I'll tell you, okay?
Oh my god!
Why is he so bad at it?
What should I do?
He's so fast.
Well, I'll help you walk.
I'm tired.
Then... I'll go to work.
I'll leave you to it.
I...
Jiang Junya.
Morning, Mr. Ma.
You did a division experiment on the work report according to the asset list.
It's very detailed and convenient to speed up.
I should do it.
I'm sorry.
I've been in MH for so many years.
I've never seen you so detailed.
Mr. Ma, you're flattering me.
My English name is Bo.
It means Bole in Chinese.
In my eyes, trust is divided into two types.
One is a wild boar.
The other is a family boar.
Do you understand what I mean?
Wild boars are good.
Wild boars are good at it.
Wild boars dare to break through and fight.
They have a future.
You're so interesting.
After work today,
you should prepare for it.
Mr. Qin from Wanbo invited us to dinner.
You're excellent.
I specially asked you to attend on behalf of the company.
Me?
Good luck.
I'm looking out for you.
Mr. Ma.
Let's go.
Mr. Yuan, the price you gave is too low.
You have a big appetite.
You're so arrogant.
You're a big business.
20% increase is too much.
Impossible.
Do you know the price of Jinding's investment bank?
I don't know.
Can Jinding compete with MH?
Their signature is not good.
But they gave a high price.
Mr. Yuan, Mr. Ma sent Jiang Jun to Wanbo to accompany Mr. Qin.
I heard he's hard to deal with.
Jiang Jun may have trouble.
I'll give you one minute to think about it.
I'll stop working with you.
But I want to remind you.
If I announce that I'll stop working with your company,
I believe no other company will be interested in your company.
Start timing.
Order the fastest flight back to Shanghai.
Okay.
Mr. Yuan, we haven't finished talking.
30 seconds.
Hurry up.
I'll answer.
Listen to me.
Wait.
Every drink should be in place.
Okay?
Come on.
You guys.
Hurry up.
You're good at everything.
One more.
I can't drink.
I'll drink.
Are you sure?
Good drink.
Where is Miss Jiang going?
I'm sorry, Mr. Qin.
I want to go to the bathroom.
Go to the bathroom and get a bag.
Come on.
I'll go make up.
Drink one more.
How about this?
I'll propose a toast.
But the first one
is to Miss Jiang.
Miss Jiang, Mr. Ma is always there for me.
He said you're a newbie,
but you're smart and smart.
He's very good at judging.
But I have a habit
of not looking at the person's face.
I've known him for a long time.
So the rule here is
to judge the person by the drink.
Wait.
This is the first time I've met you.
This drink
is not good enough.
I'll use this.
Come on.
This is right.
The last step.
This drink is called
the best.
Miss Jiang, you're so sincere.
Come on.
Mr. Qin,
I really don't want to drink with you.
I'm really allergic to alcohol.
Look at my face.
Mr. Qin,
Xiao Jiang's face is red.
She really can't drink.
Look, it's a face.
It's a face.
Don't force her.
I'll take Miss Jiang out for a walk.
It seems that Miss Jiang
doesn't want to give me a face.
It's okay.
Jiang Jun, if you really
don't want to drink with Mr. Qin,
I'll drink for you.
Come on, Mr. Qin, I'll drink for her.
Okay, come on.
Come on.
Mr. Qin is our M&H's
big client.
Anyway, Mr. Qin
will definitely drink.
Good.
You're really a person recommended by Mr. Ma.
You have a good strength. Hurry up.
Sorry, I have to answer the phone.
Hello.
Are you available now?
I'm eating with my client.
Why are you so ugly?
You go back to the building.
Send me the phone. Wait for her.
I'll ask her to come here.
Let me go.
Let go.
How are you?
Come home with me.
Mr. Yuan, Mr. Yuan.
Shut up.
Be careful.
What have we received after our oatmeal?
You were so burning,
so we need to wait for it.
I'll open the door.
Now it's on time.
It is so funny.
I'm thirsty.
Yeah, the water is...
Your face has changed.
What team did I become?
That color.
She shouldn't have...
The same color.
Are you sure she's fine?
That's none of your concern.
All my means, everything
My promise
Wait for a moment to say it out
Say it
I shouldn't drink in my working hours
I'm sick
I mean
How can you let someone like Ma Xiu Ran
ride on your head and be so powerful?
I've said it many times
This is a battlefield, not a test field
There are no rules
There are no test teachers
How can you be so easy to deal with
someone like Ma Xiu Ran?
How can I be so easy to deal with?
Are you sick?
Are you not making sense?
I'm going to be punished today
Do I have any way?
Can I defy Ma Xiu Ran's order?
How dare you defy me?
Don't touch me
What are you doing?
Get down, General
It's dangerous up there
Get down
You are a big liar
Stop it, get down
It's dangerous up there
Don't touch me
Get down, I'll take you
Are you kidding me?
Will I be fooled by you again?
Get out
Don't do anything, General
Get down
What are you doing?
It's dangerous
I'll take you
Get down
You fell down, right?
I deserve it
You said you would hold me
You are lying
I just want to teach you
Don't believe what men say
I won't believe you again
Little crybaby, I'll hold you
I've been saying this for three times
I'll be the second one to be punished
I promise I won't do it again
Silly girl, you've been transferred
I won't let you leave again
She is crazy
Shut up
Be quiet
Don't give Yuan Shuang the big wolf
Let's go home.
Try to understand
Try to say goodbye a thousand times
You can tell me lies
You can make me cry, you know why
Never been so brave
I will run away
If it's what you want
What you like, I don't mind
I can close my eyes
I can stay behind with my time
Walk into your plan
Like I never knew you were not mine
Make you satisfied
Wear another mask
You never realize things I do for love
I think I'm tired
I think I'm blind
Don't know how to feel
Don't know how to heal
You walk so fast
Can't catch your light
You fly so high
Leave all the things behind
And our story
Leave all love nowhere to find
I think I'm tired
I think I'm blind
Don't know how to feel
Don't know how to heal
You walk so fast
Can't catch your light
You fly so high
Leave all the things behind
And our story
Leave all love nowhere to find
Translated by Hua Chenyu English Subs