I'm going to make a
little bit of a
little bit
a
相信
Happy magnet eaters
Super Jam
Previously on...
leads you to a Stanford Park
but when you 28
I'm sorry.
Let's call the police.
Hello, Mr. Yuan.
Who are you?
We are the members of MH.
Someone has reported to us that
you have bribed us.
Please cooperate with us to take the investigation.
Bribed?
Yes.
Me?
Are you kidding me?
Please cooperate with us.
If the truth doesn't exist,
we will clear your name.
Okay, I'll go with you.
This way, please.
What's going on?
I don't know.
What happened?
Those people look like
members of the He Gui headquarters.
They said Mr. Yuan was bribed.
How is that possible?
Yes, how is that possible?
You two are here.
I'm here.
What you are doing is wrong.
Even if you are from the headquarters,
you can't just break other people's things.
I'm sorry.
Please don't interfere with our work.
Put it down.
Tell me.
The former colleague of the headquarters
called and said
someone reported to us that
the boss was in a serious crisis.
He doesn't know the specific cause.
Serious crisis?
How is that possible?
I don't believe it either.
But he hasn't heard the specific cause yet.
He even asked me for help.
Does Mr. Qiao know?
Yes, he doesn't know.
What about Mr. Ma?
Isn't he transferred to the headquarters?
Mr. Ma?
His father's boss is in trouble.
What can he do?
The headquarters sent someone here in such a hurry.
He shouldn't have thought of it.
The boss is in trouble this time.
But don't worry.
We have to trust the boss.
And Mr. Fan is here.
The boss will be fine.
Let's wait patiently.
Okay.
If there's any news,
tell me immediately.
Okay.
Such a big shock.
Mr. Yan.
Someone is reporting that
you're taking over the contract of Chen Xing Technology, Zhu You Yi.
Do you admit it?
No.
But in your account,
you received a large amount of money from Zhu You Yi
last month.
How do you explain it?
Zhu You Yi is both my client
and my friend.
I lent him that money.
Do you have a contract
or a loan contract?
I've said it.
I have a good relationship
with Zhu You Yi.
I don't need a contract between him and me.
For this matter,
I can confront Mr. Zhu in person.
Then let's invite Dr. Zhu in.
Dr. Zhu.
I want to ask you
if you have ever
bribe our ED.
Yes.
Did he accept your bribe?
He did.
Zhu You Yi.
What are you talking about?
I've been thinking about
Chen Xing Technology's future
and I've been thinking about it.
Why are you blaming me?
Yuan Shuai.
Stop pretending.
Is it useful?
If there's no interest,
how could you
help me
in my most difficult time?
I'm treating you
as my true friend.
That's why I lent you the money.
Lend you the money?
Who bought you?
How much did he spend?
Yuan Shuai.
Mind your attitude.
I think in this matter,
there must be some misunderstanding.
I brought Yuan Shuai out.
I know his character.
Mr. Fan.
You don't know your own face.
I know Yuan Shuai is your favorite.
But don't say it so bluntly.
Whether it's borrowing money or bribery,
Dr. Zhu.
What's your relationship
with Yuan Shuai?
Here's the thing.
More than a year ago,
Yuan Shuai became the person in charge
of the remodeling of the company's financing and assets.
I wasted a lot of money
because of the mistake I made.
The company is going to close down.
When Yuan Shuai saw my project,
he thought it was promising.
He encouraged me to make a loan
and hinted that
I would give him a refund
after the financing was done.
I agreed
and gave him a sum of money.
Not long ago,
my friend,
the student in charge of the debt collection,
helped me to invest a lot of money.
I gave him five million in return.
Mr. Yuan.
Is it true what Dr. Zhu said?
I'm not telling the truth.
No one will believe it.
Then, Dr. Zhu,
do you have any evidence?
This
is the remodeling certificate.
Because it was the first time,
he was inexperienced
and afraid of being discovered by other shareholders.
So he gave him cash
and didn't take it.
This time,
I gave him
the money for the personal account.
Actually, I don't care about the money.
I just need to have the money to develop it.
But he actually
made an excessive request.
He said that after Chen Xin was listed,
as a health agent,
he would take Chen Xin's original stock
and make a big profit.
I don't want to be kidnapped by him.
But he is the leader
of the investment bank.
So I can only report to MH
about this matter.
Zhu You Yi, Zhu You Yi.
That's great.
Why didn't I see you
as such a person?
Yuan Shuai,
you are suspected of bribery and corruption.
You have severely violated
the working discipline of MH.
We will investigate all your projects
according to the company's rules.
Yes.
Go ahead.
Do whatever you want.
Wait.
I have to say this.
Yuan Shuai has always been
a harsh person to MH.
So we can't just
listen to one side of the story
or bribe records
and charge Yuan Shuai.
Mr. Fan, don't worry.
As of now,
things are not that bad.
I will personally
plead with the headquarters and the board of directors
to let Yuan Shuai come out.
Don't make things
so bad.
At most,
we can just cancel
his qualification as a health agent
and enter the market.
It's not that serious.
It seems that
things are not that bad
now.
Whether I do it or not
doesn't matter anymore.
The truth is not important at all.
What's important is that
someone wants me to take this path.
No matter what,
the result is the same.
Mr. Yuan,
I also thought about MH's reputation.
In that case,
I should thank Mr. Lin
for being lenient.
Mr. Lin is really something.
He gave me such a big surprise
as soon as he came back.
It's your fault
that you were careless.
You didn't know how to use people.
Really?
There are only the two of us here.
Tell me.
What exactly do you want to do?
I want to be a doctor.
You see me,
even though I can't work right now,
I still believe in grams and months
to live on,
so I will make stop motion.
Or這個問題
is there anything
that you want to revolutionize around the environment
such as the origin of the new invention?
How do we end up
fifteen billion in 300 years?
People from the future
and the future
to purchase the shares of three non-sales companies in advance.
And then, they will collect the client's funds of 1,947 million yuan.
The profit is 8.68 million yuan.
In 2013, your wife, Wuji Technology,
became the fourth major shareholder of Fengshang Technology.
She invested 700,000 yuan or 650,000 yuan.
She has a 1.723% share.
In 2015, Fengshang Technology officially went public.
Until recently, Wuji Technology
held the shares of Fengshang Technology.
It's about 10 million yuan.
It's 14.2 times higher.
Enough.
Stop being a loser.
How can you take me on
when you have no evidence?
Let me ask you again.
Why are you investigating the C Group?
Mr. Lin, why are you so nervous
when I mention C Group?
Are you trying to tell me
that if I have the information about C Group,
I can do something about you?
Let's change the topic.
I heard that you and your analyst
have a good relationship.
Are you close to Jiang Jun?
Jiang Jun
is the one who was kicked out of MH by me.
You brought him back.
So you kicked him out.
He is not capable and has poor academic ability.
If I don't hire him,
what do you think will happen?
But Mr. Lin,
why do you always mention someone irrelevant?
Nothing.
Yuan Shuai.
I was just being nice to you.
I didn't warn you.
If you keep doing this to me,
it won't be that easy next time.
Including your parents abroad,
they also run a company abroad.
If I want a company to go bankrupt,
it won't be hard for me.
Lin Taimo, I'm warning you.
Don't touch my parents.
Okay.
As long as you leave MH immediately,
and go abroad immediately,
never come back.
Also,
please shut up.
It is a vineyard,
in a youngFi.
I will see you again.
You may not let me close the door tonight.
But I think
you will welcome me inside,
and also
I have all the information in my hand.
Su Chang has it all.
Su Chang.
You and Qiao Na
have to figure out
all the progress of the project.
Everyone
has to continue
the unfinished work.
The last thing.
When the company
re-divides the project,
you can report to the new leader
for yourself.
You can go back to work.
President Yuan.
Boss, I'll go wherever you go.
I said go back to work.
Didn't you hear me?
What are you doing?
Go back to work.
General department.
General him.
Do you
Mr. Fan,
don't you like Mr. Yuan the most?
Qiao Na,
don't worry about it.
The most important thing now
is to transfer the work
that Mr. Yuan has left behind
and stabilize the mood
of the following days.
Someone will make up for Mr. Yuan's
lack of time.
All right.
Go back to work.
Okay.
Hello, Lin Fei.
You know Mr. He Gui better than me.
I want you to help me ask him something.
What is the reason
for the meeting with our head office today?
Okay.
I'll wait for your news.
Thank you.
Did Mr. Yuan resign
or was he fired?
How many crimes
did he commit?
Who would be so rude to the company?
Did he really resign?
Jiang Jun,
what do you think?
Yuan Shuai.
Where are you going?
Why isn't he answering my call?
Boss, are you okay?
Why didn't you answer my call?
Yuan Shuai,
I've asked someone
to help you with your case.
Don't worry.
Yuan Shuai,
why did you answer my call?
I'm begging you.
Don't scare me, okay?
Yuan Shuai,
no matter what happens,
I'll always be on your side.
I'm not afraid of you.
I don't want to see you.
I'll be standing behind you
in every situation.
I'm going to resign tomorrow
and leave with you.
Don't leave me
and leave me alone.
I'm sorry, Jiang Jun.
I'll explain it to you later.
Go home now.
Don't ask me anything.
Don't come to me.
No.
I won't give up until I see you.
Where are you?
I'll go to you.
Okay.
Come to me then.
You're making me anxious.
Don't come over.
Do you really want to know?
Of course.
I love you.
No matter how bad the situation is,
I'm willing to go on with you.
Go on with me?
If I tell you
that I'm a person who is corrupt,
and is a person who is selfish,
will you still go on with me?
Today,
Zhu You Yi came to expose me.
Tell meization of the
NOx Groupname.
I'm sorry.
Don't joke around, okay?
Can you tell me the truth?
Jiang Jun.
Since ancient times,
how many people can resist the temptation of money and power?
Especially in our investment circle,
after so many years, everyone will change.
I don't understand.
Everyone has desires.
I'm sorry.
I lied to you again.
I'm not the person who can bring you hope and light.
But it's okay.
Just take it as the last lesson.
What do you mean?
I booked a flight tonight.
I'm going abroad.
Probably...
I probably won't come back again.
We two...
are separated.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to break up with me?
You can think like that.
From Silver Moon
I am missing you
My only sunlight
Need you to be here
Why you had to leave
Please come back, my love
Standing in a rain
Xingyi.
I need your arms to hold
Look at my eyes and say it again.
Every night you hurry back to me
When winter turns spring
I'm standing next to you
To leave the flowers grow
Winter's gone so soon
Snow's stars fall from the sky
Enough.
I'm going to miss the flight.
Why?
Still not giving up?
Do you want a kiss
This year
To commemorate our short and funny love
Why you had to leave
Oh please come back, my love
Standing in a rain
I need your arms to hold
I pray every night you hurry back to me
When winter turns spring
I'm standing next to you
To leave the flowers grow
Why you had to leave
Oh please come back, my love
Standing in a rain
I need your arms to hold
I pray every night you hurry back to me
When winter turns spring
I'm standing next to you
To leave the flowers grow
I'm sorry.
So the principle of the interview today
The wolf stays
The sheep leaves
You and I are like ants and carps
You slowly climb
I roll down
Some people have short sight
Only know the benefits of seeing in front of them
So they earn fast and die fast
I'm different
I have a long sight
More interested in long-term benefits
I am a corrupt celebrity
Conspired in the wild
We two
Thank you
Liar
You lie a knife
I didn't do anything
Don't even know
This is the truth
I thought
I think I'm blind
Don't know how I feel
You walk so fast
Can't I just let you fly so high
Live on the sky's blue line
My heart's story lives on
You have nowhere to find
I think I'm blind
Don't know how I feel
Don't know how to heal
You walk so fast
Can't catch your light
You fly so high
Leave all the things behind
And our story lives out of nowhere
Jiang Jun
I will always be by your side
Always
Episode 16
Boss, Yuan Shuai has left China.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Okay.
After ten hours,
follow his phone and computer IP closely.
I got it.
You have no choice but to leave.
Stop calling me.
The laptop power in out of power 정도.
Now only one phone wide open can disturb me.
Frank restaurants before birth
Can't rag and take my change.
Are you marriages to me?
You're crying again?
Could it be Yuan Shuai
who dragged you into this?
How could she not be here?
Go find her.
She's gone.
She's gone abroad.
Why is she abroad again?
We broke up.
She probably won't come back.
What?
Did she dump you?
No.
Who brought you here last night?
I came here by myself.
By yourself?
No.
Yeah.
She didn't say she was going to the airport.
What are you talking about?
Where's my phone?
Wang Xiaochun,
did your brother contact you?
No.
My brother didn't contact me.
Okay.
Once he contacts you,
you must tell me.
Xiaochun,
what's wrong with you?
Li Li,
I'm going to the hospital.
I'm going to the company.
Why hasn't Xiaochun come to work today?
Did something happen to her?
What's wrong with you today?
You don't like her the most.
Why are you suddenly concerned about her?
None of your business.
Xiaoting,
I think you should get along with Jiang Jun.
Why don't you call him
and ask him what's going on?
I sent him a message.
He hasn't replied to my message yet.
Jiang Jun, you're finally here.
Are you sick?
Are you feeling better?
I'm much better.
Jiang Jun,
you're finally here.
Finally, someone came to help us share the burden.
Look at this.
This is what Mr. Yuan
looks like the first day he left.
To be honest,
I used to think
Mr. Yuan is a man of a hard temper.
He's a little cold-hearted.
But now that he's gone,
our Dinghai God is like a walking thunder.
All departments are here to trouble us.
The little fish and the little shrimp are looking for tea every day.
I just heard from Xiao Jing
that a new person might come to the company today.
And he's Mr. Lin's personal assistant.
There's a new person coming so soon?
Everyone, please put your work aside
and announce something to everyone.
I know everyone is busy.
Then I'll just open the door and see the business.
Next is the new employee I hired for the investment department.
Welcome him.
Mr. Du is also a person with a strong personality in the investment department.
I believe everyone knows a little bit about him.
Then,
all the business in the investment department
will be handed over to him.
I hope everyone can cooperate actively.
Mr. Du,
I'm sorry.
say a few words.
Okay.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Du Lei.
I'm very happy
to be able to come to MH
and work with everyone.
I hope everyone will pay more attention to the future.
Thank you.
Mr. Fan,
take Mr. Du to his new office.
Jiang Jun,
come here.
Sit down first.
Thank you.
These past two days,
I asked my colleagues from the headquarters
to ask about something.
Do you know
who gave the original letter of the report?
Who?
It's the new MH's ED.
Du Lei?
Don't you think it's too coincidental?
Yuan Shuai just left for a day,
and he's about to leave.
And it's said
he's a typical candidate for Lin Tai Mo.
Yuan Shuai's trouble this time,
I think it's very likely
that it's the two of them
working together.
What does this have to do with Mr. Lin?
You've been here for a long time,
and you still can't tell?
The head of the investment department,
Mr. Lin and Mr. Fan,
have never been in harmony.
Mr. Lin has already left the headquarters,
but suddenly returned to the investment department.
This means he's starting to make some moves.
The first day he came back,
he transferred Ma Xiu Ran away.
This is a threat to Mr. Fan.
Yuan Shuai,
Mr. Fan's capable leader,
was forced to leave.
You still think
all of this is a victory?
Yuan Shuai.
First, let's welcome
Mr. Lin's return.
You'd better know
what you can say and what you can't say.
I'll be back.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Du Lei.
I'm very happy
to be able to come to MH
and work with everyone.
I hope you will take care of me
in the future.
Thank you.
Thank you for your support.
Come in.
What?
Are you here to celebrate
my joining MH?
Why are you here at MH?
Why didn't you tell me in advance?
I just want to
give you a surprise.
I think I've adjusted it.
I can go back to the workplace.
And MH
is the top company in China.
I think I won't refuse
if they give me a job.
Okay.
Congratulations, Mr. Du.
Let's have a meal together.
Come on.
What's wrong with your face?
Nothing.
I'm a little allergic.
Mr. Du.
I already know
that you wrote the letter of report.
Since you're my friend,
I don't want you to
put the charges of MH
on Yuan Shuai
and be used as a gun.
Are you sure you won't try it?
The future is good.
I know him well.
He won't do
such a thing.
And I believe
he will do it for the rest of his life.
If you keep
going against him,
I can only stand on his side.
I have both the witness and the witness.
Why do you believe
he doesn't believe me?
It's a long life.
I will definitely
find out about Yuan Shuai
and help him figure it out.
And as a friend,
I'll give you the last advice.
I hope that
the gun will turn around
and you won't hurt yourself.
I'll go first.
I'm going to be happy.
I'm going to be someone.
Try to understand
Try to say goodbye a thousand times
You can tell me lies
You can make me cry
You know why
Never been so brave
I will run away
If it's what you want
What you like
I don't mind
I can close my eyes
I can stay behind with my time
Walk into your plan
Like I never knew you were not mine
Make you satisfied
Wear another mask
You never realize things I do for love
I think I'm tired
I think I'm blind
Don't know how to feel
Don't know how to heal
You walk so fast
Can't catch your light
You fly so high
Leave all the things behind
And our story
Leave all of nowhere to find
I think I'm tired
I think I'm blind
Don't know how to feel
Don't know how to heal
You walk so fast
Can't catch your light
You fly so high
Leave all the things behind
And our story
Leave all of nowhere to find