I'm going to make a
little bit of a
f
Like the
leaves that cut the fallen leaves
No.
Good morning.
Excuse me, what do you need?
All because of you
Why don't you tell me you're back here?
Yeah, I did
Yes
I got it
Thank you
Why do you suddenly think of
opening a flower shop here?
Maybe it represents a kind of
new hope.
Every flower
is a life that blooms again.
Although life is short,
when it blooms hard,
that kind of beauty
is the most beautiful moment.
I want to pass on this happiness
to everyone.
What about you?
Have you never been there?
Mr. Li,
are you going configured to work in our gentry office?
Everyone
is here.
You can rest assured,
Mr. Li.
Shall we go?
Sister.
I didn't care about anything
and wanted to get rid of you and Dad's agreement.
I thought that life
and that way of life
were not what I wanted.
In the end,
I just didn't have the courage
to face my true self.
So I lost.
And I lost in a big mess.
If you feel painful,
then choose a way
to live a happy life.
That's the most important thing.
Do you remember what I said
before I left?
To truly love someone,
you have to give him what he needs.
Instead of thinking that he is a fool
and think he is a fool.
To tell you just how I think of you.
Oh my my my.
Those twinkling eyes.
There's where I start from and then.
Hey.
If I could write a song for you.
So that the world will sing it too.
Maple sand ring.
The canneries too.
Or draw in one symphony.
I don't know.
So baby sing.
Sing this love song I wrote for you.
There's tea in foreign tea.
Stop it.
It hurts.
Yang.
I...
Coming.
What's wrong?
What's wrong with her?
I...
Come in first.
Come in.
Yijie.
What's wrong?
What's wrong with her?
Be gentle.
I went to check her body yesterday.
Uncle Yu said...
Said what?
What did he say?
I'm so worried.
Lu Wu finally has a baby.
I'm so happy.
I want to be a father.
That's great.
I want to be a daughter.
I want to be a father.
I'm going.
Congratulations.
Xiaochuan.
If you're so experienced.
Help me to get some money.
I have something to tell her.
What's the rush?
Go.
Okay.
You're so fast.
You too.
Come on.
What about our war?
The next war.
I'll go and clean up.
What's the name of this baby?
Li Shijian?
Or...
Li Kexuan?
Li Xibu Shijian.
Li Xibu Shijian?
Why don't you give it a longer name?
It's called Li Xiaochuan Xu Li.
Love's
I've actually tried to get General.
But I feel that he doesn't want to get married now.
Why?
Have you asked him?
No.
Then why don't you ask him?
How can I ask him?
I said.
General, I want to marry you.
It's okay if he agrees.
What if he doesn't want to get married?
At that time, we two
It's going to be awkward.
How to face each other?
Being questioned like this.
It's sure that a good relationship
There will be cracks.
When that time
I went to ask him to force marriage.
No.
I don't want to be his pressure.
Actually for me.
I and General
As long as we can be together
Marry or not
Just get that paper or not.
It doesn't affect our relationship.
Then I ask you.
Then why do you want to get married?
Just according to your logic.
Then the whole world will cancel
The marriage system is fine.
This person is different from person.
I and General
He doesn't need to get married.
This kind of thing to contract.
Actually, to be honest.
You are a coward.
I'm a coward.
You are enough for me to go to heaven and earth.
I can do everything.
Then you propose.
I don't.
Then you are still a coward.
Forget it.
You are a scientific weirdo.
Ordinary man.
You can't understand my thoughts.
Brother.
Such a long time.
Even I understand.
Women are the kind of animal
With a bad mouth and a bad heart.
Okay?
You are so smart.
How can you go to this place?
You are so stupid.
What do you mean?
In this aspect, brother.
Your brother and I
Are still people who have been through.
I know this kind of thing.
You can't understand.
So think about it.
At that time, I and Lily.
And Wang Cai.
We will definitely help you.
Right? Wang Cai.
Go. Go.
Go.
Is it too long
Not to clean up this bad boy?
Propose.
How about it?
Do you feel the power of life?
Sister.
Your pregnancy is not even obvious.
How can I feel it?
Feel it seriously.
How about it?
Is there a kind of
Holy power?
Do you like it?
Give birth to one.
In this case,
Our two children
Can we kiss the doll?
Don't talk nonsense.
We are not married yet.
And
Yuan Shuai and Xiao Chuan are cousin.
Our two children are also relatives.
How can we kiss the doll?
That's right.
You said you and Yuan Shuai
Have been together for so long.
When are you two going to get married?
To be honest,
I haven't thought about it yet.
No way.
You have to wait until you are old enough
Wait until Yuan Shuai runs away.
Are you happy?
He won't.
This blind confidence is called self-confidence.
What are you afraid of?
If he runs away,
I still have you.
Just a bottle.
I'm serious with you.
I'm not kidding you.
I'm not saying I won't get married.
Isn't this...
Isn't this because he didn't propose to me?
Am I going to run over and ask him
When will he propose to me?
Ask him.
Forget it.
Who will run over and ask directly?
Me.
And then?
And then
Woke up the next morning
I found a record on my hand.
It's your part now.
Pass it to me.
This may be also your skill.
Rehearse again.
Get married
Shall I really let me work on asking him?
you'll be always on my good side
Mr. Zhang
Are you okay?
No
Take a rest
I won't tell you
if it doesn't hurt
I can resign
Thank you
I have a message for you
Give it to Mr. Luo
Ok
Take it
Call him
If Mr. Zhang can't do it
he can't be involved
I'm sorry.
Welcome home.
Thank you.
Since you're back,
let's get to work.
Let's go.
I'll take you to the same place.
There's something you should know.
Huanfei Group plans to acquire the flashback printing
and has already given a price.
Do you think
we should buy the flashback printing?
We should.
The flashback printing is now 18 yuan.
We should buy it now.
The guarantee is probably 17% increase.
If we buy 3 million shares,
we can become the main capital.
The shareholder of Shimao Technology, Ma Nvke,
will become the new chairman of Yangsheng Electric.
He's a major investor.
If we buy it now,
the profit of the stock will exceed 442.
I don't think we should buy it now.
Why?
As far as I know,
the reason why the flashback printing was acquired
was because the three founders of the company
had internal power struggles.
The company's profit dropped for three consecutive years.
So I suspect this is a fake news
to deliberately raise the price of the flashback printing.
Okay.
That's all for today's interview.
The interview results will be announced to you
through a message.
How is it?
Is it realistic?
Yes.
In two years...
Wait.
There's a saying in Maya.
If you want to go back to a place,
you can bury the button there.
What's wrong with this place?
Look.
Anyway, the previous person did this
and stayed in MH.
Susan,
the board...
I say, Susan,
why do you always hang your phone
in my office these days?
What are you laughing at?
What's the deal with you?
There's a woman outside.
Boss, don't talk nonsense.
My wife is a woman.
How could I cheat?
Boss,
I forgot to tell you.
I got married.
I'm sorry.
No wonder.
You're like the second Chunyi.
I have to congratulate you.
Congratulations.
Boss,
you've been buying this diamond ring for a long time.
Have you not proposed to Jiang Jun?
Why are you so hasty?
You're even hasty than my mom.
No,
the diamond ring is not preserved.
But it will be in the
top of the diamond ring.
You have to take the initiative
and be decisive in this kind of thing.
Take our Xinxin for example.
She always said that she wanted to be
an independent
and new generation woman.
She said that
she would never get married
if she couldn't support herself.
But when I proposed to her,
when I took out my ring,
I said,
will you marry me?
She didn't say anything.
She just said yes.
She was so happy to agree.
Really?
Yes.
Let me tell you.
I've tried it.
It didn't work.
She...
She rejected you?
I rejected her.
It was a structural,
accidental,
planned,
and without a reason failure.
My dear boss,
why are you so down?
A single blow
can make a three-way fall.
What Lao Hua said is quite reasonable
and especially evil.
This kind of thing,
you have to do it with one blow.
You've done it.
You've never seen anything like this.
And you can't do it.
You're just a woman.
You have to do it with one blow.
You have to settle it.
Don't hesitate.
One blow.
Hello?
Honey, I'm going on a business trip.
Help me pack my luggage.
We'll meet at MH, okay?
But I have work to do.
It's okay.
I've asked the bookkeeper to pick you up.
It's not far from our house.
It won't take too long.
Okay.
Hurry up.
I have something to do.
First plan completed.
Come on.
Check if the light is on.
It's on.
Okay.
I'll turn left a little bit.
A little bit to the left?
Yes.
Is it here?
Is this okay?
Almost.
Okay.
Hurry up.
The first plan is done.
There's another one here.
The second plan is done too?
Let's go.
We can go now.
Hello, Chen Na.
What are you doing, Chen?
You asked me to wait for your file.
I've done it.
It's on my desk.
But I have something to do.
Ask Chen Yicheng to go to my office.
I'm talking to Chen Yicheng about the project.
Shouldn't you do
what you have to do now?
Are you a little bit arrogant?
Send me your address.
Send me the stuff in 30 minutes.
Okay.
Su Chang.
I have something to do in the office.
Can you take me back to the office?
Then send me home.
Okay.
Boss, it's up to you.
I'm sorry.
Come along.
Hurry.
Make way.
Come.
You pick my phone.
I'm sorry.
Baby.
Today I prepared
a cake for you.
Really?
I can't believe it.
I'm so hungry.
I'm full.
No.
Xia Wan.
Why...
Why don't you try it?
I prepared it for you...
The first time.
Now it's the second time.
The second time.
You must try it.
Come on.
The first time.
The second time.
The third time.
The fourth time.
The fifth time.
The sixth time.
The seventh time.
The third time.
You must try it.
Of course.
Xiao Jun.
Help me check
what this word means.
I've been looking for it for a long time.
No.
I've already done it.
Why don't you try it?
No.
When did you
close your eyes?
The third time.
The fourth time.
Gao Cai.
Come here.
Listen.
Your mom
is very smart.
Now,
I want to surprise her.
But I can't.
So we'll just leave it to you.
This time,
I'll count on you.
You know that?
OK.
Jiang Jun.
No matter how many times
in this life,
I'll definitely go.
Come on, Gao Cai.
See?
Take this ring.
Come on, Gao Cai.
Go.
Gao Cai.
You look so beautiful today.
Your state km
Definitely has better two- Often than never
Never because no one cares
Slippery
Always
You think
What I am
want more
That way
Your state,
For my mind
No.
I think
I feel that
my life is
very long.
But after being with you,
I feel that
my life is very short.
It's so short that I'm afraid.
I'm afraid that we don't have time
to do everything
we want to do.
If
I have the honor
to be your legal husband
for this lifetime,
then I'm willing
to use the remaining time
to help things
that aren't in your power
to protect you,
雙重你
and love you.
it's to show parents
that something is still going to happen
last night
told their kids
to come eat dinner with them
they said
They're so10 story
now like I'm getting older
I'm really growing up
no one自己 never taught them
they didn't couple
I realized
So I had in mind
I'm a kid
they wererop it
I've grown up
living the dream
I love you.
Jiang Jun.
I'm sorry.
Can't catch your light
You fly so high
Leave all the things behind
Hand up story
Leave all the love away
How about I avoid it for a while?
Boss, I wish you a successful proposal.
Sister-in-law, I wish you happiness.
What's this?
This?
This is a lucky charm.
This is a goddess agreement.
As long as you sign it,
you will never run away in your life.
By the way, there is this.
This is a private company agreement
registered in your name.
I thought about it.
If you don't plan to work in the investment bank in the future,
I will resign with you as soon as you say a word.
By then, we will build a family
that belongs to our own small company.
You go out to be the boss.
You go make money and go home to support me.
You want to make me work for you?
All the money I make in the future is mine.
Even your whole person is mine.
All right, all right, all right.
My whole person is yours.
Come.
Okay.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, Mr. Jiang.
You are here.
Congratulations.
Long time no see, Ling.
Long time no see.
I'm here to deliver flowers.
Thank you.
Congratulations, Ling.
You did it.
It's so nice to see you happy.
We are both
happy, aren't we?
Don't call her Jun Jun.
Call her sister-in-law now.
I won't.
I'll call her.
Bye.
Ling,
please
take good care of our Jun Jun.
Take care of him.
Or
even if you are the cousin of Xiao Chuan,
I will definitely take care of you.
Don't worry.
You are the one
who treats Xiao Chuan well.
Don't cry.
Come here.
It's still half an hour to five thirty.
We as a company
value the time we spend.
I've calculated it.
If we
rush to the Civil Affairs Bureau now,
we might be able to catch up
with the last batch of civil servants.
But
my household register is still with my mom.
I can't go to the Civil Affairs Bureau
without my mom's permission.
But
my household register is still with my mom.
Look.
What is this?
I, Yuan Shuai,
never fight
a battle without a winner.
Why is my household register with you?
The first time I went to your house,
your mom gave it to me.
Dad.
You...
What are you waiting for?
Let's go.
There's one last thing.
Come on.
Let's go.
I can't wait to
join in one symphony.
So baby sing
this little song I wrote for you.
Though it's I do
pray it's I'm ready to
and it is just the right now for you.
After this,
we're a real couple.
What are you laughing at?
Honey.
I can't hear you.
Look at you two.
You haven't seen each other before.
You're still taking pictures?
You're still taking pictures of your wife.
Look here.
One, two, three.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, bro.
I'm gonna take a shower.
Hello.
Sorry, I forgot my wallet.
I'll send you my WeChat number.
Okay.
Okay, send it to me.
Your name is Si Lin?
Si Lin.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just thought of two friends.
One is called Xiao Wen Jun,
the other is called Yuan Shuai.
So I met Si Lin again today.
I'll go now.
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
Jia Yuan Jie.
What's up?
I have something to tell you.
Can I not listen?
I haven't said it yet.
You don't want to listen?
Because every time you make this face,
you don't have any good things.
Are you sure you don't want to listen?
I'll listen.
Anyway, no matter what you say,
I, Jia Yuan Jie,
will be your life partner.
Only you.
I've been feeling a little uncomfortable recently.
I don't want to drive anymore.
I want you to find a driver for me.
Lend me to work overtime every day.
That's all?
Yes, that's all.
I thought it was a big deal.
Don't worry.
I'll definitely find you
a very good driver.
Don't you think
I'm being serious?
You're being dramatic.
I said you're usually
good at driving.
Why are you so stupid today?
You mean
you want me to be your driver
and give you a lift?
I...
I didn't say that.
That's what you mean?
Minister exposé?
Please, come and have a seat.
customize the push and pull of mine
Take photos
I want to be in the broadcast list...
to see the photos
You're the safest one so I'm your side.
You should hire me.
Really?
I'll keep you posted
I don't have faith in everything I hear
I'll make sure that everything is separated
Don't worry about it.
I understand
How about science and technology?
Hey, can you be serious?
Then science and technology?
You...
It's not impossible.
But I think
can you stay away from your Western culture?
This is not okay.
Then do you want to listen to my brother's suggestion?
Your brother's suggestion?
What is it?
My brother's suggestion is
our child is called Li Xiaochuan, Xu Li, the sister of love.
I'm with you.
If his handsome son is called
the handsome general's chessboard, then I agree.
Isn't it called Li Mi Hu?
I think you're like a model.
Then do you want to have this mask?
Mask can be a mask.
You have to think about the name of the child.
Think about the good things.
Or Li Ceng Wang?
Or Li Bian Li Dian?
Talk about him.
You're so serious.
It's really hard to get a name.
What's wrong?
I'm delusional.
I want to be a father.
I'm a dad now!
You're a dad now.
So what should we call you?
What should we call you?
Hmm?
What do you think?
I'm hisroomsend jeweller.
I'm his Class of precocious sports ready.
I'm your father,
and I·ll play kid's minds on you also.
Please.
Let's pack.
Thank you.
Students originally trained like this.
ilde alltså FEMA.
The way I see,
it seems the way he gladly disappears is just rushing forward and disappointing us.
Pero,
What are you pushing?
You're so handsome.
What are you pushing? Don't touch me.
Jiang Chuai.
You can tell me lies.
You can make me cry.
You know why.
Never been so brave.
I will run away.
If it's what you want,
what you like,
I don't mind.
I can close my eyes.
I can stay behind.
I waste my time.
Walk into your plan.
Like I never knew you were not mine.
Make you satisfied.
Wear another mask.
You never realize things I do for love.
I think I'm tired.
I think I'm blind.
Don't know how to feel.
Don't know how to heal.
You walk so fast.
Can't catch your light.
You fly so high.
Leave all the things behind.
And our story.
Leave all love nowhere to find.
I think I'm tired.
I think I'm blind.
Don't know how to feel.
Don't know how to heal.
You walk so fast.
Can't catch your light.
You fly so high.
Leave all the things behind.
And our story.
Leave all love nowhere to find.