-Oh, it worked.
-What?
Is that your phone, Asahi?
No, it's the one I picked up.
Is it recording?
Yes.
I think the camera is working.
Let's see.
There's no one in this town.
Everyone in Tokyo disappeared.
We're in Harajuku, yet there's no one.
Yes.
What's going on?
It's been five days
since everyone disappeared.
You're taking a video again?
What are you going to do with it?
To leave a record.
And why would you want to do that?
Someone might see it.
After that,
we met a certain person.
Then we were brought to that place,
and we work there now
Here?
Are you really going in?
It's pitch black!
Momoka?
Momoka!
Time remaining, 15 minutes.
Kill them all.
Jun…
I can't do this anymore.
We've gone too far to stop.
There's no way we can return
to our original lives
after killing so many people.
You heard me, right?
Anyone who goes against me is a witch.
Please shoot me!
Stop it already!
Let's end this game.
I…
I was confined by you guys
the entire time,
even when the murder occurred.
I'm sure you know
I couldn't have been the witch.
If you aren't the witch,
then there's no need to kill me.
Please cooperate with me
and search for the witch!
Arisu!
Stop it!
Hey!
Now I know.
The reason why you attacked Arisu,
even though
he's the only one with an alibi.
That's because you're the witch!
Arisu!
You…
Are you the witch?
Yes. I'm the witch.
Shoot me.
Do it!
-Shoot him!
-Aguni is not the witch!
This is a Ten of Hearts game!
A game that toys with people's feelings!
It's not a game
where you win by killing Aguni!
You're not the witch.
So why?
That's because you have another motive.
Another motive?
The one you killed
was not Momoka.
It was Hatter.
What?
I found out after I saw your eyes.
It was as if you had given up all hope.
Those eyes.
It was the same as mine that day.
Those eyes after I killed my friends.
You're not dumb.
Yet you wanted to kill everyone
right from the start.
That's not like you!
You must have had another motive in mind.
Ever since I came to the Beach,
I thought it was strange.
If you had these many firearms,
the militants would have gained control
over the Beach a long time ago.
Yet that didn't happen until now.
In reality,
you were not in conflict
with Hatter at all.
Didn't you both actually help each other?
You wanted to make sure
that dangerous people like Niragi
don't go on a rampage.
You tried to hold them back.
You…
Weren't you and Hatter
best friends in reality?
Then, why did you kill him?
For some reason,
you couldn't forgive Hatter
for what he did.
You wanted
to stop Hatter and his crazy ways.
You wanted your best friend
to regain his senses.
Will it continue?
Those games.
I…
will create a utopia here.
For those who have fallen into despair,
if we don't have hope,
we just need to make one!
This will be the land of hope.
That's impossible.
No.
We can do it.
Everyone here
is now one!
We shall unite and gather all cards,
and return to the original world together!
These guys.
They dared
to hide their playing cards from me.
Aguni.
As of today,
I will create a third rule.
"Death to the traitors."
What would you know?
Stop it!
What would you…
THIS WAY TO THE GAME ARENA
This way.
Congratulations.
How nostalgic.
This place looks exactly
the same as before.
I'm…
at my limit.
It's getting harder
to control Niragi and the militants.
Let's end the Beach.
End it?
All the members of the Beach
are immersed in the happiness
they found there, aren't they?
Returning to the original world
after we gathered all the cards
was just a big lie you came up with!
Let's end this.
Are you going to betray me?
"Death to the traitors."
The rules of the Beach are absolute.
There's no meaning to the Beach!
Let's stop this already.
We need to aim towards hope!
Stop talking like that!
Just where is the hope within the Beach?
A world like this,
where is the hope?
In the past,
I had trusted friends alongside me.
My hope in them…
was enough for me.
For a king…
There are times where
we have to make difficult decisions.
What a pity, Mori.
I was also someone who killed my friends.
I understand the pain in your eyes.
You killed your friend.
And so you wanted
to kill everyone at the Beach,
because they were the ones
who made your friend go crazy.
Your broken feelings.
The game master made use of them!
-That's why this is a Hearts game!
-Shut up!
Arisu!
If that's true, then Aguni just wanted
to kill everyone regardless of the game?
You're joking.
And we went along with that?
Just who is the witch?
I know who it is.
The identity of the real witch.
You can always see the game master's
characteristics in a game.
In a Hearts game,
it always makes a fool out of everyone.
NATURAL BOTANICAL GARDEN
Difficulty, Seven of Hearts.
A game of betrayal
where you play with people's hearts.
Everyone!
The one that needs to hide is the wolf!
Maybe…
there really was a way to end the game
without killing everyone.
A solution
where no one has to die.
But that's impossible.
We have to hunt down the witch
and burn them
in the Fire of Judgment, right?
No.
There's a witch candidate
that makes it possible.
It is possible…
if the witch is Momoka herself.
Momoka struck the knife into herself?
Yes.
If I were the game master,
I would come up with this idea.
What a joke.
I'm the witch!
You guys want to kill me, right?
Aguni is trying
to take everyone down with him!
Hey, Takeru.
Takeru.
Takeru!
The Beach made him crazy.
You guys made him crazy!
I'm the witch!
I know how to stop Aguni!
I'll get Aguni's attention.
Use the chance
to burn Momoka in the Fire of Judgment!
Arisu.
End this meaningless massacre.
Asahi!
Listen up, everyone!
I'm the dealer of this game.
It was a reverse grip.
Fingerprints with a reverse grip
were found on the knife.
This means
Momoka grabbed the knife herself
and stabbed it through her own chest.
She's the witch.
Why would she…
kill herself for a game?
Was Momoka really the game master?
That girl also said she's the dealer.
So were we just being toyed with by them?
But she's human, just like the rest of us.
Ordinary humans…
The two of them…
They might have been
controlled by someone else too.
Aguni.
Let's just stop this.
Don't let the deaths
of the innocents go to waste.
I understand
how it feels to kill your friends.
But we shouldn't take out our frustration
on those who are still alive!
We are still alive!
We're all facing despair head-on
and fighting until the very end!
Don't look down on those
who are still alive!
The fire is spreading!
Run!
-Move the body to the Fire of Judgment!
-Hurry up!
That hurt.
In the first place,
I should have just burned down the Beach
with the Fire of Judgment.
Niragi…
Niragi?
With this, I'll clear the game!
You guys…
I'll kill all of you!
Aguni.
Three minutes remaining.
There's no time!
You grab her legs.
-Get out!
-Hurry up!
Congratulations.
GAME CLEARED
CONGRATULATIONS
There is no place
where we'll always be safe in this world.
The North Pole, which the explorer saw,
was the true form of the world
without the illusions of civilization.
When all is done,
you simply return to the soil.
This land
is the true form of the world.
I'm thankful to this place.
Now…
I'm freer than I ever was.
I guess this is the end of our paradise.
Everyone died.
Those guys.
I can't forgive them.
Let go!
You can't.
They killed all our comrades!
I won't forgive them!
Let's stop this.
We're still alive.
That's all that matters now.
That's all.
Arisu?
Arisu!
I got it.
Arisu…
You're quite persistent too.
I started to think that it's pointless
to collect all the playing cards.
Say what?
But with this,
we've got everything
except for the face cards.
But I wonder what the management team
of the game wants us to see?
-Is it recording?
-Yes.
I think the camera is working.
What's this?
It's a video that Asahi left behind.
Let's see…
There's no one in this town.
Everyone in Tokyo disappeared.
After that,
we met a certain person.
Then we were brought to that place,
and we work there now.
We help with setting up the games.
Are you really going in?
People known as dealers help
to facilitate the games.
Sometimes we join games to act as taggers,
or we act as players
to confuse other players
or to help prepare the game.
But during the games,
we're also being monitored,
and we'll be killed
if we reveal that we're dealers.
Are you recording again?
What are you going to do if they find out?
RISK OF ELECTRIC SHOCK
Is this the dealers' base?
Stop!
Place your bets!
I got a ten-day visa!
Just hurry up already!
DEALER WINS
This is…
So they are the game masters.
Many people have died.
There was a girl
who was around the same age as us.
We prepared the game
according to how our superiors wanted,
then we joined the games
and made it so that the players die.
Because of us,
many people die every day.
I can't take this anymore.
We kill people,
win games, and earn visa days.
We get to live for another two weeks,
but I don't even know
how many people we had to kill for that.
I can't take it anymore.
Momoka.
This is all a dream.
It's all right.
We will wake up from this dream soon.
I want to end everything…
This is the place.
There it is.
RISK OF ELECTRIC SHOCK
Are you serious?
You actually found this place.
As expected
from someone I have high hopes for.
We meet again.
You guys.
Thanks to you guys, I have
all the numbered playing cards with me.
Thank you.
How did you discover this place?
It took me some time to realize
that this is actually
the route map of a subway station.
What happens
when we collect all the playing cards?
I thought I would know the answer
after I came here.
But there's only one thing I discovered.
They are not game masters.
Right.
Judging from the fact that
they were all killed after our victory.
They're humans like us,
and on top of that,
there's someone above them.
Just who could they be?
Who knows?
They might be aliens.
Or even God himself.
SPECIAL URGENT BROADCAST
Congratulations to all players.
What?
Interesting.
Mira.
With the exception of the face card games,
all of you have cleared
all the numbered games thus far
and emerged the victors.
A sweet victory you've grasped
by sacrificing numerous lives.
I wonder how many
of your comrades have died?
Try remembering…
those that were shot dead with a gun.
That girl you burned alive.
Those struck with the lasers
and those that drowned.
Those whose heads were blown off.
Those comrades of yours.
The despair you've felt so far
and those dying moments
that you can never forget.
I'm extremely touched!
All of you players,
we would like to give you a present.
Are you returning us
to the original world?
There will be new games!
Let's play games together.
You'll fight for face cards!
New games?
I don't dislike the idea.
We've still got many more
wonderful games prepared for all of you,
so look forward to it!
This woman.
Is she the game master?
I'd rather see an alien
appear on the screen.
The next stage will commence
tomorrow at noon.
Let's have some fun together!
So we have to fight again.
Yes.
But one thing is different.
We're finally seeing our target.
We'll definitely find our answers there.
Subtitle translation by: Qianni Lu