My Secret Romance
♫ Love love love is so good ♫
♫ Love love is so good ♫
♫ The sensual feeling of knowing ♫
♫  Even if you don't say it ♫
♫ Love love love is so sweet ♫
♫  Love love love is so sweet ♫
♫  Milky lattes and ♫
♫ pretty blankets that make you sleep ♫
Episode 5: The Secret of a Jewelry Box
- Secretary Jang, doesn't it feel like something is missing?
- Pardon?
I just feel like something is missing.
You ate Chinese food 32 minutes ago and said,
"I feel like my stomach is going to explode."
I did. I said that, but something is missing.
Then would you like to go to a restaurant on your way back?
No, I'm not that hungry.
Isn't there something more simple?
Are you talking about your company lunchboxes, by any chance?
You're right! I could eat a lunchbox.
But it's the weekend.
Yeah, it's me.
Mommy?
M-Mommy?
- H-Hello?
- Where did she go without her son?
Three Meals a Day Jerk
Hello?
Who was that just now?
That was me, I was sleeping when you called! I thought it was my mom.
But why did you call me?
I skipped some meals.
I'll send you my address, so come and prepare my meal.
Pardon? It's the weekend though.
Haven't you already had a few days off while I was on the business trip?
- Are you trying to slack off right now?
- Oh.
It's not that.
Don't be late.
I will arrive in two hours. If you don't come,
I'll consider it as you neglecting your duties.
Dong Goo, where did your mom go?
You better not misbehave.
- Be quiet and calm, and stay right by my side. Got it?
- Yes.
Let's go.
Does he sleep on the couch? Why does he act so frugal?
It's not like he acts humbly elsewhere.
I guess he doesn't have a bedroom.
Black pepper. Black pepper...
There is none. Wow, only the house is nice.
How can a chaebol (rich person) not have a cook?
Dong Goo.
Didn't I tell you to stay still?
Did the contents break too?
Should I open it?
Ring? Necklace?
No. There must be a different owner for this.
Lee Yoo Mi? Lee Yoo Mi?
Job complete!
I'm leaving first because I have something to do. Enjoy the food.
It's not like she's a snail bride.
(Snail bride is a Korean traditional fable about a man who marries a maiden who came from a snail shell but loses her after breaking a taboo.)
She said she threw this out.
What do I do if he wants me to compensate for it?
If he asks, then I should just deny it.
It looks expensive.
Because of that rascal...
What is this?
If you put a slice of bread in your mouth while cutting an onion,
you can cut the onion without tears.
- Remember this.
- Wow!
I'm going to learn well from you and cook something delicious.
For who? Your boyfriend?
It's a secret.
He said they weren't in any relationship.
There's definitely a diamond inside.
A huge diamond.
Joo Hye Ri's beef kebabs are done!
I would like someone in the audience to
- try this for the viewers.
- Me!
I volunteer to eat it.
Can you please help us then?
It's so salty.
It's s-salty?
I'm well known for being a bad cook, but
even I can do better than this.
Teacher, you are putting a lot of effort into this lunch box.
You went out to eat with the General Manager alone. By any chance..?
I sense that a lot of care and attention went into this lunchbox.
Care and attention? No way!
I'm just putting my conscience into his daily meal.
Our General Manager Cha will probably say...
Am I a kid?
That's not it, General Manager.
If that's not it, then what? What? What?
What? Are you asking me out?
What? Why are you saying that so out of the blue?
You see. It's not like you will make this kind of lunch box for just anyone.
- I see. This lunch box does have a meaning but—
- What?
That's not what I meant.
From now on, I forbid you from
making a lunchbox with faces like this.
Like I said, you should put more effort into the cafeteria meals, not these.
Okay.
- Why did you lie?
- Pardon?
My coat.
You said you threw it out.
The thing is, it looked so expensive that I couldn't.
Is that all? Because it looked expensive?
Yes.
Do you have anything more to say?
I'm sorry.
- Just know that thanks to me you weren't fired.
- What?
Do you think the executives came to the cafeteria because they had nothing to do?
You would have been fired on the spot if you hadn't selected the right meal plan that day.
I didn't know that.
Am I getting fired? OUT!! YOU ARE FIRED!! I'm doomed!
Should I beg on my knees? Should I tell him the truth? That jewelry box looked expensive. What if he asks for compensation?
Should I get a loan? What if I can't? Am I going to jail? I don't want to go to jail.
I'm so sorry.
I mean— thank you.
Did you really do something wrong to me?
No. I mean that from now on, I will make better lunch boxes.
I will do my best.
You can leave.
She had a cute side that doesn't even suit her.
You should try it, Father-in-law.
You personally made all of this?
Yes.
I recently joined a cooking program. I'm learning little by little.
Our Hye Ri is perfect from head to toe.
You are perfect as a daughter-in-law.
How does it taste?
What do you think?
Obviously, it's delicious since you made it.
That's a relief.
I'm worried about Jin Wook Oppa.
What about Jin Wook?
I know he's an extremely picky eater,
so I'm worried about the quality of the company lunchboxes he eats.
He eats lunchboxes as a meal?
You didn't know? Oh no!
It's good you are here. She said that you eat lunchboxes. Is that true?
Yes, she's correct. I'm eating them because of health reasons.
You rascal. Just get married then!
I'm not getting married to find someone to cook for me.
It's already late as it is. I want to
hold a sturdy grandson in my hand.
You're funny, Father-in-law.
Quit being an announcer.
Really? You're going to marry me?
You will do well if you pursue acting.
- Oppa.
- I'm scared of you now.
Me?
You don't get a free pass for everything just by acting cute. Don't just show up without notice and surprise me.
Also, don't make me into a weird person like you did last time in the cafeteria.
Do you have feelings for that girl?
What is there to feel?
You can't fool me, Oppa. I have great intuition.
There is something between you two, right? I can tell.
Joo Hye Ri.
I'm not good at playing hard to get, Oppa. No. I don't play hard to get at all.
I will act how I feel for you so don't tell me what to do.
I'm going to do whatever I want to.
Everyone can see that you're my man.
Why? Because I decided so!
When will she grow up?
I think she's sick somewhere (mentally).
Diamond necklace
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
What are you so sorry about?
Just this and that.
Do you still walk in and out of Jin Wook Oppa's room with those lunch boxes?
Walking in and out with lunch boxes is my job. That's all.
Fine. I will believe you.
Three lunch boxes a day, that's all. You should know your place,
Nutritionist Lee Yoo Mi.
Hold on a moment. Joo Hye Ri, can I get an autograph?
Of course.
- What is your name?
- It's Nam Joon Young.
I see. This lunch box does have a meaning, but it doesn't mean that.
No way.
No way!
Shit.
Yes? Dinner is almost ready. Why are you calling suddenly?
Okay.
Are you okay, Teacher?
I'm okay.
Why did it have to break right now? It's like a bad omen.
For the marketing plan for the Spring/Summer 2018 edition of Cool Bodies,
- if we target the men in their 20s and 30s—
- No.
She didn't see it.
If we show them
a famous sports team and collaboration—
- If she saw it... Well...
It's not that valuable. Why does it matter?
That pervert. Why does he have this?
Cha Jin Wook, don't tell me you kept this until now?
That's impossible. That's impossible. Impossible.
I will do it again.
What are you doing? Why aren't you doing it?
He hasn't skipped a meal for a while. Why isn't he eating today?
Three Meals a Day Jerk
You've deeply insulted me!!!
Up until yesterday, he definitely
used an ellipses after his status.
Why do I get bad feelings from these exclamation marks?
No way. Did I get caught?
Why won't you personally deliver this?
I have a lot of things to do today.
Please tell General Manager that I put even more effort into it today.
I understand. I'm leaving.
You're not wearing polka dots today. It was sexy.
Do you also match your undergarments?
I'm curious. I want to see it.
What is your phone number?
010....
I said I didn't feel like eating.
I told her, but the nutritionist still brought it.
Mistake
1. Mistake. Wrong.
2. Misunderstood. Misjudgment.
Is there a problem?
This girl...
Why? Why? Why?
I said I didn't feel like eating.
Why did you bring it when I told you I didn't want? Are you a brick? What's with your clothes?
The General Manager got angry as soon as he opened it.
What on earth did you write on the note?
I'm sorry.
Steak
Steak.
My mistake.
It was just a mistake.
So don't misunderstand? Seriously.
Mistake?
So you're saying you've identified one of my flaws?
This. This...
This... Why in the hell did I leave this in here?
What is so important about this?
Oh my gosh! That scared me. Those eyes.
What the?
Whose eyes are those?
- It's delicious!
- Your mom is on the TV.
Is he sleeping?
Where's Mom?
She went out because she had an appointment.
Have you seen Dong Goo's rabbit doll?
I searched everywhere but couldn't find it. Isn't that his favorite toy?
I'll have to search for it tomorrow. Give him to me.
One second.
Hello?
Where are you right now?
I'm home.
Come out. I have something to say to you.
- Right now?
- This instant!
I can't right now. Can we talk tomorrow at work?
- You can't? Fine. I'll come to you.
- What?
You don't even know where my house—
What's wrong? Who is it?
The grim reaper who is coming to get me.
How did you know where my house was?
Resume.
I searched when I first saw you
hoping that I was seeing a hallucination.
That's my precious personal information.
You live at a place like this?
What is it you wanted to talk about, General Manager?
This is yours, right?
So this was at your house. It's my brother's.
No. It's my dog's.
So it was there.
This was in my study.
Did you go in there?
The thing is—
Stop beating around the bush and tell me specifically.
What did you see in there?
I'm sorry.
It's a jewelry box. I bought one that looks the most similar.
I know the one you have is worth so much more but
please accept this and calm down.
You opened it, right? You opened it and saw what was inside, right?
The size was pretty obvious.
Whoever wears something that big
- Will probably have neck pain!
- What?
Wearing?
- The bigger the better, right?
- Bigger?
This girl really speaks her mind!
You're really scary. Did you have fun? Huh?
Did you enjoy toying with me after you found out?
Toying with you? My mind was frazzled. It was a tough time.
You want me to believe you?
I know I accidentally touched something I shouldn't have, but
you were the one who asked me to come to your house!
If you hadn't asked me to come over on my precious weekend, I wouldn't—
Stop!
What? What about it? Just because I saw that,
do you think I would be taken aback? It's not even important.
You should stop.
Who are you? Move.
I can't. Did you not go home yet, Hyeon Tae?
Who is this bastard?
As you can see.
Is this for real, Lee Yoo Mi?
You are the general manager of the company where Yoo Mi works, right?
I don't know what the problem is but you should talk about business matters at the office.
You should go home now, that's enough.
Let's go.
Relax. Relax.
Seriously.
Who is this girl?
I found it.
I left this here.
- Did you come back just for your game system?
- Yeah.
Why were you acting like that before?
I...
Wasn't I really cool? Like the main character in a drama?
You're out of your mind.
You were in a tough situation.
Just say you have a boyfriend if he bothers you.
I'll be your boyfriend.
Forget it. It's not like that.
- I'm tired. I should sleep. I'm leaving first.
- Okay. Go on in.
Yeah, well.
There's no way she would have stayed single since then.
I thought she was his former teacher's daughter.
He told me not to get the wrong idea.
Stop beating around the bush and tell me specifically what you saw in there.
Why are you acting like this, Lee Yoo Mi?
It's not like you're in any relationship with Three Meals a Day Jerk.
Make sure to eat three meals a day with Joo Hye Ri,
and eat and live well.
Cheers, cheers!
I'm telling you I'm right.
They're really going to start dating after the drama production is over.
Oppa, I've had some drinks with coworkers.
Can you come pick me up?
Call your driver.
You're acting very arrogant, Cha Jin Wook.
What did you say, Hye Ri?
Ah, Writer! Producer!
Cheers!
- Cheers.
It's good. It's good.
How's the casting proceeding for the next week's interview?
My head hurts because of it.
The CEOs are all so busy.
- CEO?
- Yeah.
There is no one that is handsome,
capable, and eloquent.
I'll invite someone for the interview.
Really?
Do you have someone in mind who you can ask?
I do. We are very close.
Goodnight, Lee Yoo Mi.
You're the first person to ask me if I'm alright.
I have never seen a girl who cried because I asked if she was alright.
It's also a first, that a crying girl looked pretty.
Come in.
I have prepared a salmon steak lunch box for breakfast.
Take this.
Okay.
Put this away immediately.
Also,
don't ever mention this to me again.
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
I think you can let go of my hand.
I'll take my leave.
Who was that guy yesterday?
Is he your boyfriend?
If he bothers you again, just say you have a boyfriend.
Do I have to tell you about my personal life?
Does he live there with you, by chance?
I don't have to answer this because it's a personal question, right?
You don't have to.
But your taste in men isn't that great.
He looked like a total slacker to me.
Everyone in our neighborhood considers Hyeon Tae to be a total gentleman, okay?
He is very caring.
He's on a different level than a certain someone who's only slick on the outside.
Who? Slick?
I'm busy, so I'll be leaving now.
That...
She wanted me to hear that, didn't she?
Who is she calling slick? This woman...
Seriously. Why do you keep making the lunch boxes look cuter and cuter?!
Judging the appearance of my best friend?
He should just treat his own girlfriend well.
What are you mumbling about? Are you not going to work?
There's too much work to do. Why don't you come back right away after giving his meals?
It's not like you're dating the general manager.
It's exciting to have an office romance. It's a turn on.
General Manager Cha is mine.
I'm sorry.
What is that?
Oh, this? Joo Hye Ri recommended this on "The Best Pupil of Cheongnam-dong."
Do you want to try? You really don't tear up.
I'm fine.
Stop talking.
Is there a reason for you to spit all over the food? What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Your patterns are becoming flashier.
I'll take that as a compliment.
- What's this book?
- Oh, this?
I'm going to read this while I wait. "Miss Good Morning."
Someone recommended it to me.
On the Road to Europe
You must be the director where Yoo Mi works. Please go back home.
Everyone in our neighborhood considers Hyeon Tae to be a total gentleman, okay?
So he's a petty writer, I see.
Do you know him?
As you ordered, I made a dinner reservation at the Royal Department Store after your meeting.
- It's on the VIP floor–
- Cancel the reservation.
Excuse me?
I'm coming back after my meeting.
I'm going to eat my lunchbox for dinner.
Director Cha, you should return my book.
This f*cking guy.
Director Cha.
He said I didn't need to make his dinner today, so what's with this sudden message?
Dinner is just an excuse to fulfill his real objective.
Nutritionist Lee, we're heading home first.
You all worked hard today.
Someone almost filed a complaint saying that we ran out of cucumber kimchi.
Where has your mind been lately? Huh?
I'm so tired of this.
Did something bad happen to Chef?
It must be her spinal disc again.
Disc?
It's hard to stand for a long time. She won't get surgery
because of work, and she's the head chef, so she can't quit.
So please be understanding, Nutritionist Lee.
- I'll get going then.
- See you tomorrow.
- Goodbye.
- See you.
Oh, right. His dinner.
This is a Korean-style Nasi Goreng (Indonesian fried rice).
I modified the recipe to get rid of the unique scent to suit your taste.
Good work. You can go now.
Yes.
Do you want to go to Han River with Dong Goo tonight?
Deal! I'll be done with work soon.
Three Meals A Day Jerk
Why is the proportion so small today?
Prepare another dinner right now.
Right now?
I'm in trouble. I don't have enough ingredients.
These are rice balls with minced meat.
You ordered food so suddenly, I used what I had—
Okay, you can go.
Yes?
Hey, why aren't you here yet? I thought you were done soon.
I'm going crazy because of that Three Meals a Day Jerk.
He asked me for additional meals multiple times already.
Hey. He ate two dinners already. Does this make any sense?
- Is he a human?
- OMG.
Anyway, I'm running late after caring for his appetite.
So, we need to cancel our plans to go to the Han River.
Then should I pick you up?
Really?
Will you pick me up?
I'll call you back later.
Is someone coming to pick you up?
Um, no...
But, what brings you here?
- I'm hungry.
- What?!
I'd like...
ramen.
♫ What do you think is the same?  ♫
♫ Love is the same  ♫
♫ When we meet, my heart goes thump thump thump  ♫
♫ When we brush our teeth, thump thump thump  ♫
♫ When we’re apart, it’s an even bigger thump  ♫
♫ What else is the same  ♫
♫ with you and me?  ♫
♫ I wanna know you  ♫
Congratulations on your reinstatement.
– President Kim Dong Ho of Daebok Group
♫  Not your blood type or sign ♫
What Braderella left behind ▶▶▶
#He'dForgottenButRemebered #3YearsLater #ThisEmbarrassingItem
#ThinkingAgain #Unforgettable #ThatNight
#AfterThatDay #OurJinWookIsDifferent
Shall we get out there?
#It'sGettingWeird #HeSeesBraPadsWhereverHeGoes
♫ It’s getting weirder, my heart ♫
♫ You’re not even my ideal type  ♫
♫  It’s getting weirder, the way I see things are changing ♫
She's talking about me, isn't she?
She called me slick. This woman...
Seriously. And why are the packed meals getting cuter and cuter?
Huh? What's with these meals? Huh? I told you not to make me cute...
♫ Beautiful  ♫
#SlurpsUpTheFood #I'llEatItAll #I'llEatMultipleTimesTonight
This is making me more full.
So what?
There was no reason for that woman to stay single all this time.
Yeah, that's right.
#ShouldICallYouOrNot? #Timid #I'mLonely
My Secret Romance
I told you I can't trust the food you make. Let's get back to work.
I've never been insulted by an offer to eat together.
What? Why would you eat with him?
Just ten times. No more, no less.
Do you know how it is out there? This is also a part of my duties.
You've gotten the wrong idea.
I'm not his girlfriend. Just a friend.
You can stop making my meals.
Is this writer Jeong Hyeon Tae?
Don't be sick.