Here you go.
You should look after the kid whom Coach asked you to.
Who took him in should be looking after him.
If I finish your homework, you have to stop being mad at me
No.
Happy Birthday, Aom.
Where are you going?
Who is that?
What are you doing?
None of your business.
Didn't you just want me to follow you here?
Don't be shy.
Women these days do this...
stepping outside just to make a guy follow you.
What kind of man is so full of himself?
What kind of girl spies on a male dorm?
None of your business.
I'll teach you how to catch a guy.
But a woman like you probably knows.
Boys aren't comfortable around women who are talented and smart.
Join the cute club like Aom.
She always hits the mark.
Assault and battery.
I got you this time.
You didn't listen to a word I said, did you?
Yes, I was.
Come to think about it...
you're cute, attractive and well-dressed.
Want to go out with me?
Liar!
Don't think that I won't know your trick.
I've used this before when I want to shut someone up.
Scare them off and they will disappear.
I'm glad we've cleared this up.
Run along now.
Since we're similar people, let's be friends.
I'm Min.
Wan. Nice to meet you.
Since we are friends, let's celebrate.
Celebrate what?
Why don't we go to that place behind 7 Eleven?
It opens 24 hours. Have you been?
No.
You've got to try.
I'm going to climb down first. See you in front of that shop.
Go away.
Be careful when you climb down.
Don't get yourself killed and become a ghost that haunts the dorm
I don't mind haunting the female dorm
Just go,
you psycho.
Go!
Sorry!
Thank you
Working hard as an academic consultant of the swimming club, huh?
You know me?
Yes, I do. More than you think.
Where did you come from?
Just finished some homework.
Why do you have so much homework?
Let me have a look.
Who are you?
You don't have to know who I am. Just remember my face.
Now I know how feisty she is.
I will excuse myself now.
I didn't see you earlier.
Where did you go?
I was going to have dinner with that dog
The dog didn't show up.
Dinner with a dog?
Jib, tell the teacher I'm on my way.
Do you remember that nerd?
Are you okay?
Your bag...
Let me help you.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Hello?
I'm fine.
I'd like to say I'm sorry.
But you didn't watch the road.
Hello?
You're okay, right?
I'm taking off now.
Hope you're okay. Bye.
Good morning, Rector.
You shouldn't have gone through the trouble of coming here
You could've asked me to meet at your office.
Last year, the swimming club didn't join any external races.
Yes, but this year we plan to...
Your boys are quite rowdy.
How so?
I got a report saying there's a competition within the club,
which escalated to a physical attack.
I think there is a misunderstanding.
I don't think so.
The student body sent me a report with evidence
The swimming club may have to be disbanded
Hey.
Yesterday, I said 'nice to meet you'.
But it wasn't nice for you to meet me.
This will not end well.
Had you known Coach before?
Don't let me find out later.
What are you doing?
You woke up early.
Hello, dad.
I moved all my stuff last night.
I share a room with my roommate.
I met Coach Tee.
He is even cooler in person than on TV.
And tougher, too
I'll adapt.
I'm going to take a shower now.
Bye.
Had you known Coach before?
Of course.
How?
He...
Move.
He was so famous.
A national athlete with an endorsement deal
He was so cool. Totally my idol.
Didn't you know that your dad was a celebrity?
Enough
Weren't you born then?
So, you hadn't really known Coach
Not in person. He was just famous.
Why did he ask me to look after you?
How would I know?
Don't let me find out later.
What are you doing?
I'm going to take a shower.
But I was going to
I'm sorry about last night.
What was she doing here?
Is she a teacher's daughter?
Who are you talking about?
That one.
The one.
The one whom you hit while she was riding a bike.
Stop fantasizing about her.
She is unique. I can feel it.
She's the one.
What are you doing here?
You don't usually practice during lunch.
Butt out.
Why didn't you wake me up?
I did. Loudly. You wouldn't wake up.
Nothing I can do.
That'd better be true
Sure is
Enough, Pan. Don't make a scene.
You can sleep anywhere, even a locker room.
Why did you tell him?
Well... I'm going to class now. Bye.
Come here.
What are you doing here?
Just chilling by the pool.
Chill by the pool?
Are you nuts?
If you have nothing to do, go home.
I don't like to sit with a stranger.
If you can sleep in the locker room, I can sit by the pool.
It's my business.
Well, I don't like it.
I'm a senior in the club. You have to obey.
No.
No? Come here.
Want to sit by the pool? You got it.
I'll take you to the pool. To the bottom of the pool.
Guys!
Have you seen my new hair?
How does it look?
It took me a long time to style it.
Guys, I'll style it like this every day.
Do you think it looks good?
This will my signature hairdo.
Hey there.
Looking good.
Dressed up for a date?
Don't touch it.
I am curious what the hair will look like in water.
We shall test it then.
Let's do it.
No, don't!
Come on!
Jerks! My hair!
You've been repeating this word all day.
You want to go to the pool, yeah?
Go! Jump!
What are you doing?
Same stupid prank you're trying to do. Hypocrite!
Come here!
I'm not going down.
Sit!
This jerk woke up at 7 AM to style his hair.
He turned up the music so loudly.
Don't! Don't!
Put went down. Apo went down. Waii went down.
Now it's your turn.
Go!
No!
Come here!
Coach Tee!
What coach! I don't believe you.
Coach is here!
What are you doing?
Are all of you here?
Waii, where are you going?
Why? Have your meeting.
You must join as well.
No. Tell Kluay what I need to do.
No! You must stay.
Stop being such a child.
Our club is about to be disbanded
I'm late today because I went to the Finance Department.
I asked them to hold off any payment to the swimming club.
The club will be disbanded in two months,
as discussed previously.
There will be a district-level competition coming up soon.
Our swimmers may win a medal.
The swimmers have had a lot of opportunities in the past,
but didn't win anything.
The club should have been disbanded a long time ago since ...
since... a while ago.
Why the swimming club?
There are other poor performing clubs.
They have too many privileges.
Our budget is better spent doing something else
The running and football clubs also occupy the field.
The field could be more useful to others than the pool.
Wan, it's a good idea to check out the field.
Otherwise, some may say we're only gunning for the swimming
I'll check out the running club this evening.
This is how you take care of a newbie?
Who shot these? Who?
You were kidding, right?
You said that just to get Waii to stay, right?
Quiet!
Our club is about to be disbanded for real
Now can you stop playing and get serious?
Who's this?
Who is this guy?
Sawasdee krap. I am Fah.
Fah is our academic consultant that I told you via Line yesterday.
You replied with a heart sticker.
That must have been an accident.
What does an academic consultant do anyway?
I do homework.
Apo, how's your first day at the dorm?
It was okay.
Are you sure?
Yes, I am.
What happened to your hand?
I got burned by boiling water.
It's getting better.
Waii did it, didn't he?
It was an accident. Nobody did anything.
Waii told you to say that, didn't he?
You got wet today because Waii bullied you, right?
This is outrageous.
You said it like you'd know everything.
I am your father.
I raised you. I know how childish you are.
You oppose to anything that I tell you.
No, Coach. It really was an accident.
And we were just playing today.
It was fun for me.
Not everybody find it fun.
Take a look.
This is how you take care of a newbie?
Who shot these?
That's not the point.
The point is you being such a baby.
Who shot these?
Let me assure you that
Waii didn't bully me yesterday.
It was an accident.
It's true, Coach.
I can attest that Waii didn't bully Apo.
Me too
Me too.
Waii didn't bully me yesterday.
Okay. Thank you, everyone.
Waii, I'm...
As a coach, I'm sorry.
Going forward, you have to be careful.
We are being closely monitored by the student body.
All the pranks you do on another must be toned down
Others may think that our club is full of bullies.
Fah.
Yes, sir.
From now on, do not do homework for your friends.
Take care of the documents and practice schedule for the members
No more pranks or bullying
It's all Sung.
You too.
More importantly, our club has not earned
reputation for the university for years.
And it's my fault.
Luckily, the Rector gave us two months to make a name for ourselves.
In the meantime, our budget has been put on hold.
Put on hold?
Yes.
If we haven't made any mark during these two months
our club will be disbanded.
The rest of us will need to work very hard
It will be easier for Waii to win
No. You guys should compete.
I'm not ready.
Not ready or not willing to sacrifice.
I will for the team,
not for the benefits of a certain someone.
You think I'm doing this for myself?
Prove it, then.
Just resign,
and I will compete.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
You are the admin of Waii's fan page.
What are you doing here?
Nothing.
Nothing?
Don't even, Tootsie.
F... you
You're going to leave this on Waii's bike? It will disappear.
Let me help.
That is for P'Waii.
Don't. I'm your senior.
Consider this a payment for me to shut up
about you stealing Waii's bike.
I wasn't stealing. I just...
Are you calling me a liar?
Guard! Guard!
Guard!
I'll get you back, douchebag!
What did you say?
Hey, aren't you going for a swim?
No.
Are you having a period?
Since Coach told us the news,
Why? Do I hardly smile?
you haven't smiled once.
Don't you know it?
Do you think Put will be able to get Waii to compete?
I don't think so. I'll bet you 300 baht.
I think he can. I'll bet you 500 baht.
Are you bluffing me?
Up your game
Winner buy me lunch, okay?
If you're with me, you'll get free lunch for sure.
Oh yeah?
Are you really not going to compete?
In the district competition.
I cannot do it.
Are you still hung up on that?
It's still not over?
No way.
How can he say that I'm not willing to sacrifice while he...
Stop it. You shouldn't dwell on this anymore.
I must apologize to you all.
Forget about it. We are the same team.
We are in the same boat.
If you're not ready, it's okay.
We will be ready.
Thank you all of you.
Sure.
Shit, what time is it?
It's almost 5! Shit!
Runners are not as hot as swimmers.
Do you dare?
Let me take a look.
Where did you come from?
This is a good picture.
We didn't have to pose.
You were in a hurry.
And it's for this non-sense.
I think she is cute.
Who are you talking about?
Does your voice have to be that high?
Where did she go?
You both!
Excuse me.
It's you
I have a question.
Where is the library now?
Go straight and turn right.
Thank you.
Wait, my friend has something to say
Well...
I like...
the bike that you rode the other day.
The brake seemed good
Okay... Thank you.
I'm taking off. Thank you.
You like her bike, huh?
The brake was good?
Isn't it strange, though?
What is a high school student doing in the uni campus?
You shouldn't be surprised.
The uni campus is full of hot guys like me
What's wrong?
I may have sprained my ankle.
I hope you're not injured now.
The district sports competition is coming up.
I know
You should rest. I don't want you to get worse
Please tell Coach that I'm going to see the doctor today
Sure, I will.
Take care.
I'll continue with my run.
Okay. Thank you.
1 2 3 4. 1 2 3 4.
What are you doing?
Are you looking for...
Checking out guys?
The president of the club himself.
You disappeared last night.
I'm sorry. I didn't want to bother someone.
And I'm sorry that runners are not as hot as swimmers.
You're a runner.
No surprise you come and go so quickly.
Are you done here? Please leave
This is preserved for athletes only.
When did you get here?
Are you from the student body?
Yes.
Min, take care of them.
Can I take some time to observe the activity?
Coach, didn't George tell you that I'm going to see the doctor?
Are you badly hurt?
Not that bad. I just want to go for a checkup.
Do it after practice.
Yes.
Now that I'm here, I'd like to see the club's performance
We have our schedule
We can't just organize a race like that.
I didn't mean the whole club. Just you vs me.
Wan is a former runner.
Do you dare?
Hello, P'Waii's fan page followers.
I'm the admin.
Here we are in the locker room.
Is P'Waii's locker this one?
No.
I found it!
Kluay!
I'll get back at you.
Is yours getting smaller?
It's sleeping.
I meant your leg. What were you thinking?
Don't even, you small banana.
Hardly. I'm a big banana.
Stop it. I don't want to see it.
I saw the admin of your fan page.
And?
He wanted to give you some snacks.
To make sure that it's not poisonous, I took a bite.
So, are you alive and well?
Waii!
Stop!
Tough crowd
I'm alive and well.
The snacks are delicious.
Is Apo still practicing? It's been a while
He must have swum out to the Gulf.
You don't have to wait for me.
I have something to do.
You're not coming home together?
No.
See you later.
The snacks that P'Waii like.
You sick banana.
I'll be done in 10 minutes.
Working hard?
Are you afraid you will not get to compete?
I'll be out in 10 minutes.
I'm telling you, stop it.
You must obey me as your caption.
Thank you.
You're hot-tempered.
Unlike your dad.
Why should I be like my dad?
What?
Did you see your dad compete in SEA Games?
The host fans booed him but he kept his calm.
He didn't say anything but win a medal afterwards.
He was so good.
Looking at you closely, you look like your dad.
You may be a better swimmer than him.
Why don't you compete?
If you want to be like him this bad, why don't you compete?
I'm not.
wait...let's talk
sit down.
I don't know what it is between you and your dad.
But please reduce your ego and open your heart.
Our club needs you.
Our club?
Do you think of yourself as one of us?
Yes.
Coach Tee accepted us. I practiced.
I will compete as a representative from our club.
What have you done?
You have no clue, yet are good at articulation
You are not the one without a clue.
Do you know that although people say okay
deep down they want you to compete.
No one will like it if the club is disbanded.
But you won't do anything outside your comfort zone.
Don't teach me.
I will do anything to keep our club going.
How? Tell me.
I have plans.
Tell me.
You don't have plans.
Show the world that you're the son of Coach Tee,
the real Olympics hero.
Shut up!
Are you okay?
I'm okay. It doesn't hurt.
I'll get some medicines.
I went to the pool to give the snacks to P'Waii.
The snacks I prepared in the afternoon got stolen by that jerk
Not only is he ugly, he is also greedy.
Who are you talking about?
Answer me.
Try to escape.
You have it coming
How did you get in here?
I got lost.
You, little Tootsie. You're in for a world of hurt
Where did he go?
Waii, what's wrong?
What happened?
Let go.
He just answered you. His wrist hurts.
What are you doing?
Help you take this off.
Raise your arms. Come on.
Slowly.
Easy, right?
Thanks.
Huh?
Are you deaf?
You should practice saying that word.
You'll be saying it a lot.
It will take a while to heal.
Are you okay? I'm sorry.
I'll wash this.
It's okay. I'll do it.
No, I'll do it.
I'll do it.
What are you doing?
We could get past it yesterday.
There is no reason why we won't get past it today.