Kiss. Kiss. Kiss.
Okay, if you kiss this boy on the mouth,
we'll stop this right away.
From now,
Don't ever mention his name.
Do you have feelings for P'Pan?
You've been practicing for so long.
Don't you want to go somewhere?
Let's go.
The club's trip
starts now.
Yeah!
What a view!
If there was no drama,
I wouldn't have a chance to come to your home.
The view is so great.
You're right.
It's beautiful
and chillaxing.
You can choose any spot
you'd like to claim.
Can I have all?
I call dibs on the bed.
Hey,
Where's your manner?
A bed should go to the owner.
That's okay.
I can sleep in the tent.
I want the bed, too.
No, cannot
This is my room.
No boys allowed.
You want to separate by gender now?
Just in case nong Namkhaeng shows up.
Then,
If she comes,
I dare you to put your foot on my face.
You face already looks like a foot, dude.
Oh yeah, dude.
Hey, Kluay
Sit down now.
Why?
I'll put my foot on your face.
P'Pan.
Namkhaeng!
I found a patient here.
Fah,
come here.
Well,
Min is also coming.
You can come with him.
Nah
We just arrived.
Come here.
Come and join us.
The view is gorgeous.
Master Apo!
P'Dew.
I miss you so much
You're here!
Yes,
just arrived with my friends.
Who's this?
Have you eaten?
Want some mussels?
I have plenty.
Want some mussels, guys?
I want two.
Three for me.
I want four.
What about you, Apo?
No,
I'm not into mussels.
Have you tasted it?
They're fresh and sweet.
Try it.
No,
the smell is too strong.
Smelly mussels.
No, they're not.
Smell it again.
Have you washed them?
Of course.
They're all clean.
Yummy ice cream?
Can I try again?
Yes, it's good.
Where did you get it?
My ice cream?
Let's go
I can take you there.
Come on.
Come.
I'll be back.
Here you go.
These are all mine.
What about me?
you can share with me.
Where are you going?
I don't want the mussels anymore.
I'll get ice cream with Waii.
All mine.
This is mine,
that is mine.
Where are you?
Okay, I'll come down.
Where are you going?
Downstairs to see the guys.
Are you avoiding me?
What am I supposed to do?
I don't want to talk to you.
Are you still mad at me?
I'm not mad.
Fah!
Fah, it's not what you think.
Listen to me.
What are you doing?
He's not doing anything.
How can you say that?
I saw it.
Can you leave Fah alone?
Stop ruining his life?
Guys,
while we are here,
I'd like you to forget
the fact that our club is about to be dissolved.
Do you understand?
Hey, Wait
If you hadn't said that,
I would've forgotten all about it.
Yeah, you're the one who reminds us.
But if our club is dissolved, what will we do?
He just told us to forget about it.
This is just a scenario.
Let's discuss this
when we're back.
Then,
Let's play a game.
Sure,
I haven't played an online game for a while.
Not that kind of game.
What then?
We're going to play
It's Truth or Dare.
The number you're trying to reach is not available.
Hey, Fay!
Kan,
I thought you had left.
I had some errand here.
Where are the others?
They've disappeared.
I cannot reach any of them.
Maybe they went away to regroup.
I would appreciate a little heads-up,
not this...
Sorry.
It's fine.
Waii has changed so much.
That's true.
How good is that?
Good?
Yes,
He's calmer
and listens to others more.
When did this happen?
I don't know.
I'm taking off.
Got this thing to do.
Kan,
even if there's no club, find the time to meet up.
Why do think there will be no club?
The Rector...
What's up?
Nothing.
Wait for good news on Monday.
See you.
Truth or Dare?
How?
You haven't played it, have you?
The rule is simple.
You can ask any question and
the player has two options:
to perform a dare or
to answer the question...
and you must be honest!
You guys will suck at this because you are liars.
But I'll excel because
I always tell the truth.
Let's start.
Really?
Come on.
Sure,
I want to play it, too.
Got a question to ask.
Who wants the first question?
Not me.
Don't look too far.
It's you.
You're right next to me.
Why did you look around the circle?
Kluay,
Truth or Dare?
Truth.
No,
change your answer to Dare.
It will be fun.
If I said dare,
you'd ask me to do some weird shit.
I don't want that.
Fine.
Let's hear the question.
Do you like Achi?
That made him choke.
Hit the spot.
I like...
him not.
I just like to tease him.
There's nothing.
Why did you do that?
You can ask only one question.
Do you want to answer it?
I don't know.
Why did you do it, though?
I just wanted to stop those guys.
I thought doing that would put an end to it.
It did.
It ended everything.
You're an idiot.
What's that, Tomboy?
I meant
you're an idiot
like me.
I understand.
We are
all idiots.
We don't know how to express our feelings.
Does it mean that all the times that you bully Fah,
you have good feelings toward him?
Ass,
but it's true.
What?
Fah is my friend, too.
Oh,
just friends.
Let's continue with the game.
I'll spin the bottle.
Just the right person.
Sure,
I'll do it.
Fah.
Truth or Dare.
Waii may want to come home.
You've been in the swimming club for a while.
Why have I never seen you in the pool?
I'll do it.
P'Tee.
Hey,
how was your shooting today?
It's good.
Where will it be posted?
The shoot is for a fashion website.
I'll send you the link when it's done.
Thus,
You don't have to go away for days anymore, do you?
I'm not sure.
It may good if I'm not here.
How can it be?
Waii may want to come home.
I don't think so.
There's no point trying.
But Wai...
I told you...
we will not discuss this anymore.
I'm sorry.
Give me a hug.
Fah,
Truth or Dare.
Truth.
A man of truth.
You've been in the swimming club for a while.
Why have I never seen you in the pool?
That's true.
I'm changing to Dare.
You didn't even take the time to think.
My story isn't that interesting.
Dare should be more fun.
Fine, whatever you're comfortable with.
I dare you to dip yourself in the pool
for five minutes.
That's easy.
Come with me.
We can do it together.
Just five minutes in the pool
will be good on this hot day.
Isn't it too easy?
Anyone can do it.
What about five shots of liquor?
It'll be funny.
No,
just dipping in the pool for five minutes.
It's easy, isn't it?
Yeah,
I want to see you get wet as well.
Ever since you joined the club,
I've never seen you swim.
This is frigging nonsense.
Come on,
it's for fun.
Fah,
jump in.
It's so hot now.
You'll be cool and chill in the pool.
Trust me.
Jump!
Sure
Go.
Or do you have any problems?
Hey
One, two, three.
He's not going.
Let's get him drunk.
Come on.
Stop.
That's not the rule.
The rule is you do the dare.
If you don't, you need to answer
why you wouldn't go into the pool.
I'll do it.
Fah,
let's just answer it.
No.
Let's jump in then.
Stop,
what the hell are you doing?
Hey,
calm down.
It's just a game.
You may be enjoying this,
but Fah isn't.
You know that he almost drowned because of you.
What else do you need?
Almost drowned?
What happened?
Fah!
I'll check on him.
Fah, stop!
Do you think
I'm a clown?
What the hell are you talking about?
A clown who's afraid of water,
like a dog.
No one thinks you are.
At least
I don't.
What happened?
Where did Min come in?
Ask him.
He's dying to tell you guys.
I don't just want to know.
I want to hear it from you.
I want to know you more.
Why?
Because
You are my good friend.
I..
I want to be a good friend to you.
You should tell this kind of stuff to someone.
Sure,
I'll tell you a joke.
Kluay, Fah, and you
used to go the same school, right?
Yes.
We were friends.
What kind of friends?
Take it easy.
I've taken it easy for years
because Fah asked me to.
But you won't quit.
What do you want?
I want you to know the truth.
I already do.
But I don't.
What happened to you guys?
I'm so confused now.
You want everyone to know the truth.
Three years ago.
Min!
You're still late even on this important day.
I'm late because
I queued up to buy this for you.
Don't tease him.
He's really miserable as is.
In his lifetime,
he never gets to taste shrimps.
Kluay!
I've eaten them.
That's how I know I'm allergic.
Good,
it's nice to know you can't do something.
You're beating me in the swim race.
The race for scholarships is coming up.
I need to up my game.
I have this for you.
Here.
This is good.
P'Mai gave it to me.
Try it.
Who's P'Mai?
A senior who coaches my swimming.
Anyway,
try it.
It's awesome.
Thank you.
That's good.
Help!
Fah!
He got a rash all over.
What's wrong?
What did you give him?
Fah.
Leave him alone.
Kluay,
don't.
He planned to sabotage you.
I don't want to have anything to do with this kind of person.
It's best we keep to ourselves.
Dude!
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
Where do you sleep?
Next to you.
If your intentions with Waii are good,
don't do this.
Fah has never swum since.
No,
he cannot swim since.
You earned a scholarship here
and be the president of the running team
that everyone likes,
even though you stepped on your friend to come on top.
I didn't know.
I didn't plan this.
You didn't plan to take the scholarship?
That's right.
I didn't take it.
I gave it up.
You gave it up?
Yes,
I took an exam to study here.
Yeah,
Kluay.
If he'd gotten the scholarship,
he would have been in our club.
He may have asked to switch the club.
No, he can't.
They would recall the scholarship.
Since that happened,
I hadn't touched the pool either...
until I found out that
Fah is in the club.
You got transferred here.
You just talked it up to make yourself look good.
I didn't get transferred.
I asked to be transferred.
The running coach
asked me to take a rest,
so I asked to be transferred.
Because, right now
I understand Fah now.
What it feels like
when you can't do what you love.
I just want to help him.
Who are you?
Who are you to help?
Even the doctor can't help.
I think he can.
Kluay,
if you want Fah to be able to swim again,
let Min work this out.
You said it's a joke,
but it's not funny.
No?
You almost drowned!
Well, who knows..
I used to love swimming.
Look at me now.
I'm afraid of it.
And,
Why did you join the club?
I thought
if I spend some time near it,
I'd get used to it.
Where did that come from?
What are you doing?
Try it one more time.
Try what?
Come on.
No.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
No, you'll set me up again.
I won't.
I promise.
You are setting me up right now.
No, I'm not.
Hold on.
Hello, Namkhaeng.
Hello
Can you hear me?
Bad connection.
You can go home and call her.
Don't try to get yourself out of this.
Someone needs to be in the pool.
And,
Won't your girlfriend be mad
if you don't take her call?
You're right.
Hello, Namkhaeng.
I can't hear you.
Thanks.
For what?
For helping me set up the tent.
I'm sleeping here,
so I need to set it up.
Why don't sleep in the house?
No,
It's already full.
Where do you sleep?
Next to you.
It's a small tent.
It won't work.
It will if we sleep close to each other.
It's not a problem.
I'm just guessing.
I hope it's not right.
I don't want to see you do a wrong thing,
especially with Waii.
If your intentions with Waii are good,
don't do this.
Stop confusing him.
Did you call Fay and
tell her that you're here?
No.
She'd be so worried.
She didn't know that
I came here.
Why didn't you tell her?
I forgot.
Call her now.
Hey,
I know
what you're doing.
Let's just say it.
Waii, I...
You want me to lose the phone bet, don't you?
Huh?
You can't fool me.
Too bad.
Come in.
Come on.
I know.
Ready for bed?
Hey,
tomorrow,
Your turn to cook in the morning.
What are you going to make?
Hey!
What are you doing?
Sleeping.
Why do you sleeping so close to me?
I like it here.
What's your problem?
What's yours?
You don't have Coach Mai to obsess with.
So, now you're bothering me.
Sung,
this is not about Coach Mai.
Yes, it is.
When she's not around,
you come back to me.
What if you found a new girl?
I'd be dumped like a dog.
No!
For me,
you've always.
Hey,
Why you guys are going to bed so soon?
Fah,
how are you feeling?
I'm fine.
Just very tired.
Fah,
where are you sleeping?
There's an empty spot next to me.
You can have it if you want.
Fah!
It's okay.
Let me.
Fah,
where are you sleeping?
None of your business.
When are you going to stop running away from Min?
I'm not.
I just don't have anything to say to him.
Fah.
Stop talking about it.
Aren't you going to go somewhere?
I'm not in a hurry to go anywhere.
I'm here to talk to you
now
Don't you want to call Namkhaeng?
Shit,
I forgot.
You can run from Min
but you can't run from me.
Where are you taking me?
Come on.
No.
Come.
Namkhaeng,
have you been afraid of something terribly?
Yes,
lizards
What do you do to get rid of the fear?
Why do I need to get rid of it?
I'm afraid and that's that.
It makes your life difficult.
You have to be cautious all the time.
Wouldn't it be better not to be afraid?
No,
I accept my fear.
When I see a lizard,
I scream at the top of my lungs.
Pan,
who are you talking to?
Do you remember that red swimsuit?
Good thing I didn't buy it.
I wouldn't be wearing it anyway.
Do you think Fah and Min
will work it out?
Are you taking an interest in your friends' drama?
You usually don't.
I just want to know
what Fah would do
when he finds out the truth.
You mean you want to know
what you have to do.
What's this got to do with me?
You've found out the truth about Kan and Coach Tee,
and now you want to know
how to forgive them.
Are you taking a walk in my mind right now?
I also know
you want to see Coach Tee.
Wrong.
Come and talk a walk again.
Have you called Fay?
You mentioned Fay again.
If you miss her,
call her.
I thought you should.
All my life
I've been doing what I should.
Now I want to do what my heart wants.
Go for it.
Whatever it is,
I'm sure you will have thought it through
that it won't hurt anyone.
You know first-hand
what it's like
to be hurt.
Get away, I want to sleep.
Don't laugh.
I'm sorry.
"I'm sorry."
"I didn't mean to."
You said it all.
You think of me as your friend?
Waii,
no.
Waii.
Where did you go?
I went shopping
for the breakfast.
It's my turn.
I should help.
No,
I can do it myself.
Who exactly has changed?
You said that I changed when I met Coach Mai.
Yes!
I did
and I know.
I apologized to you.
What about you?
When can you be my friend again?
Hey,
wash the vegetables till they're clean.
Sure,
I'll use dish soap.
Hell no.
Who uses dish soap to wash vegetables?
You can smile now.
I know how to smile since birth.
Is he gay?
What a shame!
I hate the bastard who hurt my friend.
The bastard is P'Kluay,
the worst swimmer in the club.
Pan!
The rule is not to use your mobile phone.
You're going down!
Give it to me.
Pan, wait.
Guys!
Pan, I beg you.
Sung!
Stop it.
You'll look beautiful.
The color is just right.
Stay still.
Let us put the flower behind your ear.
How does he look?
All finished.
Sun-dried banana.
What the hell did you write?
What are you laughing at?
Pan has been using her phone.
Why isn't she getting punished?
Do you have evidence?
If I get away...
You will soon.
See?
He's my friend.
In half an hour.
30 minutes.
Let me go.
I'm begging you, let me go.
Don't complain, Kluay.
You messed up.
I only used the phone for a minute.
Why are you checking the phone?
It upsets you emotionally,
and physically.
Fah,
I'm your friend.
Yes, I am.
Help me then.
Pan,
let's write on Kluay's body.
Will this work?
Should we tie Fah to a chair?
He won't run.
Trust me
and you'll see.
I'm sorry.
"I'm sorry."
"I didn't mean to."
"I had no idea."
You said it all.
I remember.
Fah,
I think Min was telling the truth.
What are you saying, Kluay?
He didn't set you up.
He declined the scholarship.
Huh?
Your plan is working, Apo.
Oh?
You don't have to forgive me.
I just want you to know the truth.
Fine.
Now I know.
Fah!
Why are you smiling?
He doesn't seem like he wants to forgive you.
Nothing.
It feels good just to tell the truth.
If he stays mad,
I'll have to accept.
Why do you look so happy?
I think you look beautiful.
This look suits you.
You've found your way.
Congrats.
Min, you jerk.
I'm going to get you.
Stay away from me.
Your nipples are so red.
It'd be nice to get some sun.
Min, I'm begging you,
help me.
You really like
your Coach Tee, huh?
I told this to you once.
I wasn't kidding.
And you wanted to be friends with me
because of him.
Wait,
seriously?
No.
What was I supposed to do?
He told me to stay with you.
So, you wouldn't have
if he hadn't told you.
Did anyone tell me
to be here?
I want to know
why you've done all this.
Is it because you think of me as your friend?
Yes,
all of you are my friends.
It's been more than half an hour.
I should free Kluay.
Umm..
"We will shine brightly when we help others. Do good."