ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND PLACES ARE FICTITIOUS
FILMING OF CHILD ACTORS DONE
UNDER BROADCASTING GUIDELINES
LEFT TURN SIGNAL
PEDESTRIAN SIGNAL
Do you want to live at my place?
Stay at my place.
EPISODE 7
-Mr. Noh?
-Yes.
Have you eaten anything?
There's stuff in the fridge.
Help yourself to it.
I don't have anything at home. I feel bad.
Should I bring you anything?
No worries. It's okay.
I'll just order in.
Let's treat
each other's places like our own
and make ourselves comfortable.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Goodbye.
This fridge is cute.
So is the stuff inside it.
I guess she likes toast.
How has she been living like this?
I guess he doesn't have a toaster.
Do you want to live at my place?
Stay at my house.
And I'll stay at your place, Ms. Kang.
Oh, I meant that we should swap places.
What?
I don't really have any good memories
of my current place either.
Of course,
it's not as bad as your situation.
But it will be uncomfortable for you
because there's nothing at my place.
That's okay.
Plus, our units are in the same building
and are the same size.
So their values are nearly equal.
There's nothing complicated about it.
We're just swapping places
until either of us sells our apartment.
What do you say?
Then how about a month-long stay?
"A month-long stay"?
I've actually often thought about
getting out of there immediately.
But I couldn't just leave without a plan.
-Just get out of there right now.
-Right now?
-You don't want to?
-It's not that.
It's just that this wasn't planned.
They say plans change without warning.
Right.
Since when has life ever gone as planned?
It's so empty here.
I'll either have to move that
or put something in it.
I'll bring my own chair next time.
Oh, wait.
I don't even have a pillow at my place.
I should keep it down
at this time of night.
I'll just do it tomorrow.
This isn't good.
Right, I don't have a watch.
Should I call…
A text message is probably better, right?
"If by any chance you're…
still awake…"
Hey.
Good, you're still awake.
I'm on my way
to grab my charger from my car.
What about you?
I thought you might need a pillow.
Thank you.
Since you're here,
why don't you grab whatever you need?
-Then if you'll excuse me…
-Okay.
Here we go.
If I go up now,
she might feel uncomfortable.
Then I might as well…
I need to fix that motion sensor light.
Ms. Kang, you're not back, are you?
It's me.
Why am I tiptoeing in my own house?
Let's see here.
Which one should I wear?
Right.
This one is the best.
I'm leaving now.
No, wait! It's me!
-Ms. Kang, it's me.
-What?
I'm sorry. I didn't know you were here.
Are there bricks in that bag?
Of course not.
I came for this.
A new tomorrow has just begun.
Right. We usually call that "today."
Oh, that's right.
You're right.
I…
The motion sensor is broken.
Okay.
So you…
You can just keep this one on instead.
I see. Okay.
I should've told you earlier.
-I'll be off, then.
-Okay.
Right.
Okay.
Good night, Ms. Kang.
-Okay.
-Bye.
UNDERWRITER KANG HAN-DEUL
ARE YOU HOME?
HOW'S YOUR HEAD?
ACTUARY NOH KI-JUN
IT THROBS A BIT,
BUT IT DOESN'T HURT
AND YOU?
DID YOU GET WHAT YOU NEEDED?
BY THE WAY,
WILL YOU BE USING THE TOASTER?
I COULDN'T FIND ONE HERE,
SO IF YOU DON'T USE IT…
NEVER MIND, I WAS JUST ASKING.
YOU CAN USE IT, MR. NOH.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE POLITE
ABOUT YOUR OWN TOASTER
I WON'T USE IT.
I'LL BRING IT TO YOU LATER.
OKAY. MESSAGE ME ANYTIME
IF YOU THINK OF ANYTHING YOU NEED.
AND THANK YOU FOR HOLDING
THE ELEVATOR EARLIER.
OKAY. MESSAGE ME ANYTIME
IF YOU THINK OF ANYTHING YOU NEED.
WILL DO. SWEET DREAMS.
No.
WILL DO.
Great, it's my pillow.
The images carved on the moon
are not a fairy tale about a rabbit.
They're craters
formed by fallen meteorites.
Most meteorites that fall toward Earth
either burn up
while entering Earth's atmosphere,
or if they survive,
they land in the ocean.
Some cosmic disasters…
leave scars that remain raw and vivid
even after thousands of years.
I need to get a bed in here right away.
Let's just sleep.
Good morning.
ALARM QUESTION
How do I…
I thought you might need this.
I really do.
It looks like you slept really well.
Here, I'll take that.
Get ready for work.
I'll wait for you downstairs.
Crap.
Ms. Kang, over here. Get in.
How did you sleep?
Was the bed comfortable?
-I slept well.
-That's good.
Thank you for earlier.
I know you purposely came over
to help with the alarm.
I couldn't send
Jeon-man over there, could I?
Hey, this is my favorite travel mug.
How did you know?
Really? It just caught my eye.
I guess we have similar tastes in things.
Try this and see
if we have similar taste as well.
This is really good.
When did you make this?
Ms. Kang, take your time eating.
Okay.
-Let's go.
-Would you like some coffee?
-Sure.
This coffee is great.
Really? Is the flavor strong enough?
It can be stronger.
-Okay. I'll take note of that.
-Okay.
You're coming to work together now?
What's going on between you two?
We'll head up first, Ms. Jeon.
Let's go.
Coming to work together means
they're more than just colleagues, right?
What do you think, Mr. An?
Well, they must've carpooled here.
How did you know it was me?
I recognized your scent, Mr. An.
You're really cute right now,
you know that?
They say being cute is all it takes.
Just a second!
-Sorry.
-Excuse me.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Can we have a quick chat before going in?
I'm sorry, Ms. Kang,
for putting you in an awkward position.
It's okay.
It's not just because of you, Mr. Noh.
Then should we
put a name to our relationship?
If open-ended questions are too hard,
we can go with a scale of 1 to 5.
Please answer the following
by saying "up" or "down"
to describe our relationship.
Yes, ma'am.
Number one, neighbors.
Up.
Number two, work colleagues.
Number three, friends.
Up.
Number four…
Number four is…
Down.
I'm sorry. It's somewhere
between three and four,
but I can't think of a good name for it.
Since our relationship is so evasive.
Then let's call it a gray zone.
Gray zone?
Yes.
-That's genius.
-Do you like it?
For now.
Good.
Then, let's keep our relationship
in the gray until we find our number four.
Okay. Then…
I'll be "gray."
Then I'll be "zone."
And stay right next to "gray."
Hey!
We're in trouble.
-Why? What is it?
-What is it?
Ms. Woo Seon-hee filed an insurance claim.
-What?
She's filing divorce papers!
-Hold on a second.
-Look into it now!
She isn't on the first-to-sign-up list
or high-risk group list.
She's our latest applicant.
She can't file an insurance claim
because of the 90-day waiting period.
-Right.
-You're not getting it.
Don't you think I know that already?
What about the zero percent divorce rate
during the six-month term?
It doesn't matter if they divorce now
or 90 days from now.
What are you going to do about this?
They signed the divorce papers
and are at the courthouse right now!
Now is not the time
to be sitting around like this!
-No, that can't happen!
-No, sir!
-No!
-Get moving!
You don't have time to grab your scarf!
Don't make me come after you!
Get going right now!
SUPREME COURT OF KOREA
Where could they be?
Let's check the submission counter
and then split up to look for them.
But we don't know what they look like.
Just grab anyone
who looks to be 70 or older…
I think I found them.
Where?
This is what you wanted.
I gave you what you wanted, got it?
Thanks.
You never once did what I asked until now.
The least you can do is apologize.
You're such a stubborn woman!
Exactly.
So don't live with an ignorant woman
who doesn't get you.
Go find a young, intelligent woman
who is sweet and affectionate.
I'm going to live freely from now on too.
Freely?
Did you say freely?
Goodness. Calm down
before you actually pass out.
Don't work yourself up out here.
Let's just go home.
What's the matter with her?
Honey, is there food at home?
Let's eat now if your blood sugar is low.
Forget it.
You don't even like restaurant food.
Stop acting like you care all of a sudden.
I guess they've already filed
the divorce papers.
We're doomed. This whole thing is doomed.
Let's go.
Get out. Just get out.
I don't want to look at you.
What are you going to do about this?
Tell me what you're going to do!
I'm so stressed.
We still have four weeks left.
Ms. Jeon.
Hello, ma'am. I'm sorry.
Darn it.
This is a serious situation, ma'am.
A gray divorce doesn't just happen
after 10 or 20 years, ma'am.
That's why I have
all you intelligent people here.
Put your heads together
and come up with something.
We have to change her mind
within the four-week waiting period.
-Let's have a meeting.
-Yes, ma'am.
How can we possibly change her mind
in four weeks?
Why aren't you coming in?
-You'd better follow me in!
-We're coming.
All of you milling around,
get inside right now!
-Yes, sir.
-Let's go.
POLICYHOLDER PERSONAL INFORMATION
She's not on the first-to-sign-up list
or high-risk group list,
so maybe the divorce was impulsive.
The thing about divorce
is that it's never impulsive.
On what grounds?
You'd understand if you'd been divorced.
It's especially true for gray divorces.
They've probably gone through
all sorts of hardships together.
Well, damn it. Good for you.
Fine, let's move on for now.
How did she slip through
the high-risk group filter?
It could've happened
if she hadn't intended to divorce.
They filed the divorce papers together,
but you're saying
they didn't really mean it?
And on what grounds?
After they filed the papers,
we saw them go home together,
like it was the most natural thing to do.
As if they were needle and thread.
They kept talking about divorce,
but it didn't seem like
it had sunken in for them.
Freely?
Goodness. Calm down
before you actually pass out.
Honey, is there food at home?
Let's eat now if your blood sugar is low.
You're right.
How does that make any sense?
Why would they file for divorce
if they don't intend to…
Wait, do you think
they're after the payout?
If so, they'd have considered
the waiting period before filing.
No.
Right. In any case, this is weird.
The fact that she even signed up
for divorce insurance at her age is weird.
How did she even know
about divorce insurance?
That's what I'm saying.
That's because…
-What the heck?
-Jeez!
What?
Who are you?
Calm down.
-Who's that?
-Things have been happening so quickly
that I forgot to introduce him.
He's a junior colleague
who works in insurance.
Calm down. Come back and sit down.
Hey, say hello.
This is our senior managing director.
And these are members of the team.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Nam Chang-hee,
and I sell insurance in Ssangmun-dong.
-I look forward to working with you.
-Nice to meet you.
-Take a seat.
-Are you okay?
Sit down. We're short on time
and need to finish this meeting.
Ms. Jeon, please continue.
Why is he here?
The thing is, since we have
a couple of rejected cases--
Mr. Na.
I'd rather hear it straight from him.
Yes, ma'am. I'm sorry.
Mr. Na asked me
to take care of the two cases
that were rejected.
So?
So I did.
Did what?
I'm the one who got Ms. Woo
to sign up for divorce insurance.
No way.
TEXT, TEXT, TEXT
ENERGETIC AND EXCITING SINGING CLASS
Send me a text, text, text
-Just me
-Please send me a text
-Are you curious about what I do?
-Then send me a text
-If you want to know what I'm thinking
-Then you should…
Just a moment, please.
Let me dry off her tears
before we continue.
Ms. Woo is a student in my singing class.
We were singing an upbeat song
when she started sobbing.
Thank you.
Are you feeling okay now?
My friend of 30 years sent me a text
saying her house was going to get seized.
How could I refuse to help her?
The bad person here is the one
who schemed to exploit me.
But why does he only blame me
for what happened?
It turned out that she was
a victim of a phishing scam.
Luckily, she didn't lose any money.
But her husband gave her
a lot of grief over it.
He keeps saying
I'm stupid or that I'm a fool.
He says I'm frustrating and belittles me.
Just because he's the breadwinner,
he only sees me as his wife
who cooks and does laundry.
I'm nothing but a servant.
If I could, I'd get divorced right now.
Ma'am, don't say that.
That's more unfair to you.
Think of how long you've put up with him.
Unless you have something like this.
"Divorce insurance"?
Of all the people to sign up--
I thought you just needed the numbers.
Right.
Why me?
I'm terribly sorry, Ms. Jeon.
But even so,
it doesn't make sense to get divorced
over a phishing scam.
The phishing scam was a trigger.
This has been a long time coming.
That's right.
Mr. Young-kyu is very stingy and stubborn,
and he looks down on Ms. Woo all the time.
But Mr. Young-kyu
isn't the only one to blame
because Ms. Woo
has made bad financial decisions.
She's very kind,
so she agrees to act as a guarantor
and lends money to people.
Oh dear.
Goodness, the damage is too deep.
Noh Ki-jun, what should we do?
You can fix this, right?
Since we know the gist of the situation,
Ms. Joh and I will go
and see Ms. Woo Seon-hee.
Okay, good.
Okay, then Mr. An and I
will meet the husband.
-No, you can't meet Mr. Young-kyu.
-Why not?
If he finds out Ms. Woo
took out a policy, he'll lose it.
He'll scold her for being naive
and falling for a scam again.
And if he finds out
it's divorce insurance,
it'll make him want to get divorced.
I understand.
If I were to find out my wife
took out a divorce insurance policy…
The thought of it alone is horrible.
Come on, sir.
That hasn't even happened. It's okay.
It's not like the old woman
actually did it.
You punk, you can't call her an old woman.
My apologies. I meant Ms. Lee.
Mr. Na.
I'm sorry, Ms. Jeon.
We'll put off formally meeting
the husband, then.
Let's get a feel for the situation first.
How?
Mr. Na, you have pent-up anger.
You have a herniated disk in the neck.
As for me…
I threw my back out.
ONSAEM KOREAN MEDICINE CLINIC
-They must live upstairs.
-Right.
But where is…
Look.
I think that's her.
-Shall we go?
-Let's go and check.
Ma'am!
Nobody shops for groceries
and cooks every day like you.
Dr. Park is so fortunate.
-Enough with the flattering.
-Yes, ma'am.
By the way,
where is Dr. Park off to these days?
He's been going out often.
-Really?
-Yes.
He's so energetic
it's like he's turned back the clock.
He has gotten younger.
He's always been like that.
This is why you should put more effort
into your appearance too.
You should dress better
as the wife of a doctor.
Regardless of their age,
men prefer younger women.
Stop talking nonsense.
Yes, ma'am.
Why don't you come in
for a warm cup of tea before you go?
-What?
-Follow me.
Just follow me already.
-Let's follow them.
-Okay.
Mr. Na Dae-bok,
the doctor will see you now.
DIRECTOR PARK YOUNG-KYU
Hello, sir.
-Over here, please.
-Yes, sir.
Goodness, that's…
What's wrong with your complexion?
You're still young,
but you look so exhausted.
You're truly an amazing doctor
as they say.
You can tell just by looking at me
for the first time?
I need to examine you to know more.
-Give me your hand.
-Yes, sir.
Your solar plexus is blocked by something.
Doesn't your heart race occasionally?
Yes, sir. It does.
You don't sleep well,
and if you wake up early, you feel dizzy.
And no matter how long you sleep,
you still have a headache.
Yes, that's right.
You have pent-up anger.
Why are you so stressed all the time?
You're right, sir.
To be honest, I got a divorce.
I think that's why I feel this way.
Divorce?
You couldn't have made a better decision.
Your stress levels will drop then.
No, that's not true.
When I walk into a dark house after work,
it feels empty and cold.
But you save on electricity.
After I have a quick meal alone,
I wonder why my life turned out this way.
Go to a soup kitchen.
During election season,
they provide special meals
served by assemblymen.
But what if I fall sick or…
You need some acupuncture. Get up.
-Acupuncture?
-Get up.
-But…
-Take off your jacket.
But I've never had acupuncture before.
Give me this and come here.
-Excuse me? Sir, just a moment.
-Come here. Just lie down.
Nothing beats acupuncture
when it comes to releasing pent-up anger.
Goodness, Dr. Park.
How old are you, sir?
How are you so strong?
It's one of the benefits of divorce.
I don't have to waste my time arguing,
so I'm full of energy.
Isn't that a drawback though?
If you're full of energy
but lonely at night--
Streaming services!
Just watch that.
Streaming…
Streaming service.
I'll release the Hegu point,
so just relax and take a nap.
You truly are an amazing doctor.
Hello?
Goodness, Ms. Choi.
Really?
Are you free right now?
I'm just really excited, that's all.
Okay, I'm on my way right now.
A woman?
The nurse will remove
the acupuncture needles when it's time.
That hurts.
Jeez, that stings.
Oh, my back.
My back hurts.
Darn it.
-Yes, sir?
-Jeez, just…
Just what, sir?
No, we're still waiting.
Something urgent came up,
so no more consultations today.
Sir?
Jeez, just follow him!
-Hey, follow him.
-Hurry!
Right, I had something to tell you.
It's good I ran into you.
But what's with the face?
It's nothing, ma'am.
No, it's definitely something. What is it?
Her father is in the hospital right now,
but they want to discharge him
because of unpaid medical bills.
He's about to be sent home
without receiving treatment.
Goodness. You poor thing.
I think we can manage somehow
if we sell our current house
and move into a smaller one,
but there aren't any listings available.
Why don't you ask her?
Stop talking.
She doesn't have money like that.
Here.
What is this?
Actually, I've been holding on to that
to use as a security deposit
for when I find my own place.
Your own place?
Why are you looking for one?
I have my reasons.
But I think you need this more than I do.
Use this to pay off
your father's medical bills for now.
Ma'am, you're the best.
Just take it
and pay it back with interest.
I'm a witness to this, okay?
Ma'am, thank you so much.
Not a single person offered to help,
not even my husband or siblings.
We've known each other for a long time.
I'll pay this back with interest
when I sell my house.
Forget the interest.
Just waive the commission fee
when I find a place to live.
Ma'am, what's going on?
Why are you looking for a place?
I need to go home and start cooking.
My husband only eats freshly cooked meals.
Thank you, ma'am.
I'll pay you back as soon as possible!
Goodbye, ma'am!
Ladies, are you here
to get your hair done?
-We'll come again later.
-What?
I'm sorry. Goodbye.
I'm sorry.
Come and take your pick!
What brings him here all of a sudden?
How should I know?
He looks really excited though.
Hold on. This is the Titanic, right?
Hello, sir. It works fine
and costs 150,000 won.
-You look more excited.
-How did you know?
You looked like this
during elementary school treasure hunts.
Was I that obvious? Does this work, sir?
Yes, and you can have it for 150,000 won.
Hey, enough with the treasure hunt
and let's go.
How about you take it for 130,000 won?
I'd like…
Where do all of these items come from?
They say you can catch fleas
at a flea market.
Don't try to find out the source.
Look, it's a portable cassette player.
Oh, cool!
I can't believe this is still around.
It's a rare find, sir.
-You're going to buy it?
-I'd be crazy not to.
How about a 20,000 won discount?
I'm selling this at a loss.
Oh, he's selling it at a loss.
Hey.
He disappeared!
-This is bad.
-Damn it.
-What should we do?
-Thank you, sir.
-Goodbye.
-Goodbye, sir.
-Damn it.
-What should we do?
-Hey, look over there.
-Right.
Who is that next to him?
Ms. Woo?
-Ma'am.
-Ms. Woo.
-Hello.
Who are you?
We work for Plus General Insurance.
You filed a divorce insurance claim.
Right, the divorce.
I got divorced.
But what brings
insurance company employees here?
We're here because you filed
an insurance claim.
That's right. The insurance claim.
When can I get the payout?
We'd like to explain that part to you.
Is now a good time to talk?
Did you say 90 days?
Yes, it's called a waiting period.
You have to wait 90 days after signing up
before your coverage takes effect.
I'm sure you heard about this
when you signed up.
I think I did.
I probably did.
Then should I get divorced after 90 days?
Technically, yes.
But would you like to try
couples therapy during that time?
"Couples therapy"?
Yes.
We're providing marriage support measures
for our policyholders
to help improve
their marital relationships.
"Marriage support"?
Yes, you can receive couples therapy
or participate in couples hobbies.
For example, you can take
ballroom dancing lessons together.
No, I don't need any of that.
There's no additional cost,
and you'll enjoy it
once you give it a try.
I am…
getting a divorce.
But why do you want to leave him?
You've managed to live with him until now.
Because my husband
is still full of energy.
Full of energy?
Then I'll file the insurance claim
90 days from now.
We're set now, right?
Yes, ma'am.
Take care.
If you ever need help,
please contact me anytime.
Thank you, Insurance Lady.
Go on now.
-We're leaving now, ma'am.
-Okay.
-Goodbye.
Bye.
Please give us a progress update
on the insurance product.
The risk-related data
and terms and conditions you gave me
were handed over to relevant departments.
They'll inform us by the end of this month
if revisions are required.
We must hurry and ensure
we launch this product
before Plus General Insurance does.
But the risk-related data
we currently have is insufficient.
It'll take some time.
Is that so?
Then I'll work with some external teams
to gather the additional data we need.
Yes, ma'am.
What was she like in person?
She was more resolute than we'd thought.
When we explained
the 90-day waiting period,
she said she'd file 90 days from now.
We suggested couples therapy to her,
but she refused
and insisted on getting divorced.
Is that so?
What about the husband?
Right, the thing is…
The husband had
a very positive view of divorce.
He stayed firm despite the negative things
I said about divorce.
I'm not positive,
but I think he has another woman.
Another woman?
He's right.
He disappeared with a mysterious woman.
He didn't disappear.
We lost him because of you.
This is why I'm not getting married.
But…
It seemed as though
Ms. Woo Seon-hee wasn't ready.
What do you mean?
She had no grasp of financial matters
and seemed naive about the real world.
More than anything,
she still seemed to care for her husband.
I thought the same thing.
Despite everything,
she still cooked and cleaned for him
and kept calling him "my husband."
They did live together
for a long time after all.
You can't break a habit like that
just because you file divorce papers.
It could be a problem for someone her age
if her daily routine changes suddenly.
What matters to us
is whether or not
they get divorced legally.
It doesn't matter
if they're actually living well together.
I agree.
Don't just sit there looking lost.
Think of a solution or something.
This is so frustrating.
Noh Ki-jun,
don't you have any bright ideas?
If we can't stop this divorce…
But we have to stop it!
-If we can't stop this divorce…
-What?
I just said we have to stop it!
Article Two. Scope of coverage.
What are the exact terms and conditions
of Article Two?
"The insured cited in the contract
must be an adult male or female
between the ages of 18 and 80
who isn't currently engaged in an affair."
-Don't tell me…
-That's it.
-What's it?
-An affair.
If we can prove the husband
is having an affair,
we can declare this contract void.
What do you mean "void"?
It won't be terminated.
It'll be made void.
That's crazy.
Because a void contract is exactly that,
not a termination.
So it won't affect our mission.
That's right.
Awesome! Noh Ki-jun, you're a genius!
We're set now.
Let's find any evidence of an affair
and render this contract void.
So now we're digging into
someone's home life.
Do we really have to do this?
What?
Do we have to expose their private affairs
and hurt Ms. Woo?
She's decided to get divorced
and must be upset as it is.
We have to.
It's for the success of this project.
Even though Ms. Woo Seon-hee
doesn't get any benefits?
This product has to be officially launched
for others like Ms. Woo Seon-hee
to receive benefits.
If it doesn't get launched,
it's not a product.
It's just a sample.
Ma'am!
Did you get groceries?
-What?
-Did you go grocery shopping?
Yes, I guess so.
Have you had lunch yet?
Don't you know what time it is?
It's dinnertime.
What about you?
Oh, I…
What's today's date?
Today is the fourth.
Goodness, the day after tomorrow
is my mother-in-law's death anniversary.
I need to order some rice cakes.
Anyway, how do you like them?
What do you mean?
Dr. Park bought blankets from us
a couple of days ago.
Blankets?
Don't you remember? He bought
a full set of hotel-quality blankets.
What blankets are you talking about?
He bought blankets imported from Italy
a couple of days ago…
What did you say he bought?
Blankets.
Blankets that…
I must've gotten him mixed up
with another customer.
Look at the time.
I need to go make dinner.
I'll be heading home now.
-Thank you.
-Goodbye, sir.
-I'll meet you outside.
-Okay.
GUEST FEEDBACK CARD
You're really cute right now,
you know that?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IT'S CUTE
TRAVESTY
SENIOR MANAGING DIRECTOR
JEON NA-RAE
Damn it. Now what?
Die already!
Just die, you idiot.
Now, give it a tug.
They say being cute is all it takes.
SENIOR MANAGING DIRECTOR
JEON NA-RAE
I can't stand
complicated things like this.
Did you come to get something?
Yes, my watch.
-It's on your wrist.
-Yes, it is.
I meant my alarm clock.
You took that this morning.
Right.
Actually, I didn't come to get anything.
Then what is it?
I came to apologize.
You were disappointed in me earlier,
weren't you?
It wasn't disappointment
but the sense that you felt unfamiliar.
I wondered if you were the Mr. Noh I knew
or if I was mistaken.
Ms. Kang, please sit.
This will sound like an excuse,
but that was the best I could think of
because we have a mission to accomplish.
But I kept wondering
if stopping this divorce
was the right thing to do.
So I found a way to accomplish our mission
even if they got divorced.
And if he's really having an affair,
and they get divorced,
it wouldn't weigh on my mind as much.
I…
I'm a coward, aren't I?
No, I didn't know there was such a reason
behind your decision.
There's a reason why
Jeon-man calls me Travesty.
I'm good at using
sophistry and self-rationalization
to find loopholes and avoid things.
I'm sorry for the misunderstanding.
Not at all. I didn't come here for that.
I was just worried
that I had hurt your feelings earlier.
I couldn't forget that look on your face.
I was just…
looking for an answer.
Why did I feel hurt?
It was just work,
but why did I feel that way?
If it had been Mr. An
or Ah-young instead,
would I have felt the same?
It's because it was you.
I can't stay in the gray zone.
No. I don't want to.
SPECIAL THANKS TO PARK YOUNG-KYU AND
CHA MI-KYEONG FOR THEIR GUEST APPEARANCES
House swapping?
But Ki-jun's belongings are still here.
-Are you and Ms. Kang…
-What's going on between you two?
-I was wondering…
I don't want you to like me.
I don't know how to do that.
Love itself is about being childish.
Tell me again.
You're from the insurance company?
That's why you want a divorce?
Did we accomplish our mission, then?
Not yet.
We have a real mission to deal with now.
A mission?
Subtitle: Jenny Kim