ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND PLACES ARE FICTITIOUS
FILMING OF CHILD ACTORS DONE
UNDER BROADCASTING GUIDELINES
Did you sleep well?
Good morning.
When did you prepare all this?
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Holy cow, this is delicious.
What did I tell you?
Every side dish here
makes you keep eating.
The kimchi is good too.
-Does your mom make it?
-Yes, she makes it herself.
FINAL EPISODE
You're so cute. What's your name?
His name is Mi-nu.
Ah-young?
The dog's name is Mi-nu.
Min-u?
Not Min-u. It's Mi-nu.
Oh, I see. Mi-nu.
Nice to meet you, Mi-nu.
He's my one and only sibling.
I'm so busy with work
that my parents usually walk him.
But I try to do it when I can.
You must be tired
with the launch coming up.
Then do you want to try walking him?
If you two hit it off,
I might ask you to walk him sometimes.
Of course. Leave it to me.
Hey, Mi-nu. Let's go for a walk.
Come on.
Mi-nu stopped. What should I do?
Here.
TODAY'S WORKOUT GOAL
The app says he walked enough today.
-This is great.
-It's cool, right?
You're so smart, Mi-nu.
How did you know when to stop?
Here's a treat.
Honey, wait for me!
That's why I said I'd carry one.
Give it here.
My back is killing me.
I'll carry them.
I don't want your wrist to hurt.
I've carried them just fine on my own.
I'll carry them from now on.
Let's go. I'll make you
sliced rice cake and dumpling soup.
Wait for me.
The ring looks good on you.
It's late, but thank you for the gift.
I also brought you a gift
I've been meaning to give you.
What is it?
A blind date.
She's a pretty awesome person.
After avoiding me for so long,
this is why you wanted to meet?
Because of a blind date?
-Yes.
-Sorry, but no thank you.
If you're done, I think I'll get going.
Hello, Mr. Park Woong-sik.
My name is Joh Ah-young.
You became a dancer
despite your parents' objections, right?
That's pretty cool.
I don't want to get married.
Is that okay?
Are you going to leave me hanging here?
You're pretty cool too.
Anything is fine with me…
as long as we're both happy with it.
I slept through the night.
She'll be back again anyway.
Jeez, why is the fridge so full?
SORRY, I DON'T HAVE A FRIDGE
AT MY PLACE YET
BUT FEEL FREE TO HELP YOURSELF!
HAN-DEUL
BIG BRO DAE-BOK
Yes, Mr. Na?
-The rejected cases have been resolved!
-Really, sir?
PLUS GENERAL INSURANCE
PLUS GENERAL INSURANCE APPLICATION FORM
POLICYHOLDER: NA DAE-BOK
POLICYHOLDER: LEE SO-JEONG
Thank you, Mr. Na.
Oh, it was nothing.
Remember what I said?
I knew Mr. Na would sign up.
No surprise coming
from Ssangmun-dong's top agent.
How did you convince her?
Well, the thing is…
You should eat too.
What's this?
POLICYHOLDER: LEE SO-JEONG
INSURED: LEE SO-JEONG
You promised me 1% every day.
Make sure you keep your word.
Okay.
By the way,
why did you sign the form?
-Should I take it back?
-No.
I'm just curious
because it must've been a hard decision.
Was it because of the kids?
Why would it be
when they're all grown up?
This is just between the two of us.
Right.
I thought of who I was before I met you.
And who you were before you met me.
I looked back on those days.
We were so young back then.
I think we got to this point
simply because we worked so hard
to hold our family together
after getting married.
We both wanted the same thing.
All we wanted was to live a good life.
It's not like
we committed crimes or had affairs.
We just wanted to live well
and ended up like this.
Are you crying?
No.
I just ate something spicy.
Thank you, honey.
My wife and I both looked back on it.
Noh Ki-jun, you said so yourself
from your experience.
-I did?
-Yes.
"When you look back on it,
you'll find the answer."
Right.
I think there really is an answer.
In any case, thank you.
Nam Chang-hee?
Mr. Na, isn't he your junior colleague?
-Yes.
-He signed up too?
Oh, the thing is…
Is this a bad time?
I have a client in 30 minutes.
What do you need?
What is it? Do you want to break up?
Why would you say that?
We've been together for seven years.
If we're not getting married,
we should break up.
Am I wrong?
It's not that, Ga-eul--
Then what is it? Should I wait
until you've saved more money?
I've made enough money
while working at the hair salon.
It's not about that.
Then what is it?
PLUS GENERAL INSURANCE APPLICATION FORM
It's still in the pilot launch stage,
so they're looking for people
who won't get divorced.
Divorce talk? We're not even married.
You were the only person
I could think of, Ga-eul.
I'm saying we should get married.
NAM CHANG-HEE, YEO GA-EUL
Ga-eul, let's build
a beautiful life together.
What's this insurance policy?
If, by any chance, there ever comes a time
you don't want to live with me any longer,
I'll keep making
these monthly payments for you.
How could you say that?
I'll make sure that never happens
and love you until death do us part.
"Until death do us part"?
I'll never let that happen.
Do you promise?
Of course.
I see.
Gosh, who knew divorce insurance
could make people get married?
We made this product,
but I never could've imagined this.
I know. It's so ironic.
We can use this as a marketing angle.
In any case, the rejected cases
have been resolved.
I'm in a good mood,
so let's have a team dinner!
Come on, sir. Don't forget the 1%.
-Seriously, old man.
-Don't call our team leader "old man."
-It's okay.
-Apologize to him.
-I'm an old man and that's not important.
-Hold on, sir. Apologize to him.
What a close call.
Just pretend I didn't say anything.
Don't get too excited just yet.
Hello, ma'am.
Conference room.
INFLUENCER MS. A GETS DIVORCED
BECAUSE OF UPCOMING 'P' INSURANCE PRODUCT?
MS. A RECENTLY TOOK OUT
A NEW INSURANCE POLICY
I think they wrote this article
when Ms. Han Yeo-reum went live.
Jeez.
Why did they write it up
as if we really encouraged their divorce?
We can ask for the article
to be taken down.
However, the higher-ups
are concerned about this issue.
We were worried this might happen too.
But then, we have cases like Mr. Na's.
Right.
So? How do you plan on convincing them?
Noh Ki-jun, any ideas?
What about you, Ms. Kang?
I'm not sure…
You have until the next meeting.
Find a solution
to the divorce promotion issue.
If we don't resolve this,
we can't launch the divorce insurance.
-Yes, ma'am.
Yes?
Here's what you requested, ma'am.
-I'll take a look.
-Yes, ma'am.
And?
Excuse me?
Never mind. So…
Would you like
to see a movie with me tonight?
Sounds good.
The rooftop. Now.
My head's about to explode. What is it?
-Number one.
-What?
Number one. The friend mode.
Okay. Go ahead and ask.
But be quick about it.
I got a job offer.
What? From where?
An overseas branch.
An overseas branch?
Don't tell me it's Singapore.
I knew something was up.
So are you going?
Yes, I think so.
This isn't like you.
You're obsessed with safety
even when you go to a nearby market…
Is Ms. Jeon the one
who offered you the job?
She needs a risk surveyor to work with.
In that case, you should go.
Do you mean that?
Yes, totally.
Don't worry about me. We're beyond that.
You won't regret it, right?
Right.
Then that's all that matters.
And you two will be happy together?
Did you tell her you're going?
I'll tell her once the divorce insurance
is officially launched.
-Why?
-The divorce insurance isn't 100% ready.
Jeez.
When you play it safe like this,
you're An Jeon-man.
But then you're not An Jeon-man.
You've changed.
It went against my nature
to get into divorce insurance at all.
I admit that jumping into
an uncertain project
was a big leap for you.
Singapore sounds good.
It'll be a great turning point.
Thanks.
I'm off.
Off to where?
To launch this product
as soon as possible.
Wait for me.
A turning point…
What is it, sir? You can tell us.
Oh, it's just that…
I thought younger folks
would know more about this…
About what, sir?
Actually, I want to give my wife a gift.
That's so sweet.
But I've never gotten a gift
for her before.
What do women like these days?
The most memorable gift is money.
I like small gifts
that come from the heart.
"From the heart"? Jeez, that's hard.
Okay. The best kind of gift is one
when you thoughtfully sense
what someone wants.
-That's right.
-Thoughtfully sense it?
That's even harder.
But it's the kind of thoughtful gift
that will blow her away
because it requires attention.
-Why not go through her social media?
-Right.
Let me see your phone, sir.
-My phone?
-Yes, hand it over.
But why?
I'll take a good look at it.
THE NORTHERN LIGHTS
HOPE TO SEE THEM BEFORE I DIE
Hey, this is it.
What's this? The Northern Lights?
This takes more thought
since it's on the other side of the world.
Don't stress too much about it, sir.
-You got this, Mr. Na!
-How am I going to…
Why are you slacking off and not working?
Can you take a look at
the risk data I put together, sir?
What?
Let's see here.
MS. KANG
MR. NOH, YOU SHOULD HEAD HOME FIRST
MR. NOH
WHY? ARE YOU WORKING LATE?
NO, I WANT TO VISIT MY PARENTS,
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME
I'M NOT WORRIED,
I KNOW YOU CAN TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF
"The policyholder and insured will"…
Ta-da!
What's this?
Did you get them off the street?
Seriously?
Each of these flowers I chose
reminded me of you.
You're being ridiculous.
Look at all this laundry.
All right. Time to start folding laundry.
It's 1% a day.
Don't change too much all at once.
You'll get sick.
Get sick? That's ridiculous.
My liver and stomach might be ruined
because I drank so much every day.
But my heart still beats strong for you.
As far as I know,
this is my house.
What about the movie?
Watching movies at home is the best
because you get front-row seats.
Didn't you know that?
Where are the plates?
-They're in the cabinet.
-The cabinet?
He's really into the movie.
This must be your kind of movie.
You were so focused on it
that I thought
you might fall into the screen.
It was better than I expected.
It was just so-so for me.
I can't really relate
to the human-robot love thing.
I can relate to it.
Really?
Cars are just hunks of metal,
but people name them all the same.
They also show affection to robot vacuums.
That's just a waste of emotional energy.
You can't fight off feelings
that just come to you.
But if even robots can love,
and humans can't live without love,
then why do we get divorced?
That's what I wondered about.
You get divorced if you're not compatible.
You know this.
But humans and robots
aren't compatible either.
So?
What's your point?
Divorce might not always be the answer.
This needs to be clearly outlined
in divorce insurance.
You're more serious than I expected.
It's time for me to be serious.
Here we go.
I'm not done eating that.
We still have some wine left,
so let's watch another movie.
I'm sorry, but I have to work.
Right now?
I'll drink the rest of this
and watch a movie.
Go ahead and work.
You're done, right?
-No, there's still some left.
-It's just a little bit.
I'll leave on my own.
-Sorry I can't walk you out.
-I said I'm leaving.
-Wait, my bag.
-Go ahead and put your shoes on.
I have to put my shoes on before I can go.
Hurry… I mean, take your time.
I'm really leaving now.
Right, and I really have to work.
Seriously?
I seriously have to work.
Goodbye and take care.
Wait, but…
What's the matter with him?
Promoting divorce…
My wife and I both looked back on it.
Noh Ki-jun, you said so yourself
from your experience.
"When you look back on it,
you'll find the answer."
Promoting divorce…
Sounds good.
It'll be a great turning point.
Ms. Kang.
You're not on the swings tonight.
What are you doing here?
I'm just…
Is it the divorce promotion issue?
Thoughts are swirling around in my head,
but there's no flash of insight.
We should put our heads together for this.
Don't struggle on your own.
But this whole thing started in my head.
Let's have some ice cream
and wake up our brains.
Take the bigger one, Ms. Kang.
Hey, this is good.
Thank you for the bed.
I slept well because of it.
Don't mention it.
It's nothing compared to the side dishes.
Did you see your parents? How did it go?
-They're giving up on me.
-What?
I think they've maybe accepted it.
My dad is reserved and isn't good
at expressing himself, you see.
I see.
I don't think I've fully conveyed
my thoughts or feelings
to my parents until now.
"I hope I never make Mom and Dad sad."
"If I can just get past this moment,
nothing bad will happen."
That's what I thought.
But I think it's my fault
things turned out this way.
Hey, don't blame yourself.
It's not blame. It's self-reflection.
Self-reflection?
Yes.
That's why I'm going to
meet things head-on from now on.
Even if it's a bit painful
and uncomfortable,
and even if I receive hate,
those feelings I want to avoid
are still mine.
And I'm at the center of it all.
Right. I'm always in the center.
The center…
I found it.
What do you mean?
A solution.
A "self-care program"?
I start off alone as "myself,"
then meet someone and become a couple.
And if this couple eventually reaches
the point of divorce,
it's like salmon swimming upstream,
trying to return to "myself,"
where it all began.
What do we get
if we apply our previous cases?
Except for Mr. Kim Seon-man.
You always went
looking for something else,
but not for me who was right beside you.
I wanted to show it to you
and get your acknowledgment.
Remember you held out your hand
when I was about to give up in Santiago
even though we had never met before?
The moment I took your hand,
I had already acknowledged you.
-You!
Do you want them to visit during holidays?
-No.
-Yes.
-What did you say?
Did you settle on the holiday matter?
They'll visit my house
on even-numbered years
and her house on odd-numbered years.
Getting everything out in the open
before the wedding
is more suitable.
OPTIONS FOR NEW HOME
MONEY GIFT FROM HUSBAND ON 60TH BIRTHDAY
USE TO SEND ME TO A NURSING HOME
Why didn't she spend any of this?
Why is she so foolish?
I'll improve by 1% every day…
and I'll change 100% for the better.
POLICYHOLDER: LEE SO-JEONG
INSURED: LEE SO-JEONG
You promised me 1% every day.
Make sure you keep your word.
They say you have to confront reality
to understand yourself.
So I can't help but understand my partner
since they're a part of me.
Exactly.
That can become
a new turning point or starting point.
So, this could give them
the courage to start over together again?
It also includes the courage
to get divorced like Mr. Kim.
In conclusion, divorce insurance is…
A tool or opportunity
for couples to look back
and figure out
how they got to the point of divorce.
-So does it promote divorce?
-No!
-Right.
-I see.
Just like getting cancer insurance
and taking care of your health,
you can get divorce insurance
-and care for yourself and your marriage.
-That's exactly it.
Just like hospital fees that are covered
upon a cancer diagnosis,
we can improve the process
by covering self-care program costs
when high divorce risk is diagnosed.
That sounds good.
-Okay. Let's speed things up.
-Yes, ma'am.
I knew it.
All right. Let's do this.
We got this!
REASONS FOR DIVORCE
WHEN THE INSURED INFORMS…
-Can you check this for me?
-Sure.
INSURANCE BENEFITS
-Good night.
-See you.
-Good work today.
-Take care.
-Okay.
-See you tomorrow.
You didn't go home last night?
Good morning.
Good morning!
SENIOR MANAGING DIRECTOR'S OFFICE
SENIOR MANAGING DIRECTOR
JEON NA-RAE
-Take this.
-Okay.
Did you review
the fact-based analysis, Mr. Na?
-You must be exhausted.
-Ms. Jeon.
Ms. Jeon.
-Eat up.
-Thank you.
This looks great.
I'm heading out now.
Wait… wait for me.
-Bye.
-See you.
You must be exhausted.
I guess I dozed off.
Did everyone go home?
Yes, just now.
Here, Ms. Kang.
It'll wake you up.
Thank you.
I want to wake up too.
Let's do this.
We got this.
I think we're good to go.
What do you think?
I'm okay with it. What about you?
-Okay.
-Ms. Joh?
-Mr. Na?
Ms. Jeon?
-Ms. Kang?
-There's just one more thing.
What?
We also have to check the AI underwriting
since there are probably changes
based on the insight gained
through the pilot sales.
You're right.
I'll participate this time too.
After all, I'm on the task force too.
That sounds good.
But the questions
will be different than last time.
They're upgraded versions.
Okay.
DIVORCE INSURANCE
FOR A SECOND CHANCE AT LIFE
SELF-CARE PROGRAM, NEW
How did it go? What did the FSS say?
They gave the okay.
-Mr. Na.
-Great job.
Great job.
The official launch will be decided
after going through the executive meeting.
Great work, all of you.
-Thank you, ma'am.
-Great work, everyone.
Good job.
Good work, everyone.
-Good job.
-I gave it my all.
What day is it today?
We pulled so many all-nighters
that I have no idea.
Hey, what does this Chinese character say?
-"Ga" for "Home."
-"Ga" for "Home"?
"Ga" for "Home."
Let's go home.
Everyone, go home!
-We're finally off work!
-Let's go home!
-Goodbye, sir.
-Let's go.
Hey, Ms. Joh!
Ms. Joh!
How dare you leave
before your senior colleagues?
Ms. Joh!
DIVORCE INSURANCE
OFFICIAL LAUNCH PROPOSAL DRAFT
CEO: LEE WON-U
SENIOR MANAGING DIRECTOR: JEON NA-RAE
CONFIRMATION OF
DIVORCE INSURANCE LAUNCH
Good morning.
We've seen each other every day,
but why does it seem like
we haven't in a long time?
Because we were busy working every day.
But I avoided
completely running out of energy.
I just charged you up.
Me too.
I can't believe this got launched.
LAUNCH ANNOUNCEMENT
Did you know this was coming out?
It's divorce insurance.
LAUNCH ANNOUNCEMENT
PRODUCT NAME: DIVORCE INSURANCE
Ninety-eight… Hey, make it to a hundred.
Hurry. Just two more.
Ninety-nine…
Good morning.
Goodness, ma'am.
-Good morning.
Good morning.
Hello, Ms. Jeon.
Let's wrap up the task force now.
Excuse me?
The official launch date has been set,
and your work here is now done.
Jeez, I can't believe it's over.
I feel sad now that it's really over.
Well, let's just keep this
as a fond memory
since we'll be very busy soon.
Yes, ma'am.
Then are we returning
to our respective teams?
Before that,
how about a dissolution ceremony?
Like a team dinner?
Yes.
A team dinner? That sounds great.
Actually, I can't make it.
Why not?
How about the ocean?
The ocean?
We need to get out of this stuffy office
and go to a cool and wide-open space.
I'm in. I've been wanting to go.
-That sounds good.
-The ocean sounds good, Ms. Joh.
Should we look into it
and make reservations?
-I'll look into it.
-Let's do it together.
Hey, Seok-gi.
Remember the thing
we talked about last time?
Shall we leave together, then?
-Sounds good.
-Same. It's been a while.
-We're leaving now, right?
-Of course.
-Where's a good place?
-Are you coming from somewhere?
Oh, someone stopped by to see me.
Go home before you hit traffic.
-Yes, sir.
-We're going.
We're having fried chicken and beer.
Why don't you join us?
I can't. I need to cut back on drinking.
Then just have some fried chicken.
Come with us, sir.
Come on, sir.
Fried chicken…
Darn it, I can't resist that.
Hold on a second.
Honey?
Don't make dinner tonight.
I'll pick up some fried chicken.
Do you want glazed or half-and-half?
Is it okay for Mr. Na
to change all of a sudden?
He's like a different person.
They say if someone suddenly changes--
That's enough.
-It's nice to see him this way.
-I agree.
-All right. Let's head out.
-Sounds good.
Honey, is there anywhere you'd like to go?
Not really.
I traveled so much for a while, so…
Seok-gi told me
there's a place
that can rekindle your love.
Where would that even be?
It's not a joke. I'm telling the truth.
Stop talking nonsense
and hand me the laundry.
What's this?
WOOSEOK TRAVEL AGENCY
ITINERARY
Let's go see the Northern Lights.
We should see them once in our lifetime.
FLIGHT INFORMATION
FROM INCHEON TO HELSINKI
People do vow renewal ceremonies.
So let's think of this
as a second honeymoon.
I'm not dreaming, am I?
Our flight leaves tomorrow night.
Where did you get the money for this?
Let's pack our suitcases.
But the credit card payment due date…
Come on. It's our honeymoon.
Is that right?
We're at the beach!
Hurry up!
It's good now that we're actually here.
It's so nice and open.
The East Coast is the best.
That's right.
This is great. It's been so long.
The weather is amazing.
Let's take a photo.
Here we go.
One, two…
That turned out great. One more.
Hey.
One more?
Let's take one more.
Okay, one more time. One, two…
-How about a selfie?
-Sounds good.
-Make a cheek heart!
-Cheek heart.
BIG BRO DAE-BOK
-What the heck?
-Hello, Mr. Na. What's on your head?
Hello, sir.
We arrived here safely.
Look. Isn't it amazing?
-What about you guys?
-We got here safely too.
-You're looking good, sir.
-Of course I am.
Don't have too much fun without me,
or I'll be sad.
Of course not, sir.
It's no fun without you here.
-It's super boring.
-Let's just go home.
Don't worry and have fun, sir!
-Sounds good. You guys have fun.
-Bye!
-Goodbye, sir!
Goodness.
What are you doing? Let's go.
What? Already?
We have to get a good spot.
All right, then.
Goodness!
That's cute.
What? I don't come across
as someone who likes this stuff?
No, it's not that…
I used to see the world
from an investment perspective,
and I liked debating and assessing risks.
But now, I'm starting to notice
all of the little things in between.
That shows how hard
you've worked this whole time.
I'm going back to Singapore.
When?
Right after the divorce insurance launch.
That's a shame.
I just started to feel
comfortable around you.
Really?
You were the senior managing director…
and there were many barriers between us.
But as we gradually became a team,
it just happened before I knew it.
There's nothing else to think about.
Kang Han-deul and Jeon Na-rae.
That's all that matters.
You haven't told her yet?
At times like this,
you're definitely Wuss-man.
I'm going to tell her today.
Good. Imagine how she must feel
while waiting for your answer.
Hey, aren't you at least a little sad
that I'm leaving?
Jeez.
I'm not your girlfriend.
But you're my friend.
Right. Friends just need to know
they're doing okay.
Stay healthy.
Oh, and get me some duty-free whiskey
when you come to Korea.
Whiskey is expensive.
I'll get you mango jelly.
-Mango jelly?
-Or kaya jam.
JUMPING CRAB
Woong-sik is why we're here, right?
Congratulations on
the official launch of divorce insurance.
Thank you.
Thank you. You had a hand in it too.
But how did you manage to come
during planting season
when I'm in the village?
The water here is really good.
Here, try this.
-What's going on with you two?
-We're finding out.
Finding out what?
You don't need to know everything.
It's private.
-Is this right?
-Come on. They look good together.
You look good together.
Here's the food.
-Holy cow.
-Here you go. Enjoy.
-Thank you, ma'am.
This is good.
Here, try this.
-Cheers.
Until the very end…
Ms. Jeon is going to Singapore next week.
Singapore? That soon?
Please come visit when you have time.
Sounds good to me.
Everything's on you, then.
Sure. Why not?
You don't have to come
if you don't want to.
What am I supposed to do if you leave?
Ms. Jeon, you were
my super cool role model.
Thank you for saying
I was your role model.
Na-rae. Can I call you Na-rae?
I mean, it's all over now,
so why can't I just call you Na-rae?
Ah-young.
-Ah-young, don't do that.
-No?
-Woong-sik?
-Jeez.
-Is he okay?
-He drank too quickly.
It'll get on his white pants.
I knew that would happen.
Ah-young is drunk,
so please don't hold it against her.
Right, it happens.
Na-rae?
Seriously.
I like that, actually. "Na-rae"?
-"Na-rae," huh?
-That's cute.
I need some fresh air.
Ms. Kang, will you come with me?
Okay.
We'll be right back.
It feels cramped in here, doesn't it?
-Don't you agree?
-It doesn't feel cramped.
Honey.
Honey, wake up!
I wasn't sleeping. I…
Did you know?
The Northern Lights are
a shield created by Earth
to protect the life forms
living on its planet
from solar winds.
That sounds exactly…
like insurance.
That darn insurance.
You can be my Northern Lights…
until the day we die.
Seriously? Will you let me?
If Mr. Noh says
he wants to develop a new product,
tell him about
the space travel SOS insurance.
Don't hold back and push the idea hard.
Don't be a wuss.
Or I guess
I could push it forward in Singapore.
Would you really do that for me?
Yes.
Actually…
I made up my mind.
Believe me, I was going to tell you today.
At times like this,
it feels like I'm lost in a tunnel
that I thought was a cave,
and then finally finding light.
Isn't that what I said?
That's right.
So what happened?
Did you escape the tunnel?
Of course.
-Let's go see the stars more often now.
-Okay.
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
What was your question
during the tarot reading?
The tarot reading turned out to be true.
Remember how it predicted your success?
That wasn't the question I asked.
Excuse me? It wasn't?
Then what was the question?
I'm not telling you.
Seriously?
I'll tell you when the results come out.
Seriously…
No, wait. If I succeed,
I'll tell you then.
I asked if it was possible
to meet my twin flame.
"Twin flame"?
A twin flame is basically
the other part of your soul.
Humans were originally created
with four arms, four legs, and two faces,
but the gods felt threatened,
so they split them in half.
So there's someone out there
who shares the same soul as me.
They say meeting someone like that
leads to a whole new chapter in life
and not just a romance.
But it's difficult to find that person.
How can you recognize them?
They say you just do,
as if you've known them all along.
The tarot reading results said
you'd succeed.
Right.
Then what about in real life?
Did you succeed?
Did you manage to succeed?
That's when you knew, right?
When you called future Han-deul,
you asked, "Did you manage to succeed?"
And then you smiled, just like now.
You remember that?
Hey, Noh Ki-jun.
Remember today.
Of course, I remember.
I'm a little disappointed, though.
Because I knew from the beginning.
Really? Since the mattress incident?
No.
Since the supermarket.
Mr. Noh?
Come on.
Hurry.
Excuse me.
Looking good.
Which one should I wear?
Today's a special day, so I'll choose you.
Wish me luck.
I basically memorized this…
Amazing news!
Why? What is it?
We scored our first contract!
What?
-Seriously?
-Yes.
-Already?
-Who is it, sir?
The CEO's daughter.
Oh, I remember.
The one who was getting divorced
and falling apart.
That's right.
She just signed the contract.
I think we have the CEO's full support
on divorce insurance.
This is great.
What a great start!
This is insane.
-Jeez.
-Mr. An.
IS YOUR MARRIAGE OKAY?
Please come over here.
But it's so hard when you get married.
There are divorce litigation fees,
child support, and alimony.
And what about the house?
It's more stressful than marriage.
This is when you need divorce insurance.
What if you don't get divorced?
Then just get a refund.
More importantly, this divorce insurance
will not only build trust
but also help couples
to be more thoughtful.
That sounds right.
So would you like to read
the terms and conditions?
I can take a breather,
thanks to the divorce insurance.
Good work.
Not at all, sir.
It was the task force that worked hard.
I can trust them with another project.
You're departing soon, right?
Yes, sir. I'll visit you
when I'm back in Korea.
Goodbye, sir.
I'm not too late, am I?
Do you enjoy making a fool out of me?
I just…
I just couldn't find the right time…
The…
Our living arrangements in Singapore--
They'll be separate.
We need our own personal space, after all.
As expected,
we're on the same wavelength.
We're late. Let's go.
The world offers various insurance plans.
STORM AND FLOOD COVERAGE INSURANCE
EARTHQUAKE AND DISASTER INSURANCE
However,
there was no insurance
to prepare you for this until now.
And that is divorce.
Divorce insurance
that ensures your happiness.
-Plus General Insurance will support you!
-Support you!
DIVORCE INSURANCE
PLUS GENERAL INSURANCE
LAUNCHES DIVORCE INSURANCE
THE COUNTRY'S FIRST DIVORCE INSURANCE
ROCKS THE INSURANCE INDUSTRY
WE SEEK TO PREPARE OUR CUSTOMERS
FOR THIS CRISIS…
"Plus General Insurance's
stock price surges."
I think we really pulled it off.
Of course. Look who was behind it.
Not bad for a first project, right?
We did an amazing job.
No, I mean this sweater.
This is first-rate too.
You're lying.
What are your thoughts
on the official launch?
It's a shame the project is over.
But for some reason,
I'm looking forward to something more.
What are you looking forward to?
The fact that I don't know
what will happen in the future.
By any chance,
is that pride insurance still valid?
The idea of making it, that is.
Yes, it's still valid.
Then give it a shot.
But do you think it'll work?
We made it happen with divorce,
and everyone has pride.
If the talented Ms. Kang heads it,
then Noh Ki-jun will actively assist.
Okay, then. Let's make this work.
Let's make this work.
By the way, what happened
with Na-rae and Mr. An?
They're doing well.
But Jeon-man isn't the type
to go into detail about things.
"Na-rae"? When did you two get so close?
It's a secret between us women.
I see.
By the way, how long
will we keep speaking formally?
Should we speak casually, then?
Cool.
I'm sorry?
We will now begin.
What is the most important thing
for middle-aged people
to maintain their marriage?
(4) MY SPOUSE BESIDE ME
My lovely wife, of course.
Which of the following
is the most ideal way
to achieve happiness?
(1) TO BE MARRIED (2) TO GET DIVORCED
(3) TO NEVER MARRY (4) NONE OF THE ABOVE
Number five, other.
All three of the above.
Please select the advice you would give
to someone
contemplating divorce or remarriage.
(4) IF NO REGRET, GO FOR IT
Sometimes, you just need to take a leap.
Which of the following
describes the reason
for deciding to remarry?
I can't say pet rock, so…
Number one.
(1) LIFE COMPANION
What is the biggest change in your life
after getting divorced?
Number three. Having the…
HAVING THE MIND-SET TO START FRESH
…courage to start fresh.
What do you think helped you
to overcome your trauma?
(2) MAKING TODAY COUNT
No more regrets for me.
We will now move on to the next question.
Are you happy right now?
-Yes.
Goodness.
Mr. Na!
-Don't clear out your desk yet.
-What?
One last time.
What do you mean?
Let's make one last hit product.
What is it?
Pride insurance.
No!
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING
THE DIVORCE INSURANCE
-We did it!
Subtitle: Jenny Kim