ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND PLACES ARE FICTITIOUS
FILMING OF CHILD ACTORS DONE
UNDER BROADCASTING GUIDELINES
DIVORCE PROTECTION INSURANCE
Is this the promo flyer
you used at the wedding fair?
-Yes.
We received a complaint.
-What?
The flyer contains information
that violates insurance regulations.
A complaint, sir?
This isn't a contract
or terms and conditions.
We just made a small batch
for promotion purposes.
We've secured pre-approval
and included all required notices.
I'm aware of that,
but that isn't the issue.
"During the execution and solicitation
of insurance contracts,
items exceeding 30,000 won
may not be provided to consumers."
This is the provision
you allegedly violated.
-But…
-Jeez.
We only handed out wet wipes
and tissues that day.
They might've cost 3,000 won,
but certainly not over 30,000 won.
Maybe they confused the promo gift
with another company's?
DIVORCE CEREMONY
This part right here.
Can you host a divorce ceremony
for less than 30,000 won?
A divorce ceremony…
My understanding is that
the insurance law was recently updated.
The new regulation sets a limit
of 200,000 won per product
or 10% of the annual premium.
Exactly.
That's right. You're well-informed.
Then what's the issue?
The part that says,
"However, this applies solely to items
that reduce the risk of an accident."
A divorce ceremony
does not qualify as an item
that reduces the risk of an accident,
meaning it does not lower
the divorce rate for policyholders.
This is the issue.
The person who filed the complaint
pointed out this violation,
which even we had overlooked.
Yes, it seems so.
This person's skill
matches that of an underwriter.
I know.
Then I'll take that
as you admitting to it.
-But…
-Excuse me!
We didn't violate anything.
He's right. We haven't hosted
a divorce ceremony yet.
Maybe not now,
but you will later, right?
No, sir. We won't provide
any divorce ceremonies.
Then was that false advertisement?
Would you rather face
the harsher penalty of that provision?
No, sir. It definitely wasn't
a false advertisement.
Look here, Mr. Noh Ki-jun.
I mean…
It'll be fine as long as
none of the first ten people
who signed up get divorced.
How does that even make sense?
We'll provide divorce prevention
management until the contract term ends.
Just like the health management services.
If that's what you're willing to do, fine.
However,
if you end up hosting a divorce ceremony,
you will be held fully accountable,
including today's issue,
which means no limited-time sales.
And of course, no official launch.
Are we clear?
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. Understood.
-Goodbye.
-Your bag.
-Oh, my.
Get your bag.
-Hurry.
-Goodbye, sir!
DIRECTOR OH MI-YEONG
MARRIAGE COUNSELING CENTER
This is my guess
based on the material you provided.
Thank you.
You know it's unreasonable
to make judgments based on this, right?
Yes, of course.
It's unreasonable for anyone to judge
others' marital issues in the first place.
We appreciate that you responded
to our unreasonable request.
Please consider this a type of
multidimensional data collection analysis.
Of course.
This is unexpected, though.
This policyholder came up top?
The questionnaire showed
no signs of marital conflict.
They even put down zero number of fights.
You're right.
Is there a married couple in this world
without any conflicts?
No.
Almost none, probably.
That's right.
Conflict among people
is both natural and unavoidable.
Claiming there's no conflict
actually suggests there's a problem.
This person is doing everything possible
to avoid conflict.
Confronting the truth doesn't mean
it will resolve everything,
but avoiding it will
certainly change nothing.
It means there's no room for improvement.
So that's why…
Now, do you understand
why this person was my top pick?
-Yes.
I thought if a married couple
baked cookies or a cake together,
it could help mend their relationship.
So I'd like to arrange
some couples baking classes.
If that's the case, I'm not sure.
Baking requires much more focus
and effort than you'd expect.
It's one thing if they're on good terms.
But if they're not,
it could end up causing more frustration.
There are actually many couples
who end up fighting and leave.
Jeez, what the heck?
It's you.
Do you know him?
No.
His father owns this place.
He's just full of energy.
He handles the building maintenance here
and teaches at a dance studio.
Actually, I think dancing
will help you more.
There's more physical interaction
in dancing.
We meet again.
Oh, my.
So you do know him.
I'll go bake a nice cake for you.
-This must be fate.
-No.
It's just a coincidence.
I asked the couples manager for
your number because I wanted to see you,
but you didn't ask for a second date.
There were privacy issues, so--
I want you to teach dance lessons.
You're very proactive.
If that's what you want, Ms. Ah-young.
No.
This is a business proposition.
I want you to teach married policyholders
who are at risk of divorce
how to dance.
Okay.
Thank you for becoming a partner
of our divorce prevention program.
Excuse me?
What's this…
But, wait…
FINANCIAL SUPERVISORY SERVICE
Management until the contract term ends?
What made you say something so outrageous?
Well, our goal was
to have a divorce rate of zero.
But that was for a six-month term,
not the end of a contract term.
Yes, but we still don't lose out on this.
It's bad enough we have to meet
the company's conditions, but now this?
There are too many things to consider.
We just have to think of it
as people showing interest.
Right.
Ms. Ah-young!
If you dance on the street again,
I'll call the cops on you.
Will we continue to see each other?
Not on a personal level.
-Why not?
-I told you I don't believe in marriage.
But you can still date, right?
Just as there are
different types of vegans,
it's the same for people
who don't believe in marriage.
-I'm the type who doesn't even date.
-Why?
Because I refuse to waste time and energy
on something useless.
Then what do you do in your free time?
I don't have any free time.
Come on.
If I have free time,
I learn something new or pursue a hobby.
I invest that time in myself.
You sure keep yourself busy.
On that note, I got you a gift.
Please don't.
It's napa cabbage from my farm.
Actually, I'm a farmer.
I thought your father owned this building.
That's right.
But I gave up my parents'
financial support to pursue dancing.
So I looked for a job I could do
alongside dancing,
and I ended up finding this part-time job
harvesting napa cabbage.
Then I took a liking to farming
and became a farmer.
Make a wrap and eat it.
It's sweet and tasty.
Fine, then.
Being nonchalant
is what makes you attractive.
Stop, unless you want to
get slapped by this cabbage.
I'll be off now.
Goodbye, Ms. Ah-young!
Take care!
What the hell are you talking about?
Say that again.
Do what until the term ends?
Why are there more obstacles to overcome?
We already have more than enough
challenges to prevent as it is!
Here are more special management cases
we have to prevent.
What's the matter with you?
Damn it.
DR. OH'S LIST
Ten people?
Ten more on top of
the first ten who signed up?
There's this list too.
Hey, Ms. Kang.
We can look at that later.
Why bring it up now?
What's this? Ten more people?
How many are there in total? Thirty?
Damn it.
We're not
a divorce prevention management team!
It's not 30 people, sir.
It's not?
But Ms. Kang, you're never wrong.
Is there something else, then?
The experts' lists are almost the same.
Take a look, sir.
No way.
DR. OH'S LIST
PROFESSOR KIM'S LIST
So experts' views
are the same across the board?
It seems so, sir.
There's a shorter list
of people to manage now.
-Which means a higher risk.
-Why would you bring that up?
Don't you know logical conjunction?
Intersecting entity characteristics
combine multiplicatively.
But the number of entities
in the union has decreased.
When two or more entities
have corresponding input values--
Hey!
Yes, sir.
Take your arguing outside, damn it.
Read the room, will you?
What's even more shocking is that
the top pick is the same.
What?
What do you mean by that?
According to the experts, this person
is most likely to get divorced.
And this person is on the list
of the first ten people who signed up.
NUMBER 1, GU MI-RAE
What does this mean?
Am I the only one who doesn't get it?
Can someone explain this to me?
Anyone? Hello?
Excuse me. Hello?
Excuse me?
Let's see here.
If the experts chose the same person
as their number one pick,
that means their chance of divorce
is that much higher.
But if they're also on the list
of the first ten applicants,
that means…
Oh, damn it.
-Mr. Na!
Are you okay, old man?
Hey, you jerk.
Don't call our team leader an old man!
-I'm sorry, Mr. Na!
-His eyes!
-We need to do CPR!
-Do CPR!
PRESIDENT LEE JEONG-SIN
This will hit them pretty hard.
Let's see how they handle it.
DIVORCE PROTECTION INSURANCE
Ms. Jeon.
Hello, sir.
What on earth happened?
Someone filed a complaint to the FSS?
Please take a seat.
We made a mistake
with one of the provisions on the flyer.
-What?
-I'm sorry. I should've been thorough.
This product must be launched
without any issues.
You know that.
I'll pay closer attention, sir.
Damn it.
However,
it's strange how they knew
such a provision.
This could be the job of an insider,
so I'll meet with the security manager.
What?
No, there's no way
it was someone from the inside.
We should also be more careful
when sending material to the China branch.
Yes, we should.
Don't worry about that.
I'll monitor things.
Damn it.
Hey, we need to tighten security
from now on,
so that no one suspects anything.
Yes.
Make sure to be discreet.
Okay.
Get out!
Get out, now!
Get out and take care of it.
Don't you dare come back
before solving this issue!
Beg as much as you want,
but I'm not opening this door!
Mr. Na is the one
trapped in there, not us.
Gu Mi-rae…
Gu Mi-rae?
This is the person I consulted
at the wedding fair.
I remember her name.
Do you remember anything else?
I think her outfit was a bit unusual.
I was all over the place that day,
so I don't remember.
Okay. What's the address?
Yangsam-dong.
Let's head to the scene for now.
We need to go to the scene to investigate.
"Investigate"?
Are you a detective?
What do you plan to do there?
Let's just go, Detective Kang.
I mean, Ms. Kang.
What? Right now?
We have to find signs of divorce.
If there are warning signs of divorce,
we must handle it within the golden hour.
-You sound like a doctor.
-Scalpel. Never mind.
Wait, we should call her first.
Hello?
Hello, is this Ms. Gu Mi-rae?
Yes, it is. Who am I speaking with?
Oh, I'm…
We met before at the wedding fair.
The thing is…
I'm not sure if you remember,
but you and I…
Did I consult with you?
Yes, that's right.
I see. How can I help you?
The thing is…
If it's okay with you,
may I visit your place
and speak with you…
Are you asking for
a site-visit consultation?
Yes, that's right.
A site-visit consultation.
-When would you like to come?
-Excuse me?
How about today?
I happen to have some free time.
Yes, we'll head out now.
I'll see you later, then.
Yes, thank you.
She sounded way too happy to invite me.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Then we should go right away. Come on.
-Okay.
FIRST TO SIGN UP LIST, DR. OH'S LIST
I never violated
the promotional gift regulation
even when I was the top insurance agent
in Ssangmun-dong.
But you'd have to be an expert
to know such regulations.
No, there's no way someone would…
There must've been a lawyer
at the wedding fair that day.
APPROVAL DENIED
I forgot about these rejected cases.
Jeez. We have to prevent divorces
and secure contracts.
When will we get these done?
Do we need to recruit more staff?
You'll rise up, you'll rise up
If you keep working hard
It'll become a reality
You'll rise up, you'll rise up
Even if you're not good at anything
One of these days
I know you'll rise like the sun
Very good!
Ladies, did you have a good time today?
-Yes!
To keep being happy like today
for the rest of your lives,
I prepared a premium dementia
insurance policy!
Okay, ladies.
Here we go.
It's premium insurance.
That's right.
You can't trust your kids,
but you can trust this.
Yes, that's right.
-It's a premium policy.
-Okay.
Do I have to fill out this part too?
Write 5 kg less than your actual weight.
Really? Can I do that?
Okay, looks good.
NA DAE-BOK
It's my respected senior colleague.
Hello, Mr. Na.
Chang-hee, are you busy?
I'm in the middle of a consultation.
A consultation?
I shouldn't interrupt, then. I'll hang up.
I'll visit you shortly.
Okay, goodbye.
Ma'am, just fill it out.
-Did I get it right?
-Yes, you did.
Look at this kid.
He reminds me of myself back in the day.
It's great how he's working hard.
Some employees were on their computer
outside of working hours.
Is that so?
As requested, I checked the system
activity from the last six months,
and there was no sign of hacking.
But there were employees
who used their computer
outside of working hours.
Who was it?
Mr. Noh Ki-jun and Ms. Kang Han-deul
of the New Product Development Team.
Is it possible
that an outsider accessed it?
No, that's impossible.
Outsiders are prohibited
from entering after business hours,
and company computers are securely locked.
Unless they stole an employee ID number,
it's impossible to use a computer.
Understood.
Please continue to check the system.
I'll report to you on a regular basis.
If it wasn't a hacker,
who could it have been?
Yes?
You're here.
Yes, ma'am. How may I help you?
-Sir.
-Yes?
Let's launch a new product soon.
DIVORCE INSURANCE
POLICY TERMS & CONDITIONS
Divorce insurance?
Adding benefits to existing products
is rather boring now,
don't you think?
I think our perspective
on what a crisis is needs to change.
But would this be commercially viable?
I'm suggesting a new paradigm
in the existing insurance industry.
This product will definitely
question societal trends
and create waves.
On that note,
I'd like to see the official launch
of divorce insurance…
by Best General Insurance.
I think it's around here.
This is it.
-Welcome.
-Hello.
-Let's go in.
-Okay.
Thank you.
The atmosphere here is rather unusual.
It looks pretty.
Thank you for making time for us.
I should be thanking you.
-Thank you.
Shall we begin now?
-Excuse me?
Yes, of course.
Ms. Kang, do you want to explain?
-Me?
-Shall I do it?
-Oh, right.
-Ms. Kang, if you can explain…
Or shall I begin?
What's this?
So you're here because of insurance,
not a tarot reading?
-Yes.
I think there was a misunderstanding
during the explanation.
You sounded so welcoming on the phone
that I misunderstood.
I ran a tarot reading booth
at the wedding fair.
That's when I signed up for the insurance.
-I see.
-So that's why…
-I'm sorry.
I thought you came
for a follow-up reading.
It's hard enough as it is
since I decided to get divorced.
-What?
Please leave.
Wait a minute, let's--
-Let's talk for a moment.
-It'll just take a second.
Please leave.
Are you sure we can't talk?
I want a divorce ceremony.
I'll contact you once I choose a date.
-But…
-Ma'am!
Ma'am?
Choosing a divorce date, huh?
I guess people
set divorce dates these days.
If they want a divorce,
they might as well do it on a good date.
I suppose so.
When you think about it, a divorce date
is more important than a wedding date.
Do you think this gate will open again?
What are you doing?
I don't think it's the right time.
Jeez.
We're here for a tarot reading.
Can we get a tarot consultation?
That's right. A tarot reading.
I guess it opened up again.
The tea has gone cold.
Let me brew a fresh pot for you.
-Thank you.
What do you plan on doing?
I'm going to ask the tarot cards.
-Were you being serious?
-Yes.
Just a fair warning.
Tarot should not be taken lightly.
Yes, ma'am.
Please ask a question.
Will I be able to successfully carry out
the task assigned to me?
Please select three cards.
What about this one?
This one?
Or whatever you want.
Right.
This one.
-And this one.
-Yes, that one.
The cards say you'll eventually succeed
though the process may be difficult.
Really?
This card specifically indicates success.
Does this mean our project will succeed?
What is it that makes you so happy?
It's about helping you live happily
and not get divorced.
Excuse me?
So for the tarot reading to be true,
I can't get divorced.
If I get divorced,
the tarot reading will be false.
Is that it?
This is a dilemma.
Maybe this is a sign from above
that you should reconsider things.
"A sign from above"?
We first met while walking
the Camino de Santiago.
One day, I experienced severe burnout.
So I quit my job
and got plane tickets on a whim.
Safe travels.
The person who held out his hand
while I was on the ground
was my current husband.
When we learned each other's names,
we were fascinated
because my name means "future"
while his name, Hyeon-jae,
means "present."
And that's how
we just started walking together.
-Don't your legs hurt?
-It's okay. We're going downhill.
When we saw 0 km on the Fisterra marker,
we hugged each other and cried.
-We need photos!
-Yes!
-Did you know?
-What?
When he shaved his beard,
I was shocked at how good-looking he was.
They say the Camino de Santiago
and Jeju Olle Trail
established a friendship pact.
Really?
Yes, so if you complete both trails,
you can get a dual completion certificate.
It's as if the end
of the Camino de Santiago
meets the beginning
of the Jeju Olle Trail.
It's a meaningful meeting.
You're right.
So…
Would you like to walk
the Jeju Olle Trail with me later?
That was his proposal.
We registered our marriage
as soon as we returned to Korea.
My husband is a documentary photographer.
He travels the world
to take photos of animals.
He's away for at least 3,500 hours
on each assignment.
We've never once gotten into a fight.
I'd rather that we fight all the time
like other married couples do.
I've spent more time alone
after getting married
than I have with him.
Actually, no.
I've always been alone.
I don't even know if he's dead or alive.
Now he's trying to photograph
Korean tigers.
That damn tiger!
I want to have a baby
and talk and laugh
as we watch them grow up.
That's the future I envisioned.
But he's only focused on the present,
just like his name.
I see.
I'm sure he's staying true to the present
to provide a better future.
If you still have feelings
for your husband…
You two should find a solution together.
Try and find one if you can.
If you do,
I'll take it as a sign from above.
Do you have any idea
where your husband might be?
No, not really.
But he tends to upload photos
of where he stays
as his profile pictures…
It's just green.
I'm just asking out of curiosity,
but do tigers really exist in our country?
They say they've gone extinct, sir.
But according to my husband,
they definitely exist
based on consistent witness accounts.
He got a tip from a hiker
who claimed he saw a tiger
at Balwangsan Mountain
in Gangwon Province last winter.
So he took photos
of footprints in the snow.
So it's possible they exist…
I'm sorry.
He drives an off-road car with antennas
that look like insect feelers.
If you see a man with a long beard
like a Puritan,
that'll be my husband.
Please let me know if you find him,
and I'll go there.
We'll find him and contact you.
-Thank you.
Let's go.
Long antennas and a beard…
Has a Puritan beard…
What place looks that green
at this time of year?
I'll do an image search.
Okay.
I think this is the place.
"Gorangae."
This is it, right?
Yes, I think so.
What's the address?
It's Gorangae Village, Daegiri,
Gangwon Province.
-Gorangae Village?
-Yes.
Let's get going.
What? Right now?
"If there are warning signs of divorce,
we must handle it within the golden hour."
Isn't that what you said?
Let's go.
You memorized it verbatim. Let's go, then.
PLUS GENERAL INSURANCE
CLEANING SUPPLIES BOX
A toy that uses inertia
and centrifugal force.
It's a thing of beauty.
It originally comes from
an indigenous weapon called a "bola."
There are many other theories,
but that's the most plausible one.
And yo-yo means
"to come back" in the Filipino language.
Let me see it.
Do you know how to yo-yo?
No.
I just need to put my finger in it
and throw it, right?
No, you'll get hurt.
You said yourself it's a weapon.
And this model isn't
exactly for beginners.
Watch carefully.
Slip the ring on the yo-yo's string
onto your middle finger.
And you can't just wind the string
any way you like.
Use your left index finger
and wind it once first.
Then the rest of your fingers
go like this.
Think of them as support.
Okay, I got it.
-Slip it on your finger.
-Like this?
No.
-The direction is…
You have to…
Like this.
Right, just like this.
Then the rest of your fingers
go like this.
Move this here…
And then the rest of your fingers
act as support.
Once you grip the yo-yo,
raise it to shoulder level,
then extend your arm and release it.
Extend and release.
No, not like that.
Release it at the last second.
It goes in this direction.
Release at the last second.
-Release at…
-Release at the last second.
Your palm should face up.
Hold the yo-yo
in this direction.
And raise your arm to shoulder level.
Release at the count of three.
One, two, three. Release.
Hey, it's spinning.
Eyes forward.
It won't come back up if it's crooked.
Now, give it a tug.
Damn it.
TRAVESTY
What in the world? He wants to video chat?
Jeez.
AN WUSS-MAN
-No, don't do it like that from behind.
-Right.
Don't touch me there.
I'm sorry. I'm just a bit flustered.
-Mr. An, calm down.
-I didn't mean to hug you.
-Just do it calmly.
-Is that okay?
Wait, hold on.
-Are you okay?
-Mr. An!
Just calm down and do it slowly.
-Just a moment.
-Right.
Please wait.
-Damn it.
-Did it get on you?
-Not that side. This side.
-I'm sorry.
Grab my arm, please.
-Seriously?
Who was it that made you panic?
Damn it, I'm screwed.
VIDEO CALL ENDED
It was probably nothing.
I'm sure there's a reasonable explanation.
Like our intimate mattress scene?
Exactly. This is nothing
compared to what we did.
Where's Ms. Joh right now?
She says she's almost here.
Here she is.
There you are, Ah-young.
-You're here.
-You made it.
Isn't this too much?
Why are we being asked to find someone?
Think of it as going camping
where there's a nice view.
You said it was a countryside village.
There's nothing to see.
Still, let's get going.
TRAVESTY
GO TO GORANGAE VILLAGE RIGHT NOW
Holy cow.
What is it now?
He said to go
to Gorangae Village right now.
Gorangae Village?
Mr. Na!
Hey, Nam Chang-hee!
You look like you're doing great.
Why are you so early?
I came down early myself.
"Always arrive 30 minutes prior."
It's one of the Ten Commandments of Sales
you taught me.
Jeez.
But my revered mentor called me,
so I came one hour early.
You can do anything you set your mind to.
Come on.
I'll treat you to some great coffee.
Thank you, sir.
-Amazing, right?
-Yes, sir.
This coffee is for executives only.
The crema that forms on top is amazing.
-It's only for executives?
-Yes.
There's a senior managing director
on my team.
She's my direct superior.
I'm her right-hand man.
I'm amazed you started as an agent
and became a team leader.
If you keep this up,
you might become an executive.
No, that's only possible for those
from prestigious backgrounds.
I actually made more money back then.
Then why did you…
I was caught up in making sales.
I didn't get a chance
to watch the kids grow up.
There were days when I had ten meals
because I had to meet clients.
But on some days, if the timing was off,
I'd starve the whole day.
Then I'd have to entertain clients
and drink all night long.
That's why I always have
digestive issues now.
Hey, it's ready.
Now then.
The 11th Commandment of Sales.
"Eat your meals on time."
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
So how is it?
Selling insurance must be tough.
I still like making sales
since you earn as much as you work.
That sounds about right
since you don't have a wife or kids yet.
You're still in your prime.
On that note…
Do you want to work with me?
-Excuse me?
-I need you to make sales for me.
But I'm already doing that.
No, not for existing insurance.
It's for a new one.
My team has developed
a new insurance product.
Divorce insurance.
Divorce insurance?
-Yes, it's this right here.
-Yes, sir.
We're still in the testing stage
and need to meet some goals,
but two contracts got rejected.
Can you take care of them?
Do you think you can do it?
That's not that many cases.
Yes, but this insurance
is unlike any other, so it won't be easy.
Still, I know the ropes.
I'll take care of it right away.
Jeez. Baby Chang-hee is all grown up now.
It's still nothing
compared to your level of passion.
I suppose so.
I was really something back then.
It's Carrot Man!
Hey there, kids!
Kids, what color balloon do you want?
Red for you. Bye now!
Purple. Orange.
Give this to your mom.
Bye!
Ma'am!
Your child will ride a bike
on their own one day, right?
If you want your kid
to ride their bike worry-free,
even if they bump into a luxury car,
please sign up
for Child Accident Protection insurance.
Now, please take your child to school!
Get the coverage you need
with Child Accident Protection.
Sir, please take one!
Please take one.
I miss it.
I was pretty passionate back then.
I'll introduce you to my team members
once they come back
from their business trip,
so can you help me out until then?
If we get through the testing stage
and officially launch this product,
I'll make you the executive distributor.
Don't you worry about a thing, sir.
Hey, have some lunch before you go.
I'm sorry. I have to go meet a client.
Come on. Didn't I say
to eat your meals on time?
It's okay.
I'll drink something healthy there.
You have a coffee machine at home, right?
Wait a minute.
-Take these.
-But they're expensive.
Just take them.
It's okay. Take them.
Thank you.
-Thanks.
-You're welcome.
GORANGAE VILLAGE
You said there's nothing to see
in the countryside.
The view is beautiful.
I'm glad we came.
Farmers these days
seem to have a totally new vibe.
They really are.
Gosh, nice moves.
Why does that guy look so familiar?
Why did you follow me here?
You followed me, Ms. Ah-young.
Are you crazy? Why would I do that?
This is my field, by the way.
What?
I told you I was a farmer.
I'm the head of this village.
It's napa cabbage from my farm.
I thought your father owned this building.
Actually, I'm a farmer.
You're the village head?
I can't believe we met again.
This must be fate.
-No, it's not.
-We met on a blind date, we're partnering,
and now we've met again,
so what else can it be but fate?
They went on a blind date?
And they're partnering?
No, that's not it.
It must be fate.
It really is.
Nice to meet you.
-He's impressive.
-Hush, Han-deul.
You're the head of this village?
-Yes.
-Please help us.
Excuse me?
GORANGAE COMMUNITY CENTER
Hey, insect feelers. It's this car, right?
-Yes, it is.
-That's right.
There's footage of it coming in
but not leaving.
That means it's still in the village.
Yes.
There are only two ways to handle
food and accommodation in this village.
Either stay at a guesthouse
or camp in your car.
There are 32 households in the village
but only two places for car camping.
The first Resting Area
and second Resting Area near Windy Hill.
But some people make their way
up to Deulmeori Forest.
Okay, then let's split into two groups.
Ms. Ah-young and I
will search the village.
I don't want to.
It's a long way to the resting area.
It'll be easier
if you search the village with me.
We'll let the elderly
go on the long journey.
-All right, then.
-"Elderly"?
That's fine. The elders will go
on the long journey.
I almost forgot.
Have you chosen your accommodations?
Accommodations?
I can just sleep in my car, but…
I didn't think that far ahead.
We can drive home later tonight
if necessary.
Will you come back
if you don't find him today?
I know a farmhouse where you can stay.
I'll talk to the owner.
There are lots of rooms there,
and my dear Ms. Ah-young needs to sleep.
"My dear Ah-young"?
It's the house way over there
with the red windmill.
Please come down before sunset.
It's a high-altitude area,
so the weather is fickle,
and it can get dark quickly.
-Okay.
-Okay, see you later.
Okay. Oh, by the way…
Please be careful.
It's easy to get lost
with all the winding paths.
Don't worry about a thing.
I'm a human GPS.
-Then we'll see you two later.
-Okay.
Watch your step.
Just make sure you get back soon.
Shall we go, elder?
Yes.
Let's go to that village first.
-Look.
-What?
WINDY HILL
GARDEN OF HEALING
-It's this way.
-Let's go.
Let's go.
This must be the place.
But it's not here.
-Let's go up farther.
-Okay.
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
Just take my hand.
It's steeper than we thought.
I'm coming. Jeez, you're in great shape.
-We're almost there.
-Right.
Ms. Kang.
-Can we slow down a bit, please?
-It's over there.
Man, I'm dying.
-How on earth are you so fit?
-We're here.
Insect feelers.
It's the insect feeler car.
-Let's check it out.
-Insect feeler car.
-Those are feelers, right?
-Yes.
-It's a camera!
-It is!
-We found him!
-Nice job.
-Hello, sir.
-Hello.
I guess it's not him.
Right.
Let's go up and look for him some more.
Be careful. It's slippery.
Watch your step.
Be careful.
Come down slowly. Watch your step.
-It's slippery.
-Right.
Thank you.
Watch your step.
Be careful and climb up slowly.
-Hurry. Is it…
-Where?
Is it supposed to be like this?
Let's go this way for now.
There's nothing here.
Hold on.
It's already gotten this late.
The sun is about to set.
-We should head back. It's dangerous.
-Right.
-Where are we going?
-Let's go this way.
Ms. Kang, you'll die
if you fall asleep here.
-I won't die.
-Yes, you will.
I think the sun is setting.
-Watch your step here.
-What?
It all looks the same,
so I can't tell where we are.
I know, right?
Why does everything look the same?
I think we've been here before.
Does your GPS not work?
GPS never works in places like this.
Where are we?
-You must be tired.
-I'm okay.
I'm sure if we go this way…
What's this?
It's raining.
-What should we do?
-Hey, it's raining.
Oh, jeez.
Are you okay? I'm okay too.
I think we're going deeper
into the mountain.
Are you sure GPS won't work here?
Actually,
my battery died a while ago.
What about yours?
If I still had any battery left,
I'd have called Ah-young ages ago.
I'm not using it because it's dead.
Yes, of course.
Don't worry about it.
We can find our way back.
All paths are connected to each other.
-This isn't the time for bravado.
-Because the Earth is round.
I'm afraid we'll come across
something scary here.
Seriously? Why would you say that?
SPECIAL THANKS TO HAN SEON-HWA AND
KWAK SI-YANG FOR THEIR GUEST APPEARANCES
Right. I forgot I called you.
You forgot you called me?
On what basis did you call
the team members here to Gangwon Province?
I didn't call you, Ms. Jeon.
I'm asking as your ex-ex-ex-wife.
What's going on between you two?
Are you sure it's over?
We didn't even last a season.
Does the other person think so too?
What's wrong with me?
You found my husband?
There's nothing we can do but wait.
We'll just have to wait
and hope for the box to open.
What if it opens
and the outcome turns out to be a divorce?
I think it's too late.
If I see Mi-rae right now,
I think we'll really get divorced.
So we're just going to
let them get a divorce?
Can we pull that off by today?
And for less than 30,000 won at that?
Do you like hanging out with Mr. Noh?
You seem to be
in desperate need of escape.
Can you help me escape?
If you want to make a confession,
go to a priest.
I haven't committed a sin yet,
so it's not a confession.
We're not a good match.
It's too slow, rough, and uneven.
Then I'll take that as you giving up
and claim the green one for myself.
Subtitle: Jenny Kim