Lady Sin communicated with the deposed King and committed a grave crime by helping him escape.
As her crime is of an extreme degree, she will be publicly executed.
- Your Highness!
- Your Highness the Queen!
You knew that our fates should never have crossed.
Now, I finally understand my father's words.
But, if we have already met and fallen in love,
I must take responsibility for that.
Your Majesty!
Is the Royal Secretary here?  What about the Captain of Royal Guards?
No, it's not that.
- Your Highness!
- She's so pitiful!
The execution time was pushed forward? Who? Why?!
Her Highness the Queen Dowager gave the command
as she reasoned it was impossible to know what the escaped deposed King is planning.
In this life, I wish to protect that love through death.
Do you have any last words?
No.
Proceed with the deposed Queen Sin's execution!
If I am reborn,
I will never meet you, Your Majesty.
Halt!
- Your Majesty!
Chae Gyeong!
Chae Gyeong! Chae Gyeong...
Why did you end up like this?! Why?!
Let's go.
Move aside.
You said that this location was where the deposed King last slept.
I recently sent soldiers to scout this entire area but we couldn't find him.
Then searching through his relatives' houses will be the quickest.
Tell His Majesty that I will do as he wishes. I'll hand over the criminals.
What's the reason you've suddenly changed your mind?
There's no time to argue about that.
Because Sin Chae Gyeong's execution time was suddenly pushed forward, His Majesty had to personally race to the execution site.
What about Her Highness the Queen?
Although she's alive for now, His Majesty will also be put in a difficult situation if we don't hurry.
- Where are the culprits?
- Go to Mapo Port.
Mapo Port... Let's go!
Yes, sir!
Seok Hee and Gwang Ho
moved Seo No's grave to Dongjukjeon Village yesterday.
Yes, I heard.
You didn't come.
I was occupied with the merchant groups' work.
I even went to that merchant group and received a report that you did not show up for 3 days! On top of that,
I also received a report that you were seen at Yeokcham, Gimpo near the lodge that my brother last slept in.
Why did you do it?
Is this the world you so desperately wanted?
How did we end up like this?
I'll give you a chance to set things straight.
This is truly your last chance.
Your Majesty, the Captain of the Royal Guard requests to be in your presence.
Allow him to enter.
Your Majesty, I captured the real culprits involved in the deposed King's escape.
His Majesty the King is entering!
We greet you, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, these are the bandits who ambushed the dethroned King on his path to exile.
Why did you do it?
I-I've committed a crime worthy of death!
I asked, why did you do it?
We were... ordered to.
What order?
A-attack the deposed King and intentionally
- create a situation where he can escape—
- Eunuch Kim!
Yes, I intentionally delivered the news of the First Vice Premier's death.
I planned it so that the deposed King would run to the First Vice Premier's residence when he escaped.
Who? Who is it?
Who ordered such a thing?
Answer me!
The Right State Councillor.
I'm wronged, Your Majesty!
You're wronged?
Eunuch Kim is the deposed King's person.
He's plotting revenge by creating a rift in our relationship, Your Majesty!
The Right State Councillor's words are correct. You cannot just listen to their words and accuse him without a proper investigation!
That is correct, Your Majesty!
More than anything, the Right State Councillor has given both his mental and material support towards your crowning
and is your best subject.
Your Majesty, please be unbiased and conduct a proper investigation!
Of course I will. I cannot believe just one witness
and punish an official of this nation.
I'm honored, Your Majesty.
Lock the criminals in their cells. I will investigate and punish accordingly!
Drag them away and lock them in the cells!
Yes, Captain!
Are you planning to concede the Queen's position to that Sin wench?!
It's not conceding. It was never mine in the first place.
Shut it! If you're going to spout such nonsense, leave for Ming immediately.
Even if you're not here, I have many ways to accomplish my goal.
In the end, you tried to kill her?
If Chae Gyeong dies in your hands because of your decision,
how do you expect me to live?
That child's parents and all her relatives died
in your hands because of your decision.
But, do you believe that she can forget that fact
and you can live together without suspecting and resenting each other?
You're already unable to look directly into her eyes now
because you're sorry, miserable, and anxious.
Are my words wrong?
Your words are correct.
There are times when I cannot look at her directly.
But if I express with words,
touch with my hands, and embrace with my heart,
there will be a time when a scratch on the heart can heal.
There will be a time when it will get better.
"At times like this, we should always be together
and tell each other "I love you",
tell one another how much we love each other, embrace one another, and treasure each other. That's what a married couple does!"
Chae Gyeong told me that.
So Royal Mother,
please leave the two of us alone.
I desperately beg of you.
Who are you?
My name is Seo No.
My thoughts were wrong.
Since you're not beside me anymore,
I thought that it didn't matter how I lived from now on.
I heard that love is respecting the decisions of the person you love and resembling each other in thought.
That's why love is difficult.
I realized the moment I saw Sin Chae Gyeong,
true love is respecting the decision of the person you love,
even if it leads to your death.
So, I'll save the woman whom you treasured so much,
Sin Chae Gyeong,
and through this, I'll repay my debts to you.
Chae Gyeong...
Chae Gyeong!
Your Highness the Grand Prince.
Are you all right?
What happened?
What were you thinking when you saved me?!
What about you? What were you thinking?
You should have said that it was all a lie, a false accusation!
You should have requested me to catch whoever framed you!
You should have flailed and shouted that you were framed!
How could you have thoughts of dying?
What if there is something I'm more afraid of than death?
What do I do then?
What if there is something I must put my life on the line to protect?
What should I do then?
Chae Gyeong.
Why can't I entirely become your woman?
Your Majesty, I resent myself.
For the first time, I regret that I am me.
You courageously survived after losing that much blood.
What about Chae Gyeong? What happened to her?
Don't worry, Her Highness the Queen is safe.
You're not in a situation where you can move as you wish.
Let me go.
Do you have a reason you must survive?
This is something I started.
I have to finish it.
His Highness the Grand Prince used this for a long time.
He lived for five years without being able to properly breathe, walk, or smile.
Now, it is your turn.
Where did it go?
Goodness, that scared me.
Why are you serving a spoon as if it's a god?
When your mother bought your dowry, she requested that I keep this.
You never know who will attempt to harm you. That's why...
your meals should always be served in metal bowls
and you should always eat with a silver spoon.
(They believed that a silver spoon or a metal dish would be discolored if the food was poisoned.)
Goodness, I said something I shouldn't have.
Because you fear I might die?
My Lady...
This isn't living.
Even if you live for just a day, you shouldn't live like this.
What should we do?
Everyone, including Eunuch Kim, has committed suicide.
It seems the Right State Councillor's faction has gagged them.
Your Majesty, the witnesses to prove Her Highness the Queen's innocence
have all died.
We can no longer believe the witnesses' initial testimonies
regarding Her Highness the Queen's innocence.
We don't know where the deposed King is or what he is planning.
We cannot leave Her Highness the Queen alone when she is the sole witness and accomplice.
You must depose Her Highness the Queen. For the sake of the Royal Family and the Court—
I will not allow it.
Anyone who continues to accuse the Queen
and requests her deposal without new evidence
will be punished for the crime of scorning the Royal Family.
Your Majesty, please do not reject our loyalty!
Please understand!
We came this far.
If we give up now, we'll be giving up right before the summit.
Who placed the current King on the throne?
It's all thanks to us. We risked our lives and fought against the tyrannical Yeonsangun.
But now, His Majesty has chosen to close his eyes and ears and is rejecting the cries of his subjects.
Therefore, we must deliver the will of the people, the will of the Heavens, to His Majesty!
Our Snail Brides must continue
to uphold the order of the Heavens
and deliver the will of the people and the Heavens to His Majesty!
Yes, My Lord!
I will leave for Ming.
Didn't I tell you to leave?
But, what's the use of your actions now?
Without me, the Queen's position is useless.
So for our lives and our clan's safety,
please do not create anymore tension with His Majesty and instead—
You still have a long way to go.
Do you think you're my only niece?
No, nieces are useless when I  also have a daughter.
Look here, allow her to enter!
Yes, My Lordship.
Father, did you call for me?
Uncle!
Introduce yourself, she's my adopted daughter.
You're planning to make your adopted daughter into His Majesty's Queen?
There's no reason I can't.
I'll become the King's father-in-law.
His Majesty the King is entering!
Your Majesty, you're here.
Are you feeling better?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Did you have a dispute with your subordinates again today, Your Majesty?
Without any disputes, how am I supposed to run the nation?
I heard that there has been a dispute about me for days now, Your Majesty.
Who's been talking about such useless nonsense?!
We apologize, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty.
I don't really know much about the customs and manners of the royal family.
However, in non-royal households, they cut off the ribbon of the hanbok's jacket
to bid farewell.
Chae Gyeong. Chae Gyeong.
If I don't cut it off first,
I know that you will never let me go.
I would like to divorce you, Your Majesty.
Please grant me permission.
Your Majesty.
My answer,
you obviously know what it is.
Reconciliation, overcoming obstacles, courage,
resolutions, promises, and consolation...
We can be together and do those things.
We have so much we can do for each other.
Why is it that you want to say goodbye before even trying anything?!
I put you through so much, and when I think about that, I just can't bring myself to do this.
No, it won't happen.
Your Majesty.
When you were Young Master Nak Cheon in the past,
you pushed me away with all those lies.
Please recall how you felt at the time.
Out of all those lies you told,
the only truth was regarding my safety.
Isn't that right, Your Majesty?
The only thing that I also hope for is
your safety,  Your Majesty.
And also for that path that you'll be taking
there will be Seo No, my parents,
and there will be many people in this nation of Joseon who will put all their hopes in you.
So please be determined to carry on your duty
and achieve all your goals.
Afterwards, you can come to me.
Why can't we go on that path together?
Because there is a constant threat of death.
Both you and I are always on the verge of death.
As long as we are together, this will never end.
Now you have finally become the ruler of this nation.
So now you have to be finally afraid of death.
So, you should try to survive at all costs.
Chae Gyeong!
Perhaps the best way we can comfort each other is
by surviving through it all.
So, the two of us being alive and well for a long, long time
will be proof of our endless love for each other.
If I live for one year,
then I will be loving you for a year.
If I live for ten years, then I'll be loving for ten years.
If I live for 100 years,
then I will be loving you for 100 years.
Yes.
If we are both alive, even if we are not together
that in itself
is us loving each other through all the years.
There will be a lot of important things to do
and although you may have left home temporarily,
that home will still remain as it did before.
Can't that home be here?
This home belongs to the Queen.
I am just Sin Chae Gyeong.
♫  Waiting for me at the place where we  first met.  ♫
♫  Sorry, I didn't know so please forgive me.  ♫
♫  Please don't go, so I can see you again.  ♫
♫  I will love once again. You.  ♫
♫  Forever and ever ...  us.  ♫
Look over here.
Move away, move away.
Read this over here.
Read that.
Yes, that's true.
He's coming.
My goodness.
Oh my.
His Majesty is entering.
We greet you, Your Majesty.
I've been hearing that there was a lot of commotion in the capital last night.
And they say that the Snail Brides have been active again.
Have you seen it by any chance, Right State Councillor?
Your Majesty, how could that only be the will of the Snail Brides?
I saw the people of this nation uniting with one voice and one mind as I was entering the palace.
Oh, so you saw?
Yes, that's right, Your Majesty.
You might be able to ignore the voices of the governing officials, but the will of the heavens and the people
should never be ignored.
You're right.
I should not do that.
So then, about the deposing of the Queen...
It seems you got it all wrong.
What in the world is this?
- Your Majesty!
- Park Won Jong,  during the process of confiscating the wealth of the deposed king's close associates,
Shim Geun Son, Kim Sook Hwa,
Choi Sook Won, and Jang Son's homes which were confiscated for practically nothing
he expanded his own home and built many living quarters all over the place.
Park Won Jong was also responsible for the members of the rebel faction named Jo Gye Hyeong and Kim Soo Gyeong
by having meetings with them periodically.
And sold the low level government administrators' posts in the provinces which they requested.
The meeting itself is all about collecting bribes. And there also is a notorious rumor going around by officials...
Your Majesty! This is a false accusation!
Bring in the witness.
Bring the witness in.
I don't know them, Your Majesty.
How could you...
Are you going to try to get out of this by killing all the witnesses again?
Do you have anything more to say?
Royal Secretary.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Strip Right State Councillor Park Won Jong of his government position.
And confiscate all of his wealth, that he obtained unlawfully.
And punish him for what he did by exiling him.
Your Majesty! This is all a plot to frame me!
I've been wronged!
If this man acknowledges his crime and shows any remorse, I'll stop right here.
But if he keeps on denying and pretending that he didn't do anything wrong,
then I will take this as him scorning me.
I will punish him by execution
and annihilate all his relatives for high treason!
I will uphold your command.
Your Majesty.... You cannot do this.
Your Majesty!
Your Highness the Queen.
You're leaving?
I apologize for causing you concern.
There's nothing to apologize for.
Add this to your living.
What can you do when there is a fate where you must separate to protect each other?
Please protect him, even if it's from a distance.
I'll remember your words.
Your Majesty!
From now on, because my day consists of loving and missing you,
to love and miss you even more,
I will survive and survive again.
Like that, we find our own ways to protect each other.
"I... never escaped,
so Queen Sin has never helped me escape."
You must deliver this message.
Your Majesty, the Captain of the Royal Guard is here!
Allow him to enter.
Your Majesty, the deposed King Lee Yoong came to his exile location on his own.
He even sent a handwritten statement
that he never intended to escape and that Queen Sin was framed.
Hyungnim must have also wanted to save Chae Gyeong.
After your parting without acknowledgement, only a sense of helplessness grows...
As the winds grow stronger every day and night, I am gravely concerned for Your Majesty's health.
As your vigor would be drained at this month of the year, if possible, please refrain from drinking
and maintain your vigor by foods and herbal tonics that replenish your energy.
As I think of you every night, my heart sinks.
I beg that my earnestness is transmitted through Your Majesty's health and heart.
Hyungnim!
Hyungnim, are you all right?
Yeok...
Yeok, is that you?
Yes, I'm Yeok.
I'm here.
I came to see you.
Leave. Do you know what this place is?
What pathetic sight did you come to see?
How much more are you planning to laugh at me?!
Hyungnim!
Hyungnim,  Hyungnim...
Have you regained your consciousness?
Do you see me now?
How vain and futile...
I wanted to prove that Royal Father's decision was wrong,
but in no time,
just like he predicted, I became a tyrannical king.
I resembled my mother,
who became blinded by jealousy and destroyed herself.
Yeok.
Yes?
I never hated you.
I hated the person who was reflected in your eyes, me.
And the person who had the exact same eyes as you,
Chae Gyeong's eyes...
I was ashamed to look into those eyes.
So I tried to kill you and tried to ruin you.
I just...  hated and resented myself.
In the end, because I separated you two,
I was punished and left in this state.
That's what it is...
H-Hyungnim!
The punishment I did not receive in this life,
I'll receive in death.
He's here.
Finally, he's... reaching his hand out to me.
Hyungnim...
Hyung—
You should've at least had a meal with me before you left!
In a world void of
hate,
resentment, and uneasiness, please,
please rest comfortably.
Aunt.  ( Deposed Queen Sin, wife of the deposed king and aunt of Sin Chae Gyeong)
I brought some snacks.
I was making some cotton clothing to send to His Majesty and the Crown Prince
because I wasn't able to give His Majesty a birthday present.
I'll help.
My Lady!
Someone from the palace— no, from Gyo-Dong is here.
The deposed King has passed away.
Royal Mother, happy birthday!
Crown Prince, isn't this a hair-pin? How did you...
Do you like it?
- Of course I do!
- You should try it on!
Tell Yeok to become King.
Then in his place, I'll become Chae Gyeong's husband,
the First Vice Premier's son-in-law, and your
son and live like that.
Your Majesty,
in our next life,
please be born as my daughter.
I'll treasure you greatly.
Your Majesty...
It seems the horse is exhausted. Let's rest here for a moment.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Highness the Queen.
Eunuch Song.
His Majesty the King is in front of the house right now.
He said his horse is exhausted and wants to rest for a moment.
Please wait. I'll boil some horse feed.
Her Highness the Queen said she would boil some horse feed.
Boil horse feed?
What about me? Didn't she ask for me?
Chae Gyeong.
Please feed your horse this.
Sin Chae Gyeong.
I apologize for not being able to greet you.
I'm sorry, I'll get another bowl.
Can't you show me your face just once?
If I just push this door, we can meet.
Do you truly expect me to leave like this?
"No",
please just say that one word.
Then I will open this door, run to you,
and embrace you.
Did you forget?
To have to see each other,
to have to be together, to have hands touch, aren't the only ways to love.
We are different from others, so we decided that not being together and not meeting,
that is how we would protect our love for each other.
Are you wavering already?
Do you truly wish for me to leave like this?
Dragon
Husband! Grand Prince!
Husband!
♫   Suddenly the whole world is filled by you  ♫
♫   Suddenly you were there without a sound  ♫
This won't do, Chae Gyeong. I can't live without you.
Don't go.
Let us be together.
♫  What do I do now when my breath is about to stop?    ♫
♫   I want to hold you   ♫
♫   the one whose brilliance chillls my heart   ♫
What's this?
♫   I'm afraid you might fly away   ♫
It's a perfect fit.
♫   when the wind blows   ♫
♫   Because your smile and tears fill my heart,   ♫
♫    I will always love only you   ♫
It's a son!  A son!
♫   can't be secretly hidden   ♫
♫    We can't turn back because you are here.   ♫
♫    Saying I love you even   ♫
♫     without saying the words   ♫
♫    I can't let you leave my embrace   ♫
♫   I want to hold you, the one whose brilliance chills my heart   ♫
♫   I'm afraid you  might fly away when the wind blows   ♫
♫   Because your smile and tears    ♫
Chae Gyeong...
Your Majesty, I am very grateful for your desire to reinstate me.
However, Your Majesty already has a prince, your first son.
If I were to re-enter the palace to be Queen, the child that would be born from me
would be engulfed in the royal power struggle.
Please consider that happened to Your Majesty and Your Majesty's older brother.
In this world, for another story as tragic as the story of you two brothers
to occur again wouldn't be something you'd desire.
Nanny, the sleeve...
One hand-width.
And the shoulders...
One span of hand too.  One span.
Then add more to... Oh, seriously.
Why didn't you just borrow a set of clothes from him? What suffering is this!
I'm not smart so my body has to suffer.
What's the brain for?
How painful was it?
How frightening was it?
We cannot allow ourselves to recreate that tragedy again.
For me, Your Majesty,
living strong for us,
is already more than enough.
Thirty-eight years later. 1544. 39th year  of Jungjong's reign.
Eunuch Song.
Yes, Your Majesty.
His Majesty's royal body is indisposed.
Open all gates that lead to the Grand Palace.
Do not control the entrances and exits. And do not place guards.
Gangnyeong Palace (King's residence)
Thank you to the entire History Tellers' Team
Thank you to Channel Manager auroratasya
Thank you to segmenters: pilar_velasquez, kitty100, gesti_lagi, Jazmineheart, bagy,
Thank you to segmenters, cont.: andres15_867, walter_casa,  ashnita_chetty03, bjjohnsonwong, Amypun
Thank you to segmenters, cont.: c_scott, nanajie, mihaelagh, robertases, whit_eonni,  and luckylauper
Thank you to Korean to English subbers: lunarwolf523, itgirlfornow, elisem1902,
Thank you to Korean to English subbers, cont:  pikasquirtchar014, dramadramaok,  hyung529, sophie2you
Thank you to editors: Cgwm808 (chief). signsofserendipity,  elisem1902, irmar and sophie2you
Grand Prince!
Grand Prince, when did you arrive?
Bird poop, did you wait long?
I'm used to waiting for you.
Am I too late?
No. You're not late at all.
It's been very hard for you.
I am so proud of you.
You endured through it all very well.
Because I knew you were waiting, I could endure it.
Because I knew you were there in that place,
I also could protect my place.
Now, I will be by your side, my husband.
So please rest comfortably at home now.
Now I've finally come home.
I pine for you.  I admire you.
I love you, my husband.
You can just do one.
♫  Dearest, leave in peace now.  ♫
♫  You are waking up from a harsh dream.  ♫
♫  As time passes, as you count the seasons   ♫
♫  Will you be able to forget even the painful memories?   ♫
♫  The feeling it was all my fault festers in my heart  ♫
♫  This heart is tinged with the color red    ♫
♫  Just know that you are drenched by the sunset  ♫
♫  It's alright. Leave in peace.   ♫
♫  Do not turn back.  ♫
♫  Do not worry.   ♫
♫  Don't dwell over past memories.  ♫