Timing and Subtitles brought to you by the âš–ï¸Crossed PathsðŸ”— Team @ Viki.com
Son Hyun Joo
♫  Just a look across the sidewalk.  ♫&lt;
Kim Myung Min
♫  Love.  ♫
♫  That's your little life hug.  ♫
Kim Do Hoon
Heo Nam Joon
♫  Someday we'll come when this makes sense  ♫
♫ But for now, it's time to rest  ♫
Your Honor
This is a work of fiction.
Characters, places, organizations, incidents, names, ethnic groups, and settings are unrelated to reality.
Therefore, the defendant, Kim Sang Hyeok,
is hereby found not guilty.
Police Line / Do Not Cross!
Judge Song Pan Ho!
Detective Jang Chae Rim...
is dead.
Your Honor: Episode 10
Final Episode
Don't you want revenge?
Do you know how many people died because of what you did?
Script based on series "Kvodo" by Ohad Knoller, Shlomo Moshiah and Ron Ninio
I'm sure he doesn't know
that it wasn't an accident
but a planned murder.
I'm sure he'll take it all the way!
The one who colluded with him is named Tee Rab.
He's the punk Song Pan Ho shot to death that time.
Tee Rab's girlfriend apparently testified.
I'll meet that woman and verify.
Woo One Group's oldest son, Kim Sang Hyeok,
was found not guilty at the first trial.
I am deeply thankful for the fair trial
and the judge's decision that created the fair trial,
and the team of attorneys who...
stood for my innocence to the end.
After the verdict hearing, as his attorney left the Woowon District Court...
Until the day we die...
will we be able to get out of Kim Kang Heon's grasp?
Kim Sang Hyeok's younger brother, the late Kim Sang Hyeon...
On this day, the Criminal Judges Panel of Woowon District Court
refused to uphold most of Kim Sang Hyeok's charges claimed by the prosecution
saying, "There is no proof of crime in all of the charges in this case."
Meanwhile, the stock price for Woo One Group,
owned by Kim Sang Hyeok's father,
Chairman Kim Kang Heon, rose more than two percent immediately after the acquittal.
Woo One Group's stock price went down to 143,000 won in early trading,
down about three percent from the previous session,
but rose more than two percent after the trial began in the afternoon...
Kang So Yeong
Dad
Oppa, do you want to take a look around this side, too?
Sure.
Oppa, our house is pretty, right?
Yes, it's pretty.
He started planning it six months before the accident.
A punk named Tee Rab and a woman named Mi Ram hung around Sang Hyeon
and found out he'd receive a motorcycle for his birthday.
On his birthday, he followed Sang Hyeon.
And the accident happened.
Should I kick him out?
No, let him be.
He might threaten Eun.
He might do something terrible to Eun—
I'm sorry.
I'll go get changed into something more comfortable. Sit here and wait a bit.
Okay.
I didn't think...
such a thing could be possible.
The possibility that
meek young kid could've murdered my child intentionally.
The bastard who intentionally murdered Sang Hyeon
is with my daughter right now.
What could he want?
Does he want to avenge his dead mom?
How dare he? Against me?
He must've approached my daughter, Eun, intentionally as well.
What's he trying to do?
I'll take him away.
Please don't do anything.
All I wanted was...
to get my eldest acquitted and
help the rest of my family members
go on peacefully as they did before Sang Hyeon's accident.
Were they...
Were they such difficult things to achieve?
He's still a young child.
I'll accept the consequences of his crimes.
I was planning to kill you
and put an end to the entire situation.
But that wasn't the answer.
Did you say your name is Ho Yeong?
Hello.
Thank you for...
protecting my Eun.
See you later.
Yes.
Dad
Who's this?
Are you mute?
Who the f*** are you?
Oppa!
- Oppa, you're home already?
- Yes.
This is my oldest oppa.
Mom said the dinner's ready, so we should get going.
Okay.
But who's this?
Is he the boyfriend you mentioned last time, Eun?
Yes, it's Oppa Ho Yeong.
Nice to meet you.
By the way, didn't we meet somewhere?
Not sure.
Let's get going.
Oppa, come.
All right. Thank you.
You can come over.
Relax and be at home.
- And come visit often.
- Okay.
Have a seat.
Prosecutor's Office
The person you are calling is on another line.
You'll be connected to voicemail
and there will be an additional charge after the beep.
Press one to record a voice message.
Press two to leave your phone number.
After the beep, please record your message
and press the star or pound key.
If you'll ignore me to the end,
I'll also do what I can.
Please, not my son.
You had made... You made a promise to me!
You promised to spare my son!
I did everything you told me to do!
N-No, that's not it. I'm sorry.
There were times I deceived you to spare myself.
I'm so sorry.
I apologize, Chairman.
I'm sorry.
I'll be the judge of my decision and action.
Wait, don't hang up.
Don't hang up!
Son of a bitch...
How nice it would've been if Sang Hyeon were here with us.
It must've been tough for you all this time.
It wasn't that tough, really.
Everything was possible, just like living outside.
You provided for me, didn't you, Father?
But is he a decent guy?
Good enough to be invited to a dinner?
What do you think about Eun?
Isn't she a bit frustrating?
She talks and acts slowly.
No, Eun is a very kind person.
She's the kindest person I've met in my life.
Prosecutor Kang So Yeong
Do you like my Eun a lot?
- Yes.
- How much?
How much do you like her?
Prosecutor Kang So Yeong
Gosh, Father.
That's the most troublesome question for men.
What's the matter?
Two years ago...
Woo One's eldest son, Kim Sang Hyeok,
was investigated by the police for allegations of sexual assault.
You really haven't met me...
before?
I have.
When?
Precisely two years and three months ago.
Two years and three months ago?
That's quite specific.
Where did you see me?
In front of Gangam Police Station in Woowon City.
I saw you leaving after getting interrogated on a rape case.
This moron isn't normal.
Ho Yeong suffers from asthma.
He has difficulty breathing whenever he's sad or angry.
I'm sorry, Oppa.
The victim was Jo Eun Hye, Song Ho Yeong's mom.
As is fitting for Woo One,
the case was dismissed.
Song Ho Yeong held a grudge for that and
murdered your biological son, Kim Sang Hyeon.
He planned the murder for six months
and committed a murder disguised as a car accident.
Tee Rab, who colluded with him, turned up dead.
And Mi Ram, Tee Rab's girlfriend, is alive.
This is what I heard from Mi Ram.
He prepared meticulously to kill your son for six months.
That guy...
is probably with your daughter right now.
The victim was a woman named Jo Eun Hye.
The case was dismissed with no charges.
And that woman
took her own life a month later.
- That was my mom.
- Enough.
This is enough?
Do you people have no regard for what kind of emotion
other people harbor as they go on?
Have you ever even imagined
the hell your victims have to live in?
Oppa, please don't do this. What's the matter?
Don't do this.
D-Dad, I'm sorry!
Get out of my house.
Don't ever show up in front of my Eun again.
Oh, f***! Jo Eun Hye...
Who was Jo Eun Hye?
Man, I have no idea who the f*** she was.
Lies.
How...
How can you not remember?
How can you not remember her?
How can you not even remember her?
Ho Yeong.
Ho Yeong, Ho Yeong.
Please...
Please, Ho Yeong...
Stop it now.
Your father, Song Pan Ho, is on his way here.
Don't do what you'll regret and put the gun down.
Eun, hurry up and go to your room. Hurry.
I'll see this to the end.
No, I'm already at the end.
I've nowhere else to go.
Think of what you've done!
Each person's life holds different values!
My mom was more valuable than hundreds or thousands of trashy people like you!
Killing your entire family wouldn't be enough!
Oppa...
please don't do this. Please?
Please don't do this.
Don't do this. Please?
- I need to go in right now.
- You can't just enter. We'll search you first.
My son is in there. I'll just take him and leave.
Eun, don't.
Take your hand off the gun right now!
Don't do this, Oppa.
I'm sorry, Eun. I'm really sorry.
Oppa, don't do this.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
Ho Yeong!
- What is it?
- There were gunshots inside—
Ho Yeong!
My Sang Hyeon was innocent.
It's over. That's enough now.
My Sang Hyeon didn't do anything wrong.
It's all over. It's fine.
It's fine. It's fine now.
It's fine now.
Why the f*** would you grab there?
O-Oppa... Oppa...
O-Oppa, Oppa!
Oppa... Wh-Why? Oppa...
O-Oppa...
Why?
Oppa, wh-why? Oppa...
I'm sorry.
O-Oppa, you can't. Oppa!
- I'm sorry.
- Oppa...
No, Oppa!
No, Oppa, Oppa...
Oppa... Oppa!
Ho Yeong...
Hey... Hey, let's go.
Hey.
Let's go.
Let's go...
Police
Ho Yeong.
He was shot three times and died at the scene.
He was already dead when he was transferred to the ambulance.
The perpetrator is being interrogated by the police right now.
Ho Yeong.
Let's go.
L-Let's go, Ho Yeong...
I don't know where that kid got it,
but he had a loaded pistol.
He threatened the Chairman and his family
and was about to shoot.
Because protecting them is my job,
I took out the gun I had and opened fire.
Where did you get the gun?
In the outskirts of this city, a gun is easier to buy than marijuana.
That must be how he got a gun.
I want to ask you now.
Isn't it your fault that even kids like him could get a gun and
attempt to kill people?
KCSI Lee Jae Gyeong
Yes.
Yes, the fingerprint identification is done.
Out of the two guns collected at the scene,
only Song Ho Yeong's fingerprints were found on the first evidence item
and only Park Chang Hyeok's fingerprints were found on the second evidence item.
I got it.
Shit.
You people will definitely pay for
the crimes you committed,
whether it's in 10 or in 100 years.
Shouldn't you catch the guy who sold the gun to Song Ho Yeong?
Shit!
The only way for you to live is
confessing to selling the gun to Song Ho Yeong. Okay?
Gun trafficking only gets you a few years.
F*** you, Woo One!
I killed him too quickly.
I should've made him suffer more than
my Sang Hyeon did.
I'm sure other people would've had no choice but to do the same.
If you hadn't done it, I would've done it.
Forget about it.
What's important is the lives of those left behind.
You'll have to go to the police as a material witness for a few days.
After the interrogation ends,
take Eun and go stay in Switzerland.
After things settle and emotions calm down,
you can come back here and
live on as if nothing happened.
We have nothing more to lose.
Did Ho Yeong...
really do that...
to Sang Hyeon?
Why?
Did Ho Yeong...
die?
Eun, wake up. Eun!
It seems Ho Yeong bought a gun from someone named Kwon Wu Cheol
and sought out Kim Kang Heon.
There were gunshots fired inside the house.
Chairman Kim Kang Heon's secretary Park Chang Hyeok killed Ho Yeong
with a gun he had illegally. That's how the case is being built.
- Who really killed him—
- Enough.
That's enough.
Who really killed him
or if it was in self-defense...
None of that matters right now.
What matters
is what led us to this
and what have I done wrong?
Of course...
up until this point,
I've committed many wrongdoings.
However, if it meant I could protect Ho Yeong,
I believed I could do anything.
I gave my all in trying to save Ho Yeong.
"Let's just protect Ho Yeong."
Then, no matter what happened,
I thought it wouldn't matter.
But now,
Ho Yeong is dead.
How on earth...
did I lose my most precious son
when all I did...
was to try to protect him?
Dad.
Once you've recovered,
let's go somewhere far away with Mom
and quietly rest there
until everything has been forgotten.
Okay.
Thank you, my daughter.
I'm sorry, Dad.
Don't be, Eun.
You've done nothing wrong.
Everything is my fault.
I'm the one who's sorry.
I'm sorry.
Woowon Gangam Police Station
Please state what you witnessed at the scene.
We'll give you a separate answer to that in writing.
Ma Ji Yeong, who did that gun belong to?
- I—
- We'll also respond to that in writing.
I've committed sins.
Thinking you were just an oblivious child.
Deluding myself into thinking you'd live a good life if I took care of you.
Believing you were oblivious,
you'd obediently do as I told you.
And...
Ahjeossi.
Why isn't Ho Yeong in the ossuary?
Oppa will disappear if you do this.
P-Please take him to the ossuary.
Why not?
Ho Yeong suffered so much
because of his mom and me.
I want to let Ho Yeong rest now.
Now that I know how much
Ho Yeong was hurting and suffering.
Then what do I do when I miss Oppa?
Let's hold it in.
Let's hold it in,
no matter how much we miss him.
I think that's what we should do for Ho Yeong's sake.
Let's let Ho Yeong rest.
I'm sorry.
You resent me, right?
It's all my fault.
I'm sorry.
Oppa,
I'm sorry for missing you every day.
From now on,
I'll try to hold it in by myself.
You can leave now.
I'm sure Ho Yeong didn't feel lonely.
Okay.
I'm sorry, Ahjeossi.
No, you shouldn't feel sorry.
That's my burden.
I thought...
I had the right to determine the weight
of a person's sins and punish him for that weight.
That was very arrogant of me,
since a person will be appropriately punished for his crimes
in one way or another.
Through things that are caused by human relationships.
Even if I were to hide the crimes I've committed thus far,
it'd be of no use.
In the end, I reap the consequences.
No matter how much you struggle or try to run away,
you'll inevitably pay the price for your crimes.
I'm sure Sang Hyeon's death...
was the price of the crimes I committed in secret.
To hide those crimes,
I committed other crimes.
And to hide those crimes I committed,
I commit greater wrongdoings.
Human life is bound to continue like that.
All of those wrongdoings are
coming back to me in some form...
far more cruel than the things I've done.
It's not something you can hide even if you tried.
But when you hid it,
it's bound to come to you as a punishment far worse.
Had I realized my sins and repented,
could I have avoided the punishment?
There's serious damage to the cranial nerve...
I can't guarantee her physical function.
Unfortunately, the possibility of her recovery is...
When I've already committed wrongdoings,
can I avoid it just because I repent?
Punishment will come to you in whatever form.
After Ho Yeong's accident,
I've done a lot of wrong things.
Actually, I think I've been living while committing countless wrongs
that I can't even bring myself to list from even before that.
I don't intend to hide anything.
I'll tell you everything that's happened so far.
No.
Punishment is to be served in order.
You're not the one who needs to be punished first.
It's Kim Kang Heon.
As for your crimes, bury them in your heart
until after Kim Kang Heon is caught.
Don't try to get out of the heavy burden of your crimes
merely by blaming yourself with your words.
Can I trust him?
I'm sure he's full of vengeance toward Chairman Kim Kang Heon.
Vengeance?
Isn't it too one-dimensional?
With convictions like justice or a sense of calling,
hasn't he already been defeated?
All those things have already been destroyed.
Let's tame him properly.
Since there's nothing scarier than a hunting dog raised properly.
I'll come meet him in person soon.
In the meantime...
have him ready.
We'll be seeing each other again soon.
Though your father must've protected you so far,
you'll have to protect your father from now on.
I came to warn you not to be too relaxed in the U.S.
You'll mess with my father?
Including Kim Kang Heon, you'll have to protect the entire Woo One.
A mere prosecutor will?
Using the power of law?
It seemed the law lost too much of its power.
I won't trust stuff like that anymore.
I'll have to fight using power above the law.
Let's meet again soon.
I thought I should come see you at least once.
Out of all the people I've met in the process,
Eun is the only one with no fault at all.
No matter how long I think or contemplate,
why was that child forced into making such a great sacrifice?
I don't know.
I'm just carrying on.
I don't necessarily have a purpose.
I'm just living on because I'm alive.
There's no meaning.
I hope you won't be able to forget it.
It's still not over?
Do you plan to get revenge?
With what power?
No.
It's repentance, not revenge.
The wrongdoings we've committed...
You and I must repent.
The wrongs we've done,
and the reason why those wrongdoings produced this result.
I thought I was someone who can and will
judge this terrible situation.
That's why I believed I could produce
the best result in the direction I wanted.
I was arrogant.
I've contemplated countless times now.
Why?
What exactly went wrong in the process?
I'm sure this was the most certain way, right?
The way to make us repent our sins.
Thanks to our Channel Manager: Josselinelino
Thank you to segmenters:  janiedy (Chief), kitty100, ts_lambrini,
Segmenters, cont.:  kazumi_oka, henrii_11, skywalker13, msv, fecothomas_810 and wiill0w24
Thank you to editors:  cgwm808(Chief) and joysprite
Thank you to the moderators, subbers, and editors for all other langauges
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by the âš–ï¸Crossed PathsðŸ”— Team @ Viki.com
Your Honor
Thank you for watching "Your Honor"