Son Hyun Joo
♫  Just a look across the sidewalk.  ♫
Kim Myung Min
♫  Love.  ♫
♫  That's your little life hug.  ♫
Kim Do Hoon
Heo Nam Joon
♫  Someday we'll come when this makes sense  ♫
♫  But for now, it's time to rest  ♫
Your Honor
This is a work of fiction.
Characters, places, organizations, incidents, names, ethnic groups, and settings are unrelated to reality.
There's been a big accident.
You must take care of it before the police arrive.
Sang Hyeok didn't get along with Madam all this time and felt out of place.
I'm sorry to tell you, but he's also had many complaints about you, Chairman.
I heard he repeatedly said
that Woo One should be run the way his grandfather did.
After Mom passed away,
you were the only person I could depend on, Father.
But you've never once approved of me.
What can I do...
to become your beloved son?
Father.
These f***ers were talking shit about you.
Saying you're a hypocrite.
Your Honor: Episode 5
Prove your promise.
Wh-Why are you doing this?
You're a judge!
H-How can a judge kill someone?
Until my last breath, I'll never speak of H-Ho Yeong—
Did you struggle this much when my child died, too?
We need to continue our talk.
What do I need to do?
Pull yourself together.
From police investigations to indictment,
it can take as little as a week to a month
if the case becomes complicated.
There are gray areas,
but there's video evidence showing
Kim Sang Hyeok killing people at the scene.
So the police will prove 100%
the man in the video is Kim Sang Hyeok.
Once that is proven,
there's no room to move the trial.
By the time the case is in front of me,
there must be enough room for interpretation.
This is a losing battle.
I'm sure it is. I'm sure it's not an easy fight.
Since you need to commit an evil deed as a respected man.
I'm sure it's hard.
However,
it's easy for me to kill you.
You must do a very difficult job
and I must hold myself back from doing the easiest job in the world.
Script based on series "Kvodo" by Ohad Knoller, Shlomo Moshiah and Ron Ninio
Update the chairman on the status once a week.
Also, contact me if there's anything you need.
Park Chang Hyeok
Things I need?
Like reporting to the chairman and when you need to meet him...
Go through me.
Hey, Detective Jang.
Yes. I wanted to see you.
Yes.
Shall we have dinner together?
- Number one. Look into Jang Chae Rim, who arrested Sang Hyeok.
- Yes.
Number two.
How Sang Hyeok's case will be interpreted and processed within the Prosecution...
- I'm sure Kang So Yeong will be the prosecutor in charge.
- Yes.
Number three.
Starting now, check every single thing Song Pan Ho does and says 24/7 more meticulously.
Number four.
Manage the prison Sang Hyeok will be put in,
so he won't be uncomfortable.
Yes, Chairman.
What's the occasion?
Well, I was just curious how it's going.
Do you remember when your wife passed away two years ago?
I can't forget Ho Yeong's eyes from back then.
How can he be so completely sad?
How can he be so beautifully sad?
I wanted to catch the culprit who saddened a beautiful child.
However, the laws couldn't wipe away Ho Yeong's tears, nor could I.
The laws aren't to blame.
If the verdict came out that way, then it's the truth.
No.
The law was incorrectly applied.
If you had judged it, the verdict would've been accurate.
It's something I shouldn't do.
Because personal emotions could cause me to lose my legal judgment.
Even if it were incorrectly applied,
it's still the law.
And that will be the situation in the future.
That's right.
Because you're a judge, Judge Song.
But I'm different.
I'm not the least interested  in the deaths of Jeong Hae Yong and the Budu Gang members.
The bastard I couldn't catch two years ago. I want to make sure he pays for it this time.
I can't make him pay for that crime due to double jeopardy.
But I'll make him... pay as much as he should.
What happened to that child Cheong Gang?
I hid him where no one knows.
I plan to hide him completely until the trial begins.
Chairman Kim Kang Heon is a scary man, as you know.
Could I...
see that child?
Sorry?
I don't really know.
What are your current charges as a suspect?
"I don't really know."
I'm home.
Ho Yeong.
Jang Chae Rim
Hi, Judge Song. This is Detective Jang.
I'm heading back after interrogating the suspect.
I plan to secure a few more items of evidence and transfer him to the prosecution.
- Who's the prosecutor in charge?
- Prosecutor Kang So Yeong of Woowon District.
You know her, right? She blew the whistle on the prosecution's internal corruption five years ago
and she even got Chairman Kim Kang Heon locked up three years ago.
As you know, the prosecution is also widely influenced by Woo One.
I felt Prosecutor Kang would stay faithful to the laws and principles.
If Prosecutor Kang indicts, and you're the judge,
this case will be properly handled.
Did you get the suspect's testimony?
Gosh, no. He's standing his ground.
I think we'll have to go with physical evidence.
Physical evidence? Did you secure any?
First off, the video evidence I showed you last time.
Lee Cheong Gang, the witness.
I'll have to find the gun used for the crime and his location at the time of the incident.
Since the victim's son witnessed it
and there's even video evidence, there shouldn't be any major problems.
Yes. I'll be counting on you from here on.
How do you feel, Kim Sang Hyeok?
Don't you feel things are pretty much screwed up for you?
I have to discuss something with the chairman.
I have some work at the court in the afternoon.
I'd like to see him before noon.
Look out your living room window.
Were you on standby in front of my house?
What did you need to talk about?
There's a total of three pieces of evidence that Detective Jang Chae Rim can secure.
First, the video evidence of the scene and the witness, Lee Cheong Gang.
Second, the gun used for the crime.
Third, the evidence that the suspect was present at the scene.
Prosecutor Kang So Yeong of Woowon District Prosecutors' Office will be taking the case.
She's unaffected by authorities and connections.
Five years ago, she drew attention for blowing the whistle on internal corruption within the prosecution.
The situation doesn't look good.
You must shake up the evidence and diversify legal interpretations.
It seems you couldn't even sleep a wink...
because you killed a person.
Is it from a guilty conscience, or
is it from the fear you might die if you don't pull this off?
That's not it.
There's no way you have any sense of guilt.
You already committed murder twice.
That means you couldn't sleep because you wanted to live.
Right.
People are supposed to be honest with primal desires.
Woowon Gangheung Police Station
Excuse me!
- I'm here to make a report.
- A report on what?
People died at Daeyeon Port two days ago, you know.
There were gunshots, too.
Let's go inside first.
Shit.
I can't really tell.
It was too dark back then.
He might not be the one.
Hey...
who sent you?
Hey!
You!
Stay put.
You sold the gun to Kim Sang Hyeok, right?
Who's Kim Sang Hyeok?
Woo One Group's oldest son! Stop acting like you don't know.
I don't know anyone like that.
The latest one who bought a gun from me was Jo Bin.
Jo Bin?
Did you make an appointment?
I'm looking for a guy named Jo Bin.
Why are you looking for Bin?
Do I have to tell you the reason to see him?
Will three days be enough?
Actually, I'd like to see him tomorrow morning.
It hasn't even been a week since I lost a friend who was like my own brother.
And he was...
killed by your son, Chairman.
When my second son died,
you concealed and fabricated the accident, CEO Jo.
You probably didn't even think about how much pain the victim was in.
I should've killed everyone here, to be frank.
Why did I hold back?
For what?
Did I want to become the chairman of Woo One, who's respected by people?
Or could it be...
that I wanted to believe justice existed in this world?
There's no reason to see you again.
I won't have the need to come see you or
you'll no longer be around to be seen.
If you're trying to do something big, you need to move in an organized manner.
If you arrest and interrogate a suspect, write up an interrogation report on the suspect,
and transfer him to the Prosecution as you please, you make your superiors look bad.
I'll just be disciplined.
Hey, that's like saying you'll just be punished after killing someone!
Chief, are you that afraid of Woo One Group?
Could the dignity of the police, maintained for 80 years since our nation's independence
be destroyed by outer pressure from a gang—
What a load of crap, punk!
When does it start?
- What do you mean?
- My disciplinary measures.
The disciplinary process is almost complete.
- Keep a low profile.
- No.
I have investigative rights until the disciplinary duration and extent are decided.
I'll do my best until then.
Also, I'm not a kid.
Quit your nagging.
Damn it.
How did it go? Did you find out where he's at?
Yes, Team Leader.
We found out where Jo Bin is hiding, and we're on our way right now.
Yes, I'll let you know as soon as we get him.
What? Geez!
F***!
F*** those sons of bitches...
Gosh, I'm sorry.
I'm just...
furious today.
You're the only one I can talk to about these things, Judge. I'm sorry.
No, I understand.
How can they...
take a person's life so lightly?
Just how many people must die for this to end?
After Kim Sang Hyeon's hit-and-run incident, seven people died.
And there's only one suspect for all seven.
I-If...
If I had done a good job,
they'd all still be alive.
I'll go to Prosecutor Kang So Yeong in the morning and
transfer the murders Kim Sang Hyeok committed to the Prosecution.
We've got video evidence
and we've got a witness.
We'll try our best to get him a life sentence.
Even if they're Woo One,
they need to be punished in the name of justice.
That's common sense. That's right!
The reason I respect you, Judge Song...
is because you'd never waver in the face of Woo One's pressure.
Judge Song... you see...
I'm embarrassed.
Of what?
When people call me, they say, "Detective Jang."
But whenever things like today happen,
I'm so embarrassed by the fact that I'm a detective.
- Hi. You called for a driver, right?
- Yes.
The customer is not answering the phone.
You'll be connected to the voicemail.
Please give me a call when you get home, just to be safe.
Late Kim Sang Hyeon
As expected, Kang So Yeong became the prosecutor in charge.
She'll come to see me.
Jang Chae Rim
The phone is turned off. You'll be connected to the voicemail.
After the beep, there will be an additional charge.
Your Honor,
even if the victim demanded a high interest payment on a loan and threatened his family,
this is clearly a murder with intent.
Please give the maximum sentence allowed by law for the defendant, Kim Taek Soo.
You're a judge! H-How can a judge kill someone?
Your Honor.
Your Honor!
Yes, thank you.
On May 1st, which is two weeks from now, we'll hold a sentencing hearing.
Violent Crimes Department
Geez, just rewrite it.
Okay, I'll rewrite it.
Judge Song, hello.
Hello.
Where's Detective Jang Chae Rim?
Detective Jang didn't come in today.
She doesn't answer her phone, either.
Can you tell me where Detective Jang lives?
Detective Jang!
Team Leader!
I don't think she's home.
She hasn't contacted you either since last night?
Yes.
Can we call a locksmith to open the door?
Do we have to go that far?
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Huh?
Shit...
Hey, I'm at the Team Leader's house right now.
I think they got Team Leader.
Geez, who else? There's only one person we're investigating!
Get over here quickly!
I apologize.
Open. Open up.
Open up. Open up!
What's the meaning of this? I told you I'll take care of it!
Jang Chae Rim didn't do anything wrong.
She was just doing what she had to do!
Let go!
Does this world look so easy to you?
Things you can do. Things you can't do.
Things you should do. Things you shouldn't do.
The world runs based on those distinctions.
Why? Why?
Why lay your hands on things you shouldn't? Why!
In the future, set up meetings through Park Chang Hyeok.
There's nothing I shouldn't do.
Do you think the world or the laws... can protect you, Judge?
That might be the case for other people.
However, that's not the case for me.
I can just kill you and go to jail or
I can die.
You see, the laws work only for people who live by common sense.
Did you really do that today, thinking the laws...
can protect you?
I-It's a very important matter.
I must see you.
Woowon City Legal Professionals' Night
Oh, how nice.
Judge Song, nice to meet you.
How are you, Judge Song?
There are many quiet and secret locations.  Why here, of all places?
- You don't look good.
- Someone placed...
a tail on me.
Who did?
One moment.
I met Kim Kang Heon recently.
He knows I'm the culprit.
Wait, how?
It's my fault for taking the situation too lightly.
What about me? Does he know about me, too?
I'm sorry. So?
Fortunately, his oldest son, Kim Sang Hyeok,
is being held by the police on allegations
of killing Jo Mi Yeon's Budu Gang members and Lee Sang Taek.
I begged for my life under the conditions
of letting him go with a not-guilty verdict.
If the evidence is tampered with and a favorable sentence is rendered,
he probably could get what he wants.
But the problem is, even if I take care of this matter,
there's no guarantee he'll let me live.
That's true.
We're talking about Chairman Kim Kang Heon here.
I need to find a way to survive once this job is done.
Assemblyman, Chairman Kim Kang Heon came to see me two days ago.
So? Are you going to quit?
Assemblyman. You never had Kim Kang Heon come after you, did you?
It won't end with just me dying.
He has the power to get rid of this entire city.
So, you're going to spend the rest of your life in this sewer?
While wiping Kim Kang Heon's ass?
CEO Jo, a scared dog always barks louder. Okay?
This is an opportunity for us.
Looks like an opportunity to die to me.
This is the opportunity...
to have Song Pan Ho enter the Blue House*.
(* President of Korea's Office)
WOO ONE
Prosecutor Kang So Yeong, hello!
Hello.
I thought I sent you all the files. What brings you here?
It's lacking some things.
I don't think so. I sent you everything Detective Jang Chae Rim had prepared.
No. I meant the things that happened during the investigation.
Information on them seemed to be missing.
Follow me.
- Okay. I'll simply explain only once, so listen up.
- Yes.
Kim Sang Hyeon died in a car accident on April 8th at the beltway.
- Correct?
- Yes.
On April 11th, the family of the hit-and-run suspect, Lee Sang Taek,
Kim Mi Yeong, age 71, and Lee Cheong Ha, age 7, died from a gas explosion.
- Correct?
- Yes.
On April 12th, while trying to smuggle himself out of the country, Lee Sang Taek
and Budu Gang's Jeong Hae Yong and his two men assisting the smuggle, died.
The suspect is Kim Sang Hyeok, the oldest son of Woo One Group. I have a report on him.
- Correct?
- Yes, you're right.
On April 16th, Jo Bin, who gave a gun to Kim Sang Hyeok, commits suicide, suspiciously.
- Correct?
- Yes.
So, why did I only get a report on Kim Sang Hyeok?
The thing is, we were assigned only his case—
How about other cases?
Are you saying we'll just let them slide?
- That's not what we're saying.
- No.
Gosh, the police...
This is why civil servants shouldn't receive a salary.
If you got paid per case, you'd be working ever so quickly.
Eun, it looks like you lost some weight.
Are you on a diet?
No, I'm not.
But I like it when you're plump, Eun.
Did Eun get a boyfriend?
Th-That's not it!
Who are you?
Where did you guys come from?
How odd.
- Are you ninjas?
- I said who are you?
I'm Kang So Yeong from the Woowon District Prosecutors' Office.
The one who locked up your chairman.
Do I need to bring a warrant to let me in?
What a happy dinner.
You seem to smile at times lately.
Is Sang Hyeon already forgotten?
Prosecutor Kang So Yeong is here.
Yes, tell her to wait in the study.
Yes, sir.
You took my oldest son's case, huh?
Yes, you knew already, right?
I wasn't curious about whom would be taking my son's case.
I was curious about the next case you would be taking on, Prosecutor Kang.
Oh, that's right.
I'm very sorry about what happened to your youngest son.
You're just as rude as always.
A lot has happened since that incident.
The hit-and-run suspect Lee Sang Taek's mother and daughter died from a fire.
Lee Sang Taek, who was trying to smuggle himself out, and Budu Gang members died.
Also, Jo Bin, who gave a gun to Kim Sang Hyeok, died two days ago.
And Jang Chae Rim, who was investigating Kim Sang Hyeok, went missing.
The reason I came all the way here, despite being rude...
is because I think I should tell you in advance.
The unsavory events that took place after your youngest son's death...
I'll be digging into every single one.
You'd better be prepared.
How much of the world do you think you could move?
I'm a prosecutor, you know.
I guess as far as justice allows.
How much could justice protect the world?
If that's how the world has worked so far,
I wouldn't be sitting where I am right now.
What a f***ing narcissist.
Ma'am.
You're Prosecutor Kang So Yeong, right?
- Who are you?
- There's someone...
who desperately wants to meet you.
They said the meeting would be beneficial for both of you.
They have some good information.
I had my doubts, but I was right.
You have something to say to me?
Didn't my guy tell you?
This will be of help to you.
This case really is a filthy one, isn't it?
Seeing how dung flies and gnats are involved.
Isn't the police enough to deal with someone like Jo Mi Yeon?
It's a bit unpleasant for you to want to see me in person.
Isn't Chairman Kim Kang Heon the one you're trying to get?
If it's about getting Chairman Kim Gang Heon,
isn't it helpful to you under any circumstance?
- Excuse me.
- My goodness.
Y-You see, Bin killed himself two days ago, right?
But it's not suicide.
It was a murder.
I don't know who killed him.
But I do know why he was killed.
So, Jo Bin gave a gun to Kim Sang Hyeok, right?
I don't know about that.
Then, what did you come here to report?
The gas explosion at Lee Sang Taek's house killed his mother, Kim Mi Yeong, and his daughter, Cheong Ha.
I think I might know who did it.
Shouldn't you arrest those bastards?
Stop there!
Hey!
Come here!
Let go! Let me go!
I know it's you. Stay put!
All right. You broke into Lee Sang Taek's house and...
What do you call it? It's the pipe you cut.
You two injected thinner into the light bulbs and placed them back.
I don't know what you're talking about.
We don't know anything. Please just let us go home.
What the hell? You two got caught for illegal entry and murder! How dare you pretend not to know?
I really don't know what you're saying. Please have mercy on us.
This is nuts— I know you speak Korean, all right?
We really don't know!
There are many who saw you two run errands for the Budu Gang!
Is this how you want to play? Should I get an interpreter?
I really don't understand you.
You're laugh— Is this funny? Are you laughing?
Gosh, this won't do. Just get an interpreter.
Hello, Prosecutor. Long time no see.
Gosh, those punks are the ones, huh? Evil bastards.
What's all this commotion because of those punks?
Why do you think they did it?
Prosecutor, please let me know if you need anything.
I'll help you out.
Sure.
Is Detective Lee doing his job right?
Seriously.
Friends, let's get out of here.
There are too many rats inside the police station.
Prosecutor Kang So Yeong is conducting an investigation.
From what I heard, it seems she caught the punks
Chief of Police: Choi Myeong Ho
who set Lee Sang Taek's home on fire.
I think you'll have to make a big move this time.
Besides how Sang Hyeok killed the Budu Gang's men,
you'll also have to prepare how he set Lee Sang Taek's home on fire.
Whether it's the district prosecutors' office or the police station,
there's not a place where Woo One's Kim Kang Heon can't reach.
That's also why I insisted on bringing you detectives here for our plan.
Until the job is done, we'll keep things among ourselves and move by ourselves.
You got that?
Yes. Yes.
I'm Prosecutor Kang So Yeong of Woowon District Prosecutors' Office.
One moment, please.
It's the Prosecution.
Sure.
Ma Ji Yeong.
You're under arrest for instigated murder and arson.
You have the right to remain silent and appoint an attorney.
Anything you say can be used against you in court.
We brought the arrest warrant with us.
Because we have clear evidence.
Arrest Warrant
Judge Song Pan Ho, Assemblyman Jeong Yi Hwa, CEO Jo Mi Yeon, and Prosecutor Kang So Yeong.
What were they trying to do?
Prosecutor Kang So Yeong was investigating the fire incident in Jangbeom-dong.
If you look at just the pictures, it seems she got the idea from you.
Explain.
- Yes.
- Chairman, Madam has just been...
Your Honor
♫  I'll be burnt to ashes without a trace, yeah  ♫
♫  Dispersing like the smoke, you and I become yesterday  ♫
♫  Sink even deeper, to the rock bottom  ♫
♫  Going voluntarily in front of the teeth ready to devour me  ♫
♫  An expression like dawn, turning deathly pale and cold  ♫
♫  I remember everything like a tattoo  ♫
Where do you people get your complacent attitudes from?
Are you saying you will arm wrestle with us?
Do you know whom I met just now?
Whatever you do, wherever you are in this world,
I'll know everything.
And you'll pay for it.
Let's see this to the end.
I plan to enter the Blue House.
Because I'll be freed from Chairman Kim Kang Heon's threats.