The Taoism Grandmother
Episode 16
Madam, it's my sister!
Go away!
This is my second daughter of the Wen family.
Grandmother of the Su family is her biological sister.
I'll see who dares to do it!
The Wen family has been confiscated.
How can you call her your second daughter?
Madam is pregnant now.
If you're too impulsive,
you'll be beaten to death!
Go away!
Madam!
I'm a begger!
Go away!
I'll kill you if you dare to touch my second daughter!
You'll see!
You'll be beaten to death!
Madam!
I'm a begger!
Shut up!
Madam!
Tell your master
that he's a begger
and will be beaten to death!
Open the door!
Is there anyone?
Is there anyone to save my second daughter?
I know that the Yu family is only to win the treasure.
But I can't forget my kindness.
The Wen family never treats me as a servant.
The eldest son is even grateful to me for saving his life.
I must protect my second daughter.
Thank you for saving me, Brother.
Miss, don't be so polite.
It's my pleasure.
I saw that you all got wet and fried some medicine.
Drink it while it's hot.
Did you encounter any trouble?
To be honest,
the house was hit by a tornado.
We couldn't find any relatives who ran away.
Now,
we can't find anyone to save us.
I'm afraid that
the people who ran away
will be in danger.
Now,
we are just friends.
If you can't find a place to go,
my house is just empty.
You can just stay here and stay under the tree.
If that's the case,
I'll rent this house to you.
We'll talk about it later.
We should take care of each other in the comments.
It's getting late.
Take your medicine and rest early.
Mother.
Qiu Niang.
Don't be afraid. I'm here.
Sister An Nian.
An Nian doesn't want me.
I want my father.
I want my mother.
Don't cry, Qiu Niang.
We have a place to go now.
Everything will be fine.
I don't want it.
I want my mother.
I want my brother.
I want to go home.
Don't cry, Qiu Niang.
Qiu Niang.
Look, Qiu Niang.
Look at this.
Look.
People's lives
are like the glass tiles.
They are placed in the dark.
It's dark and dark.
No one cares.
They are placed in a place with light.
They can shine the bright light.
If there's no light,
we have to light ourselves.
We can shine the light.
The light is on.
The road is easy.
People
have to move forward.
It's a little bit hard now.
But I promised my wife to protect you.
I won't leave you behind.
I'll be with you.
I'll treat you as a pearl.
My name is Baoyin.
You can call me Baozhu.
I'll listen to you.
I can't get used to it.
I didn't bring your personal clothes.
I made a pillow for you with my old clothes.
They are all your regular clothes.
You sleep first.
I'll be here to guard you.
Baozhu, go to sleep.
People
have no hard work.
As long as we are alive,
there will always be hope.
Wen family is down.
I have to take good care of Baozhu.
I'm strong.
I'm not afraid of hardship.
I've learned a few words in Wen family.
I also learned to do math.
I made a trick.
I made a business of selling small dishes on the river.
It's enough for us to eat and wear warm clothes.
Today, I'll buy two small dishes and send one to you.
You can save two dollars if you buy ten dishes.
Don't miss a good opportunity.
Save two dollars if you buy ten dishes.
Come, come.
Take it.
We are here to buy, take it,
and come back home without empty hands.
Our small dishes...
I didn't expect that the village leader
moved away overnight.
He is really a man of the village.
I'm afraid I'll be implicated.
But I heard that
the Wen family was not executed for the crime.
They were just locked in the prison.
Locked in the prison?
Who told you about this?
Wait a minute.
Excuse me.
Where is the Wen family locked up?
Anjie, I'm afraid.
Sir, let me out.
Don't be afraid.
Be good.
Let me out.
Sir, let me out.
Zhu, don't be afraid.
I'm here.
Anjie, I'm afraid.
Sir, let me out.
Zhu, don't be afraid.
I'm here.
Hurry up.
Put it on your body.
Qiongniang?
It's Qiongniang.
Qiongniang.
Mother, father.
My dear.
Qiongniang.
Good girl.
Mother, she is my sister.
Anjie, I'm not Qiongniang now.
I'm Baozhu.
Baozhu.
Madam, please forgive me.
I dare not to let you know my real identity.
I'm afraid that some officials will come.
I can only let them follow me.
I gave her a name of Baozhu.
Get up.
Master, why are you only blaming me?
The Wen family is guilty of all crimes.
Only Qiongniang is the only one.
If it weren't for you,
she wouldn't be standing here alive today.
I'm grateful that you're here.
Why are you so upset?
It's a sunny day in Wen's Mansion.
You're the daughter of the Wen family.
I don't want to be a daughter.
Master and Madam are in the mansion.
They treat us as family.
It's a great favor to me and my husband.
I just want to protect my family.
I'll take it as a favor.
Where's Elder Brother?
Why isn't Elder Brother here?
I heard that he went to the academy to get someone.
But I don't know where he is.
I feel sorry for Su.
I don't know if he's alive or dead.
You're scared?
Sister said that people have to suffer.
As long as they live, they'll have hope.
Our family will be reunited.
Hurry up.
It's time.
Master, Madam, please forgive me.
I'll definitely protect Second Young Mistress.
Hurry up.
Mother.
Please.
Please don't go.
Thank you.
Good.
Sister, it's the last day of the festival.
Yes.
Life is so confusing.
I wonder if it's the last day of the festival.
Sister, there are so many lanterns here.
Many people are making wishes.
Look.
I hope that my benefactor,
Mr. Wen, will be safe and sound.
I hope that he will be safe and sound.
I hope that the Wen family will be reunited soon.
Sister, it's so lively over there.
Let's go and have a look.
Good.
First Young Mistress is here.
She is the daughter that the late emperor loved the most.
I heard that she has half a tiger's tally
and she only grows in the wind and earth.
Even the officials are afraid of her.
This garden is so beautiful.
Let's go.
First Young Mistress is used to talking about the mystery.
This is the biggest art form in the whole Bianyang.
I heard that the first Young Mistress's husband
has a foreign background.
They sent her to smoke her husband.
No wonder.
She has so many young and beautiful face.
As long as she can fall in love with the man,
no one can escape.
Sister, who is the man beside the princess?
Brother.
It's me, Brother.
I'm here.
Every rain and wind
is like a dream.
My heart is like a mountain.
I'm going to travel around the world.
I'll never forget our first meeting.
Every rain and wind
is like a witness.
I'm not loyal to you.
We're separated by the sea.
I've held your hands.
I want nothing more than you.
Every rain and wind
is like a witness.
I'm not loyal to you.
We're separated by the sea.
I've held your hands.
I want nothing more than you.
Every rain and wind
is like a dream.