The Legend of Chusen
Brother, it's me.
He's the first son of the Zhuang family.
Why is he now with the Princess?
He doesn't care about the safety of the family.
He doesn't care about the so-called literary fame?
He's even willing to be dragged by the world as a beast?
How should I explain to the King?
I didn't expect Brother to be like this.
Hush. Lower your voice.
He did it. Why can't he say it?
No wonder Brother wasn't locked up in prison.
He's the one who became the Princess.
If this gets out, how will people look at our family?
Yes, yes, yes.
The Great Wolf Army is so greedy for wealth and peace.
They only care about their own happiness,
not about their parents and sisters.
Our sister broke off her relationship with him.
She won't be a member of the Wen family anymore.
I don't think so.
Maybe...
he has some reasons.
Calm down.
The Great Wolf Army is no one.
You're his sister.
He's not your brother.
He's your brother.
No matter what, you're his sister.
You should know that.
No matter what,
he won't ignore his family's safety and only care about his own happiness.
Before he's in full power,
he can't forget about the chaos.
At least we know now
that the Great Wolf Army is safe and sound.
It's a good thing.
He's quite cautious.
We're here to serve him.
He's still suffering in the prison.
Since he's gone,
what good day can it be?
Your Highness, may you be blessed with good health.
Go and check on him.
It's just a difficult task.
How can we do it?
What?
What's wrong?
Your Highness, please calm down.
I have something to report.
You may leave.
Yes.
Your Highness,
Prince Qi has been found.
He's a well-known person.
He's the head of the legal council
that the Great Buddha Temple doesn't have.
Interesting.
So, the seventh brother
has been hiding in the Great Buddha Temple.
I'm so lucky to find him.
It seems that the opportunity has come.
He's both good at martial arts and martial arts.
If he can go out and help me,
it'll be a blessing in disguise.
There are so many guests today.
It's really a good time to get together.
My food will surely sell out.
Your Highness,
please don't worry.
I'll be back soon.
Your Highness,
please don't worry.
He's from a rich family.
Your Highness.
Please bless my Pan'er.
Mother, what wish did you make to Buddha?
I wish
to have the whole life of
my Pan'er.
How can that be?
Peace and prosperity,
The peace of the heart and the life of the child is complete.
The most important thing in a woman's life is to be complete.
Mother, I may let you down.
I dare not ask for the so-called life to be complete.
I only ask for the person I love to be healthy and safe.
This back shadow is so familiar.
Baoyin, please believe me.
You must have your reasons for doing this.
I heard that Wen family was going to be executed.
Now we are spared the death penalty.
I think you must have moved out secretly.
Thank you for taking care of my mother.
You must be tired.
I'm tired.
I was hiding from you that you were here.
I don't want to tell you.
I'll thank you in person if I have a chance.
Take care, Your Highness.
Wen family is still young.
They are afraid that you will return home safely.
Aren't you afraid that Wen family and I are both bad people?
I only know Wen family treats me well.
You saved me once.
That's enough.
Your Highness.
There is no Zhao Hua Ying in this world.
There is only one monk here.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Please forgive me.
But the Chief Princess already knows who the host is.
She has been looking for me for many years.
This day will come sooner or later.
Tell the Crown Prince to rest assured.
I promised him that I would never break my promise.
I also wronged you.
Staying by his side is not a good thing.
I will never forget it.
I will never break my promise.
I also wronged you.
Staying by his side is not a good thing.
With this sentence,
the Crown Prince is forced to be a great man.
Bring another bottle when you come again.
Your pickled vegetables taste good.
Okay.
I don't know if I will meet the big man again.
Who are you looking for?
Get lost.
Oh no.
Wen Song came here to hide from the Chief Princess.
If she sees us...
Wen Song.
You heartless man.
You got the glory and wealth.
Now you want to break the engagement?
No way.
It's not like that.
Listen to my explanation.
What else?
When you were asking about the past,
you said that you were going to break the engagement.
But you didn't.
You didn't.
You know what?
You seduced a maid from Wen Mansion
to be my maid forever.
Now the Wen family is in trouble.
You didn't care about your sister and parents.
You don't even accept my engagement.
You are a lady of the old dynasty.
You are a phoenix.
Since you want to be my maid forever,
you can't do anything.
I came here to tell you
not to wait for me.
Take the money
and marry a good man.
This is too much.
Your Highness.
Your Highness?
Who are you fooling?
This little money
is useless to me.
Your Highness.
Please forgive me.
Please give me justice.
Your Highness, please forgive me.
It's all my fault.
I believe you.
This lady is so greedy.
Kill her.
The Demon Gate is closed.
You can't kill her.
Brother Qi.
You made me look for you
after we parted this year.
The King of Qi died
in the fire 12 years ago.
I'm just a monk
who sent the Buddha with one heart
and never asked about the world.
Brother Qi.
I have a lot to tell you.
No matter who you are now,
I will always know
that you are my most respected brother.
Everyone knows
that the King of Qi who was famous
shouldn't have ended like this.
Forget it.
If you are willing to forgive
the innocent two people,
I will ask you to come in and talk to me.
God has the ability to survive.
You should also
do something for yourself.
I also hope that
I can pray for you for many years.
Get out of here.
The King of Qi
What?
Are you still thinking about your lover?
Don't make fun of me.
Or are you still thinking about your family?
I just like to humiliate you
and make you love someone you can't get.
Today is the festival.
It is indeed a good day
for a family to reunite.
It is indeed a good day for a family to reunite.
You still think you are
the leader of Qingfeng Lao Yue?
If you beg me,
I will let you go to the prison.
The King of Qi
The truth
If you are not similar to that person,
I am not the kind person
who can protect your family
and that woman.
If you are not serious,
you will lose.
I feel sorry for you
for being so ungrateful.
I know you are a man of style.
But since you are with me,
you should lose
your pride.
Otherwise,
you will hurt others
and yourself.
I will lose this time.
Look at how serious you are.
As long as I am happy,
it is not easy to make someone live.
Today is the festival.
I will spend the day with you
and go to the prison to meet your parents.
Look how nice I am to you.
Don't be so jealous
when you are not satisfied.
These buildings
are interesting.
Thank you for your concern.
I will go now.
I am busy.
I made some green beans
and pork for you.
Please come over.
Thank you, Brother Luo.
I also made some dishes
for you.
Please take them back.
Thank you.
Wait.
Why is your shirt torn?
Let me help you.
It is okay.
You are doing business
and I can do it myself.
It is not hard.
It is here.
Compared with before,
we can earn money and eat well.
It is better than many people.
It is done.
Thank you.
If there is nothing else,
I will go back first.
It is okay.
I will go first.
Brother Luo.