Wam union
ON
The
Tsk
My wife
May you live each day
Besides your handwriting is much better
You can'tbeing grateful
I set up a stage in Qingzhou
I have forgotten that there is a family in the capital.
He knows that I am in Qingzhou.
They say that now the treasury is full.
Half of it is the credit of Mr. Wen.
Really?
The bigger the official seat,
the more harsh the words.
He has asked me.
Wen.
Are you okay?
Why are you so thin?
How about you?
Is it good?
As you see,
now you are the minister of the Ministry of Revenue.
What's wrong with that?
That's right.
What he did now is what he wanted to do.
What's wrong with that?
You are back.
Who is she?
I...
It's you.
I finally get you back.
I will go to inform the lady and the master.
You are back.
There is your portrait in the house.
Mother told the servants in the house to recognize it.
No matter where you are,
you have to get it back when you see it.
Father and mother must have a lot to tell you.
You go ahead.
I have to go back to the Ministry of Revenue.
You are back.
Don't follow me.
I am back.
Where can I go?
You are back.
I finally get you back.
Baoyin.
Leave us.
Yes.
Come here.
Let me see.
I will go with you.
Come here.
My son.
You are so hurt.
Are you worried about me and your uncle?
I am worried about you.
Just keep on hammering.
Until you are satisfied.
Baoyin, where are you?
I miss you so much.
I can't find you.
Get up.
Let me see you.
You left a letter to us.
We were looking for you.
Suer sent people to the park.
But we couldn't find him.
So he went to your hometown.
We were happy.
We thought you were dead.
But we couldn't find you.
Don't you know I am a harem?
I won't die so easily.
Don't be angry.
You are so angry for a poor man like me.
You don't know it.
You should feel sorry for me.
Don't stand outside.
Come in.
Don't catch a cold.
Come out.
Look.
This peach blossom cake is your favorite.
You buy it in a queue.
You finally come back today.
Try it.
Okay.
Drink some tea.
Warm up your body.
Tell me.
Where have you been these years?
I opened a restaurant in Qingzhou with the gift of the government.
The business is good these two years.
In order to get the goods,
I opened shops in all cities.
You have been to many places.
You have seen the world.
You must have suffered a lot.
Stay at home for a few days.
Stay with your uncle and aunt.
Yes, Mr. Bao.
I have to take care of the restaurant in Qingzhou.
This time, besides seeing Erlang,
I heard that Baozhu was going to marry someone.
I came to congratulate him.
Where is he?
He must have gone to the next house.
Now the woman is not loyal.
I know it.
I have to teach him again.
I have sent someone to report.
I should be back soon.
I have heard about Baozhu's marriage.
You don't agree?
Suer is now in charge of the money of the government.
King Ying is in charge of the military power in Liaobei.
These two are the masters of the big ones.
If these two families are put together,
not only will they be suspected by others,
I'm afraid the government will not be at ease.
Sister.
You are a liar.
You said you would stay with me.
How can you leave without saying goodbye?
I don't care.
I have to keep you in my heart.
You can't run away.
Look at you.
You are still a child.
It's all my fault.
I shouldn't have come back so late.
If you leave next time, I will take you with me.
If you lie to me again, you will be a dog.
I'm not a dog.
You are going to marry a girl.
You are still so clingy.
Sister.
Tell my parents
to let me marry King Ying.
You are so shameless.
How can a girl marry a man?
I like King Ying.
I will marry him.
Now your brother is in charge of the family.
We can't make a decision.
You should go to your brother.
Your sister is tired.
She should go to rest.
No.
What if she leaves again?
I came back this time
to send you out of the house.
Don't worry.
I won't leave.
Come on, sister.
Sister, look.
These things
were brought from Bianyang
to the capital.
Brother asked Yuan Mu Yuan Yang to decorate it.
He cleaned it every day and opened the window.
He also changed the flowers in the house
every month.
I will marry you.
Sister.
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
Sister, you have a big hand.
This pearl is bigger than my eyeballs.
It's nothing.
Sister has grown up.
In the future,
everything I want is yours.
I knew you would always love me.
Sister, why are you laughing?
Qingzhou has no snow.
I haven't seen such snow for a long time.
Qingzhou has not only no snow,
but also me.
No parents, mother and brother.
I think you miss home.
Yes.
Home is better.
Qingzhou.
The wind and rain are entangled in the pain of the world.
I can't understand.
I long to see you.
In the white-hands of love,
I long to hold your hand.
The starlight shines on you.
Brother, why are you back so early?
Brother, you are so fierce.
Sister is protecting me.
I'm sorry.
The wind blows into the sky.
The heart is full of love.
I long to be with you.
I long to hold your hand.
I long to have you by my side.
You are so old.
You are still playing with the kids.
I remember
you are a few years older than me.
I have a dream of us being together.
Sister, let's go and sit.
Brother, you have to be treated by me.
You are always busy with work.
You can't see anyone.
Sister, can you help me persuade Brother
to get engaged to Prince Ying?
Baozhu, marriage is not a joke.
I have never seen Prince Ying.
I don't know how he treats you.
How can you give it to him so easily?
He treats me very well.
A few years ago, I almost broke my leg when I rode a horse.
He saved me.
He taught me how to shoot arrows
and taught me how to read and write.
He treated me like you treated me.
I was the first one to think of
what delicious food and fun to play.
Your Baozhu has grown up.
I am willing to help you.
But your brother is changing every year.
He may not listen to me.
He won't.
He listens to you the most.
He is cold now.
It's just that he has been suffering for years.
Since you left, he has been depressed for a long time.
He is determined not to accept the marriage of the official.
My father said that the official business is complicated.
My brother is more careful when fighting alone.
So he doesn't like to talk these years.
He keeps everything in his heart.
So that's it.
Sister, actually I know
that my brother doesn't want me to marry the Prince of Ying.
He doesn't want me to marry him.
He is afraid that as a general,
he may not have a day to contribute to the country.
But I'm not afraid of these.
As long as he treats me sincerely,
I will face it with him no matter what others say.
No matter what others say?
Silly girl.
How can everyone have the courage to do this?
Have you thought about it?
As long as you love each other sincerely,
you can get rid of all difficulties.
It's not impossible.
It's not impossible to get rid of all difficulties.
I hope you grow up.
Sister, it's good that you're back.
Brother can be happier.
Just help me persuade him.
Come in.
I don't know that you are changing your clothes.
So you just let me in.
You are changing your clothes.
I'll come back later.
You are not here to talk to me.
Chen...
Chen Baoyin...
Why is he so clumsy when he sees him?
I heard about Baozhu and King Ying.
As his brother,
I shouldn't break Baozhu's marriage for my reputation.
You are here
just to say this?
The past
should be put forward.
Master and Madam are old.
You should have thought about it earlier.
The situation is already high.
Don't let them worry.
You are so easy to let go.
So you are with Luo Teng.
What are you talking about?
Brother Luo and I just opened a store together.
You married into Wei family.
Have you ever thought about me these five years?
No.
If you don't want to,
why don't you dare to see me?
The End