Only two people could’ve
done it! You or Mother Müzeyyen!
Don’t you ever try to
play games like this again!
If we’re siblings, then
we should be together.
From now on, I want Burak to
live with us at the mansion.
Mercan and Ateş are the ones hurting me.
Don't worry, I know.
The photo in the study.
You put it there.
You’re doing the wrong thing, Aslı.
They’re together now. They love each other.
Everything I do, I do for love.
What are you doing
here? Get out of my house!
Burak…
come in, son. This is your home too.
This is my home and my
children’s home, Haydar Effendi!
If he’s part of this family,
he should live here too.
Since when you are the one
making decisions in this house?
Mercan is the lady of this house.
She has every right to make decisions.
Ateş Karahan secretly had Tahir
Aslan’s parents’ graves opened.
Spent a fortune to keep it quiet.
Is Ateş Karahan… Tahir Aslan?!
This is my first and last
kindness to you, Mercan.
Since you want the truth,
if you trust your love so much,
take this key and look in the basement.
"Play on her mercy, her pure heart."
"To break her from her family,
exposing Haydar’s dirt is enough."
"If the family turns on each
other, they’re easier to destroy."
What?
You can now watch arafta with
subtitles in multiple languages
and on some episodes, audio
in multiple languages as well.
For subtitles.
Tap settings, choose subtitles,
and pick your language on mobile.
Tap the top CC button
and select your language.
For audio, tap settings.
Choose Audio Track and
pick your language on mobile.
Open settings.
Choose Audio Track and pick your language.
The full Audio track upload
schedule is in the description below.
Really… Is this really you, Tahir?
Tahir?
Is this really you?
You… Who are you? What kind
of game are you playing with me?
A game… It was not a
game. It was not a game.
I truly am Tahir.
I looked for you. I thought you were dead.
I was devastated… Tahir…
I… I searched for you.
They told me you were dead.
They told me you had died.
You know I was looking for Tahir.
We looked together. We
went to Eylül’s grave.
My God, protect my sanity.
Why… Why… Tell me why?
Why so many lies? Say it… Say it, come on,
say it. Do not stay silent, say something.
Why are you silent? Say something.
I… I could not say it.
I could not.
I was unable to.
Why… Why did you do all this?
Why did you do it? Why?
Tell me, come on.
These photos, these documents,
these files, why are they here?
What are these? Why… Why are they here?
What is all this? Why are they here?
Do not just stand there in
silence, get up and say something.
Do not stay silent.
Why you played so many games,
why you hid your identity and
married me, tell me already.
This means you have been
watching us for a long time.
What are these? Why are they here?
What are these?
Why are they here?
So you have been watching
us for a long time, huh?
Or did you plan everything?
Murat’s debt,
what happened to me,
all this suffering I endured for so long.
You… You scratched out his face.
Please… Come on.
Look… You have no part in Murat’s, my
brother’s, my brother’s death, right Ateş?
Please tell me no.
Say I did not know, say
I knew nothing, please.
Say I knew nothing too…
I…
I did not want him to die.
You, the man I loved, the man I
fell for, could not have done this.
He could not. This is impossible.
I cannot be this wrong about you.
Talk to me. Say something.
Tell me this is a dream, that
I am trapped in a nightmare.
Say none of this is real,
say there is no revenge.
Tell me you are not Tahir.
Look, if you say it, I will believe you.
Come on.
Do not stay silent. Talk.
I said do not stay silent.
Why are you silent?
But you… You said you loved me.
You said you loved me deeply.
I was your precious pearl, Mercan.
Was all of it a lie?
Was all of it a game?
When you said my love, the
voice rising from your heart…
the compassion, mercy, love in your eyes
when you looked at me, was all of it a lie?
When you touched my face, that trembling
in your hand, afraid of hurting me…
Was all of it part of your revenge?
Was all of it a lie?
Was it all a lie, say it.
No.
None of it was.
All of it was real.
How was I so foolish?
How did I fail to see anything?
You… How did you become so cruel, Ateş?
Sorry, or should I call you Tahir?
Did you enjoy playing
with my feelings at least?
Did I entertain you?
What did you think?
What did you say behind my back?
How did you mock me?
You must have said how stupid she
is, how easily she believed, right?
You are right.
One must be foolish.
One must be foolish, you are right.
I came for revenge, yes.
Yes.
But I fell in love with you, Mercan.
Madly.
Do not. Do not touch me.
Let that last touch stay with me.
At least do not steal that from me.
I truly loved you, Mercan.
I never wanted to hurt you.
Stop… What love are you talking about?
There is no love inside so many lies.
Do you hear me?
There is no love.
You are a liar.
A liar.
Mercan? My daughter, what happened?
Mercan.
Haydar.
Mercan came from the storage
room like she saw a ghost.
Clearly something is there.
What do you mean something is there?
I do not know.
These people are not letting us go in.
Cemal.
Stop. It is too late now.
What is going on here?
Why are they near the storage room?
Aslı.
Mercan. We need to talk.
Open the door.
Mercan.
Mercan, please open the door.
We need to talk.
Mercan.
Are you okay, Mercan?
Open the door.
If you do not, I will break it.
Mercan, let me explain.
Listen once.
I know you are in shock. So am I.
I could not tell you the truth.
But please listen.
Go away.
Leave me alone.
I do not even want to see your face.
Mercan, please do not stay silent.
Scream, rage, get angry,
but do not stay silent.
Fine.
Then I will stay here
until you open the door.
These are photos from years ago.
Everything was in front
of us. How did we miss it?
All of this is my fault.
Panic blinded me.
The blame is mine.
Is he really Tahir?
Yes.
Tahir.
No way. How is this possible?
He was a poor orphan.
How did he gain such
wealth at such a young age?
I do not know, Nermin.
All I know is we are
inside a massive scheme.
My head…
He planned everything.
He did everything.
And I swallowed it all.
They had my son killed.
They dragged him into this pit.
Look, they have been watching us for years.
If not for you, my son would be alive.
Nermin, stop.
Who are you?
Why are you with Tahir?
Why do you hate me and my family? Speak.
Do you remember Ahmet?
Ahmet Taner.
I am sure you remember.
Ahmet was my husband.
You killed him.
What nonsense are you talking about?
I killed no one.
I did not kill Ahmet or your husband.
Ahmet was filth.
One of the men he ruined probably
killed him and dumped him somewhere.
You liar. You deny it shamelessly?
You did not only kill my
husband, you killed my baby.
What baby?
What are you talking about?
When I heard about Ahmet,
I gave birth at home.
My baby died without me ever smelling him.
I barely even saw him.
Tahir and you are chasing
revenge at the wrong door.
You knocked on the wrong door.
You nursed hatred for nothing.
I did not kill your husband.
I am here to turn your life
into hell, Haydar Yıldırım.
You already did.
You had my son killed in return
for your son’s blood price.
Nermin.
You are my son’s murderer.
You will answer for this.
Will I ask you?
This is a family matter.
It does not concern you.
What are you doing here anyway?
I am here for your mother’s health, Berat.
I said my family’s
health does not concern you.
Do you not understand? Go.
Brother. What?
Brother, will you fight
at a time like this?
Malik, please go.
We will talk later.
Fine.
Call me if you need anything.
My God, listen to them.
My mother.
Mother, are you okay?
Look, your son is happy.
Be happy too.
Look.
He married the woman he loves.
He built a home.
Mother.
Well done.
Are you mocking us?
The woman almost collapsed
and you talk about marriage.
Stay out of this, Çiçek.
Mother, you were almost
having a heart attack.
Çiçek, listen…
Why do you still pour fuel on the fire?
I am leaving then.
Yes.
This one meddles, that one meddles.
We stayed out and saw the result.
You married the first
girl you met, huh Berat?
Bravo.
Bravo, my son.
What am I here?
Who am I here? What am I?
What am I? Who am I?
Bravo to you.
Bravo to you too.
Bravo, my girl.
So my anchovy brained
son went and married you.
Why did you not say anything, my girl?
Why did you rush like
smuggling goods out of a fire?
You said yes right away and married him.
Why, my girl? Why?
We were going to tell you.
We truly were.
When were you going to tell me?
Mother…
When? You wore the dress,
the ring is on, you married.
So you married, huh?
Yes.
Çiçek.
Çiçek, for God’s sake hold me.
Hold my hand or there will be trouble.
My girl.
You did not even bother to ask my consent.
Who am I, for God’s sake?
Am I nothing?
Berat, tell me.
Mother, how could that be?
How could it?
You are my only one.
How could it… It happened.
What happened happened.
Mother…
Mother, calm down.
Come.
Bring cologne, my girl.
Okay.
Mother, not too much.
My God, help us.
Berat…
May God deal with you, Berat.
Where shall I go now?
You…
Since you did not count me…
Since you did not treat me like a person…
I am telling you both.
I do not count you either.
Done.
Go, wherever you go.
Take your wife and go.
Mercan, we must talk.
Open the door.
I wanted to explain for a long time.
I could not.
I feared you pulling away.
I could not risk losing you.
You are right.
You should have heard it from me first.
I love you, Mercan.
I am madly in love with you.
I never lied about this.
I tried to tell you, you stopped me.
Never again…
Never say you love me.
I do not want to hear this lie again.
If you loved me, you would not stop.
Everything except my love was a lie.
But you were my only truth.
You lit a fire inside me.
Do not touch me. Let go.
Your hand is bleeding.
I said let go.
I cannot leave you like this.
I will not. Do you hear me?
Come inside.
She was Ahmet’s wife.
Oh Haydar.
What have you done?
How did you let these
people into your home?
Is what she says true?
Do not talk nonsense, Nermin.
The woman is ill.
I am losing my mind.
So they came for revenge.
Tahir…
That woman called Müzeyyen
turned our lives into a nightmare.
She had our son killed.
Who knows what else she will do?
You are responsible for all this, Haydar.
You are right.
Because of me.
I should have suspected
Müzeyyen’s meaningless hatred.
What now?
Everyone is tense.
Oh Nezir, do not ask.
If only you knew what happened.
We learned who Ateş is.
I am sorry.
For everything.
For hurting you…
For lying.
Please do not stay silent, Mercan.
Scream, rage, but do not stay silent.
Why?
Why did you hide your identity?
What revenge are you taking on us?
What did we do to you?
What did I do?
What do you want from me?
Talk.
Answer me.
Why 187 days?
What is this 187 days?
If you have no answer, why talk?
Take it.
All of it is yours.
All of it.
All of it and your lies.
I cannot grasp this.
How can a person lie so much?
How does one do this?
How?
You are right.
Completely right.
Please give me time.
I…
I will explain everything.
I have no time for you.
Do you hear me?
No…
You did not only take the man I loved…
You took my childhood.
How do you do this?
How can I trust someone
capable of such schemes?
I do not trust you.
My brother would never hurt my mother.
That vile witch…
She poisoned my brother’s mind.
Çiçek, you are angry.
But think.
If Berat did not want to marry Zehra…
she could not convince him.
They married willingly.
No, Malik, I disagree.
That girl manipulates my brother.
We must save him.
Look, my love…
We do not know their feelings.
Judging is wrong.
Maybe Zehra changed.
Maybe she loves Berat…
Like he loves her.
You cannot believe this.
She loves no one but herself.
Even love serves her interest.
Think again.
What interest could Zehra have?
Money? No.
Working at the mansion?
No, she already works there.
See?
Am I the only one seeing her true face?
Something is wrong with her nature.
This marriage must end.
Çiçek…
I know heartbreak.
When I thought of losing you…
my world collapsed.
So…
if they love each other…
we should not interfere.
MALIK ARABIC 01
Meaning…
bearing sin is wrong.
No.
This marriage will not last.
Zehra will bring trouble.
I am telling you.
No way.
I asked you many times
who Ateş Karahan was.
You lied, Aslı.
I could not tell you who Ateş was.
Ateş would have killed me.
I broke Mercan and Ateş apart.
What more do you want?
You will pay for wasting my time.
What are you accusing me of?
I did not win alone.
You won too.
Without me you would not enter the company.
Ateş missed the clause thanks to me.
Yet you accuse me.
You can now watch arafta with
subtitles in multiple languages
and on some episodes, audio
in multiple languages as well.
For subtitles.
Tap settings, choose subtitles,
and pick your language on mobile.
Tap the top CC button
and select your language.
For audio, tap settings.
Choose Audio Track and
pick your language on mobile.
Open settings.
Choose Audio Track and pick your language.
The full Audio track upload
schedule is in the description below.
Are you listening to us?
Me?
No.
Come here.
I just arrived.
But when you say us…
Listen, Burak.
You wander too much.
Stop.
We will talk later.
What is it to you?
This is my mansion.
I go where I want.
Here or there.
He ruined everything.
Thank God my hand hurts…
Tahir.
So everything was your plan.
You are a menace.
How dare you enter my family?
I am not the Tahir you locked away.
Once more…
If you raise your hand again…
I swear I will break it.
What do you want?
What is your plan?
To kill me?
No.
I have no such intent.
Death would be salvation for you.
I will not grant it.
You…
You will beg me to die.
You stole my childhood.
You stole my family.
You stole my sister.
Not only my past…
my future too.
Did you think I would let this go?
You lost your mind.
This hatred will ruin…
Mercan’s life too.
Do not say Mercan’s name.
I have nothing to lose.
Except her.
Çiçek, bring hot water.
Okay.
Wow.
So Ateş Bey is Tahir?
Yes. He is our Tahir.
How did I not recognize him?
Oh my dear.
He grew into a man.
I understand nothing.
Why did he change his name?
Who is he anyway?
Did you know?
No.
I knew nothing.
I swear I knew nothing.
I heard the name Tahir for the first time.
He has a score with the family.
I vaguely remember Tahir.
His sadness makes sense now.
Tahir was a good child.
I loved him.
Oh my dear.
Does he stay here?
He became a strong young man.
It showed since childhood.
Oh my dear.
When things calm down, I will talk to him.
But chaos will grow.
It will not settle.
What did Mercan do?
This is awful.
You love a man.
Then he becomes someone else.
Awful.
I will wash the lentils.
Çiçek, turn off the stove.
Just in case.
You know something, do not you?
You eavesdrop.
Çiçek.
Speak honestly.
Sister in law?
Yes.
She is your sister in law.
Patience.
Look.
You scolded me for nothing.
Chaos is good.
Mercan’s world collapsed.
Why do you not listen to me?
Why do you create problems?
If I did not speak, Ateş would.
Good thing I did.
Their bond will never heal.
You know nothing, Aslı.
What do I not know?
How did Mercan enter the storage room?
How?
She did.
How would I know?
Using it was wrong from the start.
Someone would see.
You are lying.
What are you accusing me of?
You were going to tell everything.
She should not learn this way.
I should have told her.
I know what you did.
I did not.
She went in herself.
Why do you care so much?
If she truly loves you, she will not leave.
I cannot believe you.
Despite everything…
I was so wrong trusting you.
Look at this.
Everything spills out.
One should care for their home.
Three salaries enter this house.
They hoard money.
Fine, I know how to spend it.
Furniture must change first.
Enjoy your meal, my wife.
Thanks.
Did you rest?
A little.
Berat.
Yes?
We married today and started work.
We obey orders, right?
No honeymoon.
We married suddenly.
When would we go?
Where will we sleep?
In my room.
Do not be ridiculous.
The bed is small.
We squeeze.
No.
We must shop.
A new bride arrived.
I will not stay there.
Too small.
No space for my things.
Which room will you not stay in?
Berat’s tiny room.
You think this is a palace?
Remember.
This is the annex.
God forbid.
I love him.
Understand.
I want nothing.
I do not want to see or speak.
Mercan, please.
Let me stay near you.
As who?
Who are you?
I do not even know.
Why enter as Ateş?
I know nothing.
I will be whoever you want.
Just do not leave.
You will never forgive me, right?
Would you forgive?
Was it worth it?
All this pain?
All the suffering you caused?
My brother died because of ambition.
There are things you do not know.
I never wanted harm.
Then what?
Tell everything.
No. I do not want.
Do not explain.
I do not care why.
After destruction, what meaning remains?
I trusted you.
Trust again. Listen.
Let go.
I will not.
You played with my feelings.
I opened my heart.
You were my first and last.
Not worth it.
Worth it.
Our bond is worth everything.
You were my first and last.
My girl, what are you doing?
This is the kitchen.
Why do you not help?
I married today.
Expecting work is rude.
Today is my day off.
No one can make me work.
I need to shop.
Shame.
Will you ruin our home?
What prices are these?
I am a new bride.
I will get what I want.
My husband circles around me.
He handles it.
I am tired of sitting.
I will rest at home.
You forgot you serve Müzeyyen Hanım.
She will devour my brother.
I love him.
Deeply.
You are Ateş.
I am drawn to fire.
Lies surrounded me.
You freed me.
You gave me hope.
One more blow and I fall.
I knew this.
She will not look at me.
I lost Mercan.
I would explain.
Aslı and Müzeyyen stopped me.
However she learned…
I cannot accept forgiving Haydar.
Your suffering, your sister…
She cannot ignore this.
Something is wrong.
I told her nothing.
After all that destruction…
I could not tell her about her father.
Better she knows nothing now.
What shall I say?
Is her distance not natural?
Put yourself in her place.
She is devastated.
She loves you.
You miss my point.
Let me repeat.
She loves you.
You searched for Tahir together.
What more do you want?
She deserves truth.
I do not know.
I am lost.
I sharpened myself with revenge.
I earned money for revenge.
Müzeyyen fueled it.
Fate.
I fell for Haydar’s daughter.
I feel trapped.
I cannot give her up.
I cannot.
Ateş, listen.
You say it yourself.
You must talk to her.
Truth is her right.
I understand you.
You feel stuck.
Only way out is talking.
Or you may lose her forever.
You took not only the man I loved…
you took my childhood.
What did Mercan Hanım do?
I worry.
Strange, right?
Yes.
I am exhausted.
You are right.
With your mother’s work…
you tired.
I feel for you.
Work is not the issue…
unrest drained me.
Zehra moved in.
Seeing her angers me.
Çiçek.
I must tell you something.
What happened?
As I said…
I want no secrets.
My family planned a future in Egypt.
They want me back.
To run companies.
To marry chosen bride.
They will not approve us?
Meaning…
They approve no one unwanted.
Especially someone tying me to Istanbul…
never.
My father has not spoken for two years.
I left everything for you.
Çiçek.
From now on…
our road is hard.
My love…
strong enough.
Will you hold my hand…
stay beside me…
face everything with me?
Always.
I love you.
I love you too.
I would speak with Ateş Bey.
Speak to me.
It is important.
Ateş is not in mood.
Speak to me.
Same difference.
I will speak. Take this seriously.
Can I use this?
This contract…
Partnership with Nezir.
I never noticed this clause.
We can remove Nezir.
How did Aslı miss this?
She did not.
She hid it.
I overheard them.
Aslı is the reason.
Do not tell anyone yet.
I will investigate.
Okay.
As you wish.
Will you ignore me?
I disappointed you.
What do you want from me?
What is your aim?
You lied for months.
You made my family suffer.
You expect forgiveness?
How can I forgive?
We lived hell here.
I fought hatred for weeks.
My brother…
died.
Müzeyyen caused it.
Listen to me.
You listen.
I trusted you despite everything.
I did not run with Nezir.
I stayed.
Why did you make me love you?
What did you want?
What did I do?
You hurt my family.
What revenge is this?
What did we do?
Why the name Ateş?
Why 187 days of marriage?
187 days we were locked in basement.
Exactly 187 days.
Your father tortured us.
Darkness, hunger, cold.
He imprisoned us.
While you were safe…
we fought to survive.
You only saw me in garden.
Did you see me otherwise?
Your father gave us hell.
Without reason.
You sought revenge for this?
Was this it?
I wish it were.
I am not someone…
seeking revenge for hunger alone.
You saw my scars.
Then why Ateş?
Why all this?
My sister…
Eylül…
Your father…
my sister…
killed Eylül.
He killed Eylül.
My sister…
Your father killed my…
Your father…
my sibling…
killed Eylül.
He killed Eylül.
My sibling…
he killed Eylül.
Your father killed my sibling…
No, no, no…
No, my father is not a man this cruel.
He would never do such a thing.
You, you are lying. You
are a first rate liar.
You are saying all this to hurt me, right?
The last thing I would ever
want is to hurt you, Mercan.
I wish none of this had happened.
I wish you had never suffered.
Then what do you want from
me? Why are you doing this?
Believe me, it is all
real. None of it is a lie.
Believe me, seeing you like this breaks me.
But this is the truth, Mercan.
Stop it. Do not pretend
to feel sorry for me.
Do not pretend to love me either.
I know. All of this is part of your
revenge, part of your plan, right?
Me too. That fake love
as well. All of it, right?
Then say it. Say my
father did not kill Eylül.
Believe me, what I am saying is not a lie.
I wish none of this had ever happened.
Even if you do not believe
it, this is the truth, Mercan.
I know what I went through.
I know what my sibling went through.
I wish he had never done it.
I wish Eylül were alive right now.
But Eylül could not
endure that torment, Mercan.
I watched her losing her
life day by day before my eyes.
Every night when I close my eyes,
that basement he turned into a prison
for us for 187 days comes back to me.
I see him torturing Eylül.
I see myself failing to protect my sibling.
I could not protect my sibling.
I do not know how I am
alive while she is dead.
I do not know how I am breathing, Mercan.
I hate myself for being alive.
I keep thinking I wish I
had died instead of her.
That is the man you call your father.
He made us suffer pain beyond words.
Pain that will never fade.
Years pass, yet I am still burning inside.
That is why I named myself
Ateş. To become fire and burn.
But I never knew I would light that
fire in your heart, Mercan. I never knew.
Eylül...
Eylül.
No, no. I cannot be the
daughter of such a cruel man. No.
You might be his daughter.
But you are not like him.
You are not responsible for what he did.
I do not know anymore.
I do not know what to
believe, who to trust.
My God, what are we being punished for?
What are we living through?
Another day is over.
How many days has it been?
It has been 187 days, Eylül.
When it becomes 200, you will save
me from here, right? You promised.
Let my sister go. Let her go.
I said let her go.
Step back.
She is dead. She is dead. You
will never ask about her again.
Do you understand? You will do
exactly what I say. Speak up, damn it.
Your mother and father are dead.
From now on, this is where you belong.
Brother.
I told you to move away.
Your father killed my sibling, Eylül.
We are finished. We are
finished, Haydar. Ruined.
You heard what that woman said, right?
She has completely lost control.
Enough, Nermin. Stop hovering over me,
you are making my head spin. Sit down.
That woman has sworn revenge.
She might come after our lives
and you are telling me to sit.
How are you this calm, Haydar?
Who says I am calm, Nermin?
Do you think I know what to do?
They have cornered us badly.
This is all because of you.
We are in this mess because of
the sins you committed in the past.
That woman took revenge for what
you did to her son on my Murat.
Because of you, I buried my son.
Now it is our turn. You are responsible
for everything that has happened to us.
Enough. Enough. Murat already…
What? Murat already what?
Nothing.
There is nothing to defend
about what you did, right?
That is why you are silent.
Stop standing there.
Do something before it is too
late. Clean up this mess. Save us.
I swear I missed you so
much today, more than usual.
Someone might see us.
What happened? Did someone come?
No, no. No one came but…
The days when you will not worry about
being seen are very close. Very close.
Yes, but until those days
come, we need to be careful.
My mother has not recovered
from the shock my brother caused.
I do not want her to see us.
I am so afraid something
will happen to her.
You are right, my love.
Your Aunt Binnaz has fragile health.
And I saw how upset
you get when she is ill.
I cannot bear to see you upset.
That is why whenever you want,
however you want, it will be that way.
That is why I love you so much.
Because you are like this,
because you are understanding…
Because you look out not only
for me but also for my family.
I feel very lucky.
That luck is mine, my love.
I love you so much…
God truly loves me…
that He put someone like
you in my path. I am so happy.
Being like this feels so good.
Like what?
Like in the old days.
The truly beautiful one is you.
My parents are waiting
for me now. I need to go.
All right then, you are leaving.
Good night.
Good night. See you tomorrow.
See you.
Dad.
Yes, my daughter?
My daughter? My daughter, huh?
What about Eylül?
Her…
Did you kill her…
My daughter, what is
wrong? What is happening?
What are you trying to say?
I cannot comprehend it anymore. I cannot.
I do not know what to do.
I do not want to believe it.
The man I called father, the man I relied
on my whole life, cannot have done this.
My daughter, what are you saying?
What did I do to whom, for God’s sake?
What did you do to Tahir and Eylül, dad?
Did you really lock those
children in that basement?
Eylül…
Tell me it is not true.
Please tell me it is not true.
Tell me you did not harm
that little girl. Please.
That man called Ateş told
you all this, did he not?
He poisoned your mind.
Are you going to believe a man
you met yesterday, or your father?
That poor girl died of natural
causes on the way to the hospital.
I said they were entrusted to
me, Esma’s and Selim’s legacy.
I took care of them like roses.
Why are you shouting again?
Your voices reached upstairs.
Good you came. Answer me.
What is going on, Mercan?
Tahir and Eylül.
Did you really lock those two
small children in that cold basement?
Were you truly capable of such cruelty?
We did nothing cruel. You were
small, you would not remember.
They were very unruly, aggressive.
We could not handle them.
Time passed, I do not remember clearly but
maybe we locked them in the basement
once or twice to calm them down.
But it is not true we neglected them.
We provided everything they needed.
When I asked you before,
you did not even remember.
You said you did not know Eylül.
I do not know what to do anymore.
I do not know who to believe, who to trust.
I do not know who is telling
the truth, who is lying.
It feels like I am in limbo
and I do not know which way to go.
My daughter, your mother and I…
Do not touch me. Do not.
The day I learned his sibling
died, I should have killed him too.
So what now? Should Haydar try to run?
I have not forgotten my goal. Do not worry.
I warned the men. They are all on alert.
Haydar cannot escape anywhere.
The plan has not changed.
If you find the time between
consoling Ms. Mercan, of course.
Now it is time to stand together.
Hard days passed, harder
ones await us, friends.
I have no patience left.
I do not want to see that man
walking around the mansion freely.
Do whatever is necessary, immediately.
What do you think, Ateş? Are
we finishing Haydar right away?
I know you are torn. Not
because you pity Haydar,
but because you do not want
Mercan to suffer. I know that too.
I would not want to be in your place.
Our plan regarding Haydar has not changed.
Even despite Mercan?
Despite Mercan. This is separate from that.
Hard days await us. My God, help us.
Mom.
Yes, my child.
Thank you.
Enjoy your meal.
I am deeply hurt by you, my son.
From the day you were born, I
cared for you like my own eyes…
fed you, raised you,
brought you to this age.
But what did you do?
You left without a word
and married that girl.
You disregarded all my years of effort.
You trampled me.
Do not say that, mom.
You are precious to me.
You are my life, my very breath.
Would anyone harm the one they love most?
You erased me, my son.
Mom, my intention was not to hurt you.
I love Zehra deeply.
I wanted to build a home with her.
Because I knew you would not
approve, I chose this path.
How do you know I would not approve?
Did you ask me?
Let us say I assumed.
That is not how things work, Mr. Berat.
There is propriety, there is order.
What good is a home built after
crushing and ignoring your family?
Forgive me, mom.
We did something reckless.
Give me one chance like
the one you gave Çiçek.
You accepted Malik as a son in law…
accept Zehra as your daughter in law too.
Do you really love this girl that much?
More than you know, mom.
All that happened…
so much pain, cruelty, torture…
it is so heavy.
A child died.
My God, what kind of trial is this?
Please give me strength to endure.
Please give me strength.
My father…
Did my father really lock
Tahir and Eylül in here?
It is so hard to believe.
A person with a heart…
how does he do this to
two defenseless children?
How?
Mercan.
I was worried about you. Are you okay?
How could I be okay?
You are right.
In a situation like this…
I do not know what I can
do to make you feel better.
You want me to feel better?
Then show me a way out.
I do not want to stay in limbo anymore.
I can only show you the real way out.
And you already know the truth.
Your father took my mother, my father,
my sibling, my whole family from me.
This is the truth.
I swore revenge at their graves.
I promised myself I would
not turn back from my revenge.
This is the truth.
I only want justice for
the lives I lost, Mercan.
This is the truth.
So you want justice.
Then what was my sin?
Why did you put me through this?
I was just a small
child like you once were.
Did I hurt you? Did I burn your heart?
No.
You are the most innocent
person in this story.
I am the most innocent one,
huh? What did that change?
Me.
This love was something I did not
calculate while planning revenge.
At first, I could not
even admit it to myself.
Because the idea of falling in love
with my enemy’s daughter drove me mad.
There was a fierce battle
between my heart and my mind.
I was in limbo too.
I fell into such a love…
that my heart emerged victorious.
And now I am paying the price.
Come here, Aslı. We need
to talk. I said come here.
What are you doing? What is your problem?
Are you that curious about my problem?
This is my problem.
Say something. Convince
me. I am begging you.
Let me believe this is a lie
so I can burn it and believe you.
Where did you find this?
Is this really the question
you are asking me right now, Aslı?
Let us say I found it somewhere.
Let me tell you the real
question you should ask.
Why did you do this to us, Aslı?
I did what I believed was right.
Betraying us is what
you believed was right?
What betrayal? Who did I betray?
Mercan and Ateş were getting close.
The only person who could
separate them was Nezir.
I found a loophole in
the contract and used it.
I wanted him to tear Mercan and Ateş apart.
But Nezir did not use his chance well.
Whatever the case, it does not
change the fact you betrayed us.
You are wrong. I stayed loyal to the plan.
The real betrayal was Ateş.
He fell in love with his enemy’s daughter.
But I told you. I warned you
many times. You did not listen.
So I took initiative and took precautions.
Looking at where we are now, was I wrong?
Nothing you say excuses your betrayal.
You knowingly chose the dark side.
You are no different from the
people we came here to take revenge on.
How could you do this? I
do not recognize you anymore.
You will not tell Ateş, right?
Cemal, please do not tell him.
If you care about me even
a little, do not tell him.
I will lose him forever.
He will never even
look at me again. Please.
If you know me even a little, you
know I will not hide anything from Ateş.
Unfortunately, he has
no time for you right now.
But do not get comfortable.
One day the truth will come out.
And when it does, deal with your own mess.
Get rid of Nezir as soon as possible.
I am very sorry.
Me too.
Were you eavesdropping?
No point. I was alone in the room.
What would I listen at your door for?
Something you did not do?
Oh dear, did you become a victim of love?
Get out of my way.
All right, wait. Let us talk for a second.
You do not want to? Fine, I will talk.
Remember I told you the
other day you were naive?
I am raising the stakes.
You are the most foolish
person I have ever met.
You believed Ateş’s
love, despite my warnings.
Well, better late than never.
Enough. Enough. Leave me alone, all of you.
We will fall. But we are not done
with you and your family yet. Not yet.
I thought something warm would help.
Thanks.
Enjoy.
I think I am hurting everyone lately.
There is nothing I can do for
the glass. But there is for Mercan.
I think you should go talk to her.
I did. It did not help. She is deeply hurt.
She thinks I used her for revenge.
She does not believe I love her.
She does not believe it, huh?
Then what, does she believe her father?
She does not know who to believe.
And she is not wrong.
Her father and I both lied to her.
Not being able to help her,
having her so close yet so far from me,
hurts me deeply.
So love and revenge cannot coexist.
They must. I will not give
up my love or my revenge.
I am still so confused.
So the man we thought was
Ateş was actually Tahir.
And he says such unthinkable
things about your family.
Why would Uncle Haydar do such a thing?
They deny everything.
I do not know. One cannot
imagine such things about family.
Ateş’s words echo in my
ears, my father’s answers too.
What am I in the middle of?
I am very sorry, Mercan.
Why?
I encouraged you about
Ateş too. I regret it deeply.
Had I known, I would never
have supported this relationship.
How could you have known?
Look, even I failed to see
what was right in front of me.
Ateş, fool. You destroyed yourself.
Well done. Thanks to
you, Mercan will be mine.
Greetings, Mercan.
Your father just told me everything.
Honestly, I am not surprised.
I told you many times from the
start that man was dangerous.
Brother, what are you doing?
Just say the word. I will
make them all pay right now.
What are you saying, Nezir?
What do you think you are doing?
I will not allow you to
harm him, no matter what.
Put that gun down right
now. Do you understand?
Or you will answer to me.
Mercan, you do not understand me.
I would do anything for you.
To protect you. Because I…
Please.
I am dropping the subject
out of respect for Demet.
Let us not drag this out. I do
not want you involved. Understood?
Everything done to you concerns me too.
But know this. I am always by your side.
If you will excuse me, I will rest.
Mercan. Do not be sad.
These days will pass.
Insallah, Demet.
As I said, Mercan. You
only need to call me.
Will you excuse me?
No. I will not let you pass until we talk.
I do not want to talk.
Do not punish me with
silence. Not me, not yourself.
I do not know what to
say. Or what to believe.
And you are responsible for this.
I am like this because of your lies.
I realized I valued you
far more than you deserved.
I loved you far more than you
deserved. I regret it deeply.
Can I go now? I am
exhausted. I want to rest.
So you are tired?
What are you doing?
Put me down. Put me down.
I will not let go. Stop struggling.
I said put me down.
Put me down. Let go.
Enough already. Put me down.
Someone will see us. Enough. Put me down.
Get in here. Sit.
Let go. I am not going anywhere with you.
You are coming. Behave yourself.
Bully. What do you think you are doing?
You cannot take me
anywhere by force. Let go.
I can stay like this for hours. No
problem at all. I would even be happy.
Either you stop resisting and
come with me, or the choice is yours.
Why are you looking like that?
I still see myself.
I did not say I did not love
you. I said I regret loving you.
Do not resist. You have nowhere to run.
At least tell me where we are going.
You will see when we get there.
You will see, huh. Annoying.
Zehra is right. Look, we are
working on our second day of marriage.
Honeymoon talk is nonsense.
Damn.
Anyway.
Bismillah.
Berat.
I know you are still angry at me.
I came knowing you might snap at me.
Do not worry, I will not bother you long.
I will say a few things and go.
Congratulations.
I hope your marriage with
Zehra lasts a lifetime.
Is that what you came to say?
Of course. What did you think?
Nothing. I thought nothing.
You know what, Malik?
You are the first to congratulate me.
Thanks.
Do you know what I realized just now?
Old friends do not become
enemies that easily. Thanks.
Thanks.
Malik, Arabic 02.
So?
I am really glad you think like this.
I missed being like this.
Me too, you know.
Just like the old days.
Come on then. Grab hold
of this. Let us do it.
You immediately put me to work.
Come on. Be careful. Do not hurt yourself.
Then Çiçek will come nagging.
It will not happen, do not worry.
Careful.
Look, how would you lift this without me?
Hold it.
That is it.
Malik.
Thanks, brother.
Thanks.
If you want, I can
treat you to a meal today.
Great. I know a good place.
What was that earlier, brother?
What did I do?
Putting a gun on the
table, threats and all.
Are you a bandit?
What else was I supposed to do, Demet?
Did you not see Mercan’s state?
The poor girl is shattered.
I am madly in love with Mercan.
Do you not understand?
You protect the one you love.
I would die for her.
If needed, I would kill.
Say whatever you want.
I will never understand this mindset.
Fine.
Then do not tire yourself.
Do you want my happiness?
What kind of question is that?
Of course I want your happiness.
Then instead of posturing,
help me fix things with Mercan.
Brother, I think you
should see a psychologist.
I am honestly worried
about your mental health.
Let us go. I am not eating anything.
I do not care what anyone says.
In the end, Mercan will be mine.
Zehra, pass me that strainer.
Would it hurt you to get it yourself?
I do not feel like myself today.
I cannot even move my finger.
Good luck.
Welcome home, my husband.
Thanks.
You must be tired.
Come sit. I will pour you some tea.
That would be good.
Look how she jumped up
when she saw my brother.
For God’s sake, I have never
seen someone act this well.
It is not the girl’s fault. It is Berat’s.
Look, he is practically
falling into her mouth.
My God.
Here you go, my husband.
Thank you, my wife.
May it be sweet as honey for you.
Oh my God.
The tea is so good.
You can tell you made it.
Brother, open this for me, please.
What do you mean?
Why should Berat open it?
My husband is tired.
If you cannot, call Malik.
I am very tired, you know.
Work has drained my faith.
I mean it that much.
Oh my.
Did we tell you to dig trenches?
We just asked you to open the lid.
What is this? What
kind of behavior is this?
No.
My husband will lose strength.
My God, give me patience.
Drink.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
Give it here, my daughter. I will open it.
Here.
Why did you bring me here?
I know you like this place.
You used to come here often with Demet.
You know everything.
Who knows how long you
have been watching me.
I tried not to watch too much.
Because you enchanted me.
And that could have pulled
me away from my purpose.
Should I be happy now?
I think you should not bother yourself.
Do not waste your words either.
I do not feel like believing you.
You were writing your name in the sand.
Only Mercan.
I was so afraid you would
write another name next to it.
You never did.
One day after you left, I
wrote Ateş next to your name.
I watched it for a moment.
Then I got angry with myself and erased it.
I knew then you would be my
downfall, yet I thought I could stop it.
I could not. After that,
I tried to stay away.
But my battle never ended.
Because of you.
Am I supposed to be moved?
Not to move you. Just so you know.
These are the facts.
Do you know what the truth is?
You wrote the name Ateş next to Mercan.
If you had chosen to write Tahir,
maybe our lives would
be very different now.
But you chose Ateş.
And you fell in love with Ateş.
Yes.
I fell in love with Ateş.
Deeply.
That is why you are the greatest
disappointment of my life, Ateş.
You erased your name from the sand, right?
I will erase you from my heart.
There will not even be a trace left.
As if I never loved you.
It is over.
All that remains of me is wreckage.
Is it really that easy to tear out?
If it were that easy, I would not
be standing before you in this pain.
It will be very hard. I
know. But I will succeed.
I will not lose to you again.
Do not deceive yourself.
There are invisible bonds between us.
Like a mark written by fate.
We cannot break free.
I know it from myself.
You know it too.
Here, take it.
Go on, eat.
One of the best charities is
feeding what is given to you.
Are you feeding the cat?
Çiçek, come here. Yes.
She emptied all the food bowls.
The kitten ate everything.
I brought you tea.
It will warm you up.
Bless your hands, Çiçek.
Tea will be great.
Then let us trade.
I will take the tea, you take the kitten.
Come here.
See, she loves me. She will not let go.
You see.
She loves me too.
Do you want to feed her as well?
Çiçek, I am so happy.
We are just like the old days right now.
Yes, I am very happy too.
I find myself smiling like
crazy when I think about it.
Çiçek, we have been
together almost two years now.
But look, Berat went before us
and married the girl he loves.
I swear I am jealous of my brother in law.
He entered married life before us.
Really, who would have thought?
And with Zehra too.
Right?
What do you think?
My patience is gone.
I cannot endure it anymore.
Let us start the wedding
procedures as soon as possible.
I want it too. I cannot endure it either.
But we need to convince your family.
So everyone is content and no one is hurt.
That will happen, Çiçek. It will.
Right?
Oh my little one.
Is she not adorable?
She is.
Demet.
Shall we talk for a bit?
Of course.
Yes, I am listening.
Your brother still thinks we are together.
Did he block your way again?
He probably does not believe
it because we still talk.
I will tell him it is no longer necessary.
Why are you down?
My mind is on Mercan.
She is devastated after
everything that happened.
And all I can do is talk.
I truly do not know what to do for her.
What happened upset me too.
We also started a nice relationship.
Once trust is broken,
it is hard to rebuild.
Look, we both understood it would not work.
Demet.
Would you reconsider?
No need, Burak.
Look, we stayed friends.
Let it stay this way.
Do not expect more.
All right.
Mashallah. Did you make soup for me?
Enjoy, my husband.
I am tasting it right away.
How is it?
Let me tell you something.
This soup is perfect. Bless your hands.
Enjoy it, my husband.
May it heal you.
Berat.
We got married, but I am not at peace.
What happened?
Your mother does not
want me, and she shows it.
Can someone be happy
where they are not wanted?
It is new, my dear. She is adjusting.
It will get better. Do not worry.
Would you talk to her again?
All right. I will talk. Let
them come. I will handle it.
Do not worry.
Okay.
Let me say something.
The soup is really good.
Welcome, Çiçek.
Your sister in law made soup.
Drink it. Do not miss it.
No, thanks.
Drink it.
I said no.
Mom.
My dear mom.
My precious.
Look at this.
How are you, mom?
I am fine, my son.
Shall we talk, mom?
What will you talk
about? I have things to do.
Mom, what if you gave up this stubbornness?
Look, Zehra and I…
started a path together.
We signed, we exchanged rings.
She is your daughter in law now.
Right?
Is that not right?
Is it not?
Let me kiss your hand, mom.
Mom, look, you are upset and we are upset.
What if this coldness ended?
Would it not be better if everyone smiled?
Right, Çiçek?
Come on, mom. Be generous.
Show us your grace.
Look, I am sad.
Come on, let me kiss your hand.
Mom.
My dear mom.
You did it again. You showed your grace.
Kiss grandma’s hand.
Let me kiss it.
My dear mom.
See, she showed her grace again.
I will take the plates to the table.
Then I will…
take these too.
Brother, are you doing chores?
My eyes filled with tears.
What will happen? I can do
it. My hands will not fall off.
You will lose strength.
Çiçek.
Nothing will happen.
Çiçek, nothing will happen.
I always do it.
Son, what are you letting them do to you?
God forbid.
Mom, I guess you approved Zehra
since you let her kiss your hand.
Look at me.
Look.
Did you see?
Do I have that look?
Mrs. Binnaz, did you play a trick?
We must have played a trick.
The hand is strong or
the gentleman is strong.
We will see, Ms. Zehra.
I never wanted you to go through all this.
My heart lost control.
I could not handle you.
You captured me.
Your hair, your eyes, your
face, your smile, your heart.
I fell in love with every part of you.
We can go now.
I know you are angry at me.
But in the end, you will forgive me.
Your confidence is admirable.
But do not trust it so much.
I trust our love.
You told me so many lies.
Now you talk about the
past, love, forgiveness.
You became fire and burned everything.
You gave up on Tahir and
filled yourself with revenge.
You told me Tahir was dead.
I read his death in a
fake newspaper clipping.
Did you never think about how I felt?
I could not even rejoice that
Tahir was alive because of you.
It might be because Tahir is me.
You are annoyed with me
these days for that reason.
Mercan, what are you doing?
I am taking revenge.
You know revenge well.
I am telling you to stop.
Stop. Do not resist.
I will not let you run away anymore.
I will not give up.
I will not surrender.
You already gave up on me.
I never truly existed for you anyway.
You know that is not true.
I do not know.
All I know is you took
your revenge successfully.
When the time is up, we will divorce.
The only thing that
matters to you is revenge.
That is the only truth for you.
My revenge is as big as my love.
And just as real.
As big as your revenge?
Yes.
All right.
Then so be it.
If your love is as real
and as big as your revenge…
if you had to choose between them,
could you give up your
revenge for your love?