Ateş.
I heard a gunshot.
Son, we heard a gunshot. Are you okay?
What did you do to my daughter?
There is no need to worry, mom.
I am fine.
I was cleaning the gun.
It went off suddenly.
I am not stupid.
Ateş would not accidentally fire a gun.
Why do you interfere in
everything that does not concern you?
Your special interest in Ateş.
What is it to you?
I will ask you one last time.
Is what Ateş said true?
You could not have hurt those children.
They stayed here, but we took care of them.
Ateş is lying.
They came to prepare our end.
Everything is planned. You see it.
First they killed your
brother. Now it is my turn.
You tried to kill the woman I love.
Now that my partnership is
over, I have nothing left to hide.
Nezir?
You stand here today thanks to
the belts that struck your back.
Who were you?
What were you to me?
Why should I have taken
care of you and your sibling?
Should I have fed you at my table?
I showed you too much mercy.
The belt was not enough.
I should have crippled you.
I heard what kind of monster
you are, from your own mouth.
My daughter, there are
things you do not know.
Do not touch me. Do not
ever call me my daughter.
Can justify the cruelty you
inflicted on Eylül and Tahir,
the torture, the murder you committed.
Say the word and I will
deal with that bandit.
Look, Nezir.
I warn you again.
Do not come to me with this.
If you harm Ateş, you will face me.
Mercan had kidney disease.
She was the only compatible donor.
For Mercan to live, Eylül had to die.
Tell me, Ateş.
To save the one you love,
would you take another life?
You can now watch arafta with
subtitles in multiple languages
and on some episodes, audio
in multiple languages as well.
For subtitles.
Tap settings, choose subtitles,
and pick your language on mobile.
Tap the top CC button
and select your language.
For audio, tap settings.
Choose Audio Track and
pick your language on mobile.
Open settings.
Choose Audio Track and pick your language.
The full Audio track upload
schedule is in the description below.
I took Eylül away that day.
We were going to take her kidney...
Still haven't figured it out?
Mercan is a kidney patient.
She would have died if
she didn't get a transplant.
Eylül... I am so sorry
for what my father did.
For locking you up in there...
For the pain he caused you...
For your fears!
For the helplessness you
experienced at such a young age!
I am so helpless too...
I'm helpless because I'm the daughter of
a man like that, it destroys me every day!
I wish you were alive so I could fall
to my knees and truly apologize to you.
I am so mad at myself!
I tell myself you could have seen it.
But then I say we were too
young, how was I supposed to see it.
No matter what I say...
the outcome won't change.
Could you leave us alone?
I couldn't look after you.
I couldn't protect you...
I couldn't be a big brother to you.
I couldn't hold your hands
while you were struggling...
I wish I had died instead of you.
I feel like I'm going crazy
the more I think about it.
Who knows how scared you were?
While they sacrificed you
without blinking an eye.
What were you to them anyway...
A nobody.
You died all alone, my sister...
I promise you.
I won't die without taking your revenge.
Those who caused this
pain will never know peace.
Son!
We are father and son.
Our bond cannot be broken.
Everyone leaves, at the end of
the day, we only have each other.
A person's family is the
only place they can lean on...
I wish I could call you
father, that I could embrace you.
Even if we make mistakes, break or destroy things,
we are the ones who put ourselves back together, son.
Help me...
Don't let them destroy your father...
Come let me hug you.
Open these arms for the
people you will be a father to.
Don't waste your breath.
If I had cried, I could have convinced him.
But I couldn't cry.
Ateş.
Are you okay?
Let's go to the coast and get some fresh
air if you want. It'll be good for you.
Nothing will make me feel better.
My father killed all the hope
and happiness inside her...
Shall we walk in the garden...?
I just want to be by your side. Help-
You can't help me.
It's better if I stay alone.
I don't understand what happened but...
Alright... Whatever you want.
What am I going to do now...
What am I going to do with you...
How am I going to get out of this
without upsetting or hurting you?
So? What are we going to do now...
Don't be sad, my Çiçek. I'll
figure this out, don't worry.
There has to be a way
out, there definitely is.
How are we going to find it, Malik?
Look... My God, what are we going to do?
Are we never going to see each other again!
No, of course not. Nothing
like that will happen.
Ah... Çiçek!
Çiçek!
Come here, come here! Sit down right here!
Sit! Sit down girl! Sit!
Sit, calm down!
Oh my God, good Lord!
Stop girl! Stop!
Çiçek, calm down. There must be a mistake.
A document or something must
be missing. It's nothing else.
Don't worry, I'll find a way.
Yes, Çiçek... There must
be a way to appeal this.
Of course there is.
We'll solve this situation.
It's not the end of the world,
girl. A solution will be found.
Look on the bright side.
In a long-distance relationship,
passion and longing are always high.
You won't get bored of each other.
What are you talking about!
Are you kidding me!
Get out! Leave!
Oh for God's sake!
Calm down, Çiçek.
Okay, okay. We'll see.
Calm down, girl.
-Malik? -Hmm?
Let's go ask together,
see if we can appeal it.
Of course. Okay, my Çiçek, please
don't be sad. We'll handle it.
My God.
Don't be sad, my dear.
-Excuse us. -Alright son.
No problem, girl. No problem.
If there is a problem,
there is a cure, my girl.
What if there isn't, mom...
What if he leaves and can't
come back, mom! I can't take it!
Don't cry my dear, don't cry.
There must surely be a way.
We will try until we find it.
We will pray too.
God will help us.
We'll figure it out.
To Eylül...
That's how that scumbag
tormented my sister.
There's only one thing left to do, Ateş.
There is no point in
dragging this out any longer.
This man doesn't have the right to
take one more breath in this world!
You accuse my father of
being a murderer, right?
Are you any different from him?
You point a gun at
someone without blinking!
You're turning into the person you accuse!
What are you waiting
for, come on, shoot me!
What are you waiting for, pull the trigger!
We didn't set out on this path to kill.
I'm not a murderer like him.
I'm not going to finish
him off that easily.
I'll make him beg, make him crawl.
He's going to experience
everything he lived through tenfold.
He will beg to die.
That's how my scales of justice work.
He must serve his punishment.
But there is one more issue...
Mercan doesn't know why Eylül died.
I'll tell her when the time comes.
If she hears it not from me...
but from someone else
I will never forgive!
Is that understood?
One way or another, Eylül
died because of Mercan.
She was murdered...
Instead of making them pay for this,
you're still trying to protect Mercan.
I agree.
Mercan is off-limits.
She is different.
Ms. Müzeyyen.
Especially you, Aslı!
You heard what I said too.
Let go of me, I'll tell you. I'll talk.
I will tell you.
I took Eylül away that day!
Because we were going to take her kidney.
What?
I'll kill you!
What are you telling me?
The truth.
No!
You're doing this so I'll kill you!
Death is a salvation for you.
Still haven't figured it out?
Mercan was a kidney patient.
She would have died if
there was no transplant.
That man sacrificed my sister, Cemal.
My little sister
suffered pain far beyond her years.
And in the end, without
pitying her tears...
they killed her...
This was her whole life...
This is what my Eylül saw in this world.
Ateş.
May the Lord grant her the peace
she couldn't find in this world...
in the afterlife, my brother.
It's hard...
May she rest in heaven.
Amen.
Thanks Cemal. I'm glad you're by my side.
Don't let Mercan hear this,
don't let Mercan know that.
As if Mercan is our only problem!
It's unclear if we came here to
get revenge or to entertain Mercan!
Aslı!
We shouldn't anger Ateş,
otherwise we'll lose him completely.
We don't need to do anything.
It's enough for us to highlight
that Eylül died because of Mercan.
Ateş will never be able to stomach that.
Their story is over. Over!
Ateş has a huge weak spot for Mercan.
Tomorrow, Mercan might even ask him
to let Haydar out of the warehouse.
We need to be prepared
and take precautions.
I'm so bored of playing
this cat and mouse game.
Let's strike once, strike hard, and
destroy everything, that's what I want.
Listen to me. Listen to me.
Alright... Okay mom, we'll do as you say.
You won't stop, I know.
You're going to ruin everything.
Oh Aslı, oh...
This love has blinded you too.
Something happened, but what?
He is upset.
It's like he's avoiding looking at me...
He doesn't want to talk.
He looks grim.
The man who's been trying to
make it up to me for days is gone...
and it's like someone else took his place.
But he is the one who deceived you.
He is the one who hid his identity.
What happened now that
he's acting this way?
Because of my father, very
difficult things happened in the past.
It's normal for him to have mood swings.
But he knew these from
the start. It's not new.
That's what I'm afraid of, Demet.
It's like there's
something else I don't know.
There's a growing unease inside me.
I feel like bad things are going to happen.
We'll talk later, good night.
How are you?
I need some silence.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
It's just that there are
things I can't figure out.
Is there something else I don't know?
Mercan was a kidney patient!
She would have died if
she didn't get a transplant.
The only matching kidney was Eylül's.
We took her kidney.
If there's anything I
can do, just say the word.
I'm going to get some fresh air.
You go to sleep.
Let me come too...
You stay here. It's cold outside.
What are you hiding from me, Ateş?
Malik? Çiçek.
What happened?
Is there a solution? There is,
right, you're not leaving, right?
Wait, calm down my
dear. Come sit down here.
Sit down so I can tell you.
Hmm? Tell me.
Calm down, my love.
They're not going to grab us
by the arm and throw us out...
I called a few places but
couldn't learn anything solid.
I need to go to the Immigration Office.
We'll find out what's what from there.
Where did this come from
all of a sudden, Malik?
Isn't it so ridiculous...
Just when we reunited! It's
like someone is trying to stop us.
No one can stop us. No one can separate us.
As long as we never let go
of our hands. Let's stand tall.
We can endure anything. Anything.
My God...
Look, we're not letting
go of each other's hands.
Please don't let go of our
hands either. Show us the way...
Come.
(speaking Arabic)
Amen.
It will all pass.
My Eylül...
My sister...
How could they be so cruel to you...
Ateş.
Did I wake you?
Mm-mmm.
I'm still sleeping.
You're talking in your sleep then.
Yes. You are in my dream right now.
I hope it's a good dream.
Very beautiful.
You are holding my hand warmly.
I am telling you that I
am always by your side.
I say I will never let go of your hand...
And then you tell me that you love me.
Is that so.
You tell me that you love me.
I love you.
I love you too.
Good night.
You can now watch arafta with
subtitles in multiple languages
and on some episodes, audio
in multiple languages as well.
For subtitles.
Tap settings, choose subtitles,
and pick your language on mobile.
Tap the top CC button
and select your language.
For audio, tap settings.
Choose Audio Track and
pick your language on mobile.
Open settings.
Choose Audio Track and pick your language.
The full Audio track upload
schedule is in the description below.
I knew you had pain inside you.
But I couldn't have
imagined such a great pain.
You lived the pain I don't
even dare to think about...
No...
Don't... Ateş?
Let her go...
Ateş, wake up.
Eylül!
Ateş!
Sister!
Ateş?
Eylül!
Ateş!
You had a nightmare. It's all over.
Look, I am here.
It's over.
You're okay, right?
Okay, it's passed. I'm fine.
Ateş...
Thirty, seventy, forty... There
are three reference lines here.
Good morning.
I hope you haven't had breakfast.
I brought you some of the
famous pastry from my hometown.
Smells wonderful!
No!
Yaşar Abi... I'll be the
host. I'm waiting for my desk.
He's going to be the host.
He's grown enough to host his elders now.
I can't resist pastry. I don't
care about calories right now.
Here you go, Ms. Zahide.
I can't resist it either.
Especially not the famous one...
Give it here, come on.
This is for Demet. Maybe
she hasn't had breakfast.
It's so nice that you
stayed friends like this.
Don't talk with your mouth full!
Oh sorry, right!
So be quiet, your mouth is still full!
Okay don't get mad, sorry...
I swallowed. Don't get mad.
So?
Burak.
Are Ateş and Mercan okay? They haven't
been coming to the company lately.
They are fine... As far as
I know, there is no problem.
-As far as you know... -Hm-hmm.
I'm going to get tea. You can't
eat it dry. Do you want some?
I'll have some.
What about you?
-Black? -Black.
-Black? Perfect. -Black.
I'll bring it right away.
There is definitely a problem, I can tell.
Did you see how quickly
he closed the subject?
He went running.
If you're going to gossip, shut up. Okay?
What did I do, Zahide?
Enjoy your meal, Yaşar...
Let's see what else is here.
Mmmh.
There is also poğaça.
Anyway, let him come and we'll continue.
What kind of fate is this, Cemal!
I don't know how to act or what to feel!
What am I going to tell Mercan now...
I know she is not to blame...
I break her heart unintentionally.
Then I feel sad about that too.
She feels that I'm hiding things.
I know if I tell her everything,
she'll be completely devastated.
I'm stuck between a rock and a hard place.
I really am in limbo.
Ateş.
Have you ever come
across beautiful things...
without making sacrifices...
without fighting for them,
facing no difficulties?
I haven't, for example.
I've stumbled upon a few
coincidences, of course.
But their lifespan was short.
Your fire is big enough to burn you both.
You will make sacrifices if necessary.
You will fight to the end if necessary.
I think you should
first trust your heart...
and then Mercan. Be patient.
Time is a strange thing.
Sometimes it cures all troubles.
I think that's what both of you need.
There is something I need to
do without wasting any time.
The doctor who performed Eylül's surgery,
the one who is an accomplice to
her death... I have to find him.
Maybe they sacrificed
other children like this too.
Not just for Eylül.
I want justice for all of them.
Well said.
Let me start investigating.
Yes. Do whatever it takes.
And I'll try to make Haydar talk.
And when I find the doctor...
I will do what needs to
be done with my own hands.
It just doesn't fit!
Of course it won't fit, it's a tiny room.
It's not even a room, it's a closet.
Do I really deserve this rat hole!
So, what did you do, bride?
Were you able to settle into your room?
You see this, right?
I can't fit any of my things here.
Is this what a new
bride's room looks like!?
We are up to our necks in trouble.
We are in no position to deal
with your ridiculous problems!
Since we are family,
you have to deal with it.
What a family! Just great!
Of course, since you have to
be separated from your beloved...
you're jealous, I understand you.
But everyone has their own problems.
I reunited with my love,
and now I want to settle in.
Try to understand me too.
Don't drag it out, Zehra!
Since you say we're family,
our problem is your problem too.
We don't have mine and yours.
There's no mine and yours, but
this is a problem too, mother Binnaz.
May God help you too,
sister-in-law. Separation is hard.
Anyway, let me go get my other
suitcase. If I can fit it, of course.
Mom...
Is Malik really going to go...
I can't live without Malik.
Oh my beautiful girl. Oh my dear.
Has a lighthouse ever been seen going out?
That light always burns.
It burns so sailors can find their way.
Your love is also a love that great.
The greater the love,
the more tests it faces.
If your love is real,
be a light to each other.
That's the only way you'll
get out of this darkness.
Come on, get up. We have
a ton of work to handle.
My beautiful girl. We
will overcome these too.
You know I'm stressed these days.
If I unintentionally hurt you, I'm sorry.
There are no faults in you.
Let me just look at you with love.
Wouldn't you get bored?
That was beautiful.
Think about yourself these days, not me.
Because I always think about you...
Both you and I are going
through very difficult days.
It's normal for us to falter, to get angry.
We have to show
understanding to each other.
Otherwise we can't get past these days.
For example...
When I do this to you, you
have to be understanding.
You want a war.
Love is a war sometimes, don't you know?
Then I'll fight too.
(Laughter)
Come here.
Stop, okay!
Okay!
-Do you surrender? -I do. Okay.
Let's make peace.
Let's make peace then.
You remembered.
One of the rare beautiful
things I remember.
You were like this as a child too.
You wouldn't hurt anyone,
didn't want to stay mad at anyone.
And you knew well how
to win my heart back...
Do you remember...
One day you took my
notebook and scribbled in it.
You drew a house with smoke
supposedly coming out of the chimney.
I remember.
And you got mad and scolded me.
Then you brought me a
beautiful sketchbook and colors.
And inside...
A flower like this.
Then Eylül came and scribbled in
both our notebooks and ran away.
This flower...
Maybe it's not in the soil anymore...
It won't blow in the wind or get wet in the
rain, but it will have a new life with me.
I will keep it for the rest of my life.
What a mess they made of this place!
These are quite dirty.
Let me put this here for now.
-Mom. -Hmm?
We will go to the Immigration
Office with Malik, don't worry.
Go and find out.
I hope it's some kind of mistake
so they don't send the poor boy away.
I hope so, mother.
God be with you.
I can't fit into that tiny room.
While you should be busy with your wife's
problems, you're worrying about others!
We'll handle it, honey.
Let's just save this kid first.
Sure, I'll just keep waiting...
Girl, you're obsessed with this room stuff.
What is this anyway. It's
not like you're on the streets!
This boy's situation is more serious.
Show some understanding!
You go son, go, I'll
take care of the bride.
I'll win her heart right now.
Okay, okay mom.
See you.
Zehra, you've started talking too much.
Let your hands work, not your mouth.
You must be bored from standing around.
Take these pillowcases.
Take them and put them in the
washing machine at the mansion.
Come on, don't just stand there, come on!
Idle hands do the devil's work, let
your hands work and lighten your heart.
Come on, take these.
Like this?
Good job, just like that.
As if it's your first time doing it.
I brought you some wet wipes.
I wonder...
If these painful things hadn't happened...
Would our paths have crossed again?
Would we have met and
loved each other again?
If fate wills it, it can bring two people
together from opposite ends of the world.
Or it can make them strangers
even in the same house.
We experienced both.
Yes.
We went through more than
a single heart can bear.
You are the closest person to
me in this world, I know that.
But I also see the abyss between us.
An abyss full of lies,
pain,
and tears.
Will we be able to overcome it, Ateş?
It's not always good
to talk about everything.
Sometimes you need time
for the right answers.
Love conquers all.
It endures all answers.
It turns all impossibilities
into possibilities.
It crosses all abysses...
I'll be waiting for you
at the edge of that abyss...
I'll wait despite the lies and the pain.
That abyss is much deeper
than you think. Much darker...
Are you cold?
Yes.
Shall we go inside and drink some hot tea?
You go, I'm coming.
(sighs)
Mercan.
They locked your father in
the basement like an animal.
I have no one left but you.
Don't you turn your back on me too.
We have no one but each other, my girl.
And my father locked them in there?
We don't have a family anymore, mom.
My father destroyed our
family with what he did.
He is human, he can make mistakes!
Mistakes?
Tormenting little children
cannot be called a mistake!
They were defenseless.
They had no one to protect them!
Do you know who harms children?
Who hurts them without feeling pain...
Pure evil!
Only the most evil people
in this world harm children!
My father is one of them!
And you are too!
You knew everything
from the very beginning.
You just kept living without caring!
You don't have a heart either!
Who performed Eylül's surgery?
I don't remember.
You will remember.
You will give me that doctor's name!
So many years have passed...
Haydar! Do not test my patience!
What will change if you know his name?
A lot! Talk!
I'm asking for the last time.
Feridun...
Feridun! I don't remember his last name.
I did everything because
I loved my daughter!
I sacrificed a life for my daughter.
I chose Mercan, I chose Mercan!
I wonder what they did?
It's been hours and there is no news.
They are trying to find
out what's what, my girl.
They will call, don't worry.
Ah!
Hello.
No. Wrong number.
I got scared thinking it was bad news.
Don't fall into despair
just because a paper arrived.
You will overcome so many
more obstacles in married life.
Love brings a lot of joy,
but its burden is heavy too.
You'll say 'I will do it'.
You'll say 'I will overcome it'.
As you say this, the Lord will
breathe strength into your heart.
-Mom. -Huh?
Now that something like
this has happened to us...
I made a decision, mom.
If...
If Malik leaves and won't come back
I will go with him too.
You are my everything.
You, my brother, you are my life.
But I don't want to be
separated from Malik either, mom.
Mom, aren't you going to say anything?
Mom? You understand me, right?
You fill your waters and
I'll make you a nice sandwich.
You haven't eaten anything since morning.
I did everything because
I loved my daughter!
I sacrificed a life for my daughter.
I chose Mercan, I chose Mercan!
Ah! Ateş! What are you doing! Stop! Stop!
Are you okay? Give me your hand,
let's put it under water. Come.
I'm fine.
Does it hurt?
Wait...
Give me your hand.
You're okay, right?
I'm fine.
You are not fine.
There is something wrong.
Why won't you tell me?
I'm fine.
Let it burn.
Nothing can cool my inside.
There is this. I wrote that down too.
(indistinct dialogue)
Write this part too.
Exactly like that.
(indistinct dialogue)
Demet.
Is there any news from Mercan?
She's constantly on my mind...
She's not safe in that
house, among those people.
You're right... But
Mercan still trusts Ateş.
Out of desperation.
She acts this way out of fear.
I will suggest she moves into
the house I bought for her.
The one you bought for her?
Yes.
Brother, look...
Mercan wouldn't accept something like that.
Don't push it.
For your own good,
give up on this love now.
Give up?
Mercan is not something I can give up on.
I have always gotten everything I wanted.
Besides...
Ateş and her have no future.
I'm more certain than ever that
Mercan and I will be together.
Yes...
After what happened in their past,
those two can't be a thing anymore.
They can't be.
But still, Mercan won't say
yes to your offer of help...
We won't know until we try.
Enjoy your meal.
Thanks...
I'm one of the reasons for your pain.
I know.
I mean, I'm the daughter
of that man after all.
I believe in us, Ateş.
More than I believe in anything...
There's one more thing I believe in.
If we go back to how we were
if you hold my hand
we can face everything together.
They can't destroy us.
Neither my mom nor my dad...
nor the lies... nor our past.
Eylül...
I am so sorry for what my father did.
For locking you up in there...
For the pain he caused...
For your fears... I am so sorry for
what you went through at a young age.
Mercan
After everything we've been
through, our love deserves this.
Your heart says the same thing too, right?
Your heart also tells you to choose us.
-We can get through... -Mercan!
We cannot be together.
This love must end now.
You were right.
It won't work out between us.
What do you mean?
What does this mean?
You know exactly what it means.
No, no I don't.
Tell me plainly.
I want to hear what you have to say.
There's nothing to question.
This relationship cannot continue.
This relationship cannot continue, huh?
You... you must be joking?
After days of saying you
loved me despite everything,
and that you didn't want to break up...
Mercan, please...
Please what?
I ran away from you when
I learned the truth...
What did you do? You chased after me.
You begged me to believe in your love…
Now you stand before me...
No, no... There must be something else.
There's definitely something else going on.
There is nothing else.
I told you I wouldn't
give up on my revenge.
It was just never meant to be.
It's best to end it now.
But...
But you said you wouldn't
give up on your love either.
I know you now.
There's definitely something
you're not telling me.
What happened? Why did you
suddenly go back on your word?
There's nothing to tell.
Ateş.
Ateş, please.
I was unfair to you.
It was a mistake.
A mistake, huh?
Tell me you don't love me then.
Go on.
You can't say it.
Because you love me.
And I love you too.
Why don't we leave everything behind then?
Why don't we forget the
past and build a new life?
We can leave this place and
start fresh, just the two of us.
Being away from home is
hard, my dear. Very hard.
I told you this before.
Oh, the things I've seen and been through.
It's a mother's heart, after all.
What mother would want her
daughter to share a fate like hers?
I know, mother. Believe me, I know.
You spent your whole life looking after us.
You never complained
about it, not even once.
You only ever wanted the best for us.
You can build your child a throne,
but you cannot forge their destiny.
And Malik is your destiny.
I can see it.
The way he looks at you...
How much he loves you...
But believe me, I see this too...
His family will cause you a lot of trouble.
Will you be able to withstand that?
If you can...
I'm with you.
I would love for you to
stay with me, my daughter.
But I know you'll be unhappy.
How could I ever be
unhappy by your side, mother?
You are the great plane tree
that we lean our backs on.
Why are you two crying?
Did something bad happen?
You're really asking that?
Berat married you...
What could be worse than that?
How tactless!
I thought something truly
terrible had happened.
Come on, come on, don't start again!
But she's the one who started it!
Say something to your daughter first.
She keeps making snide remarks.
Maybe because you deserve it?
I know your intentions!
And what are my intentions?
You're jealous of our happiness!
-Really? -Mm-hmm.
You want to separate me from my
husband, but you won't succeed!
Mm-hmm.
Zehra, that's enough. Çiçek, quit it.
Stop fighting and get
back to work. Come on.
Were you here?
I've been looking for you everywhere.
I thought I'd hang out
in your room for a bit.
You seem to be in high spirits.
Of course I am.
Ateş and Mercan have broken up.
Hopefully, we'll be rid
of that Mercan for good.
Then I'll be even happier.
I hope so too, but...
Don't you go thinking this
is an opportunity for yourself.
And why shouldn't I?
I'm telling you so you don't waste
your time chasing a hopeless love.
Why should it be hopeless?
They've broken up.
Even if they split, Ateş
won't turn and look at you.
He's madly in love with that girl!
Don't you dare, mother!
Don't you ever tell me Ateş
is in love with Mercan again!
Are you trying to drive me crazy?
Don't you want me to be happy?
Why won't you support me?
Enough already! Get your head together!
Why pin your hopes on
something that will never happen?
If you love me even a
little, you'll stand by me.
If I can't have Ateş, I'll kill my...
Aslı!
That's enough!
After everything is over,
Ateş... will never be the same.
You are still very young.
When the time comes, you'll
fall in love with someone else.
You'll start a family…
But not with Ateş. I won't allow it.
(sobs)
Alright… Thank you so much.
I was just coming to see you.
What happened?
The doctor who operated on
Mercan and Eylül has died.
He had already been barred from the
profession for ties to organ trafficking.
He even served time.
Scumbag…
Who knows how many lives
he snuffed out like Eylül's…
I wish he hadn't died so we could have
beaten the life out of him ourselves...
How can a person be so heartless?
They don't care about
the lives they've ended.
Ateş. Don't.
Don't fall into Haydar’s trap.
He's provoking you.
You're not the old Tahir anymore.
You're not that helpless, orphaned boy.
You're an enemy more
powerful than he can handle.
Sooner or later, he will
pay for what he's done.
He will be his own grim reaper.
What about Mercan?
Are you going to tell her?
I don't know, Cemal.
I don't know what to do either.
Mercan won't be able to handle this.
Every time I look at Mercan, I
want to get away as fast as I can.
On the other hand, I never
want to leave her side.
On one side, my love...
and on the other...
Eylül and everything I've lived through.
Wherever I turn, it's a burning fire.
Oh, Ateş.
You calculated everything.
But you didn't account for love.
You dropped a bomb on me and then
left as if you were running away.
I wasn't running…
There was nothing left to say.
Nothing left, really?
I think there is.
Are we going to talk
about the same things again?
If necessary, yes.
You have to explain to me why
you're talking about
breaking up out of nowhere.
I don't.
I made a mistake, that's all.
I pushed you, knowing it wouldn't work.
Our paths were going to
cross sooner or later anyway.
It's best not to drag it out.
It's so obvious that you're lying.
You knew who I was from the very beginning!
You married me knowingly,
you fell in love with me knowingly!
Don't push me any further, Mercan…
I admit my mistake, what
more do you want me to do?
When the hundred and eighty-seven
days are up, I'm leaving.
It'll be over and done with.
Over and done with, huh?
Yes.
We'll share the same room
and do whatever is
required by the contract.
Wow.
I'm not following the contract.
Force me, if you think it's that easy.
Don't provoke me.
I don't care.
We made a deal
and you have to stick to it.
I don't want to talk.
I've made my decision.
You've made your decision?
Is that so?
I'm not your toy!
You can't get close one day
and run away from me the next.
If you have even an ounce of courage,
you'll tell me what's going on!
You owe me that much!
What do you want me to tell you?
Can't you see that it's
impossible for us to be together?
You are the daughter of my sworn enemy!
Don't you ever turn your back
on me while we're arguing again!
Have you lost your mind?!
Yes, I have.
-Mercan! -Let go! Let go.
I told you what you needed to know!
Don't drag this out!
Fine.
I won't.
You're right, it was a mistake…
A massive mistake at that.
You knew who I was from the very beginning!
You married me knowingly, you
fell in love with me knowingly!
I guess you're disappointed
to see me instead of Ateş.
What are you doing at Ateş’s desk?
Checking the contracts.
Let's see if there's anything
else overlooked or ignored.
You're going to check them?
What would you know about legal contracts?
You're mistaken, Aslı.
I may not be a lawyer,
but I'm not an idiot.
At the very least, I
can recognize signatures.
You've become very touchy lately, Cemal.
In fact, I'm the one
who should be offended…
You're acting as if
I'm betraying my family.
Haven't you?
My intention...
I know exactly what your intention is.
Don't waste my time with words.
I already deeply regret
not telling Ateş about Nezir.
It's eating me alive.
Cemal, please don't tell him.
I'm begging you.
Don't ruin things between us. Please.
Aslı, get your head together!
The man is madly in love with Mercan!
He will never love another
woman in his entire life.
Understand that already.
Eventually, he will forget.
And when he does, I'll
be the one by his side.
Neither you nor my mother
can talk me out of this love.
Ateş will realize eventually
that he will be happy with me.
My love is enough for both of us.
Love?
Is that what you call love?
If you truly loved him, you wouldn't
collaborate with Ateş’s enemy.
Ateş loves someone else.
You know that very well.
If he loves someone else, you would
have stepped aside so he could be happy.
Yours isn't love.
It's just a cheap obsession.
I've cleaned the upstairs rooms, mother.
Alright, dear. Thank you.
When no one is around, give
the living room a once-over too.
Will do.
Oh, Lord.
Hello.
What is this?
Did something bad happen?
What's with the look on your face? No.
No, quite the opposite.
The deportation order
hasn't been issued yet.
Oh! Thank God.
Well, that's a good thing.
Sure, it's good.
But if I can't complete the
missing documents within 24 hours,
that's when I'll be deported.
It's not a problem, we'll
handle whatever is missing.
Yes, that's right.
Mr. Haydar was a bit negligent.
(indistinct line)
There's nothing to worry about here.
Talk to Mr. Ateş
immediately, he'll handle it.
I spoke with Cemal and
explained the situation.
Thankfully, there are some
documents he requested from me.
Oh, that's good then.
I hope everything works out for you, son.
I hope so.
Make sure everything is ready
so nothing is missing this time.
Yes, yes. I'll start preparing
the documents right away.
Okay.
-We'll handle it. -See you.
Come here, come on.
My dear.
He loves me very much.
Always keep smiling
like this. Don't be sad.
Alright.
"Don't drag it out," huh?
I won't.
May Mr. Ateş be happy.
You scared me.
I'm sorry.
Leave it, I'll handle it.
There's no need!
I dropped it, I'll pick it up.
I said I'll do it.
You'll cut your hand.
And I said there's no need!
If I cut it, I cut it.
It's my hand. You leave it.
Listen to me for once!
I don't want to listen.
I broke it, I'll pick it up!
I'm not like you!
What are you trying to say?
I mean I don't break things
and then just turn my back!
Whenever we enter the kitchen
together, we break things.
Don't drive me crazy any further!
Give me a proper answer already!
Don't mess with my heartbeat.
This is the language you understand.
Breaking and destroying.
Fine, if this is what you want...
If this is what you understand.
There!
What are you doing! Stop! Stop, I said!
Stop, I'm telling you.
Mercan, stop.
I won't let go of you anymore.
Because I know you love me too.
I don't love you.
You do. You're dying for me.
I said I don't love you.
You do. I don't.
Admit it, you love me.
I said I don't!
You love me!
I love you so much.
So much... Truly so much.
You...
You are the fire. And I
am the wind to that fire.
Even though I try to
erase you from my mind,
I couldn't cast you out of my heart.
When the wind finds the
fire, it becomes immortal.
Our love is immortal like that.
Maybe this is a sign that we
shouldn't enter the kitchen together.
Maybe it's a sign that we
shouldn't do anything at all.
We were supposed to be like
this from the start anyway.
Yes.
Thankfully, it's over.
Even if a bit late, we did the right thing.
Isn't it nice?
Whenever you feel like it, you force
yourself into someone else's life.
And then you say, "Oops, I
made a mistake, I'm leaving."
Mercan, I...
I'm sorry.
-I didn't want it to be— -Don't!
Don't you dare pity me!
I don't need anyone's pity,
especially yours. Do you hear me?
What I feel for you is simply...
I respect you.
You don't respect anything.
You don't even care about
what you've burned and broken!
I picked up the pieces.
Yes, you did.
And you threw them all in the trash.
Because you can't put them back together.
Mercan bought it for him on his birthday.
What are you doing here?
This was my son's.
Just like this room.
Besides... This is my house!
I enter wherever I want!
This is my house too!
I am Haydar Yıldırım's son.
I have as much right
to everything as you do!
I knew what kind of person you
were the moment I first saw you.
You're a greedy, calculating sneak…
Get this into your head.
Haydar Yıldırım had one son.
And that's my son, Murat.
Don't you ever think
you can take his place.
I wouldn't want to take his place.
He was a murderer.
Who are you to speak of my son?
Don't you dare!
Your mother was a lowly woman
who slept with married men!
You're in no position
to look down on anyone!
My mother ran away because of you!
You keep telling yourself that!
I wouldn't want to take his place.
He was a murderer.
Malik!
What are you doing here, dear? You
were supposed to prepare your documents…
I can't find my passport, Çiçek.
I've looked everywhere, it's gone.
Alright, we'll find it, calm down…
Let me have a look
too. Maybe you missed it.
I've looked everywhere twice.
Maybe… I don't know… I thought it might
have stayed in the car, so I came here.
What would your passport
be doing in the car?
I don't know. Maybe I took
it with me, maybe it fell out…
I'm just looking around.
I just can't remember where I put it.
Time is running out, but
panicking will only make it worse.
You look around here, and I'll
search your room one more time.
Maybe we missed it.
Okay. Okay.
I went to the mosque the other day.
I wonder if I dropped it there?
I'd better go and have a look.
Thankfully, it's over.
Even if a bit late, we did the right thing.
I won't cry.
How are you, Mercan?
I'm fine, thanks.
Can we talk for a bit?
About what?
You know we can't talk comfortably here.
Shall we go outside?
No, Nezir. Whatever you
have to say, say it here.
Mercan, you know he
won't let us talk freely.
We'll sit by the shore for a while.
I promise, I won't keep you
long. I'll bring you right back.
Alright. But I can't stay long.
I promise.
Mercan!
Don't do this to me!
I brought you something to eat.
Mr. Haydar…
It's not my place, but...
Since the past has been
laid bare like this…
Isn't it time you told the truth?
Don't you dare, Binnaz… Don't you dare!
How much longer are we
going to carry this burden?
I need that secret.
If they find out, I'll make you
pay for it once I'm out of here.
And you know I will.
Come on, Mrs. Binnaz.
I'm listening.
Mercan, my heart is not at ease.
You don't accept it, but...
Nezir, we've discussed this before?
I know...
But I can't help it, what can I do...
All I care about is your safety.
It's clear what they did to your father.
Next, it'll be your and your mother's turn.
Please, Nezir.
Mercan, these people are dangerous.
They've come here with a
grudge they've held for years.
It's not right for you
to stay here with them.
Let me protect you.
I don't need anyone to protect me.
Especially not from Ateş.
He won't hurt me.
He won't hurt anyone.
Mercan, my feelings for
you have never changed.
-When you're with me— -Nezir.
Please.
Mercan, please listen.
I don't know if I'll ever have
an opportunity like this again.
One hundred and eighty-seven days.
After the hundred and
eighty-seven days are over...
Once you divorce that man...
Marry me.
I'm willing to settle for
even a single day with you.
Even just a single second.
My only concern is hearing your
voice, looking into your eyes.
I won't touch you unless you want me to.
I won't touch you until the day
I die, if that's what you want.
My only wish is to be
able to make you happy.
I'll come if you say come.
I'll go if you say go.
I'll die if you say die.
You're more precious
to me than my own life.
Once this business is over...
Marry me.
You know I love Ateş very much, Nezir.
How will you be happy with
someone who loves another?
And why should I step out of
one ordeal and into another?
Can't things be resolved without marriage?
Nothing is important to me.
Only you matter, Mercan.
Only you.
These hundred and eighty-seven days...
Marry me when you divorce.
Let me think about it.
What the hell are you saying?
What marriage after a
hundred and eighty-seven days?
I was telling her to marry
me once she gets rid of you.
Ateş, don't!
Ateş, calm down.
Our conversation was already over.
Talking was a mistake in the first place!
Why do you come here with this man?
And you say you'll think about it!
Ateş, calm down!
I won't calm down!
Look! I'm telling you,
Mercan! This man is dangerous.
Think about what I said.
In your dreams.
I won't leave her to anyone.
-Ateş! -Mercan!
I won't let you hurt her.
Who the hell are you
to think about my wife?
Nezir!
Don't you interfere!
I already have!
I won't leave you in this man's hands.
Enough! I'm sick of your fighting.
Enough already, I've had it!
Always fighting! What is this! Enough!
Whatever happens, happens.
Mercan!
Think about what I said, Mercan!
Mercan, wait!
What!
Why don't you say to my face what
you're going to think about, huh?
You heard perfectly well
what I'm going to think about.
Besides, what's it to you?
It is my business! You are still my wife!
Like you said, it's just a
marriage contract on paper!
And what are you questioning?
Nothing you say or do makes any sense!
You've been saying
"It's over" since morning.
But at the slightest thing,
you try to call me to account!
If we're just a contract to you,
why Nezir came or what he
said is none of your business!
Look, you're really
pushing your luck today!
Oh, really? I hadn't noticed.
Don't drive me crazy.
I don't even care if you go crazy or not.
Look at me!
What are you looking at?
Were you talking to me?
I was talking to you.
Do you like what you see that much?
Why are you looking at a married man?
Mercan, what are you doing? Come on.
I'm sorry.
What are you sorry for? It's
not like I did anything wrong!
Where are you going? Why don't
you tell me why you were looking!
Mercan, what are you doing?
Get a hold of yourself!
Why are you saying sorry? You
might as well have fallen at her feet!
Go chase after her, don't let her get away!
Mercan, what are you doing?
Get a hold of yourself!
I am myself! Who was that
woman? Why was she looking at you!
Mercan, you're being ridiculous.
How should I know who she is?
Quit it!
Oh, so when I do it, it's ridiculous,
but when you do it, it's normal.
Now do you see how it feels?
So you did it on purpose?
No! I didn't do it on purpose.
If you'd let me, I would've shown
her what it means to look at you.
Come on, move it.
Don't pull me. I can walk.
Were you jealous of me?
You would've seen real jealousy
if you'd looked back at that woman.
By the way, don't think
I've forgotten about Nezir.
Oh, don't you forget.
Still talking about Nezir.
So you're going to think about it...
You...
can't think...
of anything but me!
Welcome.
Good to be here.
Do you know if Mercan is around?
No. She left with
Nezir. Ateş is after them.
Oh, brother!
There's going to be trouble again.
Your brother likes to
cause trouble. Is that right?
Others create the problems, but for some reason,
it's always my brother who's "causing trouble"?
No one has had any peace since you arrived.
I don't understand you at all anyway!
Why are you so full of hate and anger?
I just don't get it.
If you knew what companionship on
a journey meant, you'd understand.
Then talk to your companion.
Tell him to stop making Mercan suffer.
Mercan fell for someone, fell
in love for the first time.
She doesn't deserve any of this.
What is it to you?
Why do you stick your nose into
things that are none of your business?
What do you want then?
Should everyone just kill each other?
Aslı, don't get involved.
I will get involved.
Don't drag it out, okay.
Don't mind Aslı… Her nerves
are a bit frayed lately.
It's not a problem…
She's always like this.
Sneaky.
Annoying.
Haydar?
Nermin?
I was wondering how you were.
How should I be, Nermin?
I'm about to lose my mind! Help me, Nermin.
Calm down, Haydar! Calm down!
What can we possibly do?
Look, your dear son is here too,
but he doesn't even care about you.
He's out enjoying himself.
I have you…
no one but you can help me.
Please, find a key or
something, do something, Nermin.
I have to get out of here.
Alright, alright.
I'll try to do something.
Hurry up.
Don't worry.
Hello?
One second. Mercan.
What!
Wait, we're going to talk.
I can't wait.
I'm listening.
Well, well. Are you coming
from a visit to your father?
How many times have I
told you not to touch me!
Just you wait, your turn will come
after your father's. Murderer's daughter!
I'm sick of your threats! Your lies.
What's a lie? Isn't your father a murderer?
You're as immoral as your father!
Even though your father killed
Eylül, you're still around Ateş.
If you had even an ounce of shame,
you'd bow your head
and stay away from Ateş!
You'd be ashamed to look him in the face!
Mrs. Müzeyyen!
Don't touch her! Let go, Ateş!
Don't you dare!
I said don't!
Don't touch her!
Are you alright? You're not hurt, are you?
Mrs. Müzeyyen!
Mercan is my wife!
My red line.
You crossed that red line.
I don't want to hear another word.
I've lost my trust in you now.
Know your place before
I lose my respect too!
My dear wife.
Hmm?
Would you pour some
tea for our mother? Huh?
Of course, my dear husband.
Let me pour some tea for our mother.
Come on, my dear wife.
Heh!
What happened?
What's the matter?
We couldn't find the passport.
What's going to happen now?
Believe me, I have no idea.
It's no problem.
There's no need to despair.
It'll turn up eventually. And
from the most unexpected place.
That's what I'm saying. We'll
find that passport eventually.
Can't Mr. Cemal do something?
I spoke with him, but... He said
he'd see if anything could be done.
Berat.
Since Malik is leaving,
let's move into his room.
Girl, are you doing this on purpose?
Is this the time, Zehra?
No, but if we know, at least we
can choose the furniture accordingly.
Look, you're really going too far.
And she calls me tactless.
Calm down.
For God's sake, keep quiet.
I want to drink my tea in peace.
I'm sick of your bickering.
Zehra.
Refresh the tea, come on. That's
what new brides do around here.
I guess your new brides are
brought in just for service then.
Thank God.
Enjoy your tea.
Thanks, Zehra. Thank you.
Well done, Zehra.
How are you?
I'm fine.
I know you're not fine.
What happened at the
shore wasn't normal either.
As if everything about
us is so normal, right?
Like what happened at the shore was normal.
We haven't had a normal
experience for a long time, Ateş.
Especially me.
You all drove me crazy together.
Forgive me.
Mother Müzeyyen can
be very cruel sometimes.
Sometimes?
You've forgotten what
was done to me, I guess?
I haven't forgotten.
And I won't...
But you see why we
can't be together, right?
The past won't let go of any of us.
If Nezir came now, would you still
be able to say those things to me?
Don't kid yourself, Ateş.
When you were jealous of Nezir...
When you stopped Mrs. Müzeyyen just now...
When you picked up the pieces in
the kitchen so I wouldn't get hurt…
All of them bore the traces
of the love you have for me.
I'm not so stupid that I
wouldn't understand that.
You love me.
And I love you too.
No one...
no one can tear you out of my heart.
Neither the anger you feel for my father
nor Mrs. Müzeyyen's
hatred can achieve that.
I understand what you've lived through.
I'm aware of the pain you've suffered.
Your lost childhood...
The sister you lost…
When I think about these, I
find your anger so justified…
All I want is to be by your side and...
to support you.
To heal your wounds.
But let go of the past now.
Look, we have a future.
-I— -Shh.
Please, don't say anything…
Sooner or later, my
childhood hero will return.
Until that day, I will wait patiently.
Look at me.
You are Tahir, don't forget that.
Hasn't Malik come yet?
-Malik? -Good evening.
Did you talk to Mr. Cemal?
I did.
He said I have to find the
passport. There's no other way.
Judging by your state, it's not
just about the passport. What happened?
Did something bad happen?
Did you get bad news?
Mr. Cemal told me...
He said someone reported me.
That's why all this is happening.
What?
What do you mean?
Reported me, that's what.
Someone specifically reported
me so I would be deported...
Who would be so hostile?
I have no idea, Aunt Binnaz.
I'll kill you!
What are you doing, let go of my arm!
You're always around Ateş!
Leave him alone!
Enough already! Get off his back!
I've told you before.
Don't get between Ateş and me!
What we go through is
none of your business!
And I've told you
repeatedly, there is no "us"!
Get this into your head.
Ateş and I won't break apart.
His storm will pass,
and he'll return to me.
You can never prevent that.
Because we love each
other. Do you understand?
I'll block it so well that…
you'll be out of our lives for good!
There's no other way!
What do you want from me?
Why do you care so much about Ateş and me?
I've made you my problem, yes.
Stay away from Ateş!
You are truly sick!
I don't want to deal
with you, get out of here!
I'm not leaving!
So that's how it is…
Then let me speak a
language you understand.
Ateş? I'm glad you're here.
We were just about to have
an inevitable conversation.
Get out, Aslı. Shut up.
I won't shut up.
Everyone is going to know everything now.
I'm tired of you wrapping
this girl in cotton wool!
She'll know the cost. And
at whose expense she lives…
It's not Haydar, you're the murderer!
She's the one who ruined your life!
Aslı, I said stop!
What do you mean?
You are Eylül's murderer!
They killed her because of you.
-Aslı, enough! -It's not enough!
The kidney you're
carrying is Eylül's kidney.
They killed her so you could live!