Haydar figured us out, bro.
He came after me. He wanted info about you.
I told him you had a brother who died.
Whatever we do, it doesn’t work.
Everything just brings them closer.
They’re practically glued together.
We need to change direction
and focus on Mercan.
In other words, she needs
to believe Ateş is bad.
I’m warning the wife you play house with.
Even if your marriage is fake,
her meeting with Nezir isn’t right.
If something needs to be
said to my wife, I’ll say it.
Don’t fight with your family because of me.
They’ll always be in your life.
But I won’t be here tomorrow.
Ateş is in love with Mercan.
What love, woman? Don’t drive me crazy!
Love makes the impossible possible.
Enough, Nermin! Stop it.
As long as I’m here, no one dares.
And don’t ever say that again.
I don’t want you
exhausting yourself like this.
Continue tomorrow.
No need to worry about me.
I promised the team I’d work.
You made a promise to
us too in the beginning.
What promise?
What is she talking about? What promise?
I
Yes.
What I wanted to say...
Where is my olive pizza?
I ordered an olive pizza, but
these aren't olive pizzas at all.
Could they have been mixed up with yours?
Sorry, I just walked in like
that, but my blood sugar dropped
or something, and now my
hands and feet are shaking.
I couldn't take it anymore, I
felt like I was going to faint
maybe I did faint and
didn't even realise it.
Since your hand is trembling
you should have been content
with what you had in your hand
I couldn't manage, Mr Ateş, I'm sorry
I can't even see right now.
Here it is!
It's mixed up
Alright, Yaşar, take your pizza
and get lost!
If you want a slice, I
can leave it, if you wish.
Yaşar, get lost!
Alright, Mr Ateş.
I still can leave it, if you wish.
Alright, Mr. Ateş.
What you wanted to say?
What I wanted to say...
Enough already!
What were you going to say?
Never mind.
It is not the right time or place, I guess.
But...
What just happened?
Aww! That's a nice one.
Nermin,
Get rid of these already,
you've been staring
at them since morning,
aren't you satisfied yet?
You can stare more later.
There are still ones I hadn't tried on yet.
I'm checking them out
Nermin, Where did you
get the money to buy them?
Nermin I'm asking where
you got the money from?
Yesterday, you were having an
attitude because I didn't give you money
I took care of myself, Haydar.
What do you mean, I took care of
myself? Don't mess up with me woman!
Where did you get the money?
I took Müzeyyen's necklace.
Did you steal it?
Of course not!
It's not theft or anything like that.
Patience, my Lord
Look at me, Haydar!
They humiliate us every day.
They didn't leave us alone,
saying they'd pay off our debt
If they’ve brought us to this state,
of course there would be a price to pay
Look!
Every day, millions are
flowing into the company
but not a penny reaches our hands.
What's more, our daughter
works day and night
Alright, you can take that mindset.
But I won't! Do you understand?
Alright, alright. Shut up, for God's sake.
So Honestly, I give up Nermin, I give up!
Alright, if Müzeyyen finds out about
this, she'll tear the place apart.
Don't involve me in this.
Don't you dare!
Honestly, my dear
Since you're my husband,
you'll naturally get involved.
If Müzeyyen the witch finds out,
we'll pay her and that'll be that
If not, they would make up for the
money they made off Mercan's back.
I'm just getting by
thinking I'm clever, you know?
Get rid of these already!
Time to sleep.
Beautiful!
I'm glad I bought it.
What type of situation we're in!
Oh, dear! What did you do my
darling? Don't you pay attention?
Stop, stop! Don't pick
it up with your hands.
I said don't touch it.
We needed a broom or something...
Oh my goodness!
Does it hurt?
Wait. I'll get you a bandage
right away, wait, does it hurt?
It's not my hand that's hurting, Mum.
It is my heart!
It hurts so bad in my heart.
Mom.
Sorry, I didn't mean to say that
Come here.
It hurts, right?
Yes.
Oh, my little girl!
Hold on, I am covering it.
Take it, you use it later.
No need.
What is this?
Come on! You can do it.
There's this missing piece, and
it just doesn't sit right with me.
Take a look at this.
I think it's fine.
No way, that wont work.
There's no need to send it,
there's really no need at all. Really.
It just won't work.
Don't get discouraged.
Nothing is wrong, believe me.
It feels like we're pushing ourselves
as if our minds are all messed up.
I just can't figure
out why it's not working.
As if there is a much different
world on the other side,
while the outside world is full of chaos.
It's not working out, we're
just pushing ourselves for nothing.
We don't have to conform
to the outside world.
But we can't ignore it either.
Like... one thing on the
inside and another on the outside
No, best not to push it. Let's
not send it. I'm giving up.
Wait a minute.
Take a deep breath.
I said take it!
Give it now.
Close your eyes.
Close them!
No cheating!
Eyes closed.
Take a deep breath.
Now give it.
One more time.
Don't open your eyes.
Trust me.
And if you wish,
We can leave everything behind right now.
Everything.
If you say "Just don't push it"
everything comes to an end.
However, if we keep going
something great could come out of it.
You never know until you try.
I understand your fears.
I'm not sure either.
But in such a short time
There may be an mistake
in what we trying to do.
Anyways,
If it were flawless and smooth,
perhaps it wouldn't be so valuable.
There should be a trace
of us in the building.
A line,
I don't know, a crooked stone.
A feeling from us in its own world.
It will stand firm there.
I don't know
Perhaps, what you call “inside
one thing, outside another” is
something deep within,
we haven't yet revealed to the outside
Perhaps, it is something
we have yet to discover.
And perhaps,
we'll be the ones who find it.
Who knows
We can't know what will happen
until it comes to light, can we?
Everything is in our hands.
It's worth a try then.
Well, let's get back to work.
Come on.
What are you looking at? Come on!
We'll make it.
Hello, Aslı, my daughter,
Did you take my necklace?
I can't find my necklace.
I looked there darling, I turned
the room upside down. it's not there.
Alright, fine.
I'll ask Zehra, that scatterbrain
may have put it somewhere else.
Zehra!
Come in!
Yes, Mrs. Müzeyyen.
Zehra, I can't find my necklace.
Do you know where it is?
No.
I never touch the jewellery box.
I don't even open the drawer, Mrs Müzeyyen.
Tell Binnaz and Çiçek
to wait for me downstairs.
Whoever dared to do this
I'll give them a hard time.
A very hard time.
I 've sent it.
Well done, everyone!
We worked hard. We worked
hard, but it was worth it.
Thank you all very much.
We worked hard and we deserved it.
Now you can go home and take a rest.
Because in the evening, you are invited to
the barbecue party at the mansion.
Super!
Yay!
That's great.
We deserved it.
I'm glad you didn't let me give up.
Even if you had wanted to give
up, no one could have stopped you.
Not even I.
I'll take that as a compliment then.
Whatever you say.
If we win this project
there will be a trace of us in it.
A crooked stone
ordinary
shapeless
Perhaps I'll come across it
while walking down the street
But that stone
will be the most valuable
stone of the project.
Yes.
Mr. Ateş,
You're well
I hope.
Well, I
I wanted to ask something
Am I invited too?
To the barbecue?
Cause I worked very hard
too, I think I deserved it.
Of course you are invited, Yaşar.
I'll make you an olive
pizza with my own hands.
Live it up, Mr. Ateş!
Thank you.
Shall we go?
Let's go!
Zehra, what are you doing?
It just came out of the oven.
It will become doughy!
Haven't you ever learned anything?
Meddlesome.
What happened now?
I don't know.
It's clear that nothing good has happened.
Who entered my room yesterday?
I was in the kitchen
all day, Mrs. Müzeyyen.
And I helped my mother, I
didn't go into your room at all.
My necklace is missing.
Whoever took it should speak up.
We're not thieves, Mrs. Müzeyyen.
Don't try to use that “poor
man's speech” stuff on me.
Someone has entered my room.
There's no one else in this house who
could have come into my room, except you.
Don't make me lose my temper.
Whoever took it, tell me
quickly or I'll call the police.
You'd better call the
police, Mrs. Müzeyyen.
That's the right thing to do.
We won't enter your room
Zehra is responsible for your room.
It was never us who manage your room.
What's going on here?
Mrs. Müzeyyen's necklace is missing.
What happened?
What's all this abundance?
Did you find a treasure?
We don't die easily, Mrs. Müzeyyen.
What happened?
What is the source of all these?
Did you find the treasure?
Or did you steal?
You stole it!
Good heavens!
Why would I steal your necklace, dear?
If stones were to rain down on our
heads, you'd still put the blame on us.
Unbelievable!
Everyone back to work!
It is time to go shopping.
I haven't hosted my
colleagues in a long time.
Even after getting married...
What were you going to say?
Nothing.
You were going to say that
we couldn't invite anyone
after we got married, weren't you?
So
Considering the circumstances
under which we got married
it seems normal.
But let's look at the present.
They'll be here in a few hours and
we haven't made any preparations yet.
Alright. Don't worry.
Now make a list and tell
Berat. He will handle it.
I want everything to be perfect.
So until morning
They worked diligently.
We neglected our work and made
them pay the price in the end.
I will make up for it.
Don't worry.
We need to prepare something
besides meat and chicken.
Alright.
Like... plenty of sweets
drinks and such
Alright.
Let's cook some venison shwarma too.
Aren't you listening to me?
Of course I'm listening.
I just said "Let's cook
some venison shwarma too".
Did you really say that?
Oh, come on, really?
I'm trying to tell you something
here, our guests are about to come
and you're just brushing
it off with a 'yes'.
It's because I trust you.
I know you'll organise it perfectly.
Whatever you say is okay.
Did I earn your appreciation then?
Lucky me!
But first
Go to your room
Take some rest.
After all, there are a
bunch of employees at home.
They take care of everything.
Then you'll do what you have to do.
I'm not sleepy, I need to
get the arbor ready first.
No matter what I say,
you won't listen, right?
It's time to put an end to things.
What happened, my dear?
Why are you looking so down?
Can't you see Mrs. Müzeyyen
She has driven me mad, you know.
What happened?
Her necklace is missing. She
gave all of us a good dressing-down.
She is anew money. What do we expect?
What do you mean?
Did she accuse you?
Isn't it always like that anyway?
First, the household staff are blamed.
I can't believe it
My dear,
I'm so sorry that you
had to go through all that.
Don't worry, everything
will work out in time.
Well, I don't really care about her.
It's my mother's silence that scares me.
This is not a good sign, Malik.
She hasn't said a word in two days.
She might be softening up?
I wish that were the case
but she doesn't bring anything out either.
II'll get everything back on track.
I promise you.
Don't you worry so much anymore.
Don't get upset, okay?
I can't help but worry.
It's not that easy.
Yeah, it's not easy.
But it's not that difficult either.
Çiçek, I cannot let you to go anywhere.
I can't bear it.
One for you,
and one for me.
Thank you.
Enjoy it.
Between you and Burak,
There's a distance now
because of your brother, right?
Yes.
I liked Burak's friends
I got very upset when I drifted
away because of my brother.
We worked very well together.
Did you just like his friendship, Demet?
Um,
I don't know.
My feelings are all over the place.
I can't put a name to what I'm feeling.
I always want to be with him
and always to talk to him.
When he stay away from me
it hurts me so much.
Might that thing you can not name be
love?
Perhaps.
I'm feeling this way about
someone for the first time
I'd say "may it be easy," but...
Zehra would handle it.
You're being stubborn again.
I'm handling it.
After all, they're already very busy.
In fact, I enjoy doing it.
Let me help too.
No, no need.
Don't put me off by chatting away now.
I need to get my work done.
Okay.
Then I'll sit here and watch you.
It will be enjoyable to watch your efforts.
That's very rude.
I don't want to get
distracted because of you.
Am I distracting you?
No, I mean, what I meant to say was...
No matter who
it would be like that.
I'm telling you, don't chat away.
You keep chatting, putting me off.
This cover doesn't
really match the service.
They contrast with each other.
Aren't they?
I think they match.
Contrast is not a flaw.
Of course not.
I didn't say it was a flaw.
I don't know.
Well, when you look at it like
that, it actually looks quite nice.
It seems to be pulling you in.
They're happy to be together.
I think they are happy too
One has the chaos,
and the other has the serenity.
They would disappear if they were the same.
But they draw attention this way.
As if without one,
the other would not exist.
What did I do with the forks and knives?
Oh my God.
Çiçek had brought them here but...
They're over there.
Correct.
I've forgotten about them.
I'm human too, after all.
I might forget, Mr Ateş.
Of course, of course.
Mrs. Mercan.
Wait a minute, let me tell you something
Come with me.
Could you
arrange these decorations, please?
You know these are heavy,
I'd rather not carry these.
Of course.
Where should I leave it?
I think here
could be okay. The corner on the right.
Is this okay?
No, there are no bushes there.
Could you take it to the left?
Move forward a little.
Can I put it? Is it good here?
No, it's not.
Look, geet it over there.
God give me patience!
You said you'd help me
Why are you complainingnow?
Decide already.
I'll end up with a hernia otherwise.
Alright, alright, leave it.
God forbid.
This is a good spot.
Are you okay?
I don't think so.
I think I fooled you.
You're so bad.
I was losing my mind.
If you keep tormenting me like this
you'll get what's coming to you.
Did you get terrified?
I don't want anyone to get
hurt because of me, that's all.
Should we bring the chairs?
They won't get cold, don't worry.
Don't look like that.
I haven't forgotten you said "Your name
is fire that's why you won't get cold"
You're right.
I suppose so, chairs are good this way.
Nice.
How quickly you were convinced.
You're right.
I like it too, it's simple and not flashy.
Like a family atmosphere.
Colleagues are considered
a part of our family
so they need to feel
comfortable at our home.
Our home?
She said our home.
You're right.
At our house
they should feel comfortable.
I'd better continue to the table.
Shall I go and check on Cemal?
Of course, of course.
Go check him.
Go.
What happened now? I am
saying "our home" and such?
What's happening, Mercan?
Put yourself together.
Mercan!
I've put it wrong.
Are you sure you've looked everywhere?
I did, my dear.
I turned the whole room
upside down, but it's not there.
It was there, in the box.
What are you doing?
I'm calling the police. If it's stolen...
Don't be ridiculous.
There's no need.
Besides, I know who took it.
How?
You know?
Who took it, Mum?
Nermin.
She went on a shopping spree
even though she didn't have a penny.
All of them were branded items.
What are you waiting for then?
Go talk to her!
Confront her!
If necessary, report her to the police.
We can even throw those
scumbags to the press.
No.
I need to prove it first.
If I make a wrong move
In the eyes of Ateş,
Nermin will be the victim,
and I will become the guilty one.
But I'll catch her at just the right moment
so she'll never be able to deny it.
Don't worry about it.
Just think about it
Her daughter is wandering
around as if she is a princess.
But her mother is actually a thief.
I'd like to see Mercan's face
when this comes out, to be honest.
We'll see.
It turned out very well.
I see you've really gotten
caught up in the marriage game
Do you really think you
can pull Ateş like that?
You're really stupid.
What do you think you're doing?
Look at these.
You really have a poor taste.
Those flowers
and so on
looks miserable.
What are you doing?
Can't you tell what I'm doing?
I'm saving you from embarrassing
yourself in front of your guests.
You're mad.
Aslıhan!
What are you doing?
Nothing.
She is a little bit clumsy, I guess.
She dropped all of them.
Oh, my god!
I am going to lose my mind.
Don't be upset.
We'll sort it out together now
No need, I'll handle it.
I didn't ask if you could handle it.
Come on, don't dawdle.
I learned that Ateş had a
brother and he died, Ziya.
Find out for me
what is his brother's name
why he died and where his grave is.
I need this information.
Perhaps, this way we can
learn something about Ateş.
I'll take the money
upfront, Haydar, my brother.
My men don't take a step without payment.
Did you think I'll get a
job done without payment?
Look.
They say, “Even if you find it on
the road, you'd better count it.”
You can presume this job is done already.
Bring me this information, Ziya.
It's very important.
It is a matter of life and death.
I'll pay you double.
Alright.
I'll take care of this.
Berat!
What are you doing here?
You don't even answer my calls.
Are you avoiding me?
Huh?
Baby, no. I'm working.
Don't you see?
Come here.
Come!
Hey.
Give me a hand.
Ugh!
Thanks.
What's up?
What's with the look?
Why would I avoid you?
My precious.
Why would I avoid you? I’m
just cleaning up, can’t you see?
Well..
They say some people from
work are coming over tonight.
So I’m just preparing and stuff, got it?
No.
You're avoiding me.
You gave up on marriage, right?
Do you regret it?
Gorgeous, why would I regret?
What I want..
Is everything to be nice..
And go in order.
In order?
Yes.
Do you think we are in order, Berat?
You didn’t get me a ring
or even tell your mom about me.
And now you're avoiding me.
You went into the channel, Berat
do you think I’m stupid?
I wasn't avoiding, no!
I didn't..
This board..
Was a little loose.
I fixed it.
That’s why I went in.
So..
Gorgeous, don't worry.
I’ll talk to my mother when the time comes.
I'll say that..
I want to marry you.
What about the ring?
Is it a surprise?
Sure, I..
Have some surprises about the ring.
I'm full of..
Surprises, you know.
Alright, nevermind the surprise.
Tell me, how is it like?
No, I can't tell.
Come on!
No, Ela. I can't.
It ruins the surprise, you know?
Oh..
Alright.
Surprise..
I'm so..
I'm so excited.
Okay then, I'll be going.
Okay.
Ela!
Be careful!
Alright, I'm so excited.
Surprise.
Yeah, surprise.
Okay, then. I'll see you.
The biggest surprise is for mom.
What do you want this time?
You..
What did you do?
I'll send them where they belong.
Trash!
How would you do that?
Who do you think you are,
questioning me like that?
Let go off me!
Shut your mouth!
Let me go!
What do you want from me?
Why do you keep treating me like this?
What did I do to deserve it?
Look at me..
Who do you think you
are, the lady of the house?
You can’t invite guests without asking me.
I invited Ateş.
You’re unbelievably shameless
and have no pride.
You’re stupid enough
to try making some cheap,
half-assed food just to seduce Ateş.
You think you can make it?
As long as I’m here, neither you
nor your mother
will be walking around this
mansion acting like you own the place.
Your reign is over.
You’re people we paid for and bought.
You got carried away
with this marriage play.
And..
If you think
you can ride on easy money,
you’re out of luck.
You can't talk to me like this.
Well, I did.
You think you’ll try to seduce Ateş
and I’ll just keep quiet, is that it?
Do you trust this?
Did you think a photo together
meant he’d take your side?
You thought he’d stand behind you?
That’s all you’re worth.
I’m sick of you walking around
acting like the lady of the mansion.
Enough!
Stop it.
I told you to stay away from Mercan.
Leave before I break your heart!
Don't cry.
I don't.
Don't mind them.
We can buy the new ones.
It's just clothes.
I don't mind them.
I was going to change.
It was a bit stained, but
it’ll probably come off.
I’m going out for a bit
and I’ll be back soon.
Wait for me in the room.
I'll be back before the guests arrive.
Where?
I'll be back soon.
I've got the chance to
talk to Mr. Kemal but,
I couldn't really learn much.
Boy,
Is that really how you expect
to get anything out of him?
It's okay.
But you..
Keep doing thing anyway.
Observe, trace.
I don't know.
If they head to the study in
the garden, eavesdrop at the door.
I mean this man goes out
to garden at night, right?
Yeah.
Okay, then.
Move in quietly
and eavesdrop on any phone calls.
Okay, Mr. Haydar.
Don't worry.
He's gone through lately.
But it's okay now.
If you help me..
You'll get no problems.
I’ll make you everything in this mansion.
Boy,
of course I'll help you.
I raised you.
What is this man plotting again?
I'll make you marry.
I'll make you have things.
God bless you, Mr. Haydar.
Thanks a lot.
To be honest, I’m glad we didn’t go home.
Otherwise, I’d have been so
tired I would’ve passed out.
I would’ve missed the amazing feast.
So you're sure that you're okay?
Well..
Yes, I am.
Of course you wouldn’t know,
Ever since Mr. Ateş came here,
even the food has improved,
we’re eating first-class now.
I’m not even thinking about what
he’s going to have at his barbecue party.
Yeah?
Demet.
Shall we go to a concert
that you'll choose?
Sure.
Yeah?
Yeah.
What is this?
Are you going somewhere?
Yeah.
Mercan and Ateş are
having a barbecue party.
We'll go there.
Ateş and Mercan..
Okay.
So that there's a party,
I'll take you there.
What are you going to do there?
We'll be there as the
employees of the company.
Demet,
I’m also a partner in this company.
Go.
Mr. Nezih, as usual.
Now, what to do with him?
I'm gonna hit him once..
Dude, nevermind him.
You'll gwt trouble for no reason at all.
Nevermid him.
Let's go eat meatballs.
I'm going to kill him.
For real.
I'm mad.
Nevermind.
Let's go, friends.
Aren't you hungry? Come on.
Come on, you’ll eat the ribs, okay?
Tch, tch. Dust on everything.
Oh God.
Look at this place.
Dust on everything.
We’ve been so caught up with the mansion stuff
that we couldn’t even look after our own place.
What is this here?
Who put this here?
What is this envelope?
Should I open it?
Otherwise..
How would I know who this is for?
I should open it.
What?
Haydar..
Haydar Yıld..
Berat Güneş..
One million?
Oh my God!
Oh!
Did Mr. Haydar give money to Berat?
Oh dear God!
Oh my dear God!
What will I do?
Haydar Yıldırım.
Berat Güneş.
Check.
One million.
Oh God.
Oh God, what do I do?
Oh God, no.
No!
Come on, where are you?
He's about to come, I assume.
Should I call him?
No.
I won't!
He might misunderstand.
Like I'm worried.
But I am.
I will call.
I don't care what he'll think.
Hello?
Where are you?
I'm still waiting for you.
I'm on my way.
I'll be there soon.
I worried when you got late.
How worried?
I knew you would make fun of me.
I was just telling you sincerely.
I'm hanging up.
No, stop.
What's up?
You know, I had something
to tell you yesterday.
Yeah?
I couldn't tell you last night.
We couldn't talk.
Yeah?
It's time to talk.
Talk about what?
When I come.
Ateş?
Ateş!
Oh God!
The person you are trying to
reach is currently unavailable.
Come on already.
Thank God, finally.
Ateş.
Why was I so scared of losing you?
Feels like it took years off my life.
What's happening to me?
Why am I this afraid?
Did the fear of losing me
really upset you that much?
Are those tears really for me?
Thank God. You’re here.
I told you I was fine. Don’t
worry. See? I’m right here.
I thought you were brushing me off.
First the hospital, then the police…
I just panicked.
Cemal wouldn’t take me with him either.
And when I couldn’t see you,
I thought you were all
hiding something from me.
You’re okay, right? Nothing happened?
I’m fine. Don't worry about me.
Why are you crying?
I can't help. My nerves are shot.
That screeching brake
sound… it’s still in my ears.
When the crash happened
right in front of me,
I had to slam the brakes.
There were injured people.
I couldn’t answer the
phone while helping them.
Then my battery died.
After that, everything turned into chaos.
-Everyone’s okay, right? -They’re fine.
We got them to the hospital in time.
Thank God no one was seriously hurt.
You must be exhausted.
We can call them and cancel if
you want. They’ll understand.
I’m not tired.
And they’re probably on
their way. It’d be rude.
Let’s go get changed.
Cemal told me not to say
anything to your family.
That's right. I asked him to.
No need to worry them.
I still don’t understand
why you left so suddenly.
You’ll understand soon. Come on.
Oh, Berat… Oh, Berat…
just wait till I get my hands
on you. You’ll see what I’ll do.
Ah... he's coming.
Where have you been?
Mom, I had things to take
care of. I handled them.
What is this?! Tell me.
Tell me what kind of dirty
business did you get into with Haydar.
What dirty business?! Mom, no!
It’s nothing like that!
Then what is it? Tell me!
I took it to pay our debt to Malik.
Obviously, Mr. Haydar didn’t
give you this out of kindness.
Well, mom, he didn’t ask for anything bad.
He just said, "Be friends with Mr. Cemal.
Find out who he is, what he’s about."
What’s Mr. Haydar's
problem with Cemal, anyway?
He didn’t say, mom.
There’s definitely
something shady going on here.
If his intentions were
good, he would’ve told you.
Listen to me, Berat.
Stay away from that man.
If you get mixed up in
Haydar’s shady business,
I won’t forgive you.
Not as your mother. Got it?
Alright, mom.
-Did you understand?! -I did. Okay. I did.
Why are you getting so worked up?
Oh God.
Mom, you obviously know something…
There’s definitely
something you’re not saying.
Ugh… we'll see what it is.
What’s all this?
Did you… buy these?
You can’t live your whole
life in the same dress.
Is that why you left?
Ateş?
Mercan?
You’re teasing me again.
But you’re actually not.
I’ve figured you out now.
But you didn’t have to.
I could’ve handled it.
I had to.
I won’t ignore the injustice done to you.
Please don’t argue.
Okay. I’m not.
You have your own sense of justice.
You never waver.
You always make things right immediately.
You never let anything stay broken.
You never let anything
fall apart and stay that way.
Knowing that… it gives
a person a little comfort.
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
And thank you… for the kind words.
Let’s see if we can get
through today without a fight.
Why would you say that?
Every time we make peace, a fight
follows. Something always breaks.
Let’s not let it happen this time.
Okay.
I hope you like them.
I already do.
I loved them all before even seeing them.
I’ll remember today forever.
I hope it fits. Check it.
If not, you can exchange it.
You’re tiny anyway.
Me?
I’m not exchanging anything.
I know I’ll love them.
Then, I’ll try one on right away.
And I’ll change right here.
Where is that witch Nermin?!
She’s going to pay for getting in my way!
Mom, calm down.
You’re only giving her what she wants.
I don’t care, Aslı. Just let her come...
Were you looking for me, Mrs. Müzeyyen?
Yes! I was!
Well, here I am.
Oh, sweetheart… you look upset.
But I understand you.
Competing with Nermin Yıldırım isn’t easy.
But don’t dwell on it.
It doesn’t matter who the president is.
What matters is the
future of the foundation.
You’ll see, as the new
president, I’ll take it to the top.
Becoming president with the
necklace you stole from me…
suits someone like you.
And forget taking it to the top
you’ll drag the foundation
straight to the bottom.
I’m sure of it.
Are you ready?
I'm coming!
You drive me crazy every single time.
I love this one.
You? How does it look? Does it suit me?
It…
It suits you beautifully.
It fits perfectly.
I didn’t know you knew me this well.
There was someone your size
there. I just described you.
Like what?
You liked it on someone else?
You'd better buy it for her, then.
Believe me, it didn’t
look half as good on her.
It’s not just the dress.
It’s who’s wearing it.
My God, what is he telling me?
Thank you.
Just in time.
Let me…
What’s wrong with it?
It’s a little messy. I’ll take care of it.
There. Better…
Why were you so scared?
I was just… scared. Isn’t that normal?
Scared of losing me?
I thought something happened. That’s all.
And then you… went out just to get a dress…
I should go downstairs.
They must have already arrived.
No need to make them wait.
Haven’t you calmed down yet, Mom?
How can I calm down, dear?
That witch drove me mad.
Nermin, Haydar, their daughters…
I’ve had enough of all of them!
If I knew Ateş wouldn’t stop me,
I’d kill every one of them one by one.
I keep telling you.
Nermin and Haydar are easy targets…
Our biggest threat is Mercan.
Maybe it’s time to end this.
What are you trying to say, dear?!
If Mercan finds out why
Ateş really came here...
His revenge plan...
Are you out of your mind?!
Never! That will never happen!
Get that out of your head!
If we do that, we put both
Ateş and ourselves in danger.
Then give me a better idea, Mom.
How will you keep Mercan away from Ateş?
Don’t you see what’s happening?
And what are we waiting for?
If I stay silent, I’ll
lose Ateş completely.
Don’t! I said don’t.
This conversation is over.
Don’t bring this to me again.
What are you doing here?
Were you waiting for me?
Did you talk to your
mother? What did she say?
What talk, my sultan?
What mother?
I’m waiting for Mr. Haydar.
So when will you talk to her?
As soon as possible.
Maybe today?
-No, not that soon. -Tomorrow?
Why are you suffocating
me like this, Zehra?
Look at me. Are you
stringing me along? Huh?
No, Zehra.
No, dear. No, my love.
I’m not stringing you along.
Enough, Berat! I'm sick of this!
Look, Berat.
Either you talk to your mother by tonight,
or you forget about me! Do you understand?
That’s my final word!
Man… unbelievable.
Yes, Ms. Binnaz? Anything you want to say?
Yes. Yes, there is.
I have a few words for you.
Mr Haydar. Until today, I
treated this mansion as my home
and you as my family.
I sheltered here with my children.
Every sin committed within
these walls is on your shoulders.
But if you try to drag
my children into those sins
if you hurt them,
This silent tongue will
speak, just so you know.
What are you implying, Binnaz?
Are you threatening me, openly?
Instead of thanking
me for helping your son,
you stand here questioning me?
Staying silent isn’t an option for you.
It’s a necessity. Don’t forget that.
I’m aware of my duty and my obligations.
And I'm fulfilling them, Mr. Haydar.
But don’t forget this either...
A mother will do anything for her children.
If necessary, I’ll risk everything.
Welcome. Welcome. Nice to see you.
Hello, Burak.
Mr. Ateş. Mrs. Mercan.
Welcome.
My brother’s coming too, just so you know.
I tried so hard but couldn’t shake him off.
He dropped me off and went
to get your favorite dessert.
He’ll be here soon.
He didn’t have to bother…
Welcome, everyone.
Oh, Mr. Cemal's here.
Welcome.
Mercan, I love your dress.
The color, the cut... everything.
It looks amazing on you.
Thank you.
It is a gift from Ateş.
I love it too, Mercan.
Your dress is on fire.
You two look great together
as a couple, Mr. Ateş.
I was just going to say the same. You
took the words right out of my mouth.
Come on, move along.
You’re left standing. Go on.
-Yes, please. Come on, this way. -Please.
Let's go, dear.
My God, what is this?
It was so funny though.
She was really funny.
I watched that movie.
It was really awesome.
I adore that actress, too.
- The woman was so funny.
- Yes, she really was.
Excuse me.
You're not cold, are you?
No, I'm not. You?
There's no reason to be cold, anyway.
I just asked since I
didn’t want you getting sick.
What’s the point of all this?
Aslı, our meat and our
grill are right here.
Everyone’s gathered.
Why don’t you have fun?
With that girl here?
Aslı, you’re about to go down in history
as the first person to
ruin my mood at the grill.
How many times ave I told
you she’s not at fault.
Let me check Cemal.
Everything okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
Everything’s perfect.
Don’t mind her.
So what about you?
What are you asking about me?
I see. You’re going to pretend
again like there’s no fire inside you.
The other heart has already
caught fire, just so you know.
Which heart?
Which heart do you
think? Obviously not mine.
By the way, can I tell you something?
Mercan almost lost her mind today.
Worse than the day you were kidnapped.
- So she was really scared?
- More than you think.
-I'll be back. -Okay, dear.
Good luck.
If it’s easy, come do it yourself.
No thanks. I’ve cooked enough for today.
It’s better for all of you if I don’t.
She thinks you can make
dry dolma without onions.
That bad?
Oh, come on.
Hey everyone. Hello.
What's Mr. Nezir doing here?
Hello. Mercan, I got
this especially for you.
Thanks. You shouldn’t have. Really.
You really went to the trouble.
It’s no trouble.
You know, it’s a pleasure for me.
So, how are you? Everything okay?
We’re fine.
So glad you came.
Thank you.
Why don't you come over?
These meats… I’m about
to give you all a real feast.
-Thank you. -Don't overcook the meatballs.
Mercan likes them medium.
The meatballs are ready.
Everything’s done. Please,
everyone, come to the table.
Ugh, I’m starving.
How are things with Burak?
Better. I think we’re improving.
He invited me to a concert this weekend.
I’m so happy for you.
That’s wonderful news.
Now you tell me.
-Me? -Of course you, Mercan.
Look, your face is glowing.
And the way you and Ateş look
at each other didn’t escape me.
Come on, where did you
get that from, Demet?
There’s no such thing.
You must’ve seen wrong.
Alright. If you say there’s
nothing, then there’s nothing.
-Mm-hmm. -Mm‑hmm.
What am I doing?
Am I giving people the wrong impression?
No… I don’t think so.
We’re just always together,
that’s why they misunderstand.
While you eat, lend me your
ears for a moment, friends.
Don’t worry, I’m not
planning a long or boring speech.
Thank you all for your hard work,
on behalf of myself and Mercan.
Without your dedication,
we couldn’t have prepared the
project presentation this quickly.
The results aren’t in yet,
but this teamwork deserves a celebration.
Good for you.
And a special thanks
to the brain of the project,
my wife, Mercan Karahan.
Without her sharp mind, creativity,
passion, and determination,
this project wouldn’t exist.
Thank you.
Those qualities belong
to all of us, not just me.
Then, enjoy your meal everyone.
Enjoy.
Enjoy it. Thank you.
I’m going to be sick.
Don’t do it in front of everyone.
Come on, don’t look
like that. Smile a little.
This game needs to end.
I’m tired of it.
Want some salad?
Yes, but just a little.
Thank you.
Here, Aslı, let me pass that to you.
Never mind, I don’t want it.
I have to speak with a client now.
There.
Why were you so scared?
- Would you like some bread?
- No, I don’t eat bread.
You don't?
So, we're cautious about our health.
Where are you going?
… to the bathroom.
Of course.
Everything looks amazing.
-You liked it? -Very much.
It wouldn't have turned out
any better without your help.
If we do something together, there’s
no chance it won’t turn out well.
How did you know what I needed?
That’s my secret.
Come on, all together.
Your brows are dark enough
to ink a decree.
This love drives me
from one land to another.
Even if Lokman the Healer came,
he’d only deepen my wound.
Let my beloved come
and tend to it herself.
Bravo!
You sang perfectly. Thank you all.
Well done, Mr. Cemal. You were really good.
-You sang so well, Mr. Cemal. -Thanks.
-Well done, Cemal. -Thank you.
Mr. Ateş, this gathering was
such a good idea. Thank you so much.
Absolutely. I don’t know about you all,
but I had so much fun. I enjoyed it a lot.
Ugh.
What are you doing here?
I… I just came out of the bathroom.
Then I couldn’t find the door.
Oh, is that so?
You’ll leave through
the same door you came in.
The-the house is so
big… I couldn’t remember.
I'll go now.
This is a photo of Haydar from his youth.
What is it doing in this guy’s wallet?
"To my Nurgül." I don’t believe this.
No, no…
What does this mean?
Could it be…?
Malik.
There’s so much work today.
My mom will be here soon.
-Why did you come, my love? MALİK:
-I wanted to talk to you, Çiçek.
What's wrong?
Everything we’ve been through,
all the trouble… it’s because of me.
I know you’ve been hurting.
And I can’t stand it.
Why are you talking like this,
Malik? None of this is your fault.
Mrs. Binnaz is right, Çiçek.
About what?
Malik! Are you going to
tell me what’s going on?
Ugh, where’s my wallet?
Ah, here it is.
How are you, son?
I’m fine, thank you, sir. And you?
It felt strange seeing you here.
I’m used to seeing you
working at the company.
I used to work a lot too
when I was young.
My circumstances weren’t great back then.
Hard work is good.
You’re right, sir.
I had a son too.
He wasn’t very good with work.
Always fooling around.
We didn’t get along much because of that.
I grew up without a father.
So I never had those conflicts.
Anyway, my friends will
wonder where I am. I should go.
I really put my foot in it.
What are you implying, Binnaz?
Are you threatening me, openly?
Instead of thanking
me for helping your son,
you stand here questioning me?
Staying silent isn’t an option for you.
It’s a necessity. Don’t forget that.
Where have you been?
I think I ate too much.
Took a walk to settle it.
Coming here was good
for all of us, wasn't it?
Yes, it really was.
We must do this more often, Ms. Zahide.
Um-hmm.
In the meantime…
There’s a different energy
between Mr. Ateş and Mrs. Mercan.
There's a difference in their
style. It looks good though.
I sure noticed.
Mr. Ateş?
I'd like to say
something, if you excuse me.
Sure. Go ahead.
Are we going to celebrate like this?
Let me take care of it, if you’ll allow me.
Of course.
Mrs. Mercan?
Please, go ahead.
Then this song is from me to you.
Oh, this is the best
song. Come on. Let's dance.
Everyone dance. Come on.
Come on, Ateş. Get up.
We can't do without you.
Come on.
Come on, Aslı. No objections. Get up.
We'll dance together. Don't do
that, at least today. Come on.
Come on, brother.
What? Come on. Get up.
-Don't be ridiculous. -Come on. Get up.
Come on.
- Come on.
- What does that have to do with anything?
I won’t let you take Ateş
from me right in front of my eyes.
There’s no other option.
You’re going to learn the truth…
… why he came here.
His revenge plan…
… everything… you'll find out everything.
And then we’ll see if you still love him…
… if you still stand beside him.
Why is he questioning so
much that I worry about him?
Why is he reading into it?
What’s wrong with caring about someone?
Unless… unless it’s more than that?
It’s like… my eyes keep searching for him.
My heart jumps every time I look at him.
What is happening to me?
What is this feeling
everyone sees except me?
Don’t be ridiculous, Mercan.
Don’t be ridiculous.
Don’t get carried away
with unnecessary thoughts.
There's no need for that.
There’s nothing. Stay calm.
My God, then why am I this uneasy?
Why are you beating like this?
Enough, already. Stop.
Just a joke.
What are you doing?
Why did you run away?
No, I didn't.
Just in time.
♪ The sweetest song ♪
♪ I’ve ever heard is your voice. ♪
♪ The most beautiful image ♪
♪ I’ve ever seen is your face. ♪
♪ You’re the softest flower
I’ve ever breathed in, ♪
♪ the most exquisite
taste I’ve ever known. ♪
♪ The only sacred place
these hands have touched ♪
♪ is the temple of your skin. ♪
♪ You are my senses, my gentleness, ♪
♪ the deepest feeling I’ve ever felt. ♪
♪ I love you more than I can say. ♪
♪ You’re God’s precious gift,
♪ ♪ and at last… I found you. ♪
♪ If only you knew how long I searched. ♪
♪ Forgive me, if I
made you wait too long. ♪
♪ I love you—truly, endlessly. ♪
♪ God’s beautiful gift… ♪
♪ and at last… I found you. ♪
♪ Thank you. ♪
♪ Thank you to the One above ♪
♪ for writing you into my fate. ♪
♪ The sweetest song ♪
My God… is this a dream?
♪ I’ve ever heard is your
voice. The most beautiful image ♪
I wish we could stay like this forever.
♪ I’ve ever seen is your face. ♪
♪ You’re the softest flower
♪ ♪ I’ve ever breathed in, ♪
♪ the most exquisite
taste I’ve ever known. ♪
♪ The only sacred place
these hands have touched ♪
♪ is the temple of your skin. ♪
♪ You are my senses, my gentleness, ♪
♪ the deepest feeling I’ve ever felt. ♪
It's time.
There are things we need to talk about.
I…
Where are you going, Mercan?
Ahh...
Mercan! Stop! What's wrong with you?!
Where are you Mercan?
Mercan!
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you running away?
Let go!
Hold still. Your hair is full of leaves.
It doesn’t matter. Just let me go.
Calm down.
What happened to you?
Nothing happened! What could have happened?
Then why were you running from me?
Then why didn’t you stop when I called you?
Because you were running!
-Because I ran? -Mm‑hmm.
I ran because you were running.
I mean… that’s not what happened!
Let me go!
I can’t. Not until I say this.
Say what?
I know you were terrified for me today.
You were devastated.
Why?
What “why”?
Because I thought you were dead!
I was sad. Isn’t that enough?
Isn’t that normal?
Is that all? Nothing more?
Yes! That’s all!
What else do you want me to say?
Just let me go!
It won’t matter if you run.
Because you…
…You're right here in my heart.
And you’re the one who can heal it.
You’re the light in all my darkness.
What are you talking about?
What "darkness"? What "light"?
Do you understand?
No!
When you look at me like that,
my heart can’t stay in my chest.
I forget how to breathe.
One smile from you and every
storm inside me goes quiet.
I feel like I can overcome anything.
You’re the heart of my
heart… my pearl, Mercan.
Whose pearl?
I'm telling you! Your scent is in my chest.
I’m gone for you. Get it?
Do you understand? Can you hear me, Mercan?
Look at me. Look into my eyes, Mercan.
Every part of me is in
love with every part of you.
What are you saying?
Again with these "Look at me" commands?
I’m saying you’ve taken over my heart!
I love you! I love you.
Do you understand?
Did he say he loved me?
Look at me. Don't cry.
I don't like whiny people.
Please, go away.
Stay away from me.
Why are you still here? Go away!
I told you to go away! Go! Leave!
"I'd rather pay the price
of love than live without it."
Leave it, I can handle.
No.
You'll cut your hand.
I won't.
You'll cut if you do like this.
Look what you did.
Did it cut?
Come.
We should clean.
It's nothing.
You're exaggerating.
I'm not.
You're not listening.
I said so.
Okay, I misunderstood.
I shall go.
I'll come after one hour.
If you let me.
Why are you here?
The meeting wasn't here.
I don't know, I thought it was here.
Isn't this a workroom?
So you misunderstood that too.
Just like the hour.
Yes I misunderstood.
Why all these questions?
As if
I had done something wrong.
You've really dragged this out.
Okay, I misunderstood. I'll go.
I'll come after one hour.
You can't tell a lie, you know that, right?
Okay.
Yes, I know.
Everyone says so.
I don't like to tell lie.
Sometimes you just have to do it.
I can't do that either.
Why are you here then?
Well, I have a guess.
I'm sorry.
I didn't realize you were inside.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have come.
It's okay.
Were you impressed?
God.
Why am I impressed?
Did you find the answer that you look for?
Not yet.
But I'll.
Don't you think that I'll give up.
When I set out on a
path, I walk it to the end.
I don't go back.
Of course, go.
All the ways are yours.
How innocent she looks.
Could you have done it?
You're confusing me.
How sleep makes even the most
ruthless person seem innocent.
As if all those harsh words
hateful glances
as if they belonged to
someone else, not to him.
Why did she cover me up?
She surprises me every time.