Senior Sahara.
Hmm?
I used to like you.
If I say that, how will you react?
Toki.
If I ever feel weak again,
can I have your energy?
Oww!
I'll inject the energy for you anytime!
Nekoto,
shall we continue our conversation
from earlier?
"Mr. Sahara &amp; Toki-kun"
(Episode 7)
(This is how Sahara and my story begins)
23.25 seconds! Amazing!
Another personal best!
Yeah!
During high school,
when I first joined the swim team,
I was quite quick-tempered
and Senior Sahara...
Honestly, I couldn't stand him.
Sahara,
Yes?
I burned today's video for you.
Thanks!
But one day...
Well then, I'll head out first.
Good job.
- Um, Senior,
- Hmm?
what was that just now?
Oh, that's Sahara swimming.
I record it from various angles.
He takes it home to analyze the form.
Oh.
He might not look like it,
but he's quite the hard worker.
Wow...
I begin to see
the true nature of Senior.
Senior!
Oh!
On the days when I felt
I hadn't practiced enough,
I always run back home.
Why do you go that far?
Well...
It's about determination, pride,
and pressure, I guess.
Oh...
I'm not some extraordinary person,
so if I don't practice,
I get anxious and
my mentality gets weaker.
That's why I have to do my best.
What have I always been
thought about this person?
Always fighting
invisible pressure to work hard.
And yet...
I misunderstood you
without knowing anything.
And I made assumptions about you.
I'm sorry.
Ah...
I don't know anything about you either.
So, let's call it even.
Huh?
From now on,
let's get to know each other better.
Nice to meet you!
Alright.
Nice to meet you.
Go!
Yes.
As a result,
after the graduation of the manager,
Senior Hasegawa...
So hungry.
I'm hungry.
I started supporting
and managing Senior.
Senior.
Hmm?
It's about time.
Ah...
Just a bit more.
10 minutes more...
Huh?
Hello? Nekoto?
Sorry for calling you out of the blue.
I tried calling Sahara,
but he's out of range.
Is he nearby right now?
Yes. I'll pass it to him.
Thank you.
Hello.
Oh, Sahara?
Long time no see. How have you been?
Yes, I'm doing well.
How about you?
Oh, I see.
Graduating does bring
its own challenges.
Could it be,
Yes.
Senior Sahara,
- thinks about Senior Hasegawa...
- Right.
Ah.
By the way,
at the recent sports festival...
(Someone you like)
Back then,
he probably drew 'someone you like.'
But...
Senior Hasegawa, who had graduated,
wasn't there...
I see...
That makes sense.
Well then.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
Yes.
You seem
to get along well with Senior Hasegawa.
Huh?
You get along with her more than I do.
Hmm?
Why am I irritated?
Ahh...
I was just getting comfy...
Wait...
What is this restless feeling?
Do I like Senior?
But I can't say it.
I just want to be by his side.
That's all I want.
I'll accept everything
from you.
Senior,
are you hiding something from me?
Huh?
I had a feeling that you were.
You're free to talk about it.
I'll accept it all.
I decided to believe those words.
So...
I like you.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
I like you, Senior.
But it's impossible for me.
The meaning of liking for you and me
is just too different.
I...
lied.
Huh?
Sahara.
Where are you?
Nekoto Minato is...
He was a man I used to like.
It's not that I don't believe you.
It's my own issue.
Will you be alright?
I can be myself now,
and that's thanks to you.
Wait for me.
It might take some time,
but when the time comes, I'll tell you.
Why did you lie?
It was the day before
the graduation ceremony.
So, please take care of
the surprise for tomorrow.
Got it! Leave it to me.
I'll share it with everyone.
I really appreciate it.
Sahara's graduation is finally here.
It's so fast.
But it's amazing, isn't it?
Getting into that prestigious university
through a sports recommendation.
And being a candidate for
the Japanese national team.
He might really make it to the Olympics.
At that moment, I realized.
Senior is going to shine on
a big stage from now on,
attracting attention from the media,
And if that happens,
won't my existence
become a burden for you?
As a lover, especially as a man...
I thought I might ruin your future.
When I found out that you got injured
at the university, I regretted it a lot.
Trying too hard
without being able to apply the brakes.
Sahara-kun, don't push yourself.
Thank you.
I should have known you
better than anyone,
yet I couldn't stop you.
It made me so angry at myself.
I see...
What a shame.
Really...
What are you doing?
I...
said things that could
create misunderstandings,
I'm sorry.
After that, I couldn't get
in touch with you at all.
But...
when I came to this school,
you were here.
I know I don't have
the right to say this.
But if
I could have another chance...
Can I say that I like you?
They both liked each other,
but because of a misunderstanding...
Should they just let it be?
What should I do?
Ah!
Nekoto.
I'm sorry, but I can't do that.
The fact that you were thinking of me,
went out of your way for me,
just knowing that makes me happy.
Senior...
Maybe we took too long to get here.
Both you and I.
You mean it's too late?
Maybe so.
But I don't regret it now.
So...
you don't have to feel
responsible anymore.
For getting injured
and quitting swimming,
it's my own issue,
but I've been causing you pain
and hurting you all along...
I'm sorry.
Certainly, Senior is too weak.
Huh?
You're hurting him like that too.
Did you think it went unnoticed?
He's special, right?
Toki-kun.
Yeah.
Very special.
Then, why don't you go after him?
Nekoto,
thank you.
Toki!
Isn't it out of character for you
to suddenly disappear?
It's not like that.
I just got tired of silently listening.
And besides...
I believe you, after all.
What?
What? A thank you, maybe?
You've always supported me,
and I've always been spoiled by you,
so, this time, I'll pamper you.
I can tell by the look on your face
that you would reject Nekoto.
But...
I came here because I was afraid.
Yeah.
Adults are unfair.
And I'm just a dumb kid.
It's fine being a kid.
Hey! Take that back!
Because, no matter how you look at it...
Hey! What happened to pampering?
Well, Toki Kanade-kun,
that's one of your cute points.
You didn't have to say 'cute, '
but I don't feel bad about it.
(This is a fictional work)
(Next episode)
If anything happens to you,
I'm not sure I can keep calm.
If there's anything, you can rely on me.
(Do your best, Sahara)
I don't want to cause
trouble to my friends.
Don't mess with Toki Kanade.
You've always been a hero to me
even before and now!