(theme music)
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
Hello, sir.
Congratulations on your release.
Right.
I'm Lee Junkyung.
Sir?
My name is Lee Junkyung.
Leave.
Sorry?
KANGCHUN PENITENTIARY BUS STOP
Sir.
There's something I need to tell--
(gasps, groans)
Go tell the chairman
that I'll stay dead quiet as promised.
I kept the promise for 15 years
so it's his turn to do the same.
(groans in pain)
(sighs)
I'm not here because the chairman sent me.
I would like to save you.
WORLD'S MOST VALUABLE DIAMOND ARROW
SOON TO BE UNVEILED
Diamond arrow?
I'm sure the notorious Lee Changwoo
will be able to pull this off.
Let me help you.
All right. Now, tell me.
Where did you hide it?
The Adamas.
You took it.
What's wrong? Did you lose it?
Enough with this act, god damn it.
Where did you hide it?
The real Adamas.
Not the fake one.
I thought I was still alive
because I'm the only one
who knows where it is.
And now you want me to tell you?
You'd better stop playing around
and come clean.
If you don't want to sacrifice
your other son too.
Go ahead and see how I'll react.
(scoffs)
All right, show me.
Show me what you can do from here.
Junkyung.
Chairman Kwon…
What?
(sighs)
(smacks lips)
You shouldn't have come here
to meet me today.
What is this about?
What about the chairman?
Do you think Chairman Kwon
has forgotten about me?
So you killed Song Suhyeon?
Did you check the body?
Then you should've brought a photo.
Not this mere sheet of paper.
(door closes)
(sighs)
Bastard.
Mr. Jeong.
I'm changing orders.
(Suhyeon gasps)
Ms. Lee.
Ms. Kim…
(clatters)
Move.
Ms. Kim.
(panting)
-(tires screech)
-Damn it.
What on earth?
Let me use your car.
(car revving)
(revving continues)
Why does he suddenly want her alive?
How annoying.
(whistles)
(whistling continues)
Hi.
You are…
I'm what?
Sun?
You know my name?
Where are you? Where?
Where are you?
Who told you?
Song Suhyeon's alive, isn't he?
(gasps, exclaims)
Damn it.
SUHYEON: I'm going to mess you up.
(pants)
(loud grunt)
(gasps)
(coughing)
(coughing continues)
(clears throat, panting)
Ms. Kim.
(panting continues)
(phone dialing)
Ms. Kim was kidnapped.
We must go rescue her immediately.
Go where?
Ares.
Come back for now.
SUHYEON: I won't do that!
If we take longer,
we'll only find her body later.
SUHYEON:
What's gotten into you people anyway?
Are you just going to watch everyone die?
When will you stop tolerating
these meaningless sacrifices?
You must be attacking them.
Why can't you stick to the basics?
Sir.
Go on.
Yes, sir.
Wait there. I'm on my way now.
(panting)
I'm sorry,
Lieutenant Lee Hyunjung.
MAN 1: We have a breach at the main gate!
We have a breach!
MAN 2: Stop those cars!
MAN 1: Security!
(tires screech)
MAN 3: Don't let them through.
We're done cleaning up the place.
Even if Team A knows, they won't be
able to find any trace of us.
-Good job.
-No problem, sir.
-Hey.
-Yes, sir?
It's a trap.
(car beeping)
MR. KANG
Sir, we're breaking through at the moment.
This wasn't their target.
If they meant to raid us,
-they would've brought a whole squad.
-Pardon?
They brought us in on purpose.
Get out of there now!
(horn honking)
(tires screech)
MR. HAN: Prosecutor Song, stop!
(honking continues)
(panting)
(grunts)
(Sun humming)
Did you sleep well?
Get up, will you?
(gasps)
(breathing heavily)
Do you want to run away?
I let you see my face
because I was going to kill you.
Why do you think
I brought you here alive instead?
What do you want from me?
We want a way into the SIH.
The infiltration team.
Show us the way.
You're wasting your time.
I'll never do that.
(sighs)
Thank goodness.
I was worried you might say okay.
I won't kill you,
even if you beg me
to kill you.
-MS. KWON: Here is the list of guests.
-Mm.
They are VIPs from the publishing,
broadcasting, and political circles.
I wonder what you'd think of it.
You've selected 80 people
to go with the 80th anniversary?
You always emphasize
that everything should be
limited in number.
Only then would it hold meaning.
Good job.
Those who get invited will be so proud
while those who are left out
will try their best
to be included next time.
IM JINCHUL, ATTORNEY GENERAL
KWON: Take the Attorney General out.
We don't need him
once the administration changes.
Invite Mr. Ha instead.
You mean the writer?
My memoir will be presented
during the ceremony.
I should treat him at least once.
By the way, the tree in the garden.
Yes, master.
Why did you suddenly cut it?
I kind of grew attached to it
since it was there for a long time.
You know Chungwoon, right?
The famous topography fortune teller.
-Yes,
-According to him,
that tree was standing
in the way of great fortune.
It wasn't doing any good for you, master.
So I…
(smacks lips)
Good job.
Anything with a bad energy
must be eliminated,
no matter how long it has kept your side
or how much you've cherished it.
Yes, of course.
DONGRIM: This is incredible.
You were invited after all.
Right, it was worth
writing the memoir all night.
By the way,
stealing the Adamas is one thing,
but will we be able to run away
with it safely from this house?
Hmm… Run away?
If we get caught, we'll be doomed.
That is
up to the heavens.
(rustling)
Hello, this is Security.
Today?
I see.
AGENT KIM: Okay.
What is it?
The head office called.
Do you know where Mr. Choi is?
Well, he went downstairs a while ago.
What did the head office want?
SECURITY CONTROL ROOM
Oh, Mr. Choi.
You can sit back down
and keep doing your work.
Is there anything particular?
No, nothing.
You look tired.
Go outside for a cigarette.
I'm okay, sir. It's working hours.
Smoking is best during working hours.
Step outside for a moment. I'll stay.
Okay, then.
SECURITY CONTROL ROOM
Section Seven.
Nothing seemed off when I went there.
This is me.
It's someone who came afterward.
(suspenseful music)
(heavy sigh)
Mr. Choi?
What?
Oh, Mr. Lee isn't loafing around.
I let him step outside for a bit.
To smoke.
Don't keep him on a tight leash.
SUHYEON: Mr. Lee killed her.
I'll go to headquarters.
No, the safe house.
Okay.
What do you think? Do you like it?
What?
Yes, it's nice.
Then will you choose this--
No, I prefer the one from the other day.
Oh, you rejected that one
so we showed it to someone else.
She's trying it on now.
Really? I guess it can't be helped then.
The truth is…
STAFF: You look beautiful.
How pretty. It looks good on you.
But it's a little too long
for you, Ms. Yoon.
-Ms. Cho.
-Yes, ma'am?
Cut off about two hems' length.
Well… Sure thing.
Forget it. I should be
thanking you instead.
I'm so grateful
that my husband has you by his side.
You're not showing any reaction again.
Others might think
I'm looking down on you.
When it's actually the other way around.
You are getting a call.
I think it's urgent.
A person named Mr. Jeong
keeps calling you.
MR. JEONG
See you around.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Your call cannot be connected…
Darn it.
Goodness.
MR. CHA: This was taken
in the parking lot of the Ares building.
And this is the dashcam footage
near the atelier yesterday…
I apologize, sir.
Do a better job, Mr. Cha.
Do you hear me?
Yes, sir.
Stand by at your houses
for the time being.
And send in the elites. Now get out.
I'm not done analyzing--
I said get out. I'll take care of it.
Just wrap up Ms. Jang's incident smoothly.
Yes, sir.
(Sun laughs)
Did you lose them or let them go?
Cut the crap.
(clicks tongue)
Let me see.
Look. Song Suhyeon is limping.
SUN: Kim Seohee is barely supporting him
as they run away.
And you couldn't get them?
Jeez.
Where did they disappear to?
To the sky? Or underground?
Jeez.
I wouldn't have to go through this mess
if you'd taken care of him properly.
You're right about that.
That witch.
DELETE
ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT TO DELETE THIS FILE?
Things aren't looking good.
Shouldn't you let me know what's going on?
I already told you everything yesterday.
Do you need another explanation?
Someone suddenly jumped
in front of my car…
and they seemed injured,
so I ended up giving them a ride.
But they asked me
to let them off on the way so I did.
Report it to the higher-ups.
How can I report something like that?
I would have to explain why you were there
and who leaked the information.
I went to get jewelry done
and I needed Ms. Jang.
That's why you looked into it for me.
Is that so difficult?
It's a trivial matter
but I'm suggesting we cover it up
because you seem uncomfortable about it.
It's not as simple as it sounds.
I may have been able
to take care of the footage,
but this isn't as simple as
asking me to find
the person who suggested the ghostwriter.
Team A is deeply involved in this case.
That has nothing to do with me.
Since when were you doing me a favor?
It was all for your benefit.
I'm telling you to cover this up
for your benefit as well. And…
make this the last time you call me first.
I understand.
I just can't wrap my head around it.
Just what exactly is happening
that you're making all this fuss?
Ms. Hyesoo.
The helicopter is here.
I won't be needing it.
I'm staying here for the time being.
What?
The satellite phone disappeared?
It was Mr. Kim's doing.
-Mr. Kim?
-I'm sure of it.
He was suspicious from the start,
saying he was a fan
and trying to get friendly with you.
Are you sure? Why would he do that?
I checked the serial number.
The SIH sent me here undercover.
(scoffs)
They can do exactly the same.
Calm down, Mr. Choi.
I'll try to talk to him.
What will you do?
Give him your autograph
and ask if he's undercover?
The briefcase is locked
with the infiltration team's PIN code,
so he won't know what's in it for now.
But he will find the satellite phone soon.
And he will figure out
whom I've been communicating with.
We have to be careful.
If it wasn't Mr. Kim,
the situation will worsen.
AGENT PARK: Mr. Choi, someone
from the head office is here.
He's entering the parking lot.
(Mr. Choi sighs)
Why would someone suddenly come
from the head office?
Mr. Kim received a call earlier.
Did he not report it to you?
Okay.
You still don't think it's him?
How exactly do you want to be careful?
What will you do?
I'll risk bloodshed if I must.
There's no time to waste!
Mr. Choi.
Meet the visitor first.
I'll look for Mr. Kim.
We must stop the two
from meeting each other.
(sighs)
(door opens, closes)
MR. CHOI: Go to the west section.
He must be patrolling the area.
(Mr. Choi grunts)
(breathing heavily)
HAESONG
VISITORS LOG
You must sign the log
before entering the building.
Mr. Choi, everything seems fine.
What exactly is broken?
Where is the briefcase?
Excuse me?
Section Seven.
Oh, the thing is…
(grunts)
Mr. Choi, why are you doing this?
Where is the briefcase?
(panting)
MR. CHOI: Tell me the truth.
Well…
I know you were there.
You took it!
-No, I--
-I checked it all, you bastard.
(choking)
Where is the briefcase?
Say it, you punk.
(choking, gasps)
(coughing)
(groans)
(panting)
(coughing, groans)
Come clean if you want to spare yourself.
I…
I really didn't take it.
I just saw it there.
What?
I got curious
about why you went there often
and tried to check the place out.
But I left it there.
I didn't even touch it.
(sighs)
Wait a second.
If it wasn't you…
Mr. Choi!
Mr. Kim?
Don't make a fuss. He just passed out.
Did he admit it?
He wouldn't admit it this easily.
What if it wasn't him?
Then who did the guy from the head office
come to visit?
Okay. Please come this way.
NAME: JANG EUIDON
PURPOSE OF VISIT: MEETING WITH MS. KWON
MS. KWON: You came on time.
How have you been, Ms. Kwon?
I've been all right.
Is the work bearable?
EUIDON: Yes, thanks to you.
About the invitations for the ceremony,
I think they should be delivered
in person to meet the formality.
I called you in to help out.
Oh, did you do what I instructed?
Yes, I have it ready.
So you need to figure out
why that man is here.
Let me make this clear.
My team has put years of effort
into this operation.
I can't let it go to waste
because of this rat.
If your guess turns out to be right,
it will ruin
more than just the SIH's plan.
Hurry and meet the guy
from the head office first.
Mr. Kim?
Are you looking for this?
Mr. Park.
What are you doing here, Mr. Ha?
Are you in league with each other?
(door slams, lock clicks)
What is going on, Mr. Choi?
What about you?
Why do you have that briefcase?
Oh, I wondered whose this was.
Give it to me.
You need to tell me what's going on first.
-You little…
-Mr. Choi.
Opium.
Opium?
That's what's in it.
(Woosin sighs)
We're trying to sneak away
those poppies in the garden.
Do you want to join us?
In exchange for my silence?
It won't be a losing deal for you.
It's quite tempting, I must say.
So, you two are like business partners.
What about him though?
Why did you beat him up?
It was my mistake.
The briefcase had disappeared,
and I thought Mr. Kim took it
so he could have it all to himself.
I gave him a beating.
-I see.
-So, are you in?
This will get you a hefty sum.
Fine.
Now let's open it and check.
What's with this mood? I knew it.
Opium was a lie, wasn't it?
(briefcase clanks)
Just what is in this briefcase?
-Give it to me.
-Oh.
You might even kill me if I don't.
Mr. Choi.
You people are
with the SIH, aren't you?
(heavy sigh)
What a life he has.
Did you ask for me?
What happened to Ms. Jang.
Was it your doing?
Yes, sir.
It seemed she spread word
about the Adamas, so for security…
I see.
I understand,
but you should've at least
reported it to me afterward.
Did you have to make me summon you?
I apologize, sir. It's my mistake.
What else is there?
Pardon?
Is there anything else
you didn't let me know?
There's nothing else.
Junkyung.
Yes, sir.
KWON:
We've known each other for a long time.
I wasn't always so fond of you.
At times, I thought of casting you away,
but when the Adamas was stolen,
you managed to retrieve it.
I've been easy on you for that.
But how long
do you think that'll last?
(nervous chuckle)
Sir, I'm not quite following you--
I know you met Lee Changwoo.
You shouldn't have come here
to meet me today.
CHANGWOO: Do you think
Chairman Kwon has forgotten about me?
Yes, I met him.
I wanted to figure out
how the SIH ended up getting involved
with Song Suhyeon.
I met him to check if the SIH
had made contact with him.
I didn't report it to you
because I didn't find any trace.
That's all, sir.
TEAM LEADER LEE: If I dodge, I'll be dead.
This is bait.
Mr. Choi.
Who are you? What's your identity?
The SIH.
What?
I'm with the SIH too!
(Agent Park panting)
(grunts, panting)
I got some nice dried persimmons.
You can have a taste of them.
Thank you, sir.
Maybe I got the wrong fishing spot.
It's not going so well.
Nothing's biting here.
(bird squawking)
Don't try to pull a trick.
The infiltration teams
don't know each other.
Did you think you were undercover alone?
I also thought this was a solo mission.
Prove it then. Open this briefcase.
You'd know the PIN code
if you're on the infiltration team.
(grunts, panting)
(Agent Park sighs)
(lock clicks)
(sighs)
Nice job fooling me
all this time, you bastard.
You should've told me.
I almost killed you for real.
Whatever. Just tell me what you'll do now.
-What?
-Him.
What will you do about Mr. Kim?
You know the infiltration team's protocol
for when your cover is blown.
There's no need to kill him.
AGENT PARK: What are you saying?
MR. CHOI:
He doesn't even know what's in here.
We'll just say
that it's opium.
What if he doesn't buy it?
Are you suggesting
we gamble with our lives? How generous.
AGENT PARK:
If things go south, it won't be just us.
The organization itself
could be in danger!
Then what? Are you saying
we should kill him for real?
Of course. We must.
Are you really from the SIH?
You little…
Should I do it?
I'll do it.
(scoffs)
Once he wakes up,
he won't remember anything.
WOOSIN: There's no need to kill him.
Maybe the SIH kills off the innocent
as if it's no big deal,
but I'm not one of you.
I won't just sit back and watch it happen.
What is this now?
You're not from the SIH?
It's a long story.
He's cooperating with our operation.
(scoffs)
Jeez, I can't get used to this.
A civilian is involved
in the SIH's operation,
and you people are all talk. What a mess!
AGENT PARK:
Whatever. Leave this place, both of you.
I'll take care of the situation.
AGENT KIM: Mr. Ha.
What is going on?
(heavy sigh)
-Move.
-I won't.
Move.
No.
(groans)
What are you up to now?
You never stay at my house for no reason.
It's because of the chairman.
He's looking forward to a grandchild
so I have to at least
make him think that we're trying.
Put up with me just until the ceremony.
It's not like I like being here either.
As expected.
You really are the lady of the house.
The more I look at you,
the more you resemble my father.
You're both cold, cruel,
and impossible to read.
Right.
And you both dearly loved Minjo.
Dearly loved Minjo?
The chairman did?
Then I wonder why he did that.
What are you talking about?
The helicopter accident.
What about that?
I wonder why he spared
the people who were involved
in the accident.
When they were responsible
for the death of his dearly beloved son.
So?
What are you getting at?
What am I getting at?
What I'm saying is that…
the chairman…
never really loved Minjo.
You're right.
Gosh, I like what you're getting at.
HYESOO: Thank you, Mr. Jeong.
No problem. I can do this much
of an errand for you.
It took me quite a lot of effort
because there weren't many materials.
Haesong took control of the situation,
so a lot of people
still don't know about his death.
ARES HELICOPTER CRASH
DATE OF ACCIDENT: APRIL 1, 2017
How did this happen?
HYESOO: Everyone related to the accident…
Yes, they were only briefly investigated
and there was no real punishment.
If it really was an accident,
he wouldn't have kept them alive.
(phone ringing)
Hello, this is Haesongwon.
DATE: 7 P.M., APRIL 23, 2022
LOCATION: BANQUET HALL IN HAESONGWON
WE'RE PLEASED TO INVITE YOU
TO THE 80TH FOUNDING ANNIVERSARY CEREMONY
SONG
Right, the writer's real surname is Song.
Ms. Kwon.
What's with that face?
Did someone die or something?
Did you know?
What are you talking about?
Mr. Kim
is dead.
What?
Unbelievable!
It was acute drug intoxication.
It seems he stole some poppies
from the garden.
Right before the ceremony? How dare he!
How do you want me to handle this?
Isn't it obvious? Cover it up!
DEATH CERTIFICATE
Thank you.
AGENT PARK:
As expected, Ms. Kwon wants it buried.
Since the poppies were
from the Haesongwon garden.
Mr. Choi.
What happened to Mr. Kim
will remain a secret between us.
(groans)
(grunting)
MR. CHOI: Stop it, you crazy bastard.
Are you really going to kill
an innocent person?
AGENT PARK:
Stop messing around. Let go of me.
I said let go of me, damn it!
Are you going to ignore protocol?
We have to kill him!
(rain pattering)
The external cause of the accident
is the poor safety management of bombs.
But it's still under police investigation.
No evidence remains.
I ordered our men to analyze
the CCTV camera footage nearby,
but we got nothing from it.
Team A probably utilized
the clear-out team.
Close the underpass to the safe house,
and have the vigilance team stand by.
-Yes, sir.
Do you think Ms. Kim is okay?
If they'd killed her,
they would've sent her body to us.
We've done all we can.
Right.
Now let's wait for their move.
The trial run was successful.
It will have enough power to kill
in actual warfare.
What do you think of it?
(scoffs)
Now you're trying to interview me?
Hey, did you make me come over
just so I could watch some show?
Did the heat get to you?
Sir.
It better be something serious,
or I'll be pissed.
Song Suhyeon is alive.
What do you think you're doing?
I ordered you
to take care of Song Suhyeon,
and you said he was taken care of.
So he shouldn't be alive, should he?
No.
(sighs)
And?
Getting rid of Song Suhyeon
won't solve the situation.
We must stack the deck
and eliminate everyone including the SIH.
Please take a look at the scenario first.
"H-File?"
H-FILE
(Hyunjo sighs)
If it's not good,
I'll smash your head first.
A terrorist bombing?
D-day is that day.
Wow, you are a lunatic.
Will you be able to smooth it over?
After the upcoming presidential election,
Haesong will take full control anyway.
We'll manipulate the media a little
and investigate it after seizing power.
And to eliminate the opponents
at the same time,
you will accuse them
of pulling the strings?
A thorough housecleaning.
That's right. We'll say they are
a radical terrorist group
who is unhappy with the regime change
and plans to take over the new government.
That will create a scare.
If we take this mood
all the way to legalizing firearms…
That'd be a blockbuster.
(book thuds)
Look at you.
-Mr. Lee.
-Yes, sir.
You brought it to me
because my father wouldn't allow it, no?
-I apologize.
-You fool.
So who's going to take the bullet?
Kim Seohee.
(distant screaming)
CHIEF JEONG: Hey.
Hey!
Take it easy, or at least gag her.
Why? I like hearing it.
You crazy witch.
Hey, Jeong.
"Hey, Jeong"?
Show some respect,
or you'll be taught a lesson.
Mr. Lee went to meet Mr. Kwon.
With Mr. Cha.
Between me and you,
who will be taught a lesson first?
That trap of yours
will end up ruining your life.
I guarantee it.
(thumps, clatters)
-(clinks)
-(grunts)
(groans, panting)
Stop it.
I don't know anything about the SIH.
You don't?
No.
Listen carefully. This is important.
We're going to blow up the SIH with bombs.
You can do it, right?
What?
You're going to carry the bombs.
I won't do it.
(scoffs, chuckles)
Want to make a bet?
HYUKPIL: Reporter Kim Seohee…
They must've taken her alive for a reason.
They're up to something.
Should we set up a task force?
No, let's stick to our plan.
The ceremony is coming up soon.
Yes, sir.
Our objective is as follows.
Before the Adamas is moved
to the ceremony hall…
SUHYEON: You took three days
just to come to that conclusion?
That you can't find Kim Seohee
unless they make a move?
Is that why
you're sitting back and waiting?
You should locate Mr. Lee.
You should've raided
Haesong's main office!
Our operation takes place today.
We must secure the Adamas.
Mr. Ha will be arrested red-handed.
While everyone's watching,
so that Chairman Kwon can't do anything.
The Adamas will become evidence.
Once we reveal that it was used
for the murder,
an arrest warrant will be issued.
Mr. Ha agreed to this.
What about Kim Seohee? Did she agree?
That you should catch Chairman Kwon
whether she ends up dying or not?
What about Ms. Lee? What about Mr. Baek?
Hey, Song.
I'm not asking for your approval here.
I'm warning you not to cause a mess
by meddling in our operation, you bastard.
The sense of justice you seek.
The sense of revenge.
That's not enough to catch Kwon Jaekyu.
Okay.
Fine.
Let's go our separate ways.
You don't care about saving people.
And I refuse to risk my life
for your ridiculous plan.
You have no more reason to keep me anyway.
(rubber squeaks)
Damn it.
WOMAN: Hello, sir.
Who?
Designer Patti Jang?
Her suicide case
and the other cases I mentioned just now.
Gather all the materials for me.
I'm on my way to work. Bye.
(Suhyeon grunts)
DEAR MR. SONG SUHYEON
WE'RE PLEASED TO INVITE YOU
TO THE 80TH FOUNDING ANNIVERSARY CEREMONY
Thank you. You may enter.
Welcome, Candidate Noh.
Long time no see, Ms. Kwon.
You didn't come
to my presidential candidacy ceremony.
Right, it's been a while.
But I'm always acquainted with your news.
You've been receiving
the highest approvals rating.
Thanks to you.
(laughs)
But Candidate Hwang
is chasing right behind me.
That makes me feel bad.
I wonder if he's got
the chairman's support.
Of course not.
If that were the case,
Hwang would be here.
Don't worry, and please come inside.
MR. NOH: Sure.
You even invited the press.
Is it going to be okay, ma'am?
Yes, we should spread the news
far and wide.
A happy occasion like this
won't come again.
DONGRIM: Mr. Ha, did you see? Those from
broadcasting stations are here too.
What an honor.
The sight of me getting arrested
will be broadcast nationally.
And thanks to it, Haesong won't
have a reason to oppose
even if the Adamas gets taken as evidence.
You're right about that,
but is it really going to be okay?
Yes, I told you so.
I'm talking about myself.
Will I be able to pull it off?
Just be your normal self.
It may seem easy,
but tripping naturally isn't…
It's not easy. Jeez, it hurts.
Yet you pull it off every day.
I know you can do it.
Dongrim.
I'm sorry I dragged you into this.
This is why I tell you all the time
that there's no pupil like me.
We're like salt and pepper.
(classical music)
-MAN: Oh, congratulations.
-WOMAN: Congratulations.
MY PATH
(paper rustles)
Excuse me.
My Path.
HYUNJO: Isn't it old-fashioned?
To put it nicely, it's classic.
Are you the ghostwriter?
Yes, I'm Ha Woosin.
Who are you?
Do you not know me?
Are you someone I should know?
Well…
(laughs)
You two have met.
HYESOO: Let me introduce you.
-This is--
-I'm her husband.
Oh, you are President Kwon Hyunjo.
WOOSIN: I've heard a lot about you.
Really?
I wonder what you have heard.
The facts.
He interviewed me for the memoir.
I see.
I know we've never met before,
but you look so familiar.
Really? I don't have
a typical face though.
Ah.
I didn't expect to see you here.
Gratefully enough,
the chairman invited me.
I see, my father invited you.
He went overboard. You must feel uneasy
to join an occasion like this.
Not at all. I was born
to enjoy this kind of occasion.
Really?
You don't look like the type
who'd snoop around a party.
(Hyunjo chuckles)
Candidate Noh has been
looking for you outside the hall.
(sighs)
Excuse me then.
I guess he didn't think the chairman
would invite me, considering his reaction.
He must feel neglected.
Or maybe he feels jealous.
-Of me?
-Oh, right.
I found out
whom you're working with.
Pardon?
The Special Investigations Headquarters.
(screaming)
Get out. Now.
-Ms. Eun.
-Don't show me that face.
I may be
able to offer some help.
Don't change the subject,
and say what you want to say.
Kim Seohee.
You know
that reporter, right? The witness.
What on earth
is this about?
SPECIAL INVESTIGATIONS HEADQUARTERS
(closing theme music)
MS. KWON: Now, we will reveal the Adamas.
SUN: You're going to carry the bomb.
We have quite the history between us.
MR. HAN: We found Ms. Kim.
They made a move.
SEOHEE: Team A didn't send me
simply to take revenge.
The detonator is in my hands.
Call the police.
WOOSIN: Since when did you know
that I was stealing the Adamas?
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs