ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
Mr. Lee.
I am your defense attorney.
I have one twisted fate.
I became a prosecutor to prevent
any more victims like my father.
But now, I'm about to defend
my father's killer.
- I refuse your help.
- You don't have the right to do that.
I know you were falsely accused,
and I'll help you clear your name.
But to do that,
you need to tell me the truth.
Once we face the truth,
we won't be able to go back.
We've come too far to go back.
Right?
I'm going to make sure
that everyone knows you're innocent.
Why are you doing this
when I didn't even ask for it?
I refused to acknowledge...
that my biological father
killed my father, Song Soonho.
- How...
- Did I know?
That you were my real father?
I'm not interested in that.
Tell me something that intrigues me.
For example, who killed him?
They say the truth lies in the past.
So let's dig into that past.
You haven't changed...
at all.
- Run!
- Hey!
You darn scumbags!
Gosh, those... Darn it.
Hey, you're with them, right?
- Who are they?
- Let me go.
Why should I? I know you're with them.
You should be apologizing to me.
- What's wrong with you?
- Don't play dumb.
- I'm not with them.
- How are you so brazen?
You saw me?
Yes, I did.
But I couldn't recognize you.
I only realized it was you
after I saw your mother.
- Let me go. It wasn't me.
- Say that you're sorry!
- You little scumbag.
- Calm down.
Suhyeon, are you okay?
Hey, lady. Educate your son properly.
He's already stealing
other people's belongings.
Who? Him?
That's not true, Mom.
I was only looking at it.
Don't you dare lie.
I know they're your friends!
Come on! They're not my friends!
I don't want to hear it. I know
you've been looking at that every day.
And today, you were going to steal it.
- Do as you please.
- What?
- Call the cops if you want.
- Suhyeon!
- That little...
- I'm sorry, ma'am.
What is he going to become
when he grows up?
Unbelievable. Kids like him
will only end up stealing things.
- Jeez.
- What did you say?
Excuse me. What did you just say?
- What?
- He said he didn't do it.
Why do you keep accusing him
when he said he was innocent?
Look at you.
The least you could do is apologize.
- Kneel. Kneel instead.
- What did you say?
You should apologize
for your son's wrongdoing!
Your son did something wrong.
So how dare you act so shamelessly?
How dare you when your son stole from me?
Do you think... Who are you?
- That's enough.
- What do you...
That's enough.
I...
Fine, I'll stop.
Jeez.
Consider yourself lucky. Gosh.
Thank you.
Aren't you...
Hey...
Why are you here?
- Youngsin.
- Don't call my name.
We broke up long ago.
I followed you here to tell you that.
Leave. I have nothing more to say.
That boy...
It's him, right?
No.
He has nothing to do with you.
I'm sorry.
I only did that back then to protect you.
Protect me?
From whom?
Who in the world are they?
It's all a lie.
I had no idea
what you did for a living
until I saw you on the news.
They said you were a thief,
and everything just made perfect sense.
I see.
"So that's why he said
he didn't have any friends or family."
He was only trying to hide the fact
"that he was nothing but a thief."
So why did you come here now?
I didn't have any other intentions.
I just wanted to watch you from afar
and see how you were doing.
No.
You don't need to do that.
Just consider us dead.
I don't want my son to know
that his father is a thief.
Don't you ever come here again.
Honey.
Excuse me.
MOVING SERVICE
Didn't you call a mover?
Oh.
Gosh.
Twins?
Suhyeon is the older one.
Woosin is the younger one.
You look like a happy family.
That's when I learned that you were twins.
I've never met your brother, Woosin,
but I'm sure you two look very alike.
Gosh, you really look like a prosecutor.
Really? So it's a success.
SONG SUHYEON
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
Woosin, I need youto pretend
to be me and meet someone.
Hello, ma'am.
I'd like to use
this room for the time being.
Are you feeling ill?
Director Eun didn't mention anything.
Please don't tell my father.
A VIP is going to use this room.
Yes, ma'am.
May I ask who's coming?
I'm sorry, ma'am. I'll get the room ready.
- Sir.
- Yes?
Please be discreet.
This is related to Haesong.
Yes, ma'am.
This is the twelve o'clock news.
Tomorrow is the election.
Due to the weekend, however,
we predict many individualswill
be going on a trip.
Worried about the low turnout,
the partiesare encouraging people to vote.
Let's put aside our sentiments
and only look at the facts.
In short, after you saw
how happy our family was,
you were planning to leave
like a true man would.
So you decided to move,
and it just so happened
that my father was the mover.
In that case,
how in the world did my father
fall victim to murder?
Mr. Lee.
It was all
due to my greed.
I thought my disappearing
would fix everything.
But then I had to face
the wretched reality.
I felt bad that your family
was struggling to make ends meet.
And it broke my heart...
that I couldn't help either.
You again?
It must pain you to be abandoned.
You never drink.
Leave...
before I kill you.
Sir.
Don't you think this situation is unfair?
You were used.
You should take your revenge
on the damn bastards.
That diamond arrow is 300 carats.
The price
is much higher than what you can fathom.
I'll give you half of the share.
Take that and flee to the Philippines.
Even Haesong won't be able to find you.
They have over 7,000 islands.
You know that.
The unveiling is around the corner.
They'll move it to the venue
the night before.
I'll take care of security.
You can sneak in during a shift change.
I have the floor plan for the safe too.
Sir, you should start afresh.
I promise that your future will be rosy.
So tell me.
When's the date?
Thank you.
So?
Why did my father have to die
because of your scheme?
That was tasty.
Let's begin now that you're done.
All right.
After being kidnapped,
they put that explosive vest on you
and sent you to the SIH?
Who kidnapped you?
Where should I begin?
I'll start from the very beginning.
So everything happened
due to an incident from 22 years ago.
Hold on. Twenty-two years ago?
- Correct.
- So in 2000?
That's right. The summer of 2000.
How old were you back then?
Seven.
By the way,
you keep cutting me off.
You don't want my statement?
- What are you talking...
- Detective Nam.
Did you see that?
He kept interrupting me from testifying.
I'm going to get a copy of this.
VIDEO FROM HAESONG CEREMONY
UPLOADING
THE PAGE YOU ARE LOOKING FOR
CANNOT BE FOUND
I think Haesong has made a move.
Probably.
I was prepared for this.
Contact the media.
But sir. There's no point
if they won't publish it.
Call them to the SIH.
Tell them it's an important announcement.
Which is...
Tell them it's about the suicide bombing.
- A press conference?
- Yes.
Mr. Ha told me.
Unbelievable. Ha Woosin?
He came by yesterday on the pretext
of meeting with the chairman.
They must've sent him
because he's their only way in.
We need to be cautious for the time being.
I was also told
to lie low.
Mr. Kang has no choice now.
He'll reveal all of his cards
and take the bull by the horns.
The SIH will be exposed.
They'll reveal what the SIH did
and why they were after Haesong.
- Are you saying...
- My task here is over.
We'll end the secret investigation
and do an open investigation.
It'll be an all-out war.
We'll take a big hit.
We have no time.
We need to make a move
before the VIP steps down.
Jeez. What's that?
What?
There are people watching.
- Get going then.
- All right.
Take better care of yourself.
You look haggard.
You look even scarier.
Be safe, okay?
Got it.
- Hey, let's go.
- Yes, sir.
Mr. Choi, we have an emergency.
Hello, sir.
You need to come with me.
Where are we going all of a sudden, sir?
Fishing.
I'm sorry, sir,
but I'm terrible at fishing.
It's simple.
You just need to determine
when to reel it in.
You throw the bait and wait endlessly.
Yes, sir.
Has it been three years
since you came to Haesongwon?
How about working directly under me now?
I'll do my utmost
if you just give me the chance, sir.
Chance?
Chance.
Hmm...
Where's Mr. Jeong?
He's inside, sir.
Let's go.
Junkyung.
Did you propose
stealing the Adamas to Lee Changwoo?
Why?
How would I dare
to do something like that, sir?
No, sir. You're mistaken.
This is a misunderstanding.
All I wanted to do was retrieve
the Adamas that he had stolen.
Sir.
You bastard. Have you gone insane?
Stop yapping and be quiet.
You're going to die soon anyway.
Damn it.
You little bastard.
Sir!
I did propose stealing the Adamas to him!
That's right.
I did say that.
I said that
because I was blinded by greed.
And I've been regretting it
for the past 22 years.
Sir, please spare me this once.
I do want to spare you.
But you should tell me the truth first.
Yes, sir.
I'll tell you nothing but the truth.
I had gone to Lee Changwoo's place
to find the Adamas.
Sir.
The door was open.
Sir?
Mr. Kim, I'm here.
The chairman will call you. Hurry.
You need to find the Adamas first.
Yes, sir.
Damn it.
What? You're not Lee Changwoo.
No wonder. Damn.
I'm screwed.
Yes, sir.
I got it.
I'm on my way.
I saw him.
His sleeves were drenched in blood.
It was him.
He was the one who kidnapped
and put the explosive vest on me.
Did you see his face clearly?
And you still remember him?
Exactly.
I just can't forget his face.
Dad.
Yes? What is it?
He was drenched in blood.
What? Blood?
Yes. I saw it.
Where? Where is he?
Over there!
Hey! Stop!
Stay still. Damn it.
It was all his doing.
He knew I'd be coming,
so he placed the fake Adamas there.
So you retrieved the fake Adamas
that he had put there?
Yes, sir.
I just wanted to return the Adamas to you
and put an end to everything.
But there was a witness.
Are you the one who called?
Could you please explain what happened?
Someone drenched in blood...
- Drenched in blood?
- Yes.
Damn it. Everything is screwed up.
Chairman Kwon
didn't know that it was fake.
That's why you made a false confession?
Because that was the safest bet.
Had Chairman Kwon known the truth,
he would've come after you two.
Just like now.
I truly had no idea that it was fake, sir.
You didn't?
- No, sir. I don't know anything.
- Junkyung.
I swear. I don't know anything, sir!
- You don't?
- No, sir.
Lee Changwoo. That jerk knows everything.
I'm certain. Please believe me.
I do.
I do believe you.
Thank you, sir.
I don't think you know anything.
But what a pity.
I would've spared you...
had you known something.
- Pardon?
- What's the point of sparing you
when you don't even know
where the real Adamas is?
Mr. Choi.
Yes, sir.
This is your chance.
Sir!
Sir! Please spare me!
Damn it!
Sir!
Congrats.
You get to take the team leader down.
It's quite a feat.
It wasn't me!
It wasn't me! Sir!
You bastard!
Damn it.
What are you guys doing?
You're whispering in front of me?
So this is what you're saying.
You witnessed a murder 22 years ago.
Correct.
And the culprit kidnapped you?
- Correct.
- And made you wear that explosive vest?
Correct.
What does that have to do with Haesong?
Because that man works for Haesong.
I see.
Don't tell me that the man you saw
was Chairman Kwon Jaekyu.
Detective.
Are you even willing to investigate this?
Ms. Kim, we have two hypotheses
about the terror bombing.
The culprit of that murder you witnessed
was Lee Changwoo.
He was falsely accused.
He wasn't the one I saw.
Are you just saying that
because of Song Suhyeon?
Because Lee Changwoo
is his biological father?
- What?
- Was this all Song Suhyeon's idea?
Did he want to involve Haesong?
Right. Coincidentally, he even appeared
at the terror bombing scene.
Was it truly a coincidence,
or was it planned?
What a load of bull.
As if we'd make such a plan.
So no? Then here's the second hypothesis.
Who is Hwang Byungchul?
He is the biggest opponent
of the current president.
And Kang Hyukpil
is a close associate of the president.
We've confirmed that Kang
warned Candidate Hwang about the bombing
and told him to evacuate.
And the latter rushed toward his car.
But the bomb was in the car.
That means Kang was the one
who lured Hwang to his vehicle.
Don't be unreasonable.
Ms. Kim.
This is what we're curious about.
We're not interested in a murder
witnessed by a little girl 22 years ago,
but in the mastermind
behind the terror bombing.
Was it Prosecutor Song
or Mr. Kang?
What a bunch of lunatics.
Are you serious?
- Let's go.
- Sir.
What if Haesong claims that
we accused them before checking our facts?
Then I'll take the fall.
KOREAN SPECIAL INVESTIGATIONS HEADQUARTERS
I heard the SIH was making
an important announcement, so I came.
I'm personally interested
in what it may be.
Right. To make it easier for you,
I've already handed out
the press release to the journalists.
I heard there's a connection
between the cabin explosion in Mount Goduk
and the terror bombing
that occurred recently.
I heard the two explosives...
were similar.
Would you like to talk in private?
Or should I continue?
Ms. Kwon sure isn't photogenic.
It's the SIH's doing, isn't it?
You're so predictable. How tacky.
Mr. Kang Hyukpil.
How do you think the public will react
once they find out
that the explosives came from the SIH?
How will you prove that it was us?
Our infiltration team
doesn't exist on paper.
Your men who died in that cabin
may be disguised
as innocent victims for now.
But how long do you think it'll take
for us to frame them
as being heinous terrorists?
Then do that.
Well, aren't you a tough guy.
I'm so intimidated.
I'm not ignorantly
threatening to eliminate the SIH.
Let's settle this politically.
Discreetly disband your infiltration team.
That's not up to me to decide.
I'm aware of that. Of course I am.
I know you're nothing but a mere puppet.
You're just...
a chess piece.
Take it.
BAEK MINSEOK
Will you reject the president's call?
Don't act like you're strangers.
I know you talk to each other every day.
Hello, sir.
Understood, sir.
Do you finally get it?
It's the president's call.
Resign from your position.
Use this to buy yourself...
ONE BILLION WON
a decent suit.
As for the reason for your resignation,
we'll come up with a valid one.
You should be thankful
that it's ending with only you resigning.
You should know that.
Okay. Let me in on it.
What will happen to Ms. Kwon?
I don't know.
Come on. You're the only one who knows
how the chairman truly feels.
Wait. Come on, now.
Once she's fired,
I'll become the head butler.
So of course I should be aware
of everything under this roof.
Ms. Yoon.
Watch the news. It'll come out soon.
The news?
How long do you think
they'll keep her alive?
Are you okay?
Bring me the key.
I made a mistake, didn't I?
- Pardon?
- About Mr. Lee.
Is it bothering you, sir?
I should've fed him dinner.
I should've killed him
when he was on a full stomach.
I'll bring out your meal
once Mr. Kwon arrives.
No, I want it now.
I can't stomach anything
if he's in front of me.
Yes, ma'am.
MR. JEONG
WE GOT HER
Where are you taking me?
I was told to escort you to the VIP room.
All right. This is the final question.
Where is the real Adamas?
Mr. Lee.
You wouldn't hand over the goods
without getting paid first.
I have nothing more to say.
Where did you stash it?
Get home safe. It was nice meeting you.
Chairman Kwon won't let you off the hook.
You don't know him that well.
He never kills anyone
he needs something from.
I'm living proof of that.
What about Woosin and me?
I know Chairman Kwon.
As soon as he gets his hands
on the real Adamas,
he will...
kill us all.
You're so stubborn.
So you're the one I take after.
Fine.
I hope today...
isn't the last day
I see you alive.
See you again.
Take a seat.
Are you going to just stand there?
I don't have much to say.
But you must want to chat.
Don't look at me like that.
You were planning on killing me
from the beginning.
After that, you were going
to hand over the fake Adamas
to Chairman Kwon.
You needed to buy time
before fleeing the country.
Even if he found out,
you could've just put the blame
on me.
I wouldn't have been able to defend myself
since I'd be dead and long gone.
However,
I'm still alive and well.
And the Adamas is gone.
A piece of advice for my dear junior.
You won't last in Team A for long
if you keep this up.
That's why I'm here.
To retrieve the Adamas and to kill you.
If you don't tell me where it is,
- that seat will be your deathbed.
- And then?
How will you find the Adamas?
You're right.
Fine, then.
If that's what you want,
then I'll grant you your wish.
Have fun rotting in jail.
Whether it be 10 or 20 years,
you'll never be released
unless you tell me where it is.
Let's see how long you'll hold out,
my dear senior.
Keep this in mind.
I will never
go down alone.
I won't be lonely after I die...
since I'll have you by my side.
Let's go.
So you're a prosecutor?
Hold on, please.
YOU BETTER PUT ON A GOOD ACT
I JUST MET IM DUKSOO
Mr. Im Duksoo.
I'm Prosecutor Song Suhyeon.
Sure.
What do you want?
I'm here
regarding the Kangchun Penitentiary
Massacre that you committed.
I read your statement thoroughly
and listened to your deposition.
- But?
- I'm confused about a few things.
I'd appreciate your cooperation.
Which parts are you confused about?
I believe I gave a detailed statement.
That is exactly what I find odd.
- What?
- This is my take on it.
You were providing detailed information,
not just a statement.
As if you were directing
the investigation.
You're really pushing my buttons.
Is this what I get for cooperating?
Do I look like I'm lying to you?
This is unexpected.
What is?
Anyone with a strong sense
of self-assurance like you
wouldn't care what others think.
You wouldn't try to persuade me like this.
Your statements on your previous crimes
were very meticulous and precise.
You only stated the facts.
So why is this statement different?
Both your statement
and the deposition say the same things.
"I'm telling the truth."
"Please trust me."
It's as if you're pleading.
What are you going on about?
Let's keep this short.
Questions.
Sure.
What was your motive for the crime?
As a death-row inmate, killing a few more
wouldn't change anything.
There was something unusual
about one of your victims.
The one with the slit throat.
That annoying bastard.
The autopsy report said
that it was done postmortem.
To just him.
Why?
I told you. He annoyed me.
He was always bragging
about how well-off he was.
It irritated the living hell out of me.
Not because you needed
to make sure he was dead?
He was the financial advisor
of an investment company.
A subsidiary of Haesong.
He was the target, wasn't he?
What are you talking about?
Simply put,
did Haesong order the hit?
I believe your son took the reward.
You crazy, little...
He made a hefty sum from shares
in a matter of hours.
What I'm trying to say is that I know
what you know.
Hey.
You're making a mistake right now.
I know.
They'll be informed of our meeting
and what we talked about.
They'll probably kill you.
I'm not too desperate
about getting out of here alive anyway.
Well, how about your son?
The Kangchun Penitentiary case.
Suhyeon was right.
SUHYEON
- Yes?
- How did it go?
Haesong is definitely involved.
There's more to this than
Haesongsimply supporting Hwang's pledge
regarding the death penalty.
The victim was too involved with Haesong.
Haesong doesn't have coincidences.
How did you find out about this?
A prosecutor named Han
was in charge of the Kangchun case.
I used him to get into ARES.
Come on. Of course I know.
How could Haesong have anything
to do with that heinous crime?
He was trying to show
his loyalty to Haesong.
But he was demoted instead.
He should've just feigned ignorance.
So I was looking into that...
Woosin.
What is it?
Let's talk again later.
Suhyeon.
Who are you?
Sun.
Die.
Die!
It's you who will die.
But not today.
Shut up.
Did the Adamas have traces
of Song Soonho's blood
or didn't it?
You little...
NATIONAL FORENSIC SERVICE
BLOOD ANALYSIS ON NEXT PAGE
BLOOD ANALYSIS RESULT
NO BLOOD ON THE ARROWHEAD OR THE SHAFT
Your dad's blood wasn't on it.
I heard the chairman gave you two days
to find the real Adamas.
You have one day left.
See you tomorrow.
Do you think I'll let you go?
Where did you get the audacity
to come here alone?
He said not today.
Wait one more day,
and I'll kill you.
What's wrong?
Too scared to kill me right now?
Do you have time for this?
You should go to Kim Seohee.
What did you say?
The interrogation is over.
We've confirmed that you were kidnapped,
and we've found a key suspect
who's responsible for the terror bombing.
A key suspect? Who?
That's confidential
since we're still investigating.
Do you expect me to believe that?
You should just go while we let you.
What about Mr. Lee Changwoo's case?
That doesn't fall within our jurisdiction.
Wait.
I'm Prosecutor Song from the SIH.
- Prosecutor Song.
- Let's go.
What was that?
BREAKING NEWS
KANG HYUKPIL OF THE SIH RESIGNS
Let's go.
Thanks.
Thank the person who saved you, not me.
You're late.
I was busy.
What do you want?
Why were you at the studio apartment?
Oh, that?
"Oh, that?"
I doubt you thought I wouldn't know.
What's up your sleeve?
For the Adamas. I want to find it.
What are you doing?
Why would you do that?
Because I want it.
Hyesoo.
Do you even know what you're saying?
You want the Adamas?
Not the Adamas, but Haesong.
I'm considering
becoming Haesong's successor.
I don't see a reason why I can't.
You're adorable.
I see. This must be why
Minjo loved you so dearly.
Keep yapping.
In the end,
I'll take everything away from you.
Whether it be Haesong or the Adamas,
you won't get any of Minjo's things.
Is that so? Then good luck with that.
But you know what? You should hurry.
Because I'll be getting my hands
on the Adamas today.
Today?
Today.
MINISTRY OF JUSTICE
Where are we going?
TO WOOSIN
I'M AT THE SIH. WHERE ARE YOU?
What's going on? Are they packing up?
Things don't look good here.
- What are you doing?
- Can't you see?
Exactly. Why are you packing up?
The infiltration team was disbanded today.
Disbanded?
It's the higher-up's order.
Higher-up? President Baek?
So? You're just going
to let go of everything?
Are you serious?
I lost. I've been defeated.
Why the sudden change of heart?
Are you trying to save yourself now?
I wouldn't have begun
if that was the case.
Then what is it?
I told you.
It's my defeat.
Do you know how many of my colleagues
died without being recognized?
Twenty-three.
Some of them were very young
and had blind trust in me.
Then there were others
who were like family to me.
I don't want
any more blood on my hands. That's all.
I'M AT THE SIH.
WHERE ARE YOU?
According to an internal source,
Director Kang Hyukpil, who
was involved in this incident,
stepped down from his position.
- He resigned? What is this nonsense?
- Sergeant Ko Chulmin
was a whistleblowerwho
opposed the SIH's wrongdoings.
His suicide note revealed his
discontenttoward its corruption
and pointed the finger at Kang.
- A suicide note?
- It has been revealed
that he decided to endhis
and his family's lives
due to the immense stress.
Meanwhile, the police have yetto
make an official announcement.
They are currently looking into the case
based on Sergeant Ko's suicide note.
Some are criticizing the police
for defending their own people.
The bereaved family and civic
groupsbelieve Kang's voluntary resignation
is proof of admission of guilt
and have demandeda thorough investigation.
Do you still believethat
justice will prevail?
I've failed.
I should've been more evil than the worst.
I should've known that being
the lesser evil wouldn't have worked.
I should've just killed Kwon Jaekyu.
Gunshots were heard upstairs.
Die.
Damn it.
- Sir!
- Search the room!
- Here!
- Call the police!
Call an ambulance!
The chairman is injured!
Over here!
It's all over now.
Not yet.
Can you dispatch your men right now?
Prosecutor Song, I have no power now.
I need to pack up by the end of the night.
Mr. Kang, I have no time
to console you right now.
"By the end of the night," was it?
That means you still have power for now.
Do your job until the end.
Woosin isn't picking up.
We must find him.
WOOSIN
Help me.
Mr. Lee.
Wake up, Mr. Lee.
Are you awake?
Where are we?
In some kind of a shipping container.
They're going to kill us.
This shipping container...
They'll probably dispose of our bodies
in the ocean.
Leaving no trace behind.
It's Team A's...
classic move.
That's why Lee Changwoo
will have no choice but to talk.
If not, his son will die before his eyes.
What choice does he have?
Uninterested?
Then why are you still here?
YOON JIN
COME TO EUNKOOK MEDICAL CENTER
THE CHAIRMAN HAS BEEN SHOT
Damn it.
Father.
HAESONGWON
Something terrible happened!
The chairman...
Please...
Die.
No one...
is going to die tonight.
Suhyeon will come.
It's a bioimplant GPS.
I already got one.
- Me?
- What is the easiest way
to make Mr. Lee talk?
Us.
One of us will have to become a hostage.
If things go awry,
at least they'll find our bodies.
Let's text each other every hour.
If we don't get a text, then...
What have...
you two done?
Hang in there.
We need someone
who knows Team A the best.
And that's you.
You're not going back to prison.
The new master wants to see us.
Team A as your partner?
Team A's partner is the owner of Haesong.
So he managed to survive.
To take Team A down, I got
kidnapped, wore an explosive vest,
and had multiple brushes with death.
After all that I went through,
that man turned out to be
a former Team A agent too.
Find the Adamas...
while I take Team Leader Lee down.
Where is the Adamas?