The story, all names, characters, and incidents
portrayed in this production are fictitious.
No identification with actual persons (living or deceased),
places, buildings, and products is intended or should be inferred.
As we are enjoying our life,
things are constantly changing,
specifically in a hectic town...
where I never wish to go back to.
For me,
this forest...
is my only safe haven.
It can never betray me.
Thank you all for helping.
Great job.
I want to thank everybody
for letting me be a part of this project.
Thank you.
Now, let's eat.
Let's go.
Thank you...
for always taking care of me
and guiding me.
Thank you again.
It is I who must thank you, Fifa,
for helping with the check dam.
You did a great job. / Thank you.
Let's go, hun.
Okay. / Let's eat.
I'll be right there in a jiff. / Okay.
How is Fifa doing?
He really gets along well with the villagers.
I heard that he helped built
a check dam recently.
You said you needed my help, didn't you?
Oh, right. I almost forgot.
Well...
I want you...
to draw something on a card.
Sure.
What do you want me to draw?
Right.
What do I want?
It's for Uncle Hem.
Can you draw him with an elephant?
Sure.
You sure are being serious with this.
I just want to do something for him.
He used to drink booze like water.
Not that he has quitted!
He is a true alcoholic.
He got dumped, you know.
Okay.
An elephant it is.
I'll trust you with this then.
Sure.
If it's Hem, it must be a lion.
Fierce
and fearsome.
Everyone!
Are you ready to welcome our singer tonight?
Give it up! / We're ready!
Please give it up to Hem!
There is nothing
That can limit us
We don't need a reason
To be together
We are not different...
I didn't know he could sing.
We have things in common
Kindred hearts are why we bond...
Here are your drinks.
That is all we need
A highball.
Thank you. / For Fifa.
For Padmé?
Here.
Your heart and mine
Nothing can come between us
Uncle Hem!
You're so cool!
We have each other
I will never leave your side
Your heart and mine
Nothing can come between us
Bravo!
Everybody,
you know,
today is a special day.
It's Hem's birthday!
Let's make a toast to him.
Cheers!
Cheers! / Cheers!
Hey, take it easy.
Fifa...
Please give this card to Uncle Hem.
Give it to him, will you?
It's your card. You give it to him.
I can't. / Come on.
Hey, Padmé! / Whoa!
She's wasted.
I need home.
Be careful.
I'll leave her to you.
Will she be okay?
I told you not to drink.
You always end up like this.
This?
It's not mine.
It's from Padmé.
She's wasted there.
But this is from me.
Well...
Welcome to Pokpa.
Thank you.
What are you, a ghost?
Love it already?
I could only say it to you
Is it?
Love is a meaningful word
But it would not impress anyone
I could only say it to you
"I COULD ONLY SAY IT TO YOU"
A loving season was born
I smell something nice miles away.
How is it?
Patterns all the way.
This is it.
That's a yes. / A yes!
Nice.
Hello, Aunty Pad!
Hi, Fifa.
Well, can we change today's menu?
Go on.
How about
a non-spicy basil chicken
with hard-boiled egg?
But...
Our staff like spicy food.
A little change could be nice, right?
You know, just to spice things up.
I also crave that menu.
Okay. Sure.
I'll bring eggs then.
Okay.
PROD
UNCLE NEUK
UNCLE SANGWAN
Uncle Sangwan!
Uncle Tong, Uncle Neuk, Uncle Kanchit.
Your lunch is here.
UNCLE TONG, UNCLE NEUK, UNCLE KANCHIT
You should share it!
Here.
Why do you need to plant so many?
This is a nursery.
They will be relocated to the forest later
to replace trees in wildfire area.
It takes decades for a tree to mature.
But when the forest fire hits,
it only takes hours to burn a forest.
Look at that stump.
It was here before I came here.
Whenever I'm feeling down,
I'll hang around this place.
Here is what is left of it.
Did someone cut it down?
There was a storm.
It didn't make it.
Hem, wait.
Hold on.
You know,
I think
that I have improved a lot at work.
By that I mean
I ace it.
I am always right on time with my delivery.
So?
So...
Won't you compliment me a bit?
Okay. Well done.
Right?
Doesn't a person
deserve a reward for a work well done?
Spill it.
I want...
My head is blank now.
I'll tell you later what I want.
But I need you to promise
to reward me, okay?
Just a couple of trouble-free days
and you already ask for a reward?
Okay, okay. Listen,
well...
Aren't you hungry? / No.
But I'm famished!
Didn't you come here with my lunch?
Do you like it?
I asked Aunty Pad to make it special today.
You have a performance review
with Mrs. Pat tomorrow at ten.
Right.
That's good then.
My scholarship result will also be out tomorrow
at six in the morning.
I really hope I get it
so I can have a talk with Grandma about that.
Hem,
can I come here tomorrow to check the result?
I tried the whole area
but only your place has signal.
Please, please?
Fine.
Thank you.
Whoa!
What?
The signal's gone!
I checked and it worked before.
Signal won't be stable in the forest.
What if there's no signal tomorrow?
I really look forward to seeing the result.
Ugh! I'm dying to go to Japan.
Let's do this.
I'll bring you where there is signal.
We can
celebrate there as well
then we can go see Mrs. Pat.
Deal.
Thank you.
I already washed it.
I also got this for you.
You're so sweet.
Now I know...
why you like it here.
Looking at the morning sky
Could not lift up my spirit
Better than looking at your smile
The wind passing by
Could not make me as ticklish
As you being by my side
You bring the change of seasons
A lonely season is gone
A loving season was born
With you by my side
I start to see the color
Of love and passion
And I wish it lasts forever
A songbird's singing
Is far less enticing
Than your whispering that you miss me
We're here!
You know,
I haven't been here since I came to Pokpa.
Really miss this place.
Close your eyes.
It feels like Pokpa.
They're not the same.
They're polar opposite.
Hem,
I really love this spot.
When I look down from here,
it really makes me realize
that the world is a vast place.
Watch me.
I'm leaving this place!
I'll explore the world!
You shouldn't trap yourself in Pokpa
just because some girl dumped you.
You got me?
Are you seeing someone?
Does it matter?
You act like a guru.
I'm not seeing anybody.
Then you just talk big.
Hi. / Hello there.
Got any Wi-Fi?
The password is YaYeeNimman.
They posted it right at the elevator.
Did they? / Yeah.
What did you order?
Here's your order.
It's not strong.
Enjoy your drink. / Thank you.
Wow.
What's this?
Try it.
It's liquor!
I'll pass.
Why? We are here to celebrate.
The result is almost out.
I want to be wide-awake.
You can have it.
Go on.
Come on, come on.
Take it easy.
You can wait for the result here.
We can go back to Pokpa tomorrow.
I'll stay up until six.
How was it?
I was so sure about it
that I did as best
as I could.
I did it better than I ever did.
But who would know
that there are plenty of people who did it better.
It's okay.
Just let it out.
I'm not sad.
I just don't understand.
Sometimes,
you don't need to understand everything.
Just leave me alone.
Wait.
You can go back.
You failed this time.
But it's not the end.
It is.
It all ended.
I already told you
that I want to leave this place.
I don't care about that soil, water,
trees, or any bullshit knowledge.
I'll be here for you.
No one is too prepared for every changes...
whether it happens in a forest or in a city.
The hardest change to face
must be
a change of heart.
Third?
Looking at the morning sky
Could not lift up my spirit
Better than looking at your smile
The wind passing by
Could not make me as ticklish
As you being by my side
You bring the change of seasons
A lonely season is gone
A loving season was born
With you by my side
I start to see the color
Of love and passion
And I wish it lasts forever
A songbird's singing
Is far less enticing
Than your whispering that you miss me
Love is a meaningful word
But it would not impress anyone
I could only say it to you
You bring the change of seasons
A lonely season is gone
A loving season was born
With you by my side
I start to see the color
Of love and passion
In every season of love
Being together in this great atmosphere
With trees, rivers, and mountains near
I am blessed to have found you
A plot from the novel "Lost in the woods" by theneoclassic
And I wish it lasts forever