[Unnatural Fire]
[Episode 7]
[Body 1]
[Body 1] [Body 2]
Take it back for testing.
Okay.
The evidence markers are in place.
[Physical Evidence of the Fire Scene]
Take photos and take them back.
Yes.
[Physical Evidence of the Fire Scene]
Alright, it matches.
The man's name is Ying Youchang.
The woman's name is Zhang Yulan.
Get me an evidence bag.
Based on the initial assessment,
this should be a homicide scene.
Not just that.
Why?
Look.
Here, here,
here,
and the edges of the victim's clothing
were all the points of ignition.
Combined with the burn
and spread traces,
it's possible
that combustion improver was used.
So,
this was arson.
What kind of combustion improver?
We'll need to run tests for specifics.
Chun, what about you?
Have you found anything?
The male victim, Ying Youchang,
was lying face down on the ground,
with his limbs bent in a fist-like position.
Both of his hands
show signs of having been bound.
The areas of his body in contact with the ground
weren't burned.
The creases at the outer corners of his eyes
make it difficult to determine if they were reflexively shut.
No soot was found in his corneas
or conjunctival sacs.
Based on all this,
we can conclude
the victim was bound
and placed face down
before death.
But it's unclear
whether the fire started
before or after he died.
Bound before death?
Placed face down?
Any external injuries?
There's a fresh impact wound
on his forehead,
with signs of vital reaction.
I guess he sustained the injury
right before the fire started.
So you mean
the male victim
might have been
attacked by the murderer
before the fire was set?
Full details
require further autopsy.
What about the female victim?
The female victim was lying on her back,
with burn injuries
that are almost identical to those of the male victim.
But there was a knife,
approximately 3 cm wide,
embedded in her chest.
The entire blade
was fully buried in her body.
The wound
shows clear signs of vital reaction.
It means she was stabbed
before she died.
So the cause of her death was likely the stab wound.
She was stabbed in the chest,
and her body was burned after death.
That's brutal.
The male victim had deep strangulation marks,
and the female victim was stabbed so violently
that the entire blade went in.
I can't imagine
what kind of grudge
would drive someone to do this.
And there were multiple ignition points
inside this house.
Once the fire started,
escape was impossible.
Multiple ignition points.
This could be
a particularly severe case
of murder and arson.
Let's all pick up the pace.
Okay.
Pai.
Transport the bodies back.
We'll start the autopsies immediately.
Okay.
I'm heading back for the autopsies.
Go ahead.
Captain Shen,
Zhang Yulan's son
still isn't answering his phone.
Keep calling.
Ask around
and see if anyone knows his address.
Get in touch with the family as soon as possible.
Okay.
I'm going out to ask around.
This time, instead of piecing together glass,
you're piecing together the door?
When you were a kid, did you
love jigsaw puzzles?
It's for work.
We're
a joint team of criminal investigation and fire investigation.
We're like family.
I'll help you this time.
Okay.
Be thorough.
Don't be careless.
Listen,
I really like your work ethic.
Ever since you
pieced that glass back together last time,
I could tell you're very meticulous.
Man, you're so skillful.
Idol, turn around.
What are you doing during work hours?
Idol, don't you remember?
The Publicity Department
wants to feature you.
They asked me to take
some photos of you as promotional materials.
It's also for work, right?
How does he look?
Handsome.
Handsome, huh?
Listen.
Come on, take a photo of me.
I'll use it for promotion later.
How do I look?
I'll send it to you later.
Thanks.
Hello, go ahead.
Well,
what's the situation on your side?
Okay. I'll be right there.
I won't disturb you further.
I can't wake him up from that side either.
Knocking is useless. Shout.
He won't wake up.
Sir!
What are you doing?
Huang Qi,
what's going on? You can't get in?
We shouted, but he won't wake up.
Sir!
Sir, wake up!
He's sleeping like a log.
If this doesn't work,
Huang Qi said he has an idea.
Put it away.
Huang Qi,
check under the mattress.
Already did, Captain Shen.
We also checked the flowerbed. Nothing there.
I really didn't expect this.
If you had, you'd be the captain.
Sir!
Come on, wake up.
Get up.
That's all?
It's all here.
Which camera's footage
do you need?
I'll pull it up for you.
No need, we'll do it ourselves.
Huang Qi, the one at the entrance.
Okay.
Alright then, make yourselves at home.
Come on, play it.
[Northwest corner]
Fast forward.
Fast forward again.
[Northwest corner]
This person.
Zoom in a bit.
[Northwest corner]
I can't see anything clearly.
Why is it so blurry?
Rewind.
Rewind to 10:45 p.m.
[Northwest corner]
Fast forward.
The rest is just the fire response.
Investigate this person.
[Northwest corner]
How about this?
You two make a copy
of this tape
and process it back at the station.
Okay.
That sign
was removed the day before yesterday.
Men's restroom is on the left!
Women's restroom is on the right!
Xu, take the left side!
Adviser Xu!
You've finished investigating?
Well...
You've finished checking the surveillance footage?
Yes.
But the footage is a bit blurry.
I need the tech department to process it.
Why aren't you going in?
You didn't find one you like?
Or do you need someone to accompany you?
I'm done.
Just kidding.
Being unable to tell left from right
is nothing to be ashamed of.
Next time you get confused,
just
touch this side.
That's left.
Come on.
Let me clarify
the identities of the two victims.
Zhang Yulan.
Ying Youchang.
Through investigation,
they were not a couple.
But they had lived together
for many years.
I'll start with Ying Youchang.
[Zhang Yulan] [Lived together] [Ying Youchang]
He returned
to this village after retiring.
[Photo of the scene]
He had no living relatives,
and his social connections were very simple.
Before retirement, Ying Youchang
worked at a construction site.
After an injury,
he had to rely on a wheelchair.
He had no job during the past two years.
The other victim, Zhang Yulan,
[Zhang Yulan] [Lived together] [Ying Youchang]
lost her husband early in life.
Her son, Hao Chengcai,
[Son: Hao Chengcai] [Husband and wife] [Daughter-in-law: Wang Yingying]
is a sales director at a foreign company.
His wife, Wang Yingying,
is an office clerk.
[Son: Hao Chengcai] [Husband and wife] [Daughter-in-law: Wang Yingying]
Her grandson, Hao Tianyou,
is in elementary school.
[Grandson: Hao Tianyou]
[Photo of the scene]
According to the neighbors' statements,
Zhang Yulan spent most of her time
taking care of her grandson at Hao Chengcai's place.
Hao Chengcai's family of three
rarely returned to the old house.
Zhang Yulan was a kind person
and never had
conflicts with anyone.
[Photo of the scene]
From their social circles,
neither of the two victims
had offended anyone.
The most useful lead now
is the surveillance footage.
How's
the recovery going?
Captain Shen,
Zhao, who usually handles this, is on a business trip.
Others have stepped in,
but the progress will be slower.
Hello, Captain Shen.
Adviser Xu.
Yesterday at the village committee,
we got a surveillance tape.
Is Mao Mao from your team
handling it?
Yes.
Here's the thing.
Our tech expert is on a business trip.
Members of the criminal investigation
and fire investigation joint team are like family.
When you're done processing it,
can you send me a copy?
Okay, no problem.
That's great.
Do you have
any new findings?
The combustion improver test results
are out.
It was the Baijiu from the scene.
So we can't rule out
the possibility of a crime of passion— an impulsive act of arson.
A crime of passion— an impulsive act of arson?
Adviser Xu, you're indeed efficient.
We're truly like family.
Alright then.
Alright, I'm hanging up.
Sorry for disturbing you.
Once the surveillance footage is processed,
send it to Captain Shen.
No problem.
These are all the clues we have for now.
Let me brief you on the task.
[Photo of the scene]
We need to conduct a more detailed investigation
into the backgrounds of the two victims.
Dismissed.
-Yes.
[Photo of the scene]
[Zhang Yulan] [Lived together] [Ying Youchang]
Go ahead.
Captain Shen,
an elderly lady claiming to be
Zhang Yulan's close friend for decades
insists on seeing you.
Let me in.
I want to see your leader!
I just want to see my old friend,
my dear friend of decades.
I heard her.
Bring her to the conference room.
Well, I...
Yulan... Well...
I... You don't understand. She...
Auntie.
Calm down.
Captain Shen will talk to you later.
Well, who?
Captain Shen.
I... I... I...
I brought Lin Jingxiang here.
I... I...
Auntie.
Go to the conference room first.
Okay.
Get her a glass of water.
I'll be right there.
Auntie, let's go.
Let's go to the conference room first.
You know what? Her whole life...
Listen, her entire life...
Captain Shen,
Zhang Yulan's son
and daughter-in-law have arrived.
You go.
Ask them to identify the body and conduct routine questioning.
Come, Auntie, have a seat.
Miss, thank you.
It's okay, Auntie.
Have a seat.
I'll go get you a glass of water.
Auntie, have a seat.
How should I address you?
What?
My...
My... My name is Lin Jingxiang.
Lin... Lin...
Lin as in... as in Shulin.
[Lin]
You don't know who I am?
You haven't asked
around about me?
You don't know my relationship
with Yulan?
We were friends for almost 40 years.
Yulan's life
was so hard.
Listen,
Yulan and I...
Since we were little, I...
We lived close to each other.
We went to school together,
walked home together,
and did homework together.
Then she got married first.
I remember it so clearly.
I got married after her.
When I got married,
she even gave me a red envelope.
Yulan lived frugally for a whole month
just for the red envelope.
She ate nothing but cornbread buns
for an entire month.
Have you... Have you ever eaten cornbread buns?
Auntie, I've never eaten cornbread buns.
Come, Bai Zhi.
Drink some water.
Auntie, have some water.
I... I... I...
What did
Zhang Yulan usually do?
Did she interact much with others?
Yu... Yulan...
Back then, she... she...
she always complained about back pain.
So I bought her medicated plasters.
I went to her house
to help her apply them.
Then I helped her with housework.
Later, she stopped contacting me.
I knew why she stopped contacting me.
Well...
She had another companion
called Ying.
Ying Youchang.
You knew him?
Ying was truly a good person.
He was
very nice to Yulan.
But that
caused
many people to gossip.
Auntie,
about the gossip
you just mentioned,
who spread it?
Well...
who else could it be?
I can repeat
some of the words,
but there are some other words I just can't repeat.
She...
They were together,
but others gossiped. Why?
Because
they didn't have marriage certificates.
That was why others gossiped.
People, you know...
Auntie, we already knew
about what you just said.
About Zhang Yulan,
is there anything else
you want to tell us?
Yulan is dead.
Yulan, you're dead,
yet someone's here
asking questions about you.
Whenever I think about it,
it breaks my heart.
Auntie, don't be too sad.
You lost a good friend.
We completely understand how you feel.
Have some water.
Captain Shen,
it's mealtime. Should I...
get you something?
Auntie,
it's mealtime.
Is there anything you want to eat?
I'll go get you some.
It's mealtime?
I... I don't want to trouble you.
I don't... don't want to trouble you.
I don't want to trouble you.
You are very busy.
Are you out
in the field more,
or do you spend more time
in the office?
Both are common.
Both are common?
Anyway, you need to eat on time.
Yes.
You can't work properly
if you don't eat well.
When I was young, I was like you.
I didn't eat on time.
I always...
skipped meals, so...
I wasn't in good health.
Now,
if I don't eat on time,
I get low blood sugar.
Right now, as I'm talking to you,
I'm feeling a bit dizzy.
Then what would you like to eat?
Just tell me.
I'll go prepare it for you.
I'm not picky.
Actually, even a bowl
of instant noodles would make me happy.
Okay.
I'll get you a bowl of instant noodles.
According to the rules,
please cooperate and wear a mask.
Here.
Chun.
These two are
Zhang Yulan's son and daughter-in-law.
You need to be mentally prepared.
You can't step forward later.
Mom.
Mom!
Calm down.
Mom.
Mom,
how did you get burned like this?
Mom!
Mom! I'm unfilial!
Mom.
Young man,
is what I told you
useful?
Yes.
What you told me is very helpful
to our investigation.
That's good.
I've finished eating.
I feel much better now.
This reminds me of the old days
with Yulan.
When we were together,
I loved instant noodles.
We both loved instant noodles.
It's just that
this bowl
is really too small.
It's not enough to fill me up.
Auntie,
are you still hungry?
In that case, here,
you can eat mine.
Is it appropriate for me to eat your noodles?
It's fine, eat.
Captain Shen.
What's up?
Hao Chengcai and Wang Yingying
have completed the body identification.
They're ready for questioning.
So you...
I'm not finished here yet.
You go first.
Hao Chengcai is here?
Yes. He came for routine questioning.
That guy...
Listen,
the son
of Yulan...
Auntie,
what about her son?
Her son...
I don't know what to say.
Listen,
actually, her son
and my son
grew up together.
Back then, people said her son
was very smart
and promising.
But over the years,
I haven't seen him amount to much.
He's grown up,
but I don't think he's all that great.
Still, he's a guy working for someone.
Last time,
Yulan told me
her son is a leader,
and his suits
are tailor-made.
Although they are tailor-made,
they... they're still suits.
In my opinion, her son is wasteful.
He insisted on
buying a...
A brooch?
Yes.
All shiny and dangling.
It cost a lot of money.
My son and I...
My son is practical.
I'm telling you,
I think her son is wasteful.
Take... Take a look.
Look.
My son is more practical.
My son
works at... at the neighborhood committee.
He also... He also...
serves over 100 people.
On every festive occasion,
my son always brings me eggs,
noodles,
and milk.
It's so practical.
Tell us about your
basic information.
My name is Hao Chengcai.
I currently work at a foreign company
as a sales director.
I admit
I...
I didn't pay enough attention
to my family,
especially my mother.
But I've been too busy with work.
I manage a small team
of dozens of people.
But I told my mother
more than once
that she should
move in with us.
The house is big enough.
There's plenty of room.
But...
But she just wouldn't agree.
She said...
She said she was used to living
in the old house.
She was worried she wouldn't be able to adjust if she moved.
If...
If she had listened to me,
this wouldn't have happened,
right?
And her daughter-in-law.
Her daughter-in-law
is all about living the high life.
She drinks bird's nest soup every day.
Two bottles a day.
But I've never seen her
give... give any
to Yulan.
Besides,
bird's... bird's nest soup is not a substitute for a meal.
In my opinion, bird's nest soup
isn't as practical as instant noodles.
If I... If I eat this,
what should you eat?
It's okay.
I'll make another bowl for myself.
You need to eat, young man.
Then how
did you all get along
in the family?
My mother raised me
by herself.
So I was very close
to my mother.
Even my son,
Tianyou.
Tianyou's grandmother
was his favorite.
I got along well with Mother too.
We lived together.
What about Ying Youchang?
I rarely saw him.
Him?
I rarely
visited the old house,
so...
I was not close to him.
Did your mother
have enemies?
Or
did she have conflicts
with anyone?
No.
Absolutely not.
My mother was
always easygoing.
She was very kind to everyone.
All the neighbors here know that.
You can ask around.
What did you do last night?
Did you contact
your mother?
Do you know
what happened at home?
Auntie,
last night,
why didn't I see you at the scene?
I was sleeping.
There were fire alarms
and police sirens going off last night.
Your sleep quality
is pretty good.
Let me tell you.
As soon as
I get into bed
and my head hits the pillow,
I can fall asleep
within three minutes.
I sleep straight through until morning.
That's great.
This morning,
I heard my husband telling my son
something happened.
My... My son cooperated
with your investigation today, right?
Yesterday at the neighborhood committee,
that was your son?
Is he handsome?
He's as tall as you.
This is the restored surveillance footage
from 10:00 p.m. to 10:30 p.m.
Take a look.
Auntie,
I need to take another look at your photo.
Auntie, continue eating.
Captain Shen.
Danggui,
where's Hao Chengcai?
He left.
Come with me to stop him.
What's wrong, Captain Shen?
At 10 p.m. last night,
the person who went to the victims' house
was Hao Chengcai.
He already told us.
[Criminal Investigation Division of Binxi Branch Bureau of the Beixun Municipal Public Security Bureau]
Look.
[Inquiry notes]
[Actually, I went to see my mom at 10 p.m. last night.]
Actually, last night,
I went to see my mom.
It was...
around 10 p.m.
What for?
Nothing.
I hadn't seen her for a long time,
so I went to check on her.
But during the visit,
we got into an argument.
I quarreled with my mom,
so I didn't stay long.
I left...
at around
10:30 p.m.
Young man.
Yu... Yulan wasn't burned
to death, was she?
Was she murdered by someone?
Auntie,
we can't disclose
details of the case.
But please rest assured,
we will give you
an explanation.
Has the video been sent?
Yes.
I sent it as soon as the restoration was done.
Look.
[This is the restored surveillance footage from 10:00 p.m. to 10:30 p.m. Take a look.]
Why is it only from 10:00 p.m.
to 10:30 p.m.?
When we were at the scene,
Li Danggui said
this half-hour was the key part.
Restore a bit more.
It might come in handy later.
Okay. I'll work on it right away.
Idol, you should go eat.
At this hour,
the dining hall is almost running out of food.
You're so hard-working.
The Publicity Department
said
they want to take some photos of you
to feature you.
[Refuse] [Answer]
[Xiangyang Nursing Home]
Hello.
Grandma wants to see you again.
She won't listen to anyone else.
Can you come now?
Okay, I'll be right there.
[Xiangyang Nursing Center of Beixun City
Xiangyang Nursing Home of Beixun City]
Grandma,
look,
this leaf is big.
This one is big.
Where's He Xi?
He usually doesn't come back from school
this late.
Did he get lost?
No.
I have to go pick him up.
Grandma.
I need to...
Grandma,
He Xi won't get lost.
He'll come back soon.
That won't do.
My He Xi is such a good boy.
He would never come back this late.
I'm going to look for him.
Adviser Xu.
You're finally here.
There was a traffic jam.
Grandma has been talking about you.
Leave her to me.
You go get some rest.
Okay.
He Xi.
Grandma.
Sit down.
You were worried?
Why are you back
so late?
I just got out of school.
I was so worried.
Really?
I cooked shrimps for you in the pot.
It's your favorite.
Okay.
We'll eat in a bit, okay?
Let me peel an orange for you first.
What did you do today?
You picked up leaves?
Look.
You picked up so many leaves?
The biggest one.
You keep it.
Eat slowly.
It's so cold.
Cold?
Let me warm it up a bit.
Let me warm it up. My hands are warm.
Hello.
Idol,
I wanted to tell you just now.
The Publicity Department is urging us.
They want you to pick two photos as soon as possible.
I've sent you all of them.
Any of them will do.
Come on, Idol.
We need your approval.
It'll only take you two seconds.
Alright, I got it.
Warm it up yourself.
I need to take care of something.
Let me take a look at the photos.
He Xi.
He Xi,
when will you come to visit me?
This one is me.
This one isn't.
You were mistaken.
Heng,
well,
when will He Xi
come to visit me?
He Xi,
when will you come to visit me?
This is great.
He Xi is a good boy.
Today, you're going
to have a new classmate.
Come.
Introduce yourself to everyone.
He Xi.
Which He Xi?
He Xi as in Jinxihexi?
Yes.
Madam,
why does it suddenly smell like fish
in our classroom?
It stinks!
Quiet.
Which of you
wants to sit with He Xi?
Madam,
I can sit with He Xi.
No need, Madam.
I'll just take the empty seat
in the back row.
Grandma,
I'm back.
He Xi,
school's over?
I'll make shrimps for you.
Watch.
I'll make shrimps for my grandson.
Wait.
It'll be ready soon.
Okay.
Uncle.
May I ask where the fish vendor is?
Turn left up ahead.
Thank you.
This is the left side.
So you're a little fish seller.
Do you want to buy fish?
Yes,
I'm here to buy fish.
What are you doing, Li Xiangqian?
Don't bully He Xi!
Xu Heng.
Come on.
What's wrong with you, Xu Heng?
Calm down.
You're selling fish like this?
They're all half-dead.
Li Xiangqian, what are you doing?
Put the fish back!
I won't.
Why should I listen to you?
Who do you think you are?
Xu Heng.
Stop it!
Don't you dare bully He Xi again!
Shut your mouth!
Stop, you two!
Li Xiangqian!
Let go!
Stop it!
What are you doing?
Alright, stop!
Come on, let's go home!
What are you doing?
You're such a troublemaker.
Where's Grandma?
She's waiting for me at home.
Why are you as impulsive
as that guy?
I did that to protect you.
I don't need it.
How much for this fish?
This... This one.
It's okay.
Lead it away!
Go!
It's tame. It doesn't bite people!
Go! Just go!
Fine.
Go away!
Forget it. I'm not buying it.
I'm not buying it.
I'm sorry, kid.
Are you okay, He Xi?
Thanks.
You'd better go home.
Go straight.
Take the first right.
The main gate is at the end.
Xu Heng.
This is the left side.
[Photo of the scene]
Captain Shen,
I've restored
another half hour of the video.
I've sent it to your email.
Thank you, Mao Mao.
[Northwest corner]
[Actually, I went to see my mom at 10 p.m. last night.]
Danggui.
Captain Shen.
Go bring Hao Chengcai in
for questioning.
Yes.
Officer Shen,
why did you call me here
again today?
Tell us
about your movements last night.
I already
told you once, right?
Why do I have to repeat it?
We need to
go over the details again.
Okay.
Last night,
around 10 p.m.,
I arrived at my mother's house.
Then
something unpleasant happened.
My mother and I
got into an argument.
I didn't stay long,
and then I left.
What time did you leave?
Around 10:30 p.m.
On my way back,
I was in a bad mood.
So I...
wanted to smoke.
But at that time,
almost all the shops on the street were closed.
I found...
a 24-hour convenience store.
Do you remember what time
you got to the convenience store?
A little past
11:10 p.m., I...
I think.
If you don't believe me,
you can check the convenience store's surveillance footage.
Everything I said is true.
Do you smoke often?
Not really.
I only smoke
when I'm upset.
So I usually don't carry cigarettes with me.
I buy them when I want to smoke.
Now let's do this.
Recount your movements
last night
in reverse order.
Why?
I told you
we need to go over the details again.
Please cooperate.
Okay.
I wanted to smoke,
so I went to the convenience store to buy cigarettes.
It was very late at that time.
And before that?
Before that, I was in my car.
I was driving,
and then... I went back to my mom's house.
Then I saw...
What did you see?
Nothing.
I'm asking you what you saw.
I didn't see anything.
A slip of the tongue.
It was a slip of the tongue.
You did see something, didn't you?
How far is the convenience store
from your house?
A few kilometers.
It's roughly halfway between my house
and my mother's house.
It's a 30-minute drive from
Zhang Yulan's house to yours.
You said the convenience store is in the middle.
That means it's a 15-minute drive
from Zhang Yulan's house
to the convenience store.
You left
Zhang Yulan's house at 10:30 p.m.,
but you arrived at
the convenience store after 11:10 p.m.
It was supposed to be a 15-minute drive,
but it took you over 40 minutes.
What did you do
during that half-hour?
You don't remember?
Here,
let me show you something.
Take a good look.
You saw your mother's house was on fire.
Did you think I couldn't see you because
you were hiding in the crowd?
Why did you lie before?
Yes.
I did go back.