[Unnatural Fire]
[Episode 24]
My father
and my mentor?
Shen Yi and Gu Nuo?
Yes.
If I'm not mistaken,
the two of them, one inside and one outside,
have been watching you closely
from home to work.
Chief Wu, that's impossible, isn't it?
I know this might be
difficult for you to accept,
but think about it carefully.
Isn't that how it is?
As I remember,
my father
only met my mentor a few times,
and it was all because of me.
I don't think so.
I believe you
don't have
the full picture of this situation.
You might be
the main target they're trying to deceive.
Why?
To know why,
that's the reason
I brought you here today.
I want you to think back
and see if there's anything
unusual
in your recent life
to see if you can provide us
with some clues.
At first,
we didn't want to tell you these things.
Firstly,
we're not sure if there's a problem
with Gu Nuo.
Secondly, you and Gu Nuo
are in a mentor-student relationship after all.
If we alert him,
whether you're aware of it or not,
it will bring difficulties
to our investigation work.
Also,
our investigation work
has reached a critical point now.
Aren't you also
confused about
many things now?
So we want
you to join us,
share information,
and work together
so we don't get stuck
in moving forward.
Take your time to think about it.
Thank you, Chief Chang.
Chief Chang,
Chief Wu,
I've been with my mentor
for so many years.
There are many details
that I can't recall
at the moment.
But there's one thing
I must tell you.
I just found out
about this matter recently.
Shen Yi
is not my biological father.
The identity of Shen Ye
was fabricated by him.
Are you sure?
Absolutely certain.
What exactly happened?
Twenty years ago,
in Binjiang University of Technology's
bomb case,
my biological father
was the victim.
His name is He Runian.
I was in charge of that case.
I'm saying you're using that case
to deceive me?
My name should be He Xi.
Two years
after my biological father passed away,
I experienced another
arson case.
I survived,
but I lost
all my memories
from before I was twelve.
It was Shen Yi
who took me away at that time.
All these years,
he has been hiding the truth from me.
There must be a reason.
And you just mentioned
that he and my mentor
have some unspeakable secret.
There must be something wrong with them.
Well,
so are you going to
continue living with him
in this current state?
My memory has just been restored.
He doesn't know about it yet.
I want to maintain the status quo,
stay by his side,
and continue the investigation.
We will keep this matter
strictly confidential.
If you need anything,
communicate directly with Chief Wu.
We can assist you.
Alright.
Chief Chang, Chief Wu,
there's one more thing.
A few days ago,
Adviser Xu from the Fire Investigation Department
was attacked.
It's also very strange.
He was the first to know
that Shen Yi had forged my identity.
They had just had a direct confrontation,
and then he encountered danger.
Moreover,
the eyewitness at the time
retracted their statement midway.
Due to insufficient evidence,
the police closed the case as an accident.
I just received news
that the worker who injured Xu Tongsheng
[The worker Qin Shun had a heart attack. He died at home.]
named Qin Shun
had a sudden heart attack
and died at home.
A sudden heart attack?
Did he have a history of heart disease?
This seems too sudden.
Go investigate.
Okay.
This matter
is far more complicated
than we imagined.
Shen Ye,
the content of our conversation today
must be kept strictly confidential.
The fact that you've regained your memory
cannot be known by anyone.
Understood.
Bro, are you busy?
Well,
I saw online a couple of days ago
that this construction site
had an accident recently.
Yes, that's right.
One of my coworkers fell
and hit someone.
Is that person okay?
He died.
Who died?
Our coworker,
Qin Shun.
How did he die?
At home,
he died of a sudden heart attack.
Did he have heart disease?
Back when he was at home,
I never heard he had heart problems.
Well.
He had poor psychological resilience.
Maybe he was just scared to death
because of this incident.
Let's not talk about it anymore.
It's bad luck, bad luck.
-Let’s get to work.
Come on, let's go.
Come on.
[The Party is in My Heart; I Will Always Follow the Party]
Come in.
Deputy Chief Peng.
Xu.
Zhao Zhiyuan
has already gone to
turn himself in to the Discipline Inspection Commission.
He's suspected of dereliction of duty.
This matter
is being taken very seriously by the organization.
All relevant information
has been synchronized with the criminal investigation department.
So, Director Zhao, he...
His attitude towards admitting his mistake is very good.
I believe the organization
will definitely investigate the course of events thoroughly
and clarify everything.
They will give him
a fair and just conclusion.
Comrade Xu Tongsheng,
if now
you are asked to temporarily oversee
the work of the Fire Investigation Department,
can you do it?
Xu,
I know
with so many things happening,
it will more or less
have some impact on you.
But I hope
that in the future,
you will still prioritize
the work of the Fire Investigation Department.
Yes.
[Certificate of Honorary Fire Rescue Assessment No.1]
[Tomb of He Dazhuang]
Fire! Fire!
There's a fire!
Help! Someone come quickly! Put out the fire!
Fire! Fire!
Help! Put out the fire!
Put it out!
Help! Fire!
Quick, give it to me! Give it to me!
Up there!
Pour it up there!
Call the police.
Someone must have
deliberately set fire to our cattle shed.
Forget it.
At least all the cattle were rescued.
It's just a cattle shed, isn't it?
Forget it?
That's impossible.
I know some of you
look down on my cattle farming.
You want to harm me.
It's not just a day or two.
I'm telling you,
this isn't over.
He Lin,
what you're saying
is a bit unreasonable.
We've been helping you for a while now,
how can you turn around and accuse us?
I wasn't talking about you.
What's this?
Let me see.
What the hell is this?
He Lin,
someone died in the fire in your cattle shed.
Someone's dead.
Hello, Fire Investigation Department.
There's been a fire in a cattle shed in Liu Village.
A skeleton was found inside.
Excuse me, please make way.
Chun.
How are you?
Has your injury healed well?
Almost.
Alright.
I'll go in and take a look first.
Quick, let's go.
Okay!
Take it easy, sis.
Chun.
Huang Qi.
Bai Zhi.
Come.
Huang Qi.
Where's your Captain Shen?
Chief Wu said Captain Shen has other tasks.
We won't see him for a while.
Dad.
Going out to buy groceries?
Yes.
Let's go, I'll accompany you.
Aren't you working?
I took some time off.
I want to rest for a couple of days.
Okay, okay, rest well.
Let's go.
Let's buy some of your favorite food.
Given the current situation,
it's too difficult to handle, sis.
It's already carbonized to this extent.
Let's take photos first.
Alright.
Jiang Li.
[11
Physical Evidence of the Fire Scene]
Serves him right!
He really deserves it, that's what it is!
He ruined the blessing ceremony.
Uncle Liu, look, just look!
-Look all this mess.
-This is the end of...
Ruining a blessing ceremony.
Oh my god!
How did it end up like this?
Serves him right!
He really deserves it!
[Trusted Meat & Vegetable Chain Store - Shanzi Branch]
This is good stuff.
This is great for making soup.
Do you want some seafood?
Let's have some seafood.
Are you eating?
This fish is good.
The seafood looks good today.
Sure.
Yeah.
Let's get some seafood.
Okay.
Pick whatever you want to eat.
Alright.
What about that?
Dad, look at that.
That place looks good too, doesn't it?
Yeah, I often came here.
Mr. Shen.
Come.
What new stock do you have?
The crabs are fresh in.
Crabs, huh?
Let's take a look.
Let's see.
These are meaty crabs.
Very fresh.
They're full, aren't they?
Want some?
Do you want to eat crab?
These oysters are good too.
These oysters are really fresh.
These scallops.
These scallops are good too.
These scallops are fine too.
We can steam these when we get back.
These scallops are good too.
With some vermicelli.
Your goods are quite big.
Steam them with some minced garlic.
It's delicious.
Are these all newly arrived?
How about abalone?
Let's make abalone chicken for dinner.
Okay, okay, okay.
Sure, sure, sure.
Let's get this then.
Alright, this one.
Clean it up well, okay?
Okay, no problem.
I'm going to the restroom.
Okay, okay, okay.
Six, six is enough.
Six.
Six will be enough.
Help me clean these up, please.
Okay.
Weigh them, please.
Yes, yes, yes. Good.
[Water is the source of life.]
[Be a civilized person, please flush water.]
Are you crazy?
Why are you following me?
Since I've come out,
I should at least see Professor Shen, right?
What are you going to do?
What do you think I want to do?
I want money.
Money is fine.
Get rid of Xu Tongsheng for me.
Okay.
It'll cost extra.
Fine.
[Be careful, it's slippery] [No smoking]
Give Shen Ye something to do.
-Okay.
-It's all taken care of.
[Be careful, it's slippery] [No smoking]
Okay.
Thank you.
With that chicken,
cook it together in a soup.
Okay.
Alright.
Thank you.
Take care.
Come again next time.
Alright.
Dad.
Alright, let's go.
It's been taken care of.
How much?
Paid in full, let's go.
I've already paid.
Alright, let's go.
Take care.
Okay.
What's going on?
It's about the fire at He Lin's house?
Serves him right.
He brought it upon himself.
He disrupted the blessing ceremony.
It's a sin.
Let me tell you.
Among all people
in this Liu Village,
only He Lin
doesn't have an ounce of reverence
towards the Fire Goddess,
You see, the Fire Goddess
has bestowed upon us the holy fire,
blessing our Liu Village.
Shouldn't we have some
gratitude?
Shouldn't we organize some
blessings, celebrations, and such
to show our loyalty?
Since our village
received this holy fire,
we've had quite a few tourists.
Some villagers have opened guesthouses,
some sell handmade crafts,
and souvenirs,
as well as our local
specialties.
But this He Lin doesn't fit in,
he goes against the villagers.
That's right.
He treasures those few cows of his,
saying that the tourists
disturb his cows' rest.
Early in the morning, he carries a speaker
and plays music for the cows.
The most infuriating thing is
in the middle of the night,
he throws firecrackers at the guesthouses
to drive away tourists.
Isn't that infuriating?
Is that something a decent person would do?
Control your emotions.
In our village,
who doesn't have a bad relationship with He Lin?
Who has a bad relationship with him?
Who could have a good relationship with him?
He affects everyone's ability to make money.
How can everyone
have a good relationship with him?
He's talking about me with his teeth bared.
He said
it was feudal superstition,
playing tricks with ghosts and spirits.
This...
Has anyone in this village
gone missing?
You suspect those bones
belong to someone who died in our village?
Yes.
Impossible.
-No! No!
-No way.
This morning,
by the time we arrived,
everyone in the village was here.
Everyone who could come did.
Are there any surveillance cameras in the village?
Yes, there are.
Quite a few, actually.
They were installed at the request
of our superiors.
Go and copy the surveillance footage.
I'll go find the owner of the cattle shed.
Alright.
Officer,
come, this way.
Over there.
He's the owner of the cattle shed.
You're He Lin?
What's your connection to the bones?
How would I know
what they have to do with me?
If they have nothing to do with you,
why are they in your cattle shed?
Officer,
my cattle shed was perfectly fine.
I don't know who
burned it down like this.
And those human bones,
how terrifying!
You must investigate thoroughly.
Who exactly set the fire?
Who threw the bones
into our cattle pen?
Are you suggesting
someone deliberately set the fire,
killed someone,
and dumped the body at your place?
Do you have any suspects in mind?
Some people
can't stand that I raise cattle.
Those rotten, malicious bastards
did something bad and for convenience
threw it next door.
-He Lin.
-What kind of person is that?
What are you saying?
Am I talking about you?
Control your emotions.
He Lin,
you don't need to beat around the bush.
Just say it clearly.
Even if I say it clearly, it's still you.
You definitely burned
our cattle shed.
What evidence do you have to prove
that I burned your cattle shed?
Officer,
he's making false accusations.
This person never tells the truth.
You can ask around in the village.
He has conflicts with so many people.
He Lin,
just for throwing firecrackers
into our yard late at night,
and playing music early in the morning
to keep me from sleeping,
I knew
you'd get your comeuppance sooner or later.
Sure enough,
you deserve it.
What are you doing?
The police are investigating.
What's your name?
Liu Bo.
So you're neighbors?
I must have done something terrible in my past life
to have such bad luck
being his neighbor.
It's irritating.
You think I enjoy being your neighbor?
Do you two have a conflict?
No conflict.
Don't even know him.
Karma.
This is karma.
The Fire Goddess has shown her power.
Tongsheng.
What's the situation on your end?
We didn't find
ignition source or combustion improver at the scene.
The place where the fire started
was where weeds were stored.
It's easy for a fire to start there.
We can't confirm the specifics yet.
Jiang Li found
some white powder at the scene.
We'll need to run tests
to determine its composition.
The remains on my end
are severely charred.
Initial assessment suggests
the victim wasn't burned alive.
It seems the body was dumped after death.
Based on how
scattered the bones are,
it's likely the body was dismembered.
Dismembered?
But the source and identity of the remains
haven't been confirmed yet.
However, He Lin has conflicts
with most people in the village.
Especially with that Liu Bo.
They're neighbors,
and their conflict is the most obvious.
Let's split up.
Even though Captain Shen isn't here,
our team is still functioning.
If anything comes up,
report back immediately.
Let's go.
He added egg whites.
I thought so.
This looks really delicious.
That's easy to do.
I'll make some barbecue for you when I have time.
I know how to.
[Refuse] [Answer]
[Wu Yong]
Look.
Hello, Chief Wu. Please go ahead.
Shen Ye.
It's like this.
There's a last-minute arrangement from above.
You need to go to the Party School for training.
The class is this afternoon.
Such short notice?
Yes.
Alright, I understand.
The team has arranged
for me to go to the Party School for training.
Now?
Didn't you already ask for leave?
It's a last-minute arrangement, isn't it?
Alright then.
Well, you have to go for the training.
Go ahead.
I'll be going then.
Go and come back soon.
Dad,
don't wait for me for dinner.
You're not coming back for dinner?
No.
Let's talk this through calmly.
Take it easy.
This guy is quite tight-lipped.
He just won't confess
where he hid the cattle.
Right.
In my opinion,
if he continues to disrupt
our blessing ceremony,
we should expel him from Liu Village.
Yes, expel him from Liu Village.
Are you all crazy?
Expel him from Liu Village.
Drive him out.
Drive him out!
[Imperial Ancestral Temple]
Alright, alright, alright.
Everyone, please calm down.
Stop arguing.
The blessing ceremony
is about to begin.
The ghost fire is coming.
Ghost fire.
Class dismissed.
Let's go, Mentor.
Let's head back together.
What's going on?
You seem distracted.
After studying all afternoon,
how much have you absorbed?
In your class,
how could I dare to be distracted?
Of course, I've absorbed
as much as you've taught.
You're just smooth-talking.
Let me tell you,
it's rare to have
the opportunity to sit in a classroom.
Take it seriously
and improve yourself.
Don't worry, Mentor.
Don't embarrass your mentor.
To be honest with you,
among this group of young cadres,
I have high hopes for you.
Back then, I wanted to join the criminal investigation department,
but my dad wouldn't agree no matter what.
If it weren't for you, Mentor,
saying that I had the potential,
my dad still wouldn't agree even now.
I'm quite curious too.
You only met my father once.
How did he agree
for me to become a police officer?
You insisted on doing it yourself.
Who could stop you?
Without you, Mentor,
I wouldn't be where I am today.
Tell me, are you
satisfied with being
a deputy captain?
No.
You are my role model.
I hope
to become someone like you.
What's the point of being like me?
In two more years,
I'll be stepping back from the front lines.
You're different.
Your potential
hasn't been fully realized yet.
Fully realize it?
My dad probably couldn't handle that.
Why?
Maybe he's afraid I'll die in the line of duty.
You're a police officer and you're still afraid of danger?
Actually, the greatest danger
isn't sacrificing oneself.
Then what is it?
Didn't you just say in class,
"Initial aspirations are easily lost.
Review the old to learn the new."
Without our initial aspirations,
we lose our principles.
The prerequisite for protecting the people
is to safeguard our own beliefs.
Belief is crucial.
You seemed distracted this afternoon.
I didn't expect you to actually take it in.
Are you showing off to me?
No.
I just had a lot of thoughts.
I feel that what you said
was particularly right.
I still have some things to do.
You go ahead.
Mentor, I'll wait for you.
No need.
You go on your way.
Sis,
burned to this degree,
I'm afraid this is probably
the limit of what human effort
can achieve in a body burning case.
Although it hasn't completely
turned to ashes,
there're only
these large pieces of bone left.
The flesh and organs
have basically all burned away.
This...
How are we supposed to investigate this?
I once heard
from an experienced employee
who had worked at a crematorium
for many years.
He said that people with terminal illnesses who take a lot of medication
or those who are obese,
when cremated,
produce a large amount of fat.
The blood seeps into the bones,
and after complete combustion,
there's a high probability
that their bones will appear red.
That's really true, Sis.
Look,
this piece of bone
that isn't as heavily charred,
its interior
is already faintly red.
I have a theory.
Later, take this piece of bone
and have it undergo
a metal cation test.
To estimate the time of death?
Alright.
Less than 90 degrees.
It's a male.
Okay, Sis.
I'll send it for testing now.
[East Village Entrance]
Chief Wu,
this surveillance camera
is the closest to the cattle shed.
It's also the only one
that captured useful information.
Seeing this kind of footage
late at night is quite creepy.
It really looks like a female ghost.
The other cameras didn't capture this person.
There are only five surveillance cameras in the entire village.
There are many blind spots.
[Baolin Village] [Shuangbai Village] [Songshan Village] [Qisheng Village] [Liu Village]
It seems only this camera is useful.
To go to He Lin's cattle shed,
one would definitely be caught on camera.
However, we currently can't confirm
the direction this suspicious person came from or went to.
Based on the video,
we need to investigate
all the women in the village with this body type.
We must find her.
-Yes.
Yes.
[Police]
Taking responsibility
is a quality
and also a responsibility.
We must have the courage to face difficulties
and challenges head-on.
We should be brave in taking responsibility.
Chief Wu,
everything is normal on my end.
There are no new discoveries.
We must adhere to
[Theory and Practice, Courage to Take Responsibility, Serving the People]
the people-centered development philosophy
and focus on people's livelihoods.
They arranged for you to go study,
surely because there's going to be some action.
You focus on your studies first.
I'll have someone keep an eye on Shen Yi.
The unidentified powder found at the scene
is phosphoric acid,
the product after the combustion
of phosphine.
The source of the fire can also be basically determined.
It's the phosphorus fire from Liu Village.
This phosphorus fire
is what we commonly refer to as
ghost fire.
That's correct.
[Stay Loyal to the Party, Serve the People, Be Impartial in Law Enforcement, and Be Well-disciplined]
[China Fire Rescue]
This phenomenon, ghost fire,
can sometimes be seen
in rural graveyards
during dry summer seasons.
This is because human bones
contain phosphorus.
As the body decomposes,
it produces phosphine.
Phosphine has an extremely low ignition point
and is highly prone to spontaneous combustion.
The flame after combustion is blue.
If other elements are mixed in,
it can also turn green, red,
or other special colors.
People find ghost fire scary
because when walking at night
and passing by a graveyard,
seeing flames
of unusual colors
can be quite eerie.
Of course, these flames
seem to follow you as you walk.
This phenomenon has a scientific basis.
In fluid dynamics,
areas with higher flow velocity
have lower pressure.
A person's movement
can cause the flames to move along with them.
The phosphorus fire drifting from a distant graveyard
to He Lin's cattle shed
is a low-probability event,
but not impossible.
The only remaining question now is
that the phosphoric acid residue at the scene
is of unusually high purity.
Let's take a look at
this surveillance video.
This corroborates
Adviser Xu's conclusion.
[East Village Entrance]
The fire source is the phosphorus fire
following behind the suspect.
So I believe
the fire in the cattle shed
was most likely an accident.
Let's pay attention to
the backpack behind the suspect.
Judging from
the shape of this backpack,
the skeletal remains at the scene
were likely brought
by the suspect.
Therefore, inside this backpack
there's a high possibility
of dismembered body parts...
Let me interrupt for a moment.
What was in the backpack
was not fresh dismembered body parts,
but rather
a skeleton that had been dead for many years.
To be precise,
it should be the remains of someone who died thirty years ago,
male skeletal remains.
This person dumped a bag of human bones
in someone else's cattle shed.
That's why
the charred bones we saw that day
were so scattered.
So where did these bones come from?
Did someone dig up someone's grave?
That can't be.
There couldn't be such a deep grudge, right?
When we were investigating in Liu Village before,
during our search,
we didn't find any suspicious women.
Now,
the identity of the remains and the suspect
both need to be re-confirmed.
What is this suspect trying to do?
Dressed like a female ghost,
and digging up someone's grave.
No,
the more I think about it, the more scared I get.
Did you only investigate women?
Yes.
Play it again.
[Stay Loyal to the Party, Serve the People, Be Impartial in Law Enforcement, and Be Well-disciplined]
[China Fire Rescue]
[East Village Entrance]
Stop.
This person walks with a swaying head,
top-heavy and unsteady.
Zoom in on the feet.
He's wearing shoes
that are smaller than his feet.
It's a male.
A man disguised as a woman to commit the crime.
[Liu Village Party Affairs and Village Affairs Publicity Bulletin Board]
Officer,
why are you back again?
What's it about this time?
Uncle Liu,
the situation is quite urgent.
This time we need to investigate
the men in the village.
The men?
How did it change to men now?
Wasn't it about women last time?
We suspect
someone deliberately set the fire.
Uncle Liu, we hope you can take the lead
in cooperating with our work.
I'll cooperate.
I will.
Mainly look for
recently dug graves,
with or without tombstones.
Don't miss any.
Don't touch anything you're not sure about.
Please cooperate with the investigation, everyone.
It's not much trouble.
Just wear these few pairs of shoes
and walk a few steps, that's all.
Please cooperate, everyone.
Let me through.
What are you doing? What's going on here?
Let her in.
What's going on?
This... What are you doing?
Just standing here,
putting on airs.
Pretending to be big shots, huh?
Why is all
this self-righteous,
family-betraying attitude?
Why are you so short-sighted
and disrespectful to gods?
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Believe in the Fire Goddess,
and you'll surely receive protection,
without a scratch.
What's the matter?
The guesthouse is closed?
No more shredded potatoes for sale?
All that hustle and bustle,
the endless stream of customers,
and all those big bills,
you don't want them anymore?
Just letting it all flow away like spring water to the east?
Is that what you mean?
The white bones in He Lin's cattle shed,
that's a stark lesson,
that's the punishment for impulsiveness.
You understand?
Wait a moment, wait a moment.
Go on, continue.
If you don't have no reverence
for the Fire Goddess,
what will happen next,
no one can know.
Not even I can.
Be more mindful.
Well.
What, what's going on, Officer?
You said in He Lin's cattle shed, there was a pile of white bones?
Yes, that's right.
How do you know it's a pile of white bones?
The fire was so intense.
We only knew after testing.
Well,
the Fire Goddess told me.
What Fire Goddess?
What retribution?
Lesson?
Those are all feudal superstitions.
As to what the specific situation is,
we still hope everyone
will cooperate with our investigation.
As for how you
knew
it was a pile of white bones,
come with us for a while.
What do you mean?
What are you doing?
What are you messing with?
You have no reverence at all.
You guys...
She deserves it.
Let's begin.
How come she's being taken away?
Isn't that a woman's embroidered shoe?
Yes, it is.
Chun.
Look.
Just by looking at this soil,
it's clear it's been recently dug up.
Bai Zhi, we've found it.
We've found it, Chun.
Fang Yu,
come here.
Start digging.
[Unnatural Fire]
[Unnatural Fire: Fire Safety Knowledge Session]
Ghost Fire is actually phosphorus.
When phosphorus reacts with water or alkali, it produces phosphine,
a colorless gas that can spontaneously ignite.
Phosphine has a low ignition point.
When it burns,
it produces a white flame with a bluish-green tint.
The phosphine released into the air during the decomposition
of human and animal corpses
creates the phenomenon known as "ghost fire."
[Fire Safety: Everyone's Responsibility]