[Unnatural Fire]
[Episode 35]
Adviser Xu.
Why do I feel that
you seem to have a crush on Chun?
Well, I can tell you very
honestly that
I care about her very much.
That's true.
I also care about her very much.
Now that she's abroad
and living alone in a foreign country,
I will care about her even more in the future.
Chun
won't stay abroad for too long.
She's a good forensic doctor.
She will definitely come back.
Nothing is definite.
You don't want her to come back?
What I want doesn't matter at all.
But I understand one thing.
Look. People can't even
control their own fates,
but they even want to control others.
Don't you think that's just wishful thinking?
That's right.
For example,
I didn't want her to go abroad,
but because of your help,
I couldn't stop her.
Studying abroad was
Chun's own wish.
What rights did I have to interfere?
No, no.
Don't misunderstand.
What I mean is that
even though Chun is usually
so close to us,
when it comes to crucial moments,
it seems that
she only listens to
you, who is her senior schoolmate.
You've hit the nail on the head.
Do you know what the problem is?
What is it?
Look.
You two always
hanged out together every day.
You two seemed very close,
but in fact, your relationship
was just like buddies.
Right?
Chun is very straightforward.
She's a forensic doctor,
but more importantly, she's a girl.
A woman
needs emotional value
and emotional support.
As a man,
it's not just about
saying it.
You need to take action.
Yes.
I'm usually too busy with work.
That's the biggest excuse.
Who isn't busy?
Am I not busy?
If you truly value this person
and like her,
no matter what you do, you'll
definitely give priority to her.
Right?
When she's in a bad mood,
you can take her out to have a meal
and cheer her up.
When she's feeling down and depressed,
you can take her to do some boxing
to let her vent it out.
These are all basic tricks.
Adviser Xu.
Don't you think so?
Chun can box too?
Her boxing skills are very good.
I can barely keep up with her now.
Adviser Xu,
stop pondering on it.
It's not something you can ponder on anyway.
Just eat.
The noodles are getting mushy.
What about you, Mr. Han?
When will you return to Americas?
I'll leave here in three days.
Oh, right.
Is there anything
you want to give to Chun?
Give it to me.
I'll deliver it to her.
No need.
With you taking care of her,
she won't be short of anything.
Alright.
That's all for our chat then.
Okay?
I still have something to do.
Besides, this place
is really unbearable.
I'm sorry.
Are you blind?
No, no, no.
Go get two bottles of mineral water.
Hurry up!
Get me an ice pack!
An ice pack!
Let me take a look.
There are no blisters. It's not serious.
Just wipe it.
It should be fine.
You think this is fine?
I'm fine just because you said so?
You're a firefighter,
b-but who am I?
What's this?
Ice water.
What did I ask for?
I asked for an ice pack! Understand?
I'm sorry.
We really don't have any ice packs here.
Stop yelling.
Apply it to your wound for 20 minutes and it'll be fine.
It... It's alright now.
Adviser Xu.
Don't always use such an
outdated method.
Can't you come up with something new?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Your friend is angry.
Please apologize to him for me.
It's okay.
Just get back to work.
I'm sorry.
"Always use."
Mom,
I've arrived at the house where I live.
Don't worry.
[Alarm]
I'd like you guys to
know each other better.
[Chapter 12: Examining Attraction and Close Relationships]
Let's start here.
Jin Chun.
Here.
[Chapter 12: Examining Attraction and Close Relationships]
I'm Jin Chun
from China.
Good.
Can you give us an introduction
about yourself?
Of course.
My name is Jin Chun.
And I used to be
a forensic scientist in the criminal investigation team.
Why did you
come to study psychology?
I got to know a lot of people
as a forensic scientist
in most cases
through their bodies.
As I examined them,
they imposed psychological labels
on myself, too.
So,
I decided to
have a break
and go to study... to study psychology
[Chapter 12: Examining Attraction and Close Relationships]
and let myself be mentally stronger.
I think if I
ever have a chance to speak for the dead again,
I hope
I can be stronger and more powerful.
I will give each
and everyone of them a better voice as clear as possible.
Thank you.
Okay.
The next one.
Hello, everyone.
My name is Guan.
[Han Jun] [Jin Chun]
[1. Planed to make Chun stay abroad]
[2. Came to the downstairs of Chun's apartment]
[3. Helped Chun handle the procedure to go abroad]
[4: Helped the director solve the welfare house's funds problems]
[5. High school classmates met again 18 years later]
[6. Happened to appear when climbing the mountain]
[7. I stood her up on a rainy day, and he appeared]
[8. Boxing, Dinner]
Twenty-seven.
He changed his car.
What's the license plate number?
The license plate number.
Xu.
Hello, Shen Ye.
I suspect that Han Jun
has been tailing Chun.
What's going on?
How about this?
Go to Chun's neighborhood now
to check the surveillance videos.
Then pay attention to
a white SUV.
What's the license plate number?
I can't see it clearly now.
I need to go to the welfare house.
Let's discuss the details when we meet.
Okay.
Mr. Zhang.
Hello.
Mr. Shen.
I've sorted them out.
Come here and watch them.
Come on. Let me watch them.
You want to watch the video from the 5th,
right?
Yes, please play it first.
[Northwest corner]
How about this?
Please rewind it to the part from the 3rd and let me check.
The part from the 3rd.
[Northwest corner]
It's still during this time period.
Okay.
[Northwest corner]
Please rewind it for me.
I'll record it.
Alright.
[Northwest corner]
Director.
Tongsheng, you're here.
Come in.
Come on. Have a seat.
Are you here for something?
Yes, of course there's something.
I'd like to ask
where I can watch the welfare house's
surveillance videos.
You can watch them right in my office.
What's wrong?
I've been studying surveillance cameras recently, haven't I?
I just want to check
whether there are any blind spots for
the surveillance cameras in our welfare house.
Just check them.
Let me know if you find any issues.
Okay.
Come on.
[Surveillance]
[Northwest corner]
Chun.
Mom, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
How is it?
Are you getting used to the food there?
Are the living conditions good?
Are you getting along well with your classmates?
Mom, you're asking me so many questions.
Which one do you want me to
answer first?
Just answer them one by one slowly.
It's pretty good.
The food is good, and the accommodation is nice.
Look. This is the place I'm living in.
How nice it is.
It looks alright.
Didn't you say it was hard to find a place to live in?
[Northwest corner]
You already know that
it was hard for me to find a place to live in.
You're quite impressive.
Indeed.
While you're there,
I surely have to be concerned
[Pay attention to children, accept them and try to understand them with sincerity.]
about every aspect, don't I?
Chun.
[Mic On] [Speaker On] [Camera On]
Tongsheng?
How is it? Pretty good, huh?
It's pretty good.
I have good health and a good mood.
Everything's good.
What about you?
So you're here to visit my mom in the welfare house today?
Yes, I'm here to visit Director Zeng.
Oh, right.
I'd like to share some gossip
about Shen Ye with you.
Recently, he...
Director.
Could you give us some privacy?
What a snooper.
Go ahead with your chat.
Let's talk later.
Alright. Let's talk later, Mom.
Oh, my God!
I've been away for just a few days,
and there's already gossip about Shen Ye?
What gossip is it?
Has Han Jun contacted you recently?
Han Jun?
He just sends me a few messages a day.
What's wrong?
You have to be wary of Han Jun.
I think he has been tailing you all this time.
Tailing me?
I've checked several surveillance cameras.
[Mic On] [Speaker On] [Camera On]
As for the places where you've been to,
he has appeared in all of them.
Moreover,
he's very familiar with your
whereabouts and movements.
Is it possible that
during that period,
he was helping me with the formalities for going abroad,
so our schedules
might have overlapped?
I've already asked Shen Ye
to check earlier surveillance videos
to see when he started
tailing you.
[Mic On] [Speaker On] [Camera On]
Is your current residence
arranged by Han Jun?
No.
I found it myself.
But he did want to help me find a place,
and I refused.
Alright.
From now on,
if there's anything that seems
not right to you,
contact the embassy immediately.
Let's stay in touch anytime.
Okay.
I got it.
You guys should be careful, too.
Don't worry.
Take good care of yourself.
[Mic On] [Speaker On] [Camera On]
Okay.
Who is it?
Jin Chun, are you in your room?
What's the matter?
I'd like to discuss something
with you face to face.
Could you come out now?
Wait a moment.
Sorry for the trouble.
Ma'am, what's wrong?
Here's the thing.
I can't let you rent
this room anymore.
You need to move out tomorrow.
Why?
Actually, I'm not
asking you to move out for no reason.
Here's the thing.
Two years ago, my son
ran away from home.
This room is his.
I haven't heard
any news about him all this time.
Just today, I found out that
he had been put in jail for fighting.
The jail called me and asked me
to pick him up tomorrow.
Look. I can't let my son
come back home without a place to live in.
So, you'll
have to move out tomorrow.
But you've
signed a contract with me.
You can't just break the contract like this.
Where do you think I can live?
If I hadn't had no choice,
I wouldn't have done this.
I...
How about this?
According to the contract, I can
compensate you for your losses.
During this period,
you can stay in a hotel first.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
I've finally found my son.
Just let us get reunited properly.
Okay?
Thank you.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
I've really caused you trouble.
Alright.
Give me some time
to find a new place.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Hello?
Do you have a house
for rent?
That house was rented out yesterday.
I forgot to remove it from the listing.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Hello?
I saw your rental
information online.
Yes.
When do you want to move in?
I want to move in
before 12 o'clock tomorrow.
That's not okay.
The current tenant won't move out until next week.
Next week?
Alright.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
[Medical School of Columbia University]
[Richard]
[Richard invites you to video call]
Senior.
What's the matter?
Chun.
What's wrong?
You seem unhappy.
Did something happen?
Nothing.
Well, our landlady met
a problem today.
I might have to move out by noon tomorrow.
Well, what's going on?
This is so sudden. Where can you
find a place to live in now?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Is the landlady there?
Ask her to come over.
I'll reason with her.
It's fine.
There's no need to reason with her.
I've already talked this over with her.
What's more,
I've already started looking for a new place.
You're unfamiliar with
the surroundings and the people there.
How can I not worry?
[Mic On] [Speaker On] [Camera On]
There's nothing to worry about.
I used to be a police officer.
Who cares whether you were a police officer or not?
Really. Let's do this.
You should move into my place.
That house of mine is vacant anyway.
Right?
If you move into that house,
I won't have to worry, either.
Senior,
I appreciate your kindness.
I won't move into your house.
These are all small matters.
I can solve them myself.
Okay?
Actually, I wanted to ask you
to do me a favor.
My house has been vacant,
and I'm worried about it.
If you move into that house,
you can help me look after the house.
Right?
Then how about this?
I definitely won't
move into your house.
But if you need me
to look after the house,
I can go check on it when I'm free.
Okay?
I'm still busy now.
I'll call you back later.
[Mic On] [Speaker On] [Camera On]
Okay?
Let's talk later.
Bye bye.
Is it this hard to rent a place?
Hello.
I've noticed that you have
a secondary bedroom for rent.
Is that right?
That's right.
How many people are there?
Just me.
When are you going to move in?
If possible, I want to move in
before 12 o'clock tomorrow.
Okay.
Currently, there's
a Chinese girl living there.
When you come,
just knock on the door directly.
But you need to pay me
a 20% deposit first.
No problem.
Thank you.
That's great.
Hello.
Are you Chinese?
Yes.
What's the matter?
I've rented
the secondary bedroom here.
This apartment isn't for rent.
Are you mistaken about this?
I don't think so.
I've just confirmed the information with the landlord.
Then I'll also
check with the landlord.
Let me show it to you.
What's going on?
This is the rental information online.
[Apartment Information]
Look.
[Han Jun] [Refuse] [Answer]
Now let me find the contract and show it to you.
Senior, what's wrong?
Chun,
have you found a place to live in?
If you haven't found it,
you should
really move into my place.
I'm here.
That will be convenient
for both of us.
I'll text you the address now.
No need, Senior.
I'm still looking for it.
I won't trouble you anymore.
I'm a bit busy now.
I'll call you back
later, okay?
Because a girl
is here to rent a room.
Alright.
I understand. Okay.
Look. This is the contract.
But the landlord
didn't rent out the room.
The information you found online is all fake.
There have been many
cases like this recently.
You've been scammed.
Oh, God.
I'm so sorry about that.
I've bothered you.
I'm sorry.
Then I'll...
I'll leave now.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Which city in China are you from?
I'm from Beixun.
No wonder your accent sounds
so familiar.
How about this?
You can stay in my place temporarily.
I mean...
you can hardly find a place to live in
within such a short time.
As a girl,
you can't sleep in the street
tonight, huh?
It's fine.
I can find a place by myself.
Thank you.
I don't mean anything else.
I just think that
we're both Chinese,
and we're both girls,
so we can look after each other.
My secondary bedroom is still vacant.
It's quite convenient.
Come in.
Alright.
Thank you.
As soon as I find a place to live in,
I'll move out right away.
I'm really sorry for the trouble. Thank you.
It's okay.
I haven't asked your name yet.
My name is Jin Chun.
What's your name?
My name is Lian Xiangqin.
Xiangqin.
Here's a new pair of slippers.
They've never been used.
You can use them from now on.
Thank you.
So, about these...
About these shoes,
is there any specific rule for placing them?
After I take off my shoes,
can I put them
here?
There is no specific rule.
You can put them wherever you like.
My boyfriend and I
place them casually, too.
Boyfriend?
I'm alone now.
He's not here now.
Jin Chun.
How long are you going to stay abroad?
About two years.
I'm here to study.
Which school?
What major?
I'm studying in the psychology training class at Chad Hahn University.
Chad Hahn University?
That's good.
If we get along well,
you can live here
for two years.
Thank you so much.
If it weren't for you today,
I didn't know where
I could stay tonight.
You're welcome.
These flowers smell so nice.
Right?
Natural fragrances
are much better than artificial perfumes.
I also like the scent
of natural fragrances very much.
It's quite soothing.
Do you usually
not wear perfume?
I can't smell any perfume on you.
That's right. I never wear perfume.
I don't really like perfume.
Me, neither.
Thank you.
Let me show you
the room where you'll be staying.
Okay.
Come on. This way.
This is your room.
The lighting is so good.
The light is great.
The room is nice, too.
Thank you very much.
I really like it.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
How about this?
To express my gratitude,
I'll cook dinner for you tonight.
Sure!
Just bring your suitcase inside first.
Alright.
What's wrong?
Does the food not suit your taste?
It's not like that.
It's very delicious.
You don't need to consider my feelings.
If you don't like it,
just tell me.
Or you can tell me what kind
of cuisine you prefer,
what flavor you like
and how your appetite is.
I'll make different dishes for you next time.
No need.
This flavor is great.
This is your hometown cuisine, right?
Yes.
It's just that your cooking
reminds me of
a close friend.
His cooking is also very delicious.
Is your friend also from Beixun?
You're so good at cooking.
Who taught you these skills?
I just love to eat,
so,
I like to study cooking skills when I have time.
I've learnt them all by myself.
How old are you?
You look
a bit younger than me.
I'm 34 now.
You're indeed two years younger than me.
Before coming here,
were you working as a psychologist in China?
No.
I studied forensic medicine for my bachelor's degree.
After graduation, I've been working in
the public security unit.
Since you worked as a public servant,
why did you decide
to study abroad?
It isn't that easy to get admitted to
the training program at Chad Hahn University.
I just wanted to further my studies.
It's quite difficult to get into Chad Hahn University indeed.
Fortunately, I have a senior schoolmate
who helped me a lot.
Otherwise, I might not have been able to come.
Is it the senior schoolmate
who keeps calling you?
Yes.
He's so nice to you.
Is he pursuing you?
No.
Not at all.
So what kind of person is he?
Let me get you a bowl of soup.
I'm quite good at making soup.
Taste it.
[Alarm]
What are you doing?
Don't use this mobile phone
alarm ringtone anymore.
I'm really annoyed.
Well...
Are you crazy?
What's going on?
[Northwest corner]
This is a surveillance video from the welfare house.
Look at this white car.
No matter where Chun went,
this car always appeared.
Fast forward it a bit more.
This part was captured
by the telescope in my house.
This white car
once appeared in the Han Group, too.
And Han Jun
once got into this car.
This car also once appeared
outside Chun's apartment.
I've looked into it, too.
From Chun's home to the Criminal Investigation Division,
from morning to night,
Han Jun showed up
at random times.
This person is definitely suspicious.
I've also shared this
information with Chun.
She said she would be careful.
Why don't we ask her to come back?
There's no rush.
This training
is quite a rare chance for her.
Let's take it one step at a time.
But the most important thing right now is that
we absolutely cannot let Han Jun leave China.
He has told me that in three days,
he'll go to Americas.
Three days.
There are only three days left. How can we stall him?
He was only tailing her.
There was no substantial criminal act.
That's why I've been thinking about
what the real problem is exactly.
How about this?
I'll inform
Chief Wu of this first.
Let's get prepared in advance.
There are still three days left.
As soon as he slips up,
we'll take action immediately.
That's all we can do for now.
[Han Jun] [Jin Chun]
[Han Jun]
[A countdown to Han Jun's departure from China: 61 hours and 59 minutes]
Jin Chun.
I'm really sorry.
I must have scared you this morning.
I want to apologize to you.
My behavior this morning
was really inappropriate.
But at that moment, I really
couldn't control my emotions.
So,
I just rushed in.
I didn't mean to do that.
And recently,
I've been living alone.
I truly forgot that you were here.
I didn't tell you my living habits
in advance.
That's just my fault.
So, I'm here
to apologize to you.
I'm sorry.
If you have any living habits,
you should have told me in advance.
I would definitely respect you.
But you shouldn't have done that just now,
suddenly
rushing in like a mad woman.
By doing that,
you invaded my privacy.
If we can't even
respect each other,
why should we still
live under the same roof?
Yes, yes,
What you said is right.
That's why I feel...
very sorry.
So, can you please not leave?
I've even made breakfast for you.
Because I'd like to apologize to you.
I know it was my fault.
I'm sorry.
Stop crying.
I won't leave.
From now on, if you have any habits,
you need to tell me.
Understand?
I'll tidy up my things
and then eat the breakfast you made.
Come on.
So this is Beixun-style breakfast?
Just eat now.
Actually,
the good friend from Beixun
I've been telling you about
is my boyfriend.
After living with him for a long time,
many of my habits
have become the same as his.
My taste
has also changed a lot accordingly.
I see.
I'm sorry for what I did just now.
I couldn't control my emotions.
Because since I was a kid,
I've had neurasthenia.
I can't stand those high-frequency sounds
from mobile phone alarm ringtones.
Your alarm clock...
I just...
lost control of my emotions at that moment.
When I was a kid, it was always my mom
who woke me up.
After my mom passed away,
I suffered from insomnia and anxiety
for a very long time.
Only after I got to know my boyfriend
was I able to sleep well again.
He has a good sleep schedule.
He also goes to bed early and wakes up early.
He doesn't need an alarm clock.
So,
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
I'm the one who should apologize.
I really didn't know
about your condition.
I'll be more careful in the future.
I'll turn down the volume of my phone.
Well, do you need me to wake you up?
That... That won't be necessary.
My boyfriend has left something nice
to me.
Your boyfriend is quite thoughtful.
Jin Chun.
Do you have someone whom you fancy now?
I don't have time to think about such things.
What about that senior schoolmate
who kept helping you?
Don't you have any feelings for him?
Feelings?
He and I
are just
senior and junior simply.
But he is indeed very nice to me.
I'm very grateful to him.
That's all.
Now with the heavy load on my brain,
I really can't think about anything else.
I just want to come here and study hard.
Studying hard is enough.
It's so delicious. The food you made is good.
Then you should eat more.
Where are the cardboard boxes
I've put in that corner?
When I was doing some cleaning this morning,
I threw them away for you.
Who told you to throw them away?
I saw that they were already dirty
and probably couldn't be used anymore,
so I...
Before you threw them away,
couldn't you ask for my opinion first?
I'm sorry.
It was indeed my fault.
I should have told you first.
Do you know what those
cardboard boxes
mean to me?
My boyfriend left
those things to me!
[You need to go out to enjoy sunshine when the weather is fine. Don't stay at home all this time, or mushrooms will sprout on you.]
[Baby, you need to go to bed early and get up early.]
Shen Ye.
Xu, here's the thing.
Recently, I've looked through
the surveillance videos of public areas.
There are a few shots of Han Jun in these videos.
His schedule seemed normal.
He was just handling business as usual.
After I sort them out,
I'll send them to you.
Alright.
How's your investigation?
Have you found anything?
I haven't...
found any issues yet.
That's normal.
He spends most of his time
at the Han Group.
He usually lives there, too.
It's indeed difficult to find a breakthrough.
Yeah.
So you went out?
I was thinking about
taking my grandma to see my father's grave.
However,
that grave is a bit too far.
I'm trying to find a way to move it back here.
I'm on the way now.
Alright.
I'll call you if anything comes up.
Okay. Be careful on the way.
I was thinking about taking my grandma
to see my father's grave.
However, that grave is a bit too far.
I'm trying to find a way to move it back here.
You haven't been back to China for 18 years.
Why did you come back this time?
Han Pei asked me to come back.
He asked me to come back
and attend Han Kun's funeral.
But my purpose was...
to come back
and relocate my mom's ashes.
[[A countdown to Han Jun's departure from China: 50 hours and 58 minutes]
Here.
[Zou Zhiwei]
Are you sure you haven't received
any application to relocate the ashes?
Definitely not.
[Refuse] [Answer]
[Shen Ye]
Shen Ye.
Xu.
About what I've told you before,
I've looked into the matter of taking ashes out of China.
Han Jun is definitely going to
take Zou Zhiwei's ashes out of China.
The household registration location
is at the Ningjiang Police Station.
I've already
contacted the chief there.
I'll text you the number.
If you have any questions,
just call him directly
and talk to him.
Okay. Thank you.
Hello?
Hello, Chief Yan.
I'm Shen Ye's colleague,
Xu Tongsheng from the Fire Investigation Department.
Captain Shen has told me about it.
Feel free to ask about whatever you want to know.
I want to inquire about someone named...
Zou Zhiwei.
Z-h-i for Zhi, and W-e-i for Wei.
Has anyone applied for or proceeded with
taking her ashes out of China?
Please wait a moment. I'll check it.
Do you mean the one
who passed away in 2003?
Yes.
No one has come to apply for that.
No?
Then if someone wants to apply for
or proceed with it,
how long will it take approximately?
According to the regulations,
these procedures are quite
complicated anyway.
All in all, to get it done,
it'll take at least two weeks.
Two weeks.
Okay. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Two weeks.
[Alarm]
Xiangqin.
Breakfast is almost ready.
We can eat now.
Xiangqin.
[Unnatural Fire]
[Fire Safety Knowledge Session of Unnatural Fire]
The single-station smoke and fire detection alarm
is a fire alarm device which plays
an important role in fire prevention and control.
It can accurately and promptly detect
the smoke caused by fire
and remind people at the scene
to report the fire and escape from the scene quickly.
It's highly sensitive and reliable.
Whether it's our home or a public area,
we need to equip the place with fire-fighting devices and maintain them properly.
[Fire Safety: Everyone's Responsibility]