[Unnatural Fire]
[Episode 21]
You haven't been home for days.
Every day, I couldn't see you.
And now, I finally get to see you.
I see you in the hospital.
You have no idea,
when I just received that phone call,
my blood pressure
shot up instantly.
Everything went black before my eyes.
I couldn't even walk straight.
What am I going to do with you, son?
If anything happened to you,
how would I go on living?
Why are you just staring at me?
I'm already so upset,
and you're not saying anything to comfort me.
What's wrong, son?
Did you have serious problems because of that accident?
I'm hungry.
Have some food. Come on.
Easy.
Take it easy.
Slow down, slow down.
Come on.
Just make do with this.
This boxed meal certainly can't compare to my home cooking.
While you're eating, you need to tell me
how exactly you ended up in a car accident.
It was really nothing.
I was just careless.
You're such a steady person.
You've never had a car accident, even when chasing criminals.
How could you suddenly be "careless"?
Dad,
stop asking.
I really was just careless.
Just let me finish my meal.
Alright.
Go ahead and eat.
If you say you were careless,
then so be it.
But I'm telling you, in your current condition,
you...
you can't continue working.
Okay, okay, okay.
I know.
I'll focus on recovery.
Drink slowly.
I don't want to eat anymore.
I'm tired.
You've only had a few bites...
Alright, alright.
Alright, get some sleep.
[Emergency Center]
What happened to Shen Ye?
Car accident.
Mild concussion.
He's in the hospital now.
How did it happen?
You tell me.
How did you just speak to him?
He's usually so steady
when driving.
When we go up there,
be mindful of what you say.
Don't agitate him again.
Do you understand?
You don't need to worry too much.
His attending physician
is my senior from medical school.
He said it's nothing serious.
He'll be discharged from the hospital after a couple of days.
Let's go.
Uncle Shen.
Why are you here?
We just want to check on Shen Ye
and see how he's doing.
No need.
Ye is sleeping.
It's not a good time.
You should go back.
Uncle Shen, may I ask
why he had a car accident?
Was it intentional or...
Are you asking me?
Are you asking me
why he had a car accident?
I should be the one asking you that.
Before the accident, wasn't he
with you guys?
Yes, he was with us.
You were having a meal, right?
Did you drink?
No, right?
Fine.
Since you're here,
let's lay everything out.
What's going on here?
Why has my son been
through a lot
when he has been with you lately?
First, he had a severe allergic reaction to shrimp.
He nearly died.
And then,
he's been working around the clock with you
on cases.
I never get to see him,
and he can't even eat the meals I cook.
He doesn't even check in with me anymore.
And now,
he's had a car accident.
Is it
that if he stays with you any longer,
I'll lose my son forever?
Uncle Shen,
you're taking this too seriously.
Besides,
Shen Ye knows what he's doing.
Today was just an accident.
An accident?
Right, right, right.
For outsiders like you,
it's just "an accident."
But I'm his father.
I can't bear these "accidents."
If you really consider him a friend
and want the best for him,
then stay away from him.
What exactly is your purpose?
My purpose?
I just want my son to be well.
I hope my son is safe.
That's my purpose.
What's wrong?
What do you mean by asking me that?
You know
exactly what I mean.
Ridiculous.
Is it wrong for a father to want his son
to be well?
I just want him to be safe.
Is that wrong?
Who are you to him, anyway?
What gives you the right
to talk to me like that?
Isn't that going too far?
What are you arguing about?
Do you not know what time it is?
This is a hospital. Leave now!
We're so sorry.
We'll leave right away.
We're really sorry.
Uncle, he really didn't mean it that way.
I apologize to you.
Please get some rest early.
We're leaving now.
Let's go.
Come on, let's go.
We're so sorry.
I know you're anxious,
but you need to have some sense of propriety.
I wasted my breath telling you that downstairs just now.
Let's go.
I'll take you back.
[Shen Yi] [Adoption] [He Xi]
If you really consider him a friend
and want the best for him,
then stay away from him.
Don't you think
there's something wrong with his behavior?
[Shen Yi] [Adoption]
Absolutely,
and extremely baffling.
Danggui,
do you know
where Shen Yi works?
Thank you.
Fill this out
and give it back to me.
[Small Experiment, Big Wisdom]
Hello,
are you here to
enroll your child?
Hello.
I'm actually looking for Mr. Shen Yi.
You're interested in
the science exploration class, right?
We have many
excellent teachers here.
Let me find some of their profiles for you.
No need, no need.
I'm just here
to find Mr. Shen Yi.
Young man,
let me tell you,
Mr. Shen is not good.
My kid
took his class before.
I'm telling you, the discipline was terrible.
Yeah.
Mr. Shen
only focuses on his own experiments
and doesn't manage the children at all.
This is our
Mr. Wang's profile.
You can take a look first.
No need. It's like this.
My nephew
took Mr. Shen's class before
and really liked him.
So I made a special trip here
to thank him.
I'm sorry,
but Mr. Shen Yi has already resigned.
Resigned?
Yes, he left not too long ago.
I don't get it—
at his age,
how can he be such a poor teacher?
Thank you.
You know what,
I heard that this Mr. Shen
is a professor at the Binjiang University of Technology.
If he is really a university professor,
why would he come here
to teach children?
I think your daughter's teacher
would be more suitable.
Excuse me,
I'd like to ask about something.
Where did the patient named Shen Ye
in bed nine go?
He was discharged this morning.
Discharged?
Shouldn't he
be under observation for a few more days?
It was the patient's father
who requested an early discharge.
And the patient had recovered well,
so the doctor allowed him to be discharged.
He just needs to come back for regular check-ups.
Alright, thank you for your help.
[Contact]
[Shen Ye]
Hello,
the subscriber you have dialed is powered off.
Sorry...
Hello,
this is the office of
Binjiang University of Technology.
Hello,
I'm Xu Tongsheng, the adviser from
the Fire Investigation Department of the Fire Brigade.
It's like this.
I have a few questions about
Mr. Shen Yi
that I'd like to ask you.
Are you available right now?
May I come over?
I'm sorry,
but we're about to finish work.
Why don't you come back tomorrow?
Alright.
Thank you then.
Stop knocking.
That family isn't home.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Chun.
Hey, Danggui.
Have you been in touch
with Shen Ye in the past few days?
Captain Shen has taken leave.
He hasn't contacted me these past few days.
Why don't you try his place?
I'm at his place right now.
No one's home.
Then I have no idea.
Alright, got it.
[Recents]
[Xu Tongsheng]
[Where are you?]
[I went to the hospital to see you, but they said you...]
Where are you?
I went to the hospital to see you, but they said you had been discharged.
You're not at home either.
Are you okay now?
Let me know when you see this.
Even just an emoji would be fine.
[Shen Ye]
Hey, Chun.
Hey, Senior.
Yesterday,
I went to visit a colleague of mine
named Shen Ye.
I'd like to ask
how he's doing now.
Shen Ye...
His injuries weren't severe.
Although he was discharged early,
he had already recovered
quite well by then.
In principle,
there shouldn't be any further deterioration.
When does he need a follow-up?
He's scheduled it for today.
It should be about time.
Senior,
could you please keep him there for me?
I'll come over right away.
Okay.
Please come in.
Hello.
I'm Xu Tongsheng, the adviser from
the Fire Investigation Department of the Fire Brigade.
Hello.
You're the one who called yesterday
asking about Mr. Shen Yi, right?
Yes, that's me.
Nice to meet you.
Please wait a moment.
Here, please have a seat.
Okay, thank you.
Please sit.
After receiving your call yesterday,
I thought about it.
The name, Shen Yi...
does sound familiar.
So,
I specifically looked him up
in our system today.
He was
indeed a teacher
here before,
but I'm not familiar with him.
If you don't mind my asking,
what's wrong
with Mr. Shen Yi
that requires you
to come here specifically to ask about him?
Stand properly.
Nurse.
Nurse, we're here for a follow-up.
Shen Ye.
Patient, please come with me.
This way.
Let's go.
I'm sorry,
but hospital regulations state
that patient's family members
must wait outside.
Alright then.
He's not feeling well.
Please take care of him for me.
Sure, don't worry.
Come on, be careful.
Slow down.
If you put it that way,
I do recall something.
About...
ten or so years ago,
there was an explosion
in our laboratory.
The person in charge at that time...
was named Shen Yi.
And this incident
is brought up every year
as a negative example
of the laboratory's fire safety,
so that's why it sounds familiar.
Do you know the specific details
of what happened back then?
I hadn't been transferred here at that time,
so I'm not familiar
with the details.
I can't tell you much about it.
But if you want to know
more about this,
how about...
I take you to check the archives?
That would be great.
That will do, right?
Alright,
let's go to the archives room.
Come on,
[Doctor's Office]
Senior.
Where is he now?
Take a look at this first.
[Beixun No. 1 People's Hospital Blood Analysis Report]
How much do you know
about your colleague's
previous health condition?
We just had a physical check-up last month.
He even bragged to me,
saying his health was excellent
and that all his indicators were normal.
So his liver function
absolutely couldn't have any problems.
Something's off.
Look here.
[Alanine Aminotransferase] [Aspartate Aminotransferase]
These two indicators
have risen sharply in a short period,
indicating that his liver function is compromised.
Drug poisoning?
It's possible.
Senior,
what medicine did you give him
before?
Just some basic, common medications.
They wouldn't have
caused this after taking them.
Senior,
can you do me a favor?
Don't give
this report to his family members yet.
Take me to see him directly.
I want to talk to him face-to-face.
Okay, I'll make a call.
Nurse.
The patient you helped me
sent in just now,
Shen Ye.
It's been a while now.
Are the results out?
You see,
everyone is queuing up for their examinations.
As for the results,
please be patient and wait a bit longer.
No...
[Nurse Station]
[Beixun No. 1 People's Hospital Blood Analysis Report]
[Clinical Diagnosis: Liver Function Damage]
[Archives Room]
All the files
should be here, but...
the laboratory file
is missing.
Missing?
Yeah.
All other files are here, but...
only that one is gone.
Don't worry.
I'll look for it again.
Nurse Lei!
Take us to find Shen Ye.
Dr. Liu,
Shen Ye was forcibly taken away
by his family.
Taken away?
Where did they go?
I saw them go straight downstairs.
Senior, I... I have to go.
I'll explain later.
Be careful!
Have you seen a patient
named Shen Ye?
Danggui,
Shen Ye is in danger.
Come with me now.
Chun.
Hurry up.
[Adhere to People First, Life First—Fully Enhance Public Safety Capabilities]
[Emergency Center]
Danggui,
go get the car.
Yes.
I'm really sorry.
Look at me.
I couldn't help at all.
Made you come here for nothing.
Think about it again.
Think
if there's anything else.
It doesn't need to be as detailed as the files.
That explosion incident...
was a big deal.
After all, someone died.
He was also one of our professors
at our school.
His surname was...
He.
Yes, surnamed He.
What was his full name again?
He...
Look at my memory...
He... like He... something Nian, I think.
He Runian?
Yes, yes, that's right.
He Runian.
How did you know that?
Chun,
what should we do now?
Let's see where they're staying first.
Danggui, you take the stairs.
We'll communicate via phone.
Yes.
Seventh floor.
They're on the seventh floor.
Okay. I got it.
[6th floor]
701.
Alright, I'll be right there.
Dad, where's my phone?
Still thinking about work now.
Finish your milk first.
I have your phone.
For the next few days, your phone...
I'll hold onto it for you.
I'm going out in a bit
to buy groceries.
For the next couple of days...
we won't be going back to our hometown.
It's quiet here.
You stay here
and focus on getting better first.
I'll nap for a bit.
Go ahead and nap.
I'll be back soon.
Let's go.
Knock on the door.
Captain Shen?
Captain Shen, it's me, Danggui.
Captain Shen.
Captain Shen!
It's me, Danggui!
Captain Shen.
Captain Shen, it's me, Danggui.
Danggui, knock harder!
Captain Shen!
It's me, Danggui!
Open the door!
Captain Shen!
Director Zhao.
Where's Xu Tongsheng?
I think he went to
Binjiang University of Technology.
BUT?
What did he go there for?
I don't know then.
Alright then.
When he comes back,
tell him to come see me.
Okay.
Come in!
Director Zhao,
you wanted to see me?
I heard you went to...
Binjiang University of Technology?
Yes.
I went to investigate Shen Yi.
Have you had too much free time lately?
Xu Tongsheng.
Can you understand
your position?
This is the Fire Investigation Department of the Fire Brigade.
We went to all that trouble
to have you transferred here,
not for you to
investigate personal matters.
If you keep acting like this,
with no sense of organization or discipline,
you might as well go back to your unit.
For what reason?
Just because of this little matter?
Why do you think?
Because your organizational affiliation
is originally with the unit.
How long you're temporarily transferred here
is up to me.
Director Zhao,
you never submitted the revised conclusions
for the old cases
to the criminal investigation department, right?
I don't need you
to teach me how to do my job.
Go back right now.
Get back to your unit!
No matter where I go,
I will find out the truth.
Shen Yi must
give Shen Ye some kind of drug again.
Drug?
Could Captain Shen be in danger?
Let's call the police.
Have you forgotten
you're also a police officer?
Do we have any actual evidence
that can prove
Shen Yi deliberately
wanted to harm his son?
Besides,
Shen Ye trusts him so much.
Chun.
He bought so many groceries.
I guess he's
not planning to go out anytime soon.
So what should we do?
Hello?
Chun,
I need Shen Ye's help,
but for some reason,
I can't reach him.
Where are you?
I'm at the Fire Investigation Department.
Wait for me there.
I happen to have something to tell you.
See you in a bit.
Take me to the Fire Investigation Department.
I can find
someone unfamiliar to come over while I'm there.
Shen Yi knows you too well.
Tongsheng.
Where's Shen Ye?
I need his help to investigate Shen Yi.
I know where he is.
Take a look at this first.
What's this?
Shen Yi has been giving Shen Ye
a large amount of drugs
and has cut off
his contact with the outside world.
Shen Ye has been missing for two days.
None of us can reach him.
How is he now?
He's been locked up by Shen Yi.
I know the address.
I've already reported the situation
to the captain.
He asked us to find a way
to save Shen Ye first,
and he'll handle the rest.
Drink slowly.
Who is it?
Delivery service.
Deli...
Hello, you have a local express delivery.
I didn't order any local express delivery service.
701. This is the place.
That's right.
[Speed Express]
[Binjiang University of Technology Laboratory Explosion Accident: Renowned Professor Tragically Killed]
[Why Are University Lab Explosions So Frequent? These Risks Must Not Be Ignored]
Delivery guy, wait a sec!
Hold on!
I've already reported to Chief Wu.
Fortunately,
Danggui mentioned to me
that Shen Ye keeps a spare key in his office.
I'm talking to you!
Stop!
Professor Shen.
We meet again.
What do you mean by this?
There are some things...
I don't want Shen Ye to hear,
so I made you meet me here.
I have nothing to talk to you about.
I know everything you've done.
He Xi!
You're very familiar with this name, aren't you?
Wh-What's wrong?
There's a surveillance camera in the living room.
If the camera can also listen in,
what if Shen Yi is listening?
What should we do now?
We can't get in anymore.
Tongsheng, are you there?
There is a camera in Shen Yi's living room.
I don't know if there's
audio monitoring too.
Check
if Shen Yi is wearing
an earpiece.
If he is,
just cough once.
He coughed twice.
No audio monitoring.
No, that's not right.
That means there's both audio monitoring
and the video feed.
How did you figure that out?
Tacit understanding.
Let me tell you a story.
Twenty years ago...
Professor Shen
was in charge of an experimental project.
At that time, he was truly...
renowned and full of ambition.
And that experimental project
carried all of his ambitions.
However,
this project
didn't go smoothly.
After yet another failure,
Professor Shen decided to take a reckless gamble.
But this decision...
also led to devastating consequences.
That's all in the newspapers.
You called me here just to say this?
I'm saying all this
to remind you
that He Xi's father
died because of you.
If you have something to say, just say it.
Shen Ye is He Xi.
He Runian, whom you caused to die,
was his real father.
I'll tell you one more time.
He didn't die because of me.
That experiment was just an accident.
His death pained me too.
Then what was your purpose
in adopting him?
Purpose?
My colleague passed away.
Out of kindness,
I adopted his child.
Is that wrong?
You forged his identity,
[Draw a Beautiful Future]
fabricated his past,
and made him believe
that you were his biological father.
Why did you do all of that?
The doctor told me not to tell him.
He had completely lost his memory at that time.
I didn't want him to suffer
secondary trauma,
so I concealed his past.
What's wrong? It's as simple as that.
You've been drugging him
and still say you don't want to hurt him?
Adviser Xu.
You're being overly concerned about
my family affairs, aren't you?
I'll say it again, just like I did that night
at the hospital.
You have no right
to interfere in matters between my son and me.
Understand?
What's the point of you doing this?
Shen Yi's heading back.
Shen Ye.
Captain Shen.
Get him out of here first.
Come on.
Alright.
Hurry, hurry. Let's go, go, go.
Move quickly.
Go, take the stairs, take the stairs.
Come on, quickly.
Quick, quick.
Slow down.
Slow down, slow down.
Ye.
Careful, careful, careful.
Mao Mao,
you go start the car first.
Leave it to us.
Okay.
Go quickly.
What are you doing?
Let's go, go, go.
Watch his feet.
How did he get like this?
It's probably
caused by some kind of sleeping medication.
Is he in any danger?
Not exactly.
We just don't know
when he'll wake up.
Thank you both
for your hard work today.
Then... you should stay at a hotel tonight.
I'll transfer the money to you in a bit.
No need.
We can stay anywhere.
Would you like something to eat?
No, we're good.
You've worked hard.
We're leaving now.
We're off.
[The Party is in My Heart; I Will Always Follow the Party]
Our operation today
was so thrilling.
If your hands hadn't shaken,
the operation would have been perfect.
I was...
Director Zhao.
Why are you two
still wandering around here
at this hour?
Well, I...
Right, Jiang Li?
Well, Director Zhao,
Mao Mao hasn't finished his lab report.
I'm making him
finish it and give it to me.
Director Zhao, are you on duty today?
Yes.
Mao Mao,
you're always like this.
Can't you give me a break?
However, Jiang Li,
it's already so late.
The report can wait a bit longer,
right?
You should
take some time to unwind.
It's okay.
Okay, Director Zhao.
Yes.
Then, Director Zhao, we...
We're off then.
Go ahead.
I'm at Xu Tongsheng's apartment.
Check the surveillance cameras
along all possible routes from my house,
one by one.
I know it takes time...
but I need to know now
where my son is!
[Refuse] [Answer]
[Wu]
Hello?
Captain Wu,
why are you calling so late?
Is there something urgent?
It's about the joint task force.
Well,
it's actually good timing.
I was planning to talk to you about this tomorrow.
Our Adviser Xu
might have a job transfer coming up.
But there will be other colleagues
to assist you.
Adviser Xu will be transferred away?
Adviser Xu has been doing great
in the fire investigation.
Well,
something happened?
It's not like that.
It's just our standard
internal work arrangement.
What could happen?
Then you'll be losing
a capable assistant.
If I were you, I wouldn't let him go.
What were you going to
tell me earlier?
Funny enough,
Shen Ye on my side is also on leave.
I was thinking,
since our task force has just been formed,
we shouldn't let this delay our progress.
But now it seems
your situation is similar to mine.
At this rate, I guess
you and I might have to
jump in ourselves, huh?
Relax.
The work won't be affected for sure.
Is there anything else?
No.
Oh, wait.
There's one thing I've been wanting to ask you.
Well, I heard
that Adviser Xu
comes from a family of firefighters, right?
No such thing.
Who told you that?
I don't know, just something I overheard.
Maybe it's because Adviser Xu
is doing such a great job.
It just feels like
he must have been influenced by his family background,
perhaps following in his parents' footsteps or something.
Alright, alright, no problem then.
Okay.
[Unnatural Fire]
[Fire Safety Knowledge Session of Unnatural Fire]
For the safety of the lab,
such as ensuring proper storage of flammable chemicals
and following standardized procedures during experiments.
Laboratories store various chemical agents.
Fire causes are numerous,
and risks are high.
One must strictly follow laboratory safety operation regulations
and operate equipment under professional guidance
to prevent fires caused by improper procedures.
Before conducting experiments, carefully check power sources,
pipelines,
fire sources,
and auxiliary instruments and equipment.
After experimental operations,
turn off all instruments and equipment,
and return items to their proper places.
Control the amount of chemicals stored in the laboratory.
All reagents must not be mixed
and must be handled, preserved, and stored according to regulations.
[Fire Safety: Everyone's Responsibility]