[Unnatural Fire]
[Episode 3]
[Rescue]
Adviser Xu, what is this?
Let's see if the lighter
can ignite the items
sprinkled with the combustion improvers on the scene.
Can't it ignite them like this?
That mat on the scene
was burned like that.
That mat is made of anti-flaming material.
Only a big fire
could burn it down like that.
A lighter with a low heat value
may not be capable of igniting it.
Replace it with another one.
This doesn't seem to work either, Adviser Xu.
Replace it with another one again.
Idol.
Li Danggui said Chen Xue confessed that
she had used a lighter
to ignite the car.
Really? Then how do you explain this?
Chun.
This is a newly discovered stinky tofu shop.
Taste it now.
Why are you so attentive to me for no reason?
What do you mean by that?
Firstly, our relationship is good.
Secondly,
we've finished interrogating
Chen Xue.
But the result
isn't what I've hoped for.
The impact of a single evil thought
goes far beyond this.
But what we can do
is to restore the truth
as much as possible.
Taste it now.
You're both here.
Chen Xue is not the murderer.
What did you say?
I did an experiment.
With the same temperature,
humidity and other environmental conditions
as those on the day of the accident,
I sprinkled the same type of alcohol
on the same cushion
and carpet
from Han Pei's car.
But the lighter couldn't ignite them.
So the lighter wasn't the source of the fire.
Chen Xue thought she was the murderer herself.
But that's impossible.
Chen Xue is not the murderer?
That's right.
What was the cause of the explosion
and the fire?
The temperature of an ignited lighter
is between 200 to 500 degrees.
I used an alcohol lamp
and an alcohol spray gun
to ignite the items on the scene
under the same condition simultaneously.
Only the alcohol spray gun could ignite them.
So the temperature of the fire source
was at least 800 degrees.
So you mean
something with a temperature of over 800 degrees
ignited the scene?
Yes.
What is it?
I'm not sure yet.
Chun.
I noticed a detail
on the autopsy report.
There are some red spots on the left part
of the corpse's neck.
What casued those spots?
About the corpse, this is the only
part that can't be explained properly.
Some red spots were found on
the wrinkles of the victim's neck indeed.
But ordinary fire
wouldn't cause
such spotted wounds.
According to the positions and depths of the wounds
as well as the internal tissue tests,
these wounds
were not the causes of the victim's death.
Can you tell me
the exact time when these wounds appeared?
I can only say that
there are vital reactions
on these wounds.
This means these wounds
had all been formed before the victim died.
As for the exact time,
I'm not sure about it, either.
Alright.
Then I'll go back
to continue the experiment.
Shen Ye.
See you later.
[Category: 3/16 Car Fire & Murder Case]
The experimental result
from the Fire Investigation Department
shows that Chen Xue is not the murderer.
That means
thanks to the Fire Investigation Department,
we have to start over.
Chief Wu, don't worry. I...
I didn't want to
put too much pressure on you.
But as you know,
this case is very special.
Many people are watching.
I understand.
I never doubt your ability.
But you have to have your own opinions.
You can't listen to everyone indiscriminately.
Alright.
Get back to work.
Chief Wu.
Come in, please.
This is today's newspaper.
Okay. Thank you.
Close the door for me.
Okay.
Got it.
I'll ask them to close the case as soon as possible.
Let's start the experiment.
Replace it with another one.
When the mat was burnt for 20 seconds
and for 25 seconds,
compared with the actual accident vehicle
on the scene,
the fire spread traces within 20 seconds were shallow,
and after it was burnt for 25 seconds,
the mat was almost burned down.
At that time, Han Pei's car speed was probably
about 120 km/h.
How about this, Jiang Li?
Mark the accident section
on the map
and extend it 650 meters forward
to
the area that is 840 meters away.
Yes.
Is it done?
This section.
[The location of the accident] [650 meters away from the accident spot] [840 meters away from the accident spot]
Alright.
Idol.
I still don't understand.
Why should we go to
the place where the fire first started?
Captain Shen.
Why are we going to the hospital now?
Now there's an explanation for the combustion improver
and the lighter
in the car.
We haven't confirmed the identity
of the person lying in hospital now.
Our focus
is still to find the source of the fire.
is to see the fish take the bait.
This fire source probably came from
outside the car.
Then the small red spots
on the neck of the corpse
might have been caused by
an external fire source
that was hard to detect.
And this fire source's
heat value is extremely high.
If it was done by someone,
the murderer's target
was probably Han Pei.
Because we declared to the public that
one of the two brothers died, and the other got injured.
The murderer must be very concerned about
the condition of the survivor.
If Han Pei had been the survivor,
the murderer might take action again.
If Han Jun had been the survivor,
he would be in a very dangerous situation, too.
Because he knows
everything that happened at that time.
Now we need to
go to the place where the fire started and see
whether there are any clues about
the external fire source.
Let's go to the hospital now
and get ready to arrest the suspect.
Yes.
Rubber?
Take photos!
Take them back to office.
[Physical Evidence of the Fire Scene]
Captain Shen, the fish took the bait.
How come this rubber seems to have been burnt?
Do you mean that
something with a temperature of over 800 degrees
ignited the scene?
Some red spots were found
on the wrinkles of the victim's neck indeed.
But ordinary fire
wouldn't cause
such spotted wounds.
[Picture 8: Rubber Particles]
[Physical Evidence of the Fire Scene]
And this one, too.
But
the quality needs to be ensured, right?
Yes.
Don't... Don't give me bad-quality
products by that time.
Alright. So it's settled then?
Okay.
Gentlemen.
Are you two also police officers?
Yes.
We're with those two guys.
So the person who is chatting with them
is the repairman that fixed Han Pei's car?
Yes, that's Mr. Wang Xi.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Captain Shen.
Adviser Xu.
We've met each other quite often lately.
Yes, what a coincidence.
Wang Xi.
What did you do to Han Pei's car?
Tell me about it briefly.
Just regular maintenance.
What else besides the maintenance?
There was
nothing else.
Didn't you remove the tires?
The tires?
Didn't you remove them?
I did that routine
dynamic balance test for him.
How about this?
Show me
your work manual.
Danggui, go with him.
Idol.
I'll check it now.
What did you find?
Do you think there's something wrong with the tires?
There's something wrong with Wang Xi.
You're really something.
You're good, too.
You found this place.
Captain Shen!
Where is he?
What happened?
He ran away.
You two call for help now.
Xu, come with me.
Be careful.
This way!
Stop!
Xu!
Go to the left!
Stop chasing me.
I can't run anymore.
Aren't you quite good at running?
You ran so fast.
Tell me. Why did run away?
Because I didn't know
why you found me.
You didn't know?
You didn't know, and you ran away as soon as
we mentioned the tires?
What else could it be except for having a guilty conscience?
No.
Look. The car was fine
when it left from my place.
I don't know why your
friend mentioned
those tires.
Here's the situation of the investigation
about the car burning case this time.
We first checked the accident vehicle's
motor system,
fuel tank and mechanical system
thoroughly and conducted an overall analysis.
But we didn't find
any traces of human destruction.
[Picture 1: Combustion Improver] [Picture 2: Combustion Improver] [Picture 3: Lighter] [Picture 4: Lighter]
When we went back to the scene for a survey,
we found that
there were combustion improvers
and a lighter which was a fire source.
After experiments, it proved that
the lighter couldn't ignite the car.
So we speculated that
the real fire source
should be something with an extremely high heat value.
In addition, after the forensic doctor's autopsy,
there had been no explanation
for the spark marks on the victim's neck.
[Picture 1: Autopsy] [Picture 2: Autopsy]
Then we speculated that
the fire source might have come from outside the car.
So,
through the fire spread traces of
of the burning carpet,
I managed to infer
the actual ignition time.
When we once again went back to the location
where the accident vehicle had caught fire
and investigated the case,
we found
[Picture 1: Rubber Particles] [Picture 2: Rubber Particles]
some rubber particles.
Our test showed that
those rubber particles
were from the front wheel
on the side of the driver's cab of the accident vehicle.
[Picture 2: Rubber Particles]
Wang Xi.
As a repairman,
you're familiar with tires, right?
The front and back wheels of a car
are usually of the same model.
Therefore, many people
wouldn't care too much about them
while installing them.
Sometimes,
to ensure the consistency of the abrasion degree,
you might switch the front and back wheels deliberately,
Am I wrong about that?
No, you're not wrong.
But Han Pei's car was an exception.
There were obvious differences between
the front and back wheels of his car.
Once they were switched,
due to the mismatching situation,
they would have intense friction with the hubs.
You know that too, right?
The metal fragments
that have been caused during the friction
correspond with the conditions of a fire source.
Meanwhile, that's also a perfect explanation
for the spark marks on the victim's neck.
So,
we've thoroughly figured out
the truth of this case.
Han Pei went to the repair factory to get the car that day.
I think he checked the car on the spot.
But he was not a professional after all.
It was also hard for him to notice that
the tires were installed reversely.
Take care, Mr. Han.
Take care.
So he left
without noticing it.
On the day of the accident,
Han Pei and Han Jun
went to pay tribute to Han Kun.
At first,
Han Pei drove the car in the city.
The car speed wasn't very fast,
and he didn't drive very far.
The tire friction
was not too serious.
So it didn't arouse
anyone's attention.
Later, Han Pei drove the car to the suburbs.
The car speed became faster.
The tire friction
started to cause metal fragments and sparks.
They kept splashing
in all directions.
Some flew into the car through the windows.
Some went onto the neck of Han Pei, who was sitting
on the driver's seat.
Some fell onto
other parts of the car.
At this time, the friction of the tires
was big enough to make the car out of control
and ignite the car.
So the main causes
of this case
are the tires that you installed reversely.
You were quite smart.
But because of these tires,
we also found
the real cause of the fire.
Well...
Even if the tires had been installed reversely,
I might have
done it carelessly.
Carelessly?
Don't you know
how many experiments you've done?
[Picture 1: Abandoned Tires] [Picture 2: Abandoned Tires] [Picture 3: Abandoned Tires]
These tire surfaces
are consistent with the abrasion marks
I got in the lab.
They can prove that
Wang Xi conducted
a test to commit arson.
Do you have anything else to say?
All that you said was just a coincidence.
I'm just an petty employee.
Why would I
kill Han Pei, who was
such a big boss?
Yesterday afternoon,
you went to
No.1 People's Hospital, didn't you?
Why did you go there?
I... I went there to visit a friend.
Whom did you visit?
Tell me!
Just tell me!
Do you need me to go with you?
I went to the hospital just to visit...
To visit someone who was
almost killed by you.
Right?
We declared to the public that
one of the two brothers died, and the other got injured.
But we didn't say
which of them was dead or injured exactly.
You just wanted to find out
who was the person you had
taken great pains to kill.
Right?
Well, you've been talking for a long time.
You're just trying to trick me into confessing it.
I...
I told you
I had no reason to kill Han Pei.
You failed to see your mother for the last time.
Does that count?
Is that a reason?
This is your boss's statement.
You were the exclusive maintainer
for Han Pei's car.
Han Pei had a bad temper.
He once went to see you
and smashed your mobile phone.
But coincidentally,
on the day when your mobile phone was smashed,
your mother was being rescued in the hospital.
The people from the hospital
kept calling you.
But they couldn't reach you.
When you arrived,
[Death Notice]
your mother had already passed away.
That was the reason.
[Death Notice]
Han Pei deserved to die!
Doctor!
How is my mom?
The surgery went well.
The patient's basic condition is bad.
For the next period,
she'll have to stay
in the ICU for observation.
Okay.
Excuse me. I have to answer the phone.
Mr. Han.
Where are you?
Come back to the repair factory now.
Well, Mr. Han,
I have something urgent to deal with now.
I can't go back.
Cut the crap.
If you don't come back now,
just never come back.
Understand?
Well...
Mr. Han.
I've told you to come whenever I summon you.
Is it so hard?
I'm sorry, Mr. Han.
Well... W-What's wrong with your car?
Wash my car for me.
Washing your car?
Yes, wash my car.
What are you looking at?
Well, my mom is in hospital.
Hello, Wang Xi.
Due to an emergency situation, your mother
died despite our rescue efforts.
Before your mother passed away,
she even wanted to see you for the last time.
Unfortunately,
she didn't make it to the end.
Mom!
Because of Han Pei,
I failed to see my mother for the last time.
For the last time.
So you planned to
kill Han Pei?
I knew he had the habit of driving fast.
So I switched the front
and back tires of his car.
I didn't really want him to die.
I just wanted him to suffer a bit.
I thought since the car had been burnt like that,
it wouldn't leave any evidence.
In the end, you still found out about the truth.
If someone did it,
there would be traces.
It would still be the same even if it had been burnt.
If someone did it,
there would be traces.
It would still be the same
even if it had been burnt.
That's all for my report.
[China Fire Rescue]
[Stay Loyal to the Party, Serve the People, Be Impartial in Law Enforcement, and Be Well-disciplined]
Deputy Marshal Gu.
Is there any problem
with our investigation?
[Stay Loyal to the Party, Serve the People, Be Impartial in Law Enforcement, and Be Well-disciplined]
No.
No, no.
Xu is known for
being meticulous.
Every time he wrote a report,
[Gu Nuo, Deputy Marshal of the Criminal Investigation Corps of Beixun Public Security Bureau]
it would be a thick stack.
That's great. Great.
Just now...
As I've been suffering from
farsightedness recently,
when I read these
densely written characters,
it was a bit difficult for me.
Some content is too professional.
If I had only written the conclusion,
I'm afraid amateurs wouldn't be convinced.
Of course.
In fact, our Criminal Investigation Division
also needs to master
this kind of professional knowledge.
Well, Shen Ye.
Yes!
When you go back,
popularize such knowledge in your team.
Yes.
Marshal Gu.
Then we'll close
Han Pei's case.
Sure.
Alright.
So that's all
for today's meeting?
Well...
Since all the leaders are here,
I have a suggestion.
Go ahead.
I suggest that
the Fire Investigation Department and the Criminal Investigation Division
should jointly establish
a quick response system
for major fire cases.
It means that in the future,
if we encounter
any investigation work
related to fire,
our Fire Investigation Department will fully cooperate.
I, Shen Ye,
and Jin Chun
will jointly establish an investigation team
and work together.
This is good.
I'm afraid
this requires
approval from the superiors of both units.
It can't be formed so easily as you wish.
That's right.
We still need to ponder on this.
What's more, the key is
whether there have been any precedents before.
There are precedents.
I've looked into it.
I think it's okay.
Deputy Marshal Peng.
Look. Xu and
our team
can work together so closely now.
I think we might as well
establish a joint team.
In this way,
it can largely improve
our work efficiency.
As for the procedure,
we'll handle it.
I also think that this is a good thing.
I agree.
Okay.
How about this?
It's settled
like this for now.
After we go back,
Deputy Marshal Peng and I
will report it to
the higher-ups.
Alright.
That's all for our
meeting today.
Dismiss.
Adviser Xu.
The Fire Investigation Department, the Criminal Investigation Division and forensic doctors work together.
It's a good idea.
Uncle Shen.
Hello, Uncle Shen.
Hello.
So you're going out to work?
We're going to the local police station.
[Shen Yi, Shen Ye's father]
Okay. Just go.
Uncle Shen, you're here.
-Hello, Uncle Shen.
Have you had lunch?
-Yes.
So you both have had lunch?
Hello, Uncle Shen!
Hello.
Uncle Shen.
I haven't seen you for a long time.
That's right.
Gosh.
Have you had lunch?
Go upstairs to eat something.
No.
I just want to discuss something with Ye.
Alright. Captain Shen will come down soon.
Okay.
Goodbye, Uncle Shen.
Get back to work.
Okay.
Dad!
Stop running!
Well...
Why don't you go inside?
I'm just here to deliver lunch to you.
If I go inside, it might affect your work.
Where's the food?
The food...
Well...
Well, why did you put it there?
This...
Uncle Shen.
You're here.
I'm here.
Go upstairs and have a seat.
No, we'll just chat for a while.
We'll just chat for a while.
Get back to work.
Just get back to work.
I'm afraid it might affect your work.
Well, next time,
just put it in the janitor's room.
The janitor's room?
What if you forget to take it?
Besides,
we have a canteen here, don't we?
Can the food in your canteen
suit your taste better than my cooking?
Look at you.
I've noticed that you've become thinner recently.
If you don't eat something good,
how can you stay healthy?
Alright. I got it.
Come on. Just go back.
I'm leaving.
Alright.
You don't need to wash the utensil.
Bring it over after you eat the food.
Okay.
Send me a message when you get home.
There's soup. Hold it steadily.
Okay. I got it.
Hello, Uncle Shen.
Hello, hello.
Hello.
When you finish, print it.
[Stay Loyal to the Party, Serve the People, Be Impartial in Law Enforcement, and Be Well-disciplined]
Let me take a look at yours.
Okay.
Is it okay, Captain Shen?
Yes. Go ahead.
How about this?
Make another version.
Use bigger fonts
so that Marshal Gu can read it easily.
Bigger fonts?
Bigger fonts.
Mentor.
Now?
Alright. Okay.
I'll be right there.
Send it to me when it's done.
Okay.
Adviser Xu, you're here.
Where is my mentor?
Who is your mentor?
You've seen him before. Marshal Gu.
I think he'll be here soon.
This is for you.
This is good.
We can close the case this time.
Marshal Gu.
Mentor.
Both of you are here.
Look. Look.
Mind your appearance and manner as a policeman.
Mentor, what's the matter?
Why did you come all the way here?
What's the matter?
It's something good.
Come on. Have a seat.
Adviser Xu.
The quick response system
for major fire cases
which you've mentioned...
QR...
QRSCAN.
It has been approved.
So soon?
I photocopied
this official document.
There are many details inside
which you need to pay attention to.
You two have to learn them carefully.
Let's discuss this privately.
After the joint investigation team
is established,
we'll be a family.
You two have to collaborate well.
After all, you're from two different units.
Some work needs to
be handled properly
so that others won't gossip about you.
Don't worry, Mentor.
I'll guide him.
You even want to guide him?
You must be dreaming.
I think you need guidance from others.
Xu.
This guy
seems unreliable.
But he can handle
his work well.
I hope that you two
can get along well with each other.
Don't worry.
Our minds
are kind of in sync.
What do you mean by "kind of?"
Our minds are in sync.
Alright. It's good that your minds are in sync.
Anyway,
I won't talk too much about the major principles.
Come to me if you need anything.
I'll strongly support you.
Okay, Mentor.
Thank you, Marshal Gu.
Alright.
I have a meeting to attend.
You two
have to study
the document carefully.
Okay.
Mentor, take care.
Take care, Marshal Gu.
Bye.
I didn't expect
Marshal Gu to be your mentor.
Now you understand the saying,
"A great mentor tends to have accomplished disciples." Huh?
Come on. Let's go to my place.
Huang Qi, photocopy this.
Okay.
Come on, everyone.
Put aside your work for now.
I have two things to say.
Firstly,
it's a good thing that the case is closed.
Secondly,
the joint investigation team formed by us
and the Fire Investigation Department
is officially established today.
There are two happy events at the same time.
-Good!
Also,
let me introduce him to you all.
This is the adviser of the Fire Investigation Department
of the Rescue Brigade of Beixun Fire Bureau,
Xu Tongsheng.
We'll be a family from now on.
Welcome.
Hello, Adviser Xu.
I look forward to working with you.
Let's collaborate
to finish our work properly.
I've booked a restaurant.
Let's have a meal together.
This guy is quite proactive.
Alright. You'll take your men
and I'll take my men.
Whose treat is it?
It's my treat.
With this joint team,
you're quite different now.
Let me tell you.
Get off work and get changed.
Let's have dinner.
Ask Chun and Pai to join us.
No problem.
Let's go, Adviser Xu.
Thank you for your hard work today.
Eat as much as you want today.
Make yourselves at home.
Here are the kebabs.
Coming.
Here is the main course.
Come on. Share it over here.
Huang Qi.
Show your skill of eating 100 mutton kebabs
and 20 pig kidneys
to the fellows from
the Fire Investigation Department.
Let's start ordering food.
Stop eating.
Go check those kebabs.
I'll go, Captain Shen.
Sit.
Have a good chat with Adviser Xu.
Okay.
Danggui.
Chun told me that
you guys had been working on
Han Group's case for a long time.
So you guys must know
Han Pei very well, right?
We've met him a few times before.
But this group...
Han Group
has been in Beixun for many years.
It's a very large corporation.
Han Pei
was kind of a celebrity.
He was usually quite arrogant.
What's the relationship between Han Pei
and Chen Guang, the guy who was shot dead?
They used to be childhood friends.
Chen Guang once helped him
manage a security company.
I have another question.
Han Kun
was such a big boss.
I think he enjoyed good medical services.
Why did he pass away so suddenly?
What was the reason?
Come on. Here are the kebabs.
Hurry up! Come on! Here!
This boss...
What do you mean, Adviser Xu?
You've invited us out for dinner
to ask about information?
No.
I want to know more about the case.
Alright, alright.
Let's not talk about work today.
Guys, raise your glasses.
Today,
our quick response team is established.
We'll be a family from now on.
Let's celebrate for it.
Come on. Let's drink a toast to this big family.
Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
Listen to me.
Let's enjoy our dinner today
and not talk about the case.
Alright. Cheers.
Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
Han Pei is already dead.
How do you know it was Han Pei who died,
instead of Han Jun?
Come on. Sit down, guys.
Mao Mao.
Can't you stop talking while eating?
Adviser Xu.
To be honest,
actually, at first,
we also thought that
this matter was quite fishy.
But according to the surveillance video
from the underground garage in Han Pei's house,
as well as Chen Xue's testimony,
Han Pei was indeed the one
who died on the driver's seat.
What's more, Wang Xi's target
was Han Pei, too.
What if Chen Xue and Wang Xi lied?
What if they were accomplices?
You seem to only care about
who actually died.
Although this case is closed,
I think there's still a problem.
According to what you said,
the person lying
in hospital now
might be Han Pei, too?
That's possible.
But it's also possible that
the one lying in hospital now
is Han Jun.
Right?
Captain Shen.
The Exit-Entry Administration Bureau
replied to my message.
They said when Han Jun came back to China,
he entered
from a very remote land border port.
He didn't leave any
fingerprint information.
[When Han Jun came back to China, he entered from a very remote land border port. He didn't leave any fingerprint information.]
Shen Ye.
This case is not over yet.
We have to keep investigating it.
There must be something wrong.
[Han Jun is awake.]
Han Jun is awake.
Let's go take a look.
I'll go with you guys.
I'm acquainted with both Han Pei and Han Jun.
Danggui.
Take care of everyone.
Huang Qi, let's drive the car there.
Enjoy your meal.
Ma'am, so you won't go on eating?
Take my silkworm pupae with you.
It's alright. Let's continue to eat. Come on.
I jumped off the car instinctively.
I don't remember what happened
after that.
Oh, by the way,
how is Han Pei?
Han Pei was sitting on the drivers seat
and couldn't escape in time.
Unfortunately, he passed away.
He's your elder brother.
Aren't you sad?
When I was 18, I left home
and settled in Americas.
The situation of this family
has nothing to do with me.
You haven't been back to China for 18 years.
Why did you come back this time?
Han Pei asked me to come back.
He asked me to come back
and attend Han Kun's funeral.
But my purpose
was to
move my mom's ashes to another place.
I've noticed that when you came back this time,
you entered from a land border port.
Why didn't you choose a direct flight?
Han Pei arranged it for me.
He said there were no tickets for direct flights.
I was also in a hurry
to come back before my mom's death anniversary.
That was why I entered from that port.
Senior Han Jun.
Do you remember me?
Jin Chun.
Actually, I recognized you
as soon as you
came in just now.
I was afraid you might not remember me,
so I didn't dare to say hello to you.
Why are you
with these
police officers?
They are all my colleagues.
I'm a forensic doctor now.
I heard that you got hurt,
so I asked them
to bring me here to see you.
It's surprising that you still remember me.
Of course I remember you.
Back then,
we even hosted
the graduation ceremony together.
I was in Grade 10 and you were in Grade 12.
Do you still remember that?
Yes, I do.
That was my last time attending
our school's activity
before I went abroad.
At that time,
we always rehearsed
in the same classroom.
And our rehearsal would last for a whole afternoon.
I still remember that back then,
there was a classmate's name
which I always couldn't pronounce correctly.
Her name was Du Danning.
I always called her Du Danling.
Yeah.
At that time,
I even taught you a way
to overcome it.
That's right.
You taught me a tongue twister.
It's "a vine on a high mountain."
It was quite effective.
I remember that
you were very fluent in it.
I even asked whether you were a professional in this field.
I didn't expect that
you would remember it so clearly.
Yes.
Now that I'm talking with you, I remember everything.
I remember that
you did very well in biology.
You once didn't get a full mark
in the final exam.
You were upset for so long that day.
Now that you're a forensic doctor,
you can exert
your strengths.
Yes.
How time flies.
Chun.
Do you think he is Han Jun?
All the details
are consistent.
There were even
some things that I had forgotten,
and he described them all so precisely.
No one else knows about this, right?
Of course no one else knows about this.
I'm sure about it.
Speak.
Captain Shen.
My police academy classmate
has just informed me that
he happens to have
Han Pei's fingerprint records which he left
18 years ago when he was put into a juvenile prison.
He has compared them.
[Li Danggui]
They don't match the fingerprints of the injured man.
The person who has survived now
is Han Jun.
Okay. I got it.
Dad.
Mom.
He Xi.
I'll definitely find out about the truth.
[Ms. Sun]
Ms. Sun.
Hello, Adviser Xu.
I'm calling you
because I want to thank you
for saving my life that day.
And you've been so serious about
Wei Kang's case.
It's my duty.
There's one more thing.
Adviser Xu.
I want to leave Beixun.
[Ms. Sun]
What?
You... You're leaving?
But...
But what did Wei Kang experience before his death?
What was he going to say in court as a witness?
This...
This case is not completely over yet.
But Han Pei is already dead.
No matter what the truth is,
Han Pei was the murderer.
Now that he's dead,
everything should be over.
Adviser Xu.
[Ms. Sun]
Although I don't know
what you've been through,
I always feel that you have the same
feeling as I did at that time.
Those deceased people
also wouldn't want us
to live in pain.
You also can't represent the deceased people.
[Ms. Sun]
Tongsheng.
It's time to let go of it.
[Special Reference Letter for Investigation Materials of Beixun Fire Rescue Brigade]
Tongsheng.
The truth is still important.
Xu Tongsheng.
If your parents were still alive now,
they would also
hope that
you can live well.
But just like Director Zhao,
I also don't want you to be sad.
[Special Reference Letter for Investigation Materials of Beixun Fire Rescue Brigade]
[Unnatural Fire]
[Fire Safety Knowledge Session of Unnatural Fire]
Here are the ways to escape after a vehicle has caught fire.
Safety hammers in public vehicles.
Emergency hammer is also called safety hammer.
They're usually found
by the windows of buses and subways.
How do we use a safety hammer correctly when we're trapped
in a vehicle in an emergency?
Pick up the hammer.
Hammer the four corners of a toughened glass.
Don't hammer the middle part.
The middle part is the firmest area,
and it's not easy to break it and escape through the window.
If the glass doesn't fall immediately after it's broken,
we can kick it open with our feet.
After the glass falls, jump out of the vehicle in an orderly manner
and go to a safe place.
[Fire Safety: Everyone's Responsibility]