[Unnatural Fire]
[Episode 38]
[Binxi Branch Bureau of the Beixun Municipal Public Security Bureau]
[Han Pei] [Han Group]
[Han Pei]
[3.16 car accident case]
[Fan Yi] [Explosion]
[Lian Xiangqin] [Abduction]
[Han Jun & Han Pei: twin brothers]
[Jin Chun]
[Lian Xiangqin and Jin Chun's abduction and assault case on November 15]
[The explosion at the Ducheng Processing Factory]
[3.16 car accident case]
[The Dujing Food Processing Factory's poisonous cheese case]
[The Xu family's case in 2005]
Why did you imprison
Lian Xiangqin and Jin Chun?
I didn't imprison them.
Are you not aware of
the relationships
among us?
Lian Xiangqin
is my ex-girlfriend.
Jin Chun was my current girlfriend.
The two of them
had some conflict.
So we
should find a place
to talk properly, right?
So she invited us to
that basement.
We barely talked
before an argument broke out.
Then she said some harsh words,
threatening to burn us to death
and die together with us.
I got angry,
so I left.
You attempted to murder Xu Tongsheng.
How do you explain that?
I really don't know what to say.
L-Look at
what I'm like.
I attempted to kill him?
If Captain Shen hadn't arrived in time,
honestly,
I would have been beaten to death by him.
Don't you know
what happened?
You can check the surveillance footage.
It's all there in the footage.
I was walking peacefully on the street,
and he suddenly appeared and attacked me!
I couldn't just stand there
and let him beat me, right?
At most, what I did
could be considered excessive self-defense.
Take a good look!
Do you know where you are?
Stop quibbling!
Officer,
why are you getting worked up?
Aren't we supposed to rely
on evidence when we speak and act?
This never happened.
Why are you trying to pin this
on me?
Chief Wu,
everything is ready.
Leave it to me.
Go ahead.
[Xu Qingsong] [Cheng Qiuyue]
I'm about to start.
[Camera 01]
[Stay Loyal to the Party, Serve the People, Be Impartial in Law Enforcement, and Be Well-disciplined]
Captain Shen,
you're finally here.
I hope you can find out the truth soon
and clear my name.
Long time no see,
Han Pei.
What did you say?
If it weren't for me last night,
you would have been beaten to death by Xu Tongsheng.
So you should
interrogate him and ask him
why he did that to me.
No one can judge me,
except myself.
Does that sound familiar?
In the fire case
of the Xu family in 2005,
[Ducheng Processing Factory] [Investigating fire-fighting equipment]
the victims were Xu Qingsong
and his wife, Cheng Qiuyue.
The suspect is Han Pei.
In the Dujing Food Processing Factory's case,
[The Dujing Food Processing Factory's poisonous cheese case]
the victims were Wei Kang
and Sun Ling.
[The Dujing Food Processing Factory's poisonous cheese case]
Du Danning committed suicide.
The suspect is Han Pei.
In the 3.16 car accident case,
the victim was Han Jun.
[Han Pei's car exploded and was on fire]
The suspect is Han Pei.
In the Ducheng Processing Factory's serial cases,
the suspect is Han Pei.
[Lian Xiangqin and Jin Chun's abduction and assault case on November 15]
In the 11·15 Lian Xiangqin and Jin Chun's
abduction and assault case,
the victim was Jin Chun!
The suspect is Han Pei.
[Han Pei] [Han Group]
Han Pei is the suspect
in all those cases.
[Han Pei]
And you
are Han Pei.
What do you mean, Captain Shen?
Why are you blaming me
for everything Han Pei did?
[The Xu family's case in 2005] [Victims: Xu Qingsong and his wife Cheng Qiuyue]
Just so you can close the cases,
right?
Han Pei is dead!
I am Han Jun!
You may have fooled everyone in this country,
but you can't fool Lian Xiangqin,
who spent every day with Han Jun
abroad.
Her testimony
has already confirmed
you are not Han Jun,
but Han Pei.
How can you believe
that crazy woman?
She committed arson and murder!
She can't be trusted!
What is this?
You don't know?
Very good.
You were so confident
that there was no evidence left in this world
that could prove you are Han Pei.
You think you can rest easy
after becoming Han Jun?
But what's fake
will always be fake.
There will always be a flaw.
This necklace belongs to Lian Xiangqin.
There are two fingerprints inside.
One belongs to her,
and the other belongs to Han Jun.
You said you are Han Jun.
Then why don't the fingerprints match?
Because you're not Han Jun.
You are Han Pei!
Jin Chun
gave her life to get this
just to expose your identity
and convict you!
Because you
are Han Pei!
The game is over?
It's over.
I was just one step away.
[The Dujing Food Processing Factory's poisonous cheese case]
You think
I wanted to do that?
I was left no choice!
None of them were good people!
When I was little,
my father always favored Han Jun.
Not just him.
Everyone around me
thought Han Jun was better than me.
They thought he was a good student
and had a good personality,
perfect in every way.
Standing next to him,
I was nothing but a bad example.
Fine.
Then I thought I'd let everyone see
Han Jun's ugly side.
I heard
your mom died in a really disgraceful way.
Is that true?
I heard...
He could be provoked very easily.
As long as someone mentioned our mother...
Who do you think you are?
He'd immediately go crazy.
Brother,
I saw everything you did today.
Given what you did,
you're gonna end up in juvenile prison.
They deserve to die.
Don't you want to go abroad?
I don't want to go abroad.
Even with a record,
it won't affect me.
How about this?
Later, you tell the police
that you are Han Pei.
Han Pei,
come here!
Did you hear that?
Dad made the same choice as I did.
Go now.
Oh, my foolish little brother.
He knew nothing.
He even thought
he owed me a huge favor.
What's your name?
Han Pei.
Come with us.
So the one in the detention center
was Han Jun.
The fingerprints were also his,
but the name was yours.
That's right.
Back then, you sent Jin Chun
to test me and see who I really am.
Honestly,
I found it
utterly ridiculous.
Back in school, the one rehearsing
and hosting on stage
was me.
And that
time capsule thing—
I knew all about it.
Later, Han Jun came back.
My father sent him abroad
to study law
at a prestigious school.
I thought that was the end of it,
but I didn't expect
my father was still the same.
The person
he cared about
was still Han Jun.
At that time, I thought
maybe I should do something big
to prove myself.
Coincidentally,
the fire department came to look for trouble.
I thought it was a perfect chance.
Last time,
the food processing factory
was shut down because of Xu Qingsong.
He pushed for a fire safety inspection,
and we haven't been able
to resume work since.
And now he's here again,
getting in my way.
If he keeps digging,
we'll really be in trouble.
He just wanted
a capable son.
I helped him solve
such a big problem.
I thought
he would come to his senses.
I killed someone for him,
but he cowered.
About our business in the basement,
I've decided to quit.
Mr. Han,
my technology is now mature.
We can scale up production anytime.
Why don't you reconsider?
If we stop now...
After all,
we've invested so much already.
Enough.
Stop talking.
Don't try to persuade me.
This is too dangerous.
I've made up my mind.
I'm old.
I just want to wait peacefully for Jun to come back
and hand the factory over to him.
I lived with frustration
for over a decade.
Until about a year and a half ago,
Shen Yi came to me.
He said this business was far more profitable,
and that factory
couldn't make much money.
That's right.
Even an idiot could see that.
So I decided
to get it done.
Do you have any idea
how risky this is?
But if you want to make money,
of course there will be risks.
You want to make more money,
so the risks will be
bigger, right?
I don't want to take such big risks anymore.
I already learned a lesson 18 years ago.
It must be even more difficult now.
We will find
an opportunity to make big money.
Your brother is doing well now.
When your brother
comes back and takes over the factory,
we can make big money
in a down-to-earth way.
Dad,
you always think about
giving the factory to him,
but you should at least ask him
if he wants it.
Shut up!
I'm telling you,
they're cracking down harder on drugs.
A batch of goods has already been seized.
Those people have been arrested.
I've made
my decision!
Don't think I don't know what
you two have been doing
behind my back all these years.
I'm warning you both.
If I ever catch you
involved in drugs again,
I'll make sure
you both pay dearly for it.
Han Jun can do it,
but I can't!
You know what?
If Han Jun brought this up today,
that old man would have agreed
without a second thought.
I think...
he's old.
He's not as bold as he was.
That's right.
What else can he do?
If he only relies on those factories,
he can't even earn enough to retire.
Calm down.
Try again.
There might still be a chance.
A chance?
Do you think I can persuade him?
Pei.
Brother.
This is what I think.
After all, you're family.
Parents always give in
to their children's soft words, not hard ones.
Take
the medicine to your father.
Say something nice.
It might work.
I can only try.
Don't get your hopes up.
How did it go?
Listen,
that old man has gone crazy.
He jumped up and nearly hit me.
Well... how come I'm always
not good enough in his eyes?
Calm down.
Let's wait until he cools off.
Then we'll figure something out.
Oh, right.
Fan Yi is ready.
But he can't do it alone.
We need to find him a helper.
Do you have
anyone in mind?
What's that sound?
Dad!
Dad, what's wrong?
Get up!
What's wrong?
Feeling unwell?
Hang in there!
Pei.
Pei, wait!
What are you doing?
Wait!
Please, wait a moment before making the call!
Please,
let me finish.
If you don't
make this call now,
our plan
can be carried out smoothly, right?
If he...
he just...
just dies like this,
no one will
stop you, right?
No one will
compare you to Han Jun anymore.
Right?
Moreover,
you can also
easily earn the money
you haven't been able to earn in over ten years.
Think about it.
It's up to you.
So you watched Han Kun die?
He got more cowardly as he got older.
He only loved Han Jun.
But to be fair,
I didn't kill my father.
Shen Yi instigated me to do it.
The split?
He had been using it
to threaten me ever since.
Let's go with a 30-70 split then.
You take 30%. I take 70%.
It's settled.
Well, Pei.
All the data and technology
were organized and developed by me.
The split...
is not really fair, right?
What?
You're still not satisfied?
You're just a dog we keep.
I'm being generous enough by giving you 30%.
Even if I won't give you a penny,
what can you do?
Who are you yelling at here?
Calm down, Pei.
I'm just trying to discuss with you.
Take a look at this first.
Then we'll talk.
50-50.
We split it evenly.
I thought about it again.
Actually, the split you mentioned earlier
is quite good.
I take 70%.
You take 30%.
I thought after my father died,
I could take control of everything.
But who would have thought
Shen Yi would use
such a dirty trick?
Listen,
what happened at the Ducheng Processing Factory
was all Shen Yi's doing.
I protected him.
I did everything I could
to clean up his mess.
Wei Kang has been taken care of.
However, the fire department is still investigating.
Okay. I got it.
Wang Xi, that idiot,
wanted to kill me.
He just
gave me a great gift.
Why are you here?
We might not be able
to cover up Wei Kang's death anymore.
His wife, who's a journalist,
has been investigating us.
Then get rid of her too.
When it's done, I'll arrange for you to go abroad.
Keep your promise.
Jun.
Yes, it's me.
Dad's death anniversary is coming up.
Aren't you coming back?
I've been very busy lately.
If you come back,
you can see Mom too, right?
Okay.
I'll make some arrangements.
Let me know when you've made the arrangements.
I'll book a ticket for you.
After all these years,
mentioning Mom still works like a charm.
But Mom was good to me.
She gave me
a twin brother.
Thanks to him,
I could have a chance to start over
when people like you
pushed me to the brink.
Still the same, right?
Actually, I can stay at a hotel.
Why stay at a hotel?
You're already home.
Besides,
Mom always hoped
we could get along well, right?
Right.
Then I had him stay at home
and leave his fingerprints.
I'll go tidy up then.
Okay.
Jun,
I want to ask you something.
If one day,
someone wants to harm me,
and I need you,
a great lawyer, to save me,
would you save me?
We're brothers.
I need to avoid a conflict of interest.
If he could say one good word
or show even the slightest bit
of treating me
as his brother,
I wouldn't have done that.
But you see,
he was such
a selfish person.
So why should I
show him any mercy?
Stop the car!
Are you crazy?
Don't do this! Don't be impulsive!
Get off!
Get lost!
That bitch.
Does she want to die?
Jun,
my eyes feel uncomfortable.
You drive.
Okay.
It was easier to switch our positions.
I stopped the car
where there were no cameras
in the tunnel.
He didn't suspect me.
He was just thinking about how to bring
our mother back.
So I sent him
to reunite with our mother.
Stop the car!
Han Pei.
Help me.
After you switched your identities,
didn't Shen Yi ever suspect you?
He did.
That cunning man,
how could he not be suspicious?
Mr. Han,
this gentleman wants to see you.
Okay.
Hello.
Can I help you?
Han Jun?
Yes.
Don't you remember me?
When you were little,
I went to your place often.
Now that you mention it,
you do look a bit familiar.
But I can't be sure.
May I know your name?
Well...
why was it so coincidental?
Your brother was just about to get arrested,
and you came back
from abroad.
And you coincidentally had a car accident.
Yes.
I didn't expect
something like that to happen.
Han Pei called me back
to visit our parents' graves,
but
such a terrifying thing happened.
This room
has no cameras or recording devices.
I just want to hear you say one thing.
You're really going
to give up our business?
I'm not interested in the Han family's business.
Since this happened,
I can only
deal with it as soon as possible.
After it's done, I need to go back to the Americas.
You're going to get rid of the Ducheng Processing Factory too?
Of course.
Then sell it to me.
So that's why
you came here.
Sure,
we can talk about it.
Please, have a seat.
By the way,
how should I address you?
He thought he had everything
perfectly planned,
but I saw through it long ago.
He restarted the drug factory
just to test me.
If I'm Han Pei,
I would definitely take action.
Then he could continue to manipulate me.
If I'm Han Jun,
he would take the processing factory for himself
and run off with all the assets.
So that package was
deliberately sent to Shen Yi by you?
That's right.
[Reader Submissions]
I just wanted to take a gamble with you,
to see
if you could sway Shen Yi.
Remember,
[Same-City Express Delivery Receipt]
you must
give this to Shen Yi
personally.
Take this.
This...
Thank you.
Bro, don't worry.
I'll go right away.
Okay.
You killed Han Jun.
And you designed Shen Yi's death.
That was for revenge.
But what about Jin Chun?
Jin Chun was different!
[Jin Chun abducted and killed]
I truly love her.
To make her give up being a forensic doctor
and go abroad with me,
I went to great lengths.
You are
just too empathetic,
and you have a strong sense of responsibility.
I think you need
external help now.
My alma mater,
Chad Hahn University,
has a psychology seminar program...
Thank you, Senior.
I don't need that option.
Just when
I was at my wits' end,
Du Danning showed up.
They were best friends.
She was very competitive.
Just a little setback could
make her fall apart,
along with Jin Chun.
You can send the test report
to Du Danning now.
Then,
as I expected, she committed
suicide.
I've made all the arrangements
for you.
There won't be any issues.
And I've taken care
of your recommendation letter
and application materials too.
Once you pass the language test
and get your visa,
you can enroll right away.
Senior,
I'm really grateful to you.
[Jin Chun abducted]
You said you love Jin Chun,
then why did you set that fire and burn her?
I also love my father
and my brother.
But
none of them loved me.
You think no one loves you.
That's because
you don't deserve to be loved.
You said everyone
forced you into this situation,
but in fact,
it was your selfishness and greed
that drove you to commit crimes
and put you in this seat today.
You think that by becoming Han Jun,
all your past sins
can be erased?
They won't.
A mask is just a mask.
You have to pay the price for everything
you've done.
Because you
are the true,
heinous perpetrator.
You said no one can judge you,
except yourself.
But today, I'm telling you,
him, her, her, him—
every one of them
can judge you!
Han Pei,
as long as you did it,
there would be traces.
What awaits you
is the punishment of the law.
[It's all over.]
It's all over.
This morning,
the Supreme People's Court of Beixun City
held a trial for the chairman
of Han Group,
Han Pei.
The final verdict is as follows:
Han Pei was found guilty of arson,
intentional homicide,
illegal imprisonment,
drug manufacturing and trafficking,
and incitement to murder.
He was sentenced
[Han Pei's case was brought to trial today. Han Pei was sentenced to death with immediate execution for multiple crimes.]
to death with immediate execution
and deprived of political rights
for life.
It'll fall if you leave it like that.
That brat
didn't even turn off the lights.
[Binxi Branch Bureau of the Beixun Municipal Public Security Bureau;
Criminal Investigation Division]
What time is it? You're still not off work?
Chief Wu,
we should update the photo wall for this quarter.
Leave that for tomorrow.
Go back to rest.
Okay.
Goodbye, Chief Wu.
[Outstanding Criminal Police Officers]
[Legal Education Bulletin Board]
Chief Wu,
being able to empathize with the deceased
is not my flaw.
Instead, it's a kind of ability.
As long as I adjust my mindset
and use it properly,
it will become
my greatest weapon
to speak for the deceased.
So, Chief Wu,
wait for me to come back
and continue to fight alongside everyone.
Okay?
Silly girl.
[Binxi Branch Bureau of the Beixun Municipal Public Security Bureau;
Criminal Investigation Division]
[Jin Chun was posthumously awarded the honorary title of Hero of Righteous Action by Beixun City]
This is the place she always wanted to visit.
What do you think?
I didn't lie to you, right?
It's beautiful, right?
It's stunning.
What are your plans for the future?
No matter in the past or the future,
I will always
stand against crime
to be this world's
most steadfast guardian.
What about you?
Like I said,
anything done
will always leave a trace.
From now on,
I will continue to search for the truth
on the path of fire investigation.
I hope...
I can heal everyone
I meet
to make this world
a better place,
a much better place.
You know what?
The three of us
are destined to be best friends.
Because...
fire tries to burn wild grass up in vain.
They rise again when spring winds blow.
Fire tries to burn wild grass up in vain!
They rise again when spring winds blow!