[Lee Min-ki]
[Nana]
[Kang Min-hyuk]
[Oh! Master]
These pages are warm to the touch.
The smell of fresh printer ink.
Female killer...
I added some murder scenes that I like.
And introduced the Guitarist.
There are also some romantic scenes.
In the last mission, she pulls the trigger
but fails to kill him.
-She suffers from memory loss.
-What are you doing here?
Can't you tell? I'm working.
How can you be here right now?
My mom is here.
Oh, I forgot.
-Hurry before my mom sees you.
-Okay.
-Hurry up.
-I'm packing my computer.
-Hurry.
-Honey.
Honey, good morning.
It must've been hard
to meet your deadline.
What do you want for breakfast?
Kimchi stew with lots of fatty pork?
I'll fix it for you right now.
[Oh! Master]
[Episode 4]
That's strange. We're out of fatty pork.
Joo-in, let's go to the supermarket
to buy some groceries.
Sure, Mom.
Honey! I'm going to buy groceries.
So be patient.
-Mom, get changed.
-Oh, okay.
Leave after we go out, okay?
-Okay.
-Good.
No! No! We have to look for Dad!
No.
Oh, your dad must have been very hungry.
He's waiting at the table
for his breakfast.
Honey, I'll fix breakfast in a minute.
Be patient.
-Why didn't you go?
-Joo-in, I could use your help.
Oh, sure.
You can leave.
I'll come up with an excuse.
My mom is going to keep
thinking you're my Dad
until her mental state returns to normal.
So leave the house while she's cooking...
Honey, the stew is almost ready.
I need you to taste it first.
Taste it? Well, you don't need me
to do that.
Mom and Dad
always call each other, "Honey".
Honey, ask Joo-in to taste the stew.
Joo-in, looks like Dad isn't feeling well.
He's too busy to even taste the stew.
Massage his shoulders, Joo-in.
I don't think he needs a massage.
I'm fine. She doesn't have to.
Dad used to massage your legs so that
you would grow tall.
Why are you being like that?
I'll rub your shoulders, Dad.
-Just go through the motions.
-Okay.
But your shoulder muscles are tight.
Let me see.
What on earth?
You don't actually have to do it.
Well, you worked hard all night.
So your muscles are bunched up.
You need to eat anyway
so stay for breakfast.
You love fatty pork.
There's a lot of chunky pork
in the stew today.
It looks delicious.
Why did your dad have to like fatty pork?
Open wide.
Well,
I'll let you have the first one.
Enjoy it, Honey.
Do you feel embarrassed to eat it
because Joo-in is watching?
Mom, seems like
Dad doesn't want fatty pork today.
Open wide.
I need to go to work now.
You work at home.
Where do you plan on going?
And you just finished your deadline.
I was hoping we could go out today.
Why don't you go out with Joo-in?
All right then.
But Dad.
"Dad"?
Why don't we all go together, Dad?
So... So where are we going?
How about a botanical garden?
Mom loves flowers.
I'd love that. A botanical garden!
My mom adores flowers.
But the nursing home won't allow
patients to bring fresh flowers.
So I always bring her artificial ones.
That made me a bit sad.
Remember these Camellia flowers?
You gave me Camellias when you
asked me out on our first date.
Oh, I do remember.
And you told me what they symbolized.
Since Dad worked all night,
I don't think he remembers.
It means, "I love you
more than anyone else."
Dad would never forget that.
Those words set my heart aflutter.
You know what different flowers symbolize?
I did my research.
Are you saying I wouldn't have
characters that like flowers in my shows?
My mom is having a good time.
Thanks to you, she thinks she's with Dad.
Glad to hear that.
Stand right there.
You came out well. You look so pretty.
Let me take a photo of the two of you.
-What?
-All right.
How about we take one together?
1, 2...
Can you both try to smile?
You normally smile.
Dad. Say cheese.
Cheese.
It was great to see so many flowers.
Where else do you want to go, Mom?
We don't have to go anywhere.
All right then. Let's head home.
I just want to hold hands like this.
Joo-in, hold Dad's hand.
What? My palms are too sweaty.
I don't like touching sweaty palms.
Since when did you care about that?
-Wait.
-Mom.
Let's go.
I wish Joo-in would find a boyfriend
and get to hold hands on a date.
Joo-in, what kind of guy do you like?
-What?
-She asked you what's your type.
Well, any guy who treats you well, Mom.
That's you, Honey.
You're always nice to me.
Then you're the type of guy she likes.
Joo-in likes Dad so much.
Someone's playing the guitar.
It feels like time is standing still here.
It's nice.
Mom, would you like to freeze time?
Yes.
I wish we could stop time
and freeze this very moment.
Any song requests?
"The Shampoo Fairy".
If you can't play it,
then just put the guitar down.
Joo-in, your dad has a few skills
that I never told you about.
♫ Pushing through the square screen ♫
♫ Gently approaching me ♫
♫ A silvery illusion ♫
♫ She is my own little fairy ♫
♫ Like the early morning fog ♫
♫ She comes closer to me ♫
♫ Her long hair, waving ♫
♫ She whispers with a soft smile ♫
♫ Whenever I see her ♫
♫ I'm not lonely anymore ♫
♫ Even my sadness ♫
♫ Disappears in the yonder ♫
♫ She is my ♫
♫ Shampoo fairy ♫
♫ Now I will ♫
♫ Love you ♫
That was terrific. I'm having a happy day.
Oh, it's not much.
Thanks, Dad.
For making Mom happy.
I didn't make her happy.
I was just playing a song
in front of two happy people.
You're such a witty talker.
Thanks for making this a special day.
Oh, sure.
What did they say? Is KT Cosmetics
going to sign Kim Ji-yeon?
[They'd like to convey
the company's decision in person.]
You've been their spokesperson
for five years, after all.
Out of courtesy, they would like to
tell you in person.
So you should meet them.
You said they'd tell us their decision.
Nobody mentioned having a meeting.
I'm in the middle of something
right now, so I can't go.
"Can't go"? Why not?
Sorry. Let me call you back.
Isn't that your sponsor
who wants a meeting?
-Yes.
-Why are you hesitating then?
How can I leave my mom here?
I'll stay with her.
You've been asking me to
pretend to be your dad.
Now's the time to ask for a favor
so that you don't miss your meeting.
Your mom wants what is best for you.
I wouldn't be happy to hear that you
got replaced by Actress Kim Ji-yeon.
Could you take my mom home?
I'll return in a short while.
A quick winding will do.
There you go.
I like the melody.
The director will be here in a minute.
Meanwhile, you can read the terms.
Thank you.
[Contract Renewal]
Jeong Yu-jin...
[Jeong Yu-jin, Director, KT Cosmetics]
That's the same name as my friend.
Yu-jin?
Surprised to see me?
I wasn't planning on joining
the family business.
That's why I didn't tell you
about what my family does.
But I ended up joining.
Your company's CEO is young though.
That's my sister.
My parents decided to retire.
I didn't know anything about you.
Do you feel like I lied to you?
How could you not mention
your family even once
while I was your company's
spokesperson for five years?
I wonder why I never said it.
What?
Do you remember what you told me once?
I said a lot of things. How could I?
You said I was a scion pretender.
If I had told you my family owns KT,
it would have changed our friendship.
But denying it would make me a liar.
So don't get mad at me for keeping
this a secret until now, okay?
Of course, I won't. You're my friend.
None of that matters to me.
So let's talk about your contract renewal
as our company's spokesmodel.
Indeed, Director Jung.
I appreciate it that you were
not embroiled in any scandals
for five years
while you were under contract.
So I added a retainer bonus
and increased the size of the contract.
Take a look at it
and sign it when you're ready.
I heard rumors that
Kim Ji-yeon would replace me.
But did you pull some strings?
If you find someone that's better
than you, please recommend her to us.
I couldn't find an actor
with a better image.
You have high standards, I see.
Kim Ji-yeon is our spokesperson
for our other brand.
How about we go out and celebrate
since you got your contract renewed?
I would love to, but I can't right now.
Can we do it another time?
Of course. I live in Seoul now.
You're going to be staying?
Yes.
-That's great.
-Me too.
You're closing already?
Oh, you didn't say you were coming.
What's up?
Did I come at the wrong time?
Are you busy?
No, I just wanted to close early.
Just because?
I like your outlook.
If you like something, you just like it.
You don't need a reason.
That's true.
Hae-jin,
let's go to a BB gun range.
I hit the target.
You're good at shooting.
That was fun.
You were always different
from the other girls.
You were different too.
It's strange though.
It feels like we've hung out
this whole time.
I don't feel awkward at all.
Maybe because we share good memories.
That hasn't changed.
I'm happy to have a new friend.
Me too.
You won the plush toy in one attempt.
I never won a toy.
I've always been good at winning prizes.
Most people have dinner
with their families at this hour.
My only son has his own place.
And my husband usually
eats out by himself.
What about you? You live by yourself
and eat your meals alone.
-Don't you get lonely?
-Sometimes.
But I was married once.
I like my current life.
Living together with someone
doesn't necessarily mean you feel close.
I'm the opposite.
I'm asking my son to move in with us.
But he won't listen.
If you want to be close to him,
it's better to leave him alone.
Living separately
could actually bring him closer to you.
Come in.
Want a beer?
Sure.
When I got back and saw you and Mom
dancing together,
I almost cried.
Looking at you now,
you resemble him a lot.
My dad.
Are you going to keep staring?
Thanks for spending time with my mom
and helping me.
I wasn't trying to help
just because she's unwell.
What?
Your mom has a special ability
that other people don't have.
She can recreate her past
and relive it.
And it was my lucky day to be able to
use your mom's ability for one day.
I think you're a good person, Bi-soo.
I'll go to bed now.
Oh, okay.
A good person?
A good person.
["Guitarist, Female Killer", Episode 1]
Mom!
Mom.
What are you reading, Mom?
"Guitarist, Female Killer".
I haven't read that before.
It's a page-turner.
I think you'd be perfect for this role.
Han Bi-soo wrote this, didn't he?
Han Bi-soo?
You knew it was him?
Yes.
Actually,
I regained
my senses later in the afternoon.
[I snapped out of my episode]
[when I was listening to the music box.]
[He resembles your dad a lot.]
[I was so mortified
that I made a big mistake.]
Did you tell Writer Han?
Yes. But I asked him for a favor.
[I asked him if he could]
[spend the whole day]
[with me and act like my husband.]
[And he asked me what I wanted
to do with my husband]
[if he were still alive.]
[So he]
agreed to dance
to my favorite music with me.
Just like how your dad and I
used to dance.
I see.
[Sein Hospital]
Where's the VIP patient
that was admitted last night?
We're readying him for surgery.
Who will operate?
Dr. Lee will, Doctor.
No, tell them I'll lead the surgery.
Okay, I'll let them know.
What were you two doing in there?
Are you sick, Honey?
-What?
-She had a stomachache. It's not serious.
You just came out of
the radiography room. That's not serious?
Am I overreacting?
Lower your voice.
I have surgery to do,
so let's talk later about this.
-What are those pills for?
-I have indigestion.
Thanks to you, I had a great stay, Honey.
Be safe, Honey.
We took away a lot of your time
when you needed to write.
So get some rest.
Sure. Dad will get some rest.
So drive Mom back, Joo-in.
Okay.
Let's go.
Oh, gosh.
Yes.
-Where are you writing the script?
-In the house.
I'm at the house right now.
[Jae-hwan's stuff is here,
but I don't see any of your belongings.]
The jig is up. So tell me.
Mr. Yoo.
Jae-hwan won't tell me
where you're staying.
Mr. Han, did you hear that?
I didn't tell the boss anything.
Just remember that.
[What does it matter where I work?]
I'm writing a sick script,
so don't worry about it.
You can end the lease for that house.
Find a workspace for Jae-hwan.
I'm back.
You came quick.
My mom needed to rest too.
Did you get some rest?
Yes, until someone started talking to me.
By the way, my mom likes your script.
"Guitarist, Female Killer".
She read my script?
She said the role would fit me.
Your mom has a good eye.
What about you, Joo-in?
Joo-in?
I don't like calling you Master.
Fine. I'll be patient.
I'll give you my answer
after I receive episode two.
You're pushing me to finish episode two,
aren't you?
I found this in the mailbox.
Doesn't your agency
receive your fan letters?
There's no return address and no name.
How did it get mailed?
You must've bragged to all your friends
about the new house you bought.
I only told a few friends.
What's wrong?
[Die. Your most glorious day will turn out
to be the worst day of your life.]
Someone seems to hate you a lot.
There's no explanation or any reasons.
It's a typical hate letter.
You can't stay in this business
if you let this bother you.
I'm going to take a nap.
Sure.
I think she should be concerned.
Is something worrying you?
-What?
-You rub your ear when you're worried.
I got this letter.
It was hate mail sent by
someone who doesn't like me.
I'm trying to not think of it,
but it's hard not to.
Let's go.
Are we going somewhere?
A place you were at 14 years ago.
All right. Time's up.
Thank you for your work.
Everyone, give her a hand.
-What is that?
-A unicorn.
Why am I riding a unicorn?
Unless you're extremely lucky
or blessed by the Almighty,
it's nearly impossible to ever
meet a unicorn.
I'm not a lucky person.
Not true. You'll find luck soon.
And what if that doesn't happen?
I'll make it up to you then.
Luck follows those who smile.
You're going to get lucky soon.
You're so silly.
When did you set up your room like this?
What?
You still have this drawing?
Of course.
"Your most glorious day"?
It will turn out to be
the worst day of her life?
Which day will be Joo-in's
most glorious time?
Oh, gosh.
It'll turn out to be the worst day
of her life?
It feels like I'm at an art exhibition.
You're pausing your career
as a visual artist?
Yes, for now.
I'll resume when I feel like it.
Here.
Vin Chaud smells so nice.
Drink it slowly. It's hot.
This brings back memories
of my first trip to Paris.
It was five years ago.
You had just finished your
third TV miniseries as the lead.
You even remember that?
I was thrilled that we had
the shoot on location in Paris.
You know I went to see you
in between the shoots.
I know.
And you drank three glasses of Vin Chaud.
I prepared them myself.
You make the best Vin Chaud.
You should serve it to the girl you love.
She'll love you even more.
I think I'm an eligible bachelor
even without my mixology skills.
Then date someone.
I'll find someone soon.
You're very confident.
I would say that I'm prepared for dating.
It's so good.
[Oh Joo-in]
I'll cook a nice meal for you sometime.
You don't need to.
Leave the cooking to me.
What a nice house.
[When you brought me here]
[and told me you'd get
your old home back one day,]
[I knew you'd succeed.]
Thanks. Now you have to go.
After I see you go in.
But why aren't you asking me
if you could see my house?
Well, you'll invite me over
when you feel like it.
Go first.
Okay. Bye.
Be safe. Bye!
Why are you standing out here?
You're reckless.
Where were you this whole time?
I was with a friend.
You're not concerned?
-About what?
-That threatening mail.
You're worried about my safety?
Yes.
I'm really worried about that letter,
but you're not worried?
Looks like you have a boyfriend.
What did he say about this situation?
I don't have a boyfriend.
What?
You should be careful
about going out at night!
Okay?
What do you think, Joo-in?
You know what I like.
It's very pretty.
-You like it?
-It's so pretty.
Can you show me another outfit?
Sure.
-What about this one?
-It's a beautiful dress.
-Oh, I like the color.
-It's very pretty.
And the embroidery design is cute.
It's nice.
You're stunning.
Okay?
Joo-in, you're the last survivor
in this business.
-How is this?
-Where are your angel wings?
I like it.
I'll have these three dresses
tailored to fit her.
I'll pick them up afterward.
What?
I need to check them one last time.
Oh, well...
Joo-in will want to try them on
at her home.
Can I come along?
You've been working so much.
I don't want to burden you.
-Gwang-ja, could you pick them up?
-Sure.
-Good job.
-Thanks.
Let's go.
"Announcing the winner of
the Drama Writer category"
"is the winner from the previous year."
"He's the master of writing thrillers.
Writer Han Bi-soo."
Did you call my name?
You surprised me.
Why didn't you tell me
that you would be at the awards too?
It's nothing special.
Good for you.
It's my first time hosting an award show.
I'm so nervous.
Why would you be nervous?
You'll be on stage, and everyone
will be sitting below you.
Just look down.
I envy your ego.
So will you be there?
More importantly,
you need to be careful tomorrow.
The letter said the most glorious day
will turn out to be your worst day.
And tomorrow is the special day
that the letter is referring to.
Who is it?
It's Gwang-ja.
Joo-in.
Joo-in, I brought your dresses.
Mr. Han, since you're staying here,
I'm the one who has to bring stuff to her.
They're so beautiful. These dresses.
-Did they do a good job?
-Yes.
You'll be the most searched name tomorrow.
Ta-da.
-This is for Part 1.
-Part 1? It's so pretty.
[2021 Asia Drama Awards]
[2021 Asia Drama Awards,
Sponsored by KT Cosmetics]
Having KT Cosmetics as our main sponsor
brings more prestige to the awards.
Thank you so much.
We get to promote
our brand at the same time.
So we're thankful to you.
I hope your lounge is to your liking.
Our staff will come to usher you in
when it's time to present an award.
-Thank you.
[-I'm your host for tonight.]
[Hello, everyone.
We're at the Asia... Sorry.]
[2021 Asia Drama Awards]
[I'm Actress Oh Joo-in,
and I will be co-hosting the awards.]
[It's so great to be standing on stage]
[2021 Asia Drama Awards]
[in front of so many fellow colleagues
and industry movers.]
[Someone said that living together]
[Chairwoman Kang Hae-jin]
[doesn't necessarily mean
you become closer to them.]
[Sorry for pushing you like that.]
Mom...
Why is she acting weird these days?
[Chairwoman Kang Hae-jin]
Did you find her?
I thought it would be too hard.
[Nabom Nursing Home]
I came to see Ms. Yoon Jung-hwa.
Can I see her?
She's in the therapy room.
Tell me what illness my wife has.
I don't know what you presume it is.
-It was a routine exam.
-Dr. Jung.
I could find out even
if you don't tell me.
I can't share her medical history
with you even if you're a senior doctor.
-I'm her doctor, and that's the law.
-You think I don't know medical law?
You're asking me to break the law?
Dr. Jung!
Is she in serious condition?
Is it more
serious than I think it is?
Jung-hwa.
What?
Hi, Hae-jin!
Thank you.
Why are you saying that?
I was so worried that
you would ignore me when you saw me.
Thank you for not turning me away.
You just have to say sorry for being late,
and that would be that.
Why are you speaking nonsense?
-What?
-Why are you dressed in black?
You're going to wear that there?
To where?
I can't believe it.
You pleaded with me to go with you.
You said you set up a double blind date.
Oh, I did.
You hate wearing black.
You said it was a stuffy color.
You're acting pretty strange, you know.
I act different sometimes.
Does he know
that you're going on a blind date?
-Who?
-You told me about the guy at church.
He plays the guitar and makes you laugh.
You said he was a wonderful guy.
You're talking about Chang-gyu?
You said you liked him.
You really want to go on a blind date?
I'm not dating Chang-gyu,
so it's all right.
Until Chang-gyu asks me out on a date,
I'm going to meet other guys
as much as I want.
You're so clever.
Ms. Yoon. I was looking for you everywhere
to check your blood pressure.
Your turn passed,
so I'll come back in the evening.
So please be patient, ma'am.
She called me ma'am.
Hae-jin, you heard her say it, right?
She must have made a mistake.
-She's weird.
-Don't let it bother you.
Who are you?
You were terrific in the rehearsal.
It'll be okay even if you're
half as good in the actual awards.
I was so nervous up there.
It's hard to believe your opinion.
I agree with her.
I couldn't tell at all
that you were nervous.
Really?
Who could that be?
Mr. Han, what are you doing here?
-Hey, I'm here.
-What?
You were wondering if I would attend.
Can anyone enter your dressing room?
Yes, you just entered.
Not me.
No one could come in here.
Everyone is busy.
[You're the star
of the award show, Joo-in!]
Don't you have bodyguards?
Nobody stopped me from entering.
-Is everything good?
-Yes.
I just finished the rehearsal
and did a wardrobe change.
I'm very busy.
Don't let your guard down until the end.
[You're the star
of the award show, Joo-in!]
Are you finished with the rehearsals?
You were terrific.
Yes, Joo-in.
I'm heading to your dressing room.
Count to 10.
I'm almost there.
What a nice dressing room.
[You're doing great, Joo-in.]
"Your first fan, Jeong Yu-jin".
He sent a nice bouquet.
-You didn't have anything to eat, right?
-What did you bring?
Grab a bite.
You'll be hosting for hours.
Thanks.
But who's the person
I saw leaving your room?
-Do you have a new road manager?
-Of course not.
Gwang-ja would be devastated.
She's my new stylist. Choi In-young.
[It's my first time working with her,]
[Oh Joo-in's Dressing Room]
[but she looks familiar.]
[Am I confusing her with someone I know?]
You meet a lot of people.
How can you remember every face?
You think so?
I can't put a finger on it.
[I really can't recall where I met her.]
[Don't worry about it.]
[Let's eat.]
[It looks delicious.]
Be honest.
-You waited for me to come, right?
-Not at all.
You suddenly disappeared.
You didn't like me anymore.
Why would I be here if I didn't like you?
And it took you 40 years to come.
That's pretty long.
If I hadn't come today,
we might have never been reunited.
If we had never met...
What can you do about it?
You hated me that much?
I hated you, but I also missed you.
Why weren't you by my side
during my hardest moments?
You should have come to me first
if you were having such hard times.
When I was happy,
I didn't think about you much.
When I was going through tough times,
I didn't want to show that side to you.
I only have myself to blame.
You can't blame yourself.
That's life.
-Hae-jin.
-Yes?
But why did you cut off all contact
with me and leave to study abroad?
I was going to marry someone.
But he died in an accident.
I should've told you everything,
but I couldn't do that.
After he died,
I continued to live my life
with a broken heart.
I couldn't stand it.
I turned my back on everyone.
I was too focused on coping with my grief,
I wasn't able to think about you.
Sorry.
My husband died and left me widowed.
He gave me so much love.
That made the loss harder to deal with it.
Those bad husbands.
Look at us.
We had similar experiences
because we're friends.
I know.
Why do we share that?
I'm so relieved to have found you.
[The Asia Drama Awards]
[Asia Drama Awards will return
in a moment.]
[will return in a moment.]
[Tune in for Part Two.]
"Overseeing the crew"
"and bringing everyone together
as a team..."
"Overseeing the crew..."
"Bringing everyone together as a team..."
[You're doing great, Joo-in.]
"Overseeing the crew and
bringing everyone together as a team..."
You're tired, aren't you?
Have a refreshment.
Thanks.
Where is Gwang-ja?
She went to return the jewelry.
Okay.
Yes?
Oh Joo-in.
Mr. Han, are you bored?
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
[You're the star
of the award show, Joo-in!]
A stalker will take the next step
after they send a threatening mail
to their victim.
Okay. I'll watch out.
Joo-in, you're precious.
Precious to your fans who adore you
and to your mom.
And to me.
A home needs a homeowner.
Okay. I'll be careful.
Keep up the good work.
Okay.
[Part 2 of the Asia Drama Awards
will begin in 30 minutes.]
[We need everyone in the audience to]
[return to their
designated seats, please.]
[I will repeat.]
[Part 2 of the Asia Drama Awards
will begin in 30 minutes.]
[We need everyone in the audience to]
[return to their
designated seats, please.]
Thank you.
Excuse me, In-young.
I'm feeling tired.
I'll take a 10-minute nap.
Wake me up later.
Okay.
[Ms. Oh needs to be on standby backstage.
But why isn't she here yet?]
[Hyun-joo went to check on her.]
[I'm going crazy.]
In-young.
Why are my hands tied?
You brought this upon yourself.
What are you doing, In-young?
If you scream, it could get worse.
You still don't recognize me?
I was hoping you'd recognize me.
That's all I want.
Just one wish.
I gave you multiple chances.
But you couldn't remember me.
In-young.
Help me!
In-young!
[Open the door!]
Help me.
[Oh Joo-in's Dressing Room]
We need Ms. Oh to be on standby
in 10 minutes.
Okay.
In-young.
Please open the door.
[In-young, can you hear me?]
-In-young.
-I told you, didn't I?
Your most glorious day
will turn out to be
the worst day of your life.
[-The person you have reached...]
-What on earth
[The person you have reached
is not available.]
[-Please try again.]
-That's Joo-in's...
Help me!
Is anyone there?
[I'm locked inside!]
[Can anybody hear me?]
[With Joo-in, the actress I love]
[I hope you'll reach your goals,
In-young.]
[I'll try hard to succeed,
and I hope you'll succeed too.]
[Someday, I hope we can work together.]
[That's right.]
[But I cannot go without mentioning this.]
[New, up-and-coming actors.]
[Because they have shown
tremendous talent.]
[We can't find her.
Please wait a little more.]
[Part Two of the Asia Drama Awards]
[will begin soon.]
[-Please return to your...]
-We can't find Ms. Oh.
[Jeong Yu-jin's Dressing Room]
-We're looking for her.
-What's going on?
[I will repeat.]
Ms. Oh is missing.
Everyone is looking for her.
-What?
[-Part Two]
[of the Asia Drama Awards
will begin soon.]
[Please return to]
[-your designated seats.
-The person you have reached is not...]
I think there's a problem.
-Could you follow me?
-Sure.
[Part Two of the Asia Drama Awards]
[will begin soon.]
[Please return to your designated seats.]
[I will repeat.]
-Help me.
[-Part Two of the Asia Drama Awards]
[will begin soon.]
-Someone save me.
[-Please return to]
[your designated seats.]
[-Thank you.]
-What?
-Joo-in!
-Let me.
[Someone save me.]
What on earth?
-Do you have the key?
-I'll bring it.
Mr. Han...
Joo-in!
Are you okay?
Hold on.
Joo-in.
It's all right.
It's okay, Joo-in.
Joo-in!
[Oh! Master]