[Lee Min-ki]
[NANA]
[Kang Min-hyuk]
[Oh! Master]
I knew the day would come
when my mom
wouldn't be able to recognize me.
But I thought that day would be far away.
Even if she didn't recognize other people,
I thought she'd
be able to remember me.
I told myself that.
I couldn't handle the day
that would happen to her.
It looks like you can handle it
without a problem.
Your mother is so thoughtful.
She assigned you a different role
to keep things interesting.
Today, she thought you were
a student of her husband.
I wonder what role
she'll give you next time.
Try to go along with it.
You're an actress. That's what you do.
You can do this.
-It's nothing to cry about.
-You're right.
I'm relieved that I'm an actress.
I'm confident in playing a daughter role.
And I could play other roles too.
I'll be able to keep her amused.
Thanks to her,
you'll improve as an actress.
Even if the day comes
when Mom will completely forget who I am,
I'll remember her.
You're her daughter.
Nobody can change that.
I'm the witness.
Writer Han, do you think I can handle it?
You're already doing a fine job.
You're doing a fine job.
-That was a La Bise.
-What?
It's the French form of greeting.
You know, La Bise.
Is this how the French do it?
If you're very close friends in France,
they kiss like that.
For real. I saw French friends kissing
each other on the cheeks
with my own two eyes.
I don't understand why you'd
use La Bise now though.
It's a sleep-tight kiss.
But it's daytime.
You can sleep at any hour if you want.
When you're tired, you take naps.
It was a long day for you, wasn't it?
Oh, I'm suddenly thirsty.
You'll get a stomachache
if you drink water too fast.
That was so dumb of me.
[Oh! Master]
[Episode 7]
"La Bise is planting an air kiss on each
cheek while making a kissing noise."
[La Bise]
An air kiss?
It wasn't an air kiss.
"Your lips should absolutely not
touch the cheek."
[Absolutely not]
Absolutely not.
What on earth?
-Mom?
-Yes, Joo-in.
Did you have a nice nap?
Yes. Why are you looking at me that way?
As if you haven't seen me in a while.
Did I make a funny expression?
You're leaving?
I need to go.
Thanks to you, I had a lot of fun today.
Stay a little longer.
That's probably Hae-jin.
I asked her to give me a ride back.
She's on her way out, Mom.
Why don't you two go out
for some fresh air instead of staying in?
Why don't we?
I'm meeting Yu-jin a bit later.
He has something to tell me.
Then let me tag along.
I'd like to see him too.
-You want to see him?
-Sure.
Is there any reason
why I can't see Mr. Jeong?
No.
I'm surprised to hear that
you wanted to see me, Mr. Han.
Well, you're friends with Joo-in so--
I'm actually her boyfriend.
Today's lunch is my treat
since you're visiting our neighborhood.
Thanks a lot.
What did you want to tell me?
Do you need some privacy?
Should I excuse myself?
No, it's not. That's why I was okay
with having you come too.
Joo-in, Reporter Lee would like
to interview us together.
He says he has time tomorrow.
What do you think?
How do you feel about it?
Do you want to do it?
Of course I want to do it.
Avoiding the press
isn't the best strategy.
Let's do the interview then.
You'll give an interview together?
But you're not even a real couple. So why?
I don't think anyone would be interested.
I feel like you would be interested.
Oh, isn't it
your birthday tomorrow, Yu-jin?
Wow. You remembered my birthday.
How could I ever forget your birthday?
Tell me what you want for your birthday.
Anything.
Let me see.
I need to think about it.
Sure.
What did we do last year on my birthday?
We had a creamy beer.
-In Yeonhui-dong.
-Yeonhui-dong.
You flew here from Paris.
-What did we do on Christmas last year?
-We went to Naksan Park.
You were the one who always came to Seoul.
That's not important.
We always spent time together
on special days.
On Valentine's Day last year!
I was in my study at my house.
And what were you doing?
I had pulled all-nighters
for three days straight,
trying to finish the draft script
for the hit show, "Doctor Psycho".
Nobody gave you any Valentine's chocolate?
I thought Valentine's Day was
a day when you write scripts
and take an aspirin to cure your headache.
I'll give you chocolate
on Valentine's from now on.
If that's what you want,
I guess I can't reject it.
Memories lose their power.
What's important is the present.
What happened to me earlier?
We went to Chang-gyu's record store,
and you took a nap.
You can tell that
something is amiss by just looking
at your child's expression.
That look on their faces.
I think I did something wrong
and upset Joo-in.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Hae-jin.
All right. You need to know
what your daughter underwent.
She's probably very upset.
No way.
You couldn't recognize Joo-in.
What can I do?
I don't care if I forget other things.
I prayed to the heavens to let me
never forget Joo-in's face.
Don't hold any grudges.
You're not the only one suffering.
Other people face hardships too.
People keep it to themselves,
so you never hear about it.
Just focus on the present.
Look. You're drinking this wonderful tea.
It's nice, isn't it?
Yes.
Are you really going to
do the interview tomorrow?
I have to. It's something
I have to get over with.
And Yu-jin wants to do it.
You can still say no.
As long as it's not something difficult,
I want to go along with what Yu-jin wants.
He squashed the article
about us living together
by announcing that he was dating me.
I don't believe he did that for your sake.
It was for his own selfish interests
that he announced he was dating you.
Well, I don't think that's a bad thing.
Lucky for you that
a lot of people like you.
[Open]
Chang-gyu.
What brings you here at this hour?
Were you heading home?
[Closed]
No. Come in.
[Open]
This is about a month's supply of candy.
So what is it that you want
to talk about today?
-I came to talk about my son.
-What?
Thanks for being
such a good friend to my son.
Don't ask me to keep treating him nicely.
I've been nice to him so far.
-Right.
-Have you gotten soft with age?
That's ironic.
Your name literally means "strong".
Bi-soo might act tough, but he's not.
I already know that.
I first met him when he was 18.
I remember that he was very sad.
He cried in the listening room
while listening to a song.
He cried?
I guess he got dumped by a girlfriend.
He was inconsolable.
I asked him what was the matter,
but he wouldn't tell me.
It's the first time I heard that.
You two really are close.
Have a candy.
How do I look?
I couldn't get any sleep.
-You look fine.
-Thanks for the compliment.
There's something I want for my birthday.
What is it? Ask for anything.
Instead of being my fake girlfriend,
be my real girlfriend.
How does that work?
Just be my real girlfriend.
No matter who you meet or where you go,
think of me as your boyfriend.
No more faking it.
All right. Got it.
What on earth?
What's wrong with me?
I heard that you knew
each other for 10 years.
When did that change?
It just happened suddenly.
I realized I loved her while I was
working on an art exhibit in Paris.
I found myself drawing her
in all of my paintings.
The person I wanted to be with
was in Seoul.
It didn't feel right to be
so far in Paris all by myself.
That's when I knew for sure.
Being next to Joo-in
was where I should be.
When did you find out that
Yu-jin was in love with you?
I had no idea.
He often said that he misses me
and that I look pretty.
But that's how it was all the time,
so I didn't notice he had changed.
Of course, Joo-in didn't know at first.
I was always too late
in realizing my feelings
and telling her how I feel toward her.
Now hold that pose.
You two look great.
Could you tell me when you thought of
Yu-jin as a romantic partner?
Back in high school,
I thought Yu-jin knew me pretty well.
When we made our
relationship public recently,
I realized he knew me well
because he was in love with me.
How does that feel?
Going from a friend to a boyfriend.
Before, he was a friend
I could tell my personal secrets.
Now, he's my boyfriend
and part of my personal life.
I like both sides.
[I first met him when he was 18.]
[I remember that he was very sad.]
[He cried in the listening room
while listening to a song.]
What are you doing?
-What? You didn't call.
-You look surprised.
Can't I come over when I want to see you?
Your dad isn't home at this hour,
you know.
What should we do?
Is there anything you want to do, Mom?
When you're having a tough time,
you keep it to yourself, don't you?
I heard the first time you went
to Just Record, you cried there.
Gosh, Chang-gyu! Why did he tell you that?
You hardly ever cry in front of me.
What made you cry there?
In front of a stranger.
That was a long time ago.
I hardly remember it.
Just look after your health, Mom.
What?
You retired.
If you want to travel and have fun,
you need to be healthy.
Bi-soo, I'm thinking about checking
into Jung-hwa's nursing home.
A nursing home?
Why?
I have chronic gastritis.
I was too busy to get it treated.
Can't you get outpatient care for it?
It's better that way.
You also know many specialists.
It's not serious.
I just need to follow a strict diet.
It's nothing to worry about.
I want to be near Jung-hwa.
Why didn't you ever show any symptoms?
How was I supposed to know
that you had chronic gastritis
when you look healthy to me?
Why are you yelling? I'm sick, I said.
You have to get better. Okay?
That's why I'm going there.
Of course, I will.
I want to have a homemade meal, Mom.
Here you go.
You were craving seaweed soup? That's it?
What's wrong with seaweed soup?
Will you make seaweed soup
for me in October too?
You forgot my birthday?
How could I forget your birthday?
I gave birth to you.
I'll make you better seaweed soup then.
That's a promise.
-How's the show script coming along?
-It's fine.
I added a subplot
based on your suggestion.
My suggestion?
Boy meets girl, girl meets boy.
That kind of stuff.
-You said you wanted that.
-Yes, I do.
Put in a lot of funny scenes.
So that I can laugh
when I watch your show.
Just wait for six more months.
That's when the show will be aired.
So laugh all you want.
-Do you know what I wish for?
-What's your wish?
To see you have good thoughts,
laugh a lot, fall in love,
and be loved back.
My goodness.
It's perfect.
I'm here to save your life.
I told you who I was.
The person who would save my life?
You're going to die.
-Cheers.
I'm glad you were born. Happy birthday.
I also think it was a good thing
that I was born.
-Thanks.
-For what?
For solving my problems.
So did you like my birthday gift?
Loved it.
I was pretty happy.
Wish it was for real though.
It was real.
The interview I gave
and the things I said. They're true.
You said that you were always too late
in realizing your feelings.
Well, I don't want to make
the same mistake.
That's why I'm thinking
carefully about us.
Don't make me wait too long.
Consider how long we've been friends
and how long I've waited.
Okay.
Let's eat.
Thanks.
♫ Happy birthday to you ♫
Where's my birthday cake?
Can't you treat my mom here instead
of her going to a nursing home?
Of course, I told her that I'd treat her.
But she wouldn't listen.
Doctor, you can make her listen.
Your mom told me
that she doesn't want to waste her time
on a small chance of being cured.
She chose to go to a nursing home
to at least monitor her condition.
How much longer does she have to live?
Nobody knows for sure.
Will she be able to live
for more than six months?
-I can't guarantee that.
-But you're a doctor.
You can't make a medical prediction?
I'm sorry.
I should apologize.
I lost it for a second.
There's nothing I can do
to save my mom.
Bi-soo.
Let your mom decide how she wants to spend
her remaining time.
It's her precious time, after all.
Hi, Writer Han.
Would you like to drink beer together?
No, thanks.
Is there anything you want to talk about?
[Let your mom decide
how she wants to spend]
[her remaining time.]
[It's her precious time, after all.]
What are you doing, Mom?
You don't sound like your usual self.
You're so perceptive.
Writer Han is in a depressed mood.
It's a little concerning.
[I think I know why he's like that.]
His mom is moving to my nursing home.
We'll be sharing a room.
Writer Han's mom? Why?
Chronic gastritis?
So that's why he's in a bad mood.
Bi-soo is probably worried about his mom.
I remember the time you left to
stay at the nursing home.
As I was leaving after dropping you off,
I felt it was all my fault.
I was ridden with guilt.
Joo-in, don't feel guilty.
In life, lots of things happen
that have nothing to do with you.
All right.
I'll give him some advice later.
Sleep well, Mom.
Drink a lot of fluids
and don't forget your meds.
Okay. I'll stop.
Sleep tight.
You're writing the scripts at a good pace.
And the plot is good.
You came all the way here
just to show me this?
Mr. Han, what are you doing?
I hope you'll grant me this favor.
Wait a minute. This is unsettling.
Did you do something crazy again?
Chief, please move up
the show premiere to an earlier date.
What are you talking about
out of the blue?
I'll work my butt off
to finish the scripts.
So please move up the premiere date.
Could you move it up by three months?
You know that's not possible.
What are your reasons
for making such a tough request?
There's someone I want to show my TV show.
But it's uncertain
if she'll be alive till then.
I didn't see your name
on the chemotherapy list.
Are you giving up?
I came by before I move
into the nursing home.
Do you recall anything that
happened to Bi-soo when he was 18?
What?
Bi-soo's grades fell sharply then.
He also stopped talking to you.
Although you didn't have
a warm bond with him,
he still looked up to you.
That's true. It's all my fault.
What?
When he was 18, he was under a lot
of pressure due to college admissions.
I wasn't there for him during that time.
I was busy at the time with VIP surgeries.
That's it?
Bi-soo said he was going
through a tough time.
But I didn't make myself available.
I think I disappointed him.
Someone seems to have hurt him.
Can't you try to be more nurturing?
It's not too late.
Even if it's hard for you,
try to be a better dad.
Why aren't you wearing your gloves?
I forgot.
I'm so busy.
It's your fault that my life got
complicated. Why did you say that?
What did I say?
I didn't do anything.
You told my mom that I cried.
Now she's worried.
She's overreacting.
Young men cry sometimes.
The record is skipping.
How are you able to laugh often?
Tell me your secret.
You do it effortlessly without thinking.
Laughing easily like me isn't easy.
But there's a method to it.
What's your method?
It keeps skipping.
Surprise.
Oh, my goodness.
Look at this room.
I decorated this room without telling you.
-Do you like it?
-I love it!
It's like a hotel suite.
I think I'll remember every moment
I spend here with you.
That's the plan.
Think of this as a hotel room
on a vacation trip....
Where is this place? Hawaii?
Jung-hwa.
I need my meds.
Why did you lie to me that
you had chronic gastritis?
I didn't expect you
to figure it out so fast.
I wanted to enjoy our time together
without any worry.
How did this happen to us?
I'm sick and so are you.
We're not competing
to be sicker or anything.
But I'd say I won today
in the illness category.
I could never beat you in a competition.
But I thought I was winning
in that category.
Jung-hwa, I always come out on top.
Hello, Joo-in.
How have you been?
Bi-soo is in the listening room.
With practice, you can laugh often?
My gosh.
-Hi, there, Writer Han.
-What's up?
How did you know I would be here?
I had a feeling that I'd find you here.
You know everything about me, I see.
I have to host a radio show tomorrow.
So? You came to brag about it?
I have to give advice to listeners.
But the scheduled guest can't come.
So?
I'm a writer in high demand, you know.
But you're asking me
to be the backup guest?
Then I'll ask Yu-jin if he can do it.
Wait!
Since you came all the way here to ask me,
I'll make an exception and do the show.
I knew you'd say yes.
You didn't have to come here to ask.
You could have just given me a call.
-I was concerned.
-About what?
Does it worry you a lot that your mom
moved to a nursing home?
How did you find out?
Your mom's roommate is my mom.
My mom will be fine.
Of course. She's a strong woman.
It's you whom I'm worried about.
If you ever need any help, just tell me.
My mom has been there
much longer, you know.
The first night here is the hardest.
It's not hard at all.
After two days, you'll finally
be able to settle in
and feel like this is my place.
If you can't sleep,
then don't try so hard.
You can sleep tomorrow or two days later.
You're right. I'll eventually sleep
for good at some point.
I smell warm milk.
I guess you remembered the time
I gave you warm milk.
That was for me?
I thought you were going to
pour it down the sink.
Oh, that's right.
-Guess I can't drink this.
-Why not?
I have to read
the radio show script tonight.
But if I drink this, I'll fall asleep.
I hate to waste this,
but I'll have to throw it out.
Don't pour it down the sink.
I'll drink it.
You will? Then it won't go to waste.
Drink it all up.
Don't waste a single drop.
Okay.
I learned from someone
that drinking warm milk
will relax your mind
and make you sleep well.
Really?
Writer Han.
Chronic gastritis is a serious disease,
but it's curable.
Don't worry too much about your mom.
It won't be easy to treat this time.
-What?
-She has pancreatic cancer.
She was diagnosed with it six months ago.
Mom thinks I don't know.
I'm acting like I don't know for her sake.
I'm fine.
She wants me to smile more,
so I'll keep smiling.
You can't smile all the time.
You can yell, cry, or pout
around me if you want.
That will help you smile
when you're with her.
You better be prepared.
You know I have a bad temper.
Try me.
I'm pretty tough, you know.
["Guitarist, Female Killer", Episode 1]
[Mom]
[You're smiling.
My wish has been granted.]
[Now fall in love.]
Gosh, Mom.
You're warming up?
You'll finally debut
as a radio show host today?
I'm nervous because it's my first time.
You're nervous?
I hardly ever get nervous.
Approach the hosting job
as if it's an acting role.
That could work.
I think you could have become
a great advice columnist.
Of course.
So what's your closing line?
Well, it's in the script,
but it's kind of forgettable.
Every radio show host
needs a catchy closing line.
What are you doing?
I'm pretending I'm listening to you
on the radio.
Go ahead. Say your closing line.
Have a romantic night.
Who says that in real life? It's awkward.
-Good night to everyone.
-That's boring.
This is hard.
I like you all!
Take out "all".
Say it as if you're talking to one person.
-I like you.
-Can't hear you.
-Closer!
Like you're whispering into someone's ear.
I like you.
Would it be better to say,
"I love you" than "I like you"?
Come on. I'm waiting.
I love you.
Don't show any hesitation.
Say it with conviction.
I love you.
You nailed it.
Go with that.
[Please take good care of DJ Joo-in.]
These presents are enough
to give to all the staff here.
[Hello, I'm your DJ tonight, Oh Joo-in.]
I'm a generous guy.
What is this?
I envy Joo-in.
-Hello.
Let's do a great show today, Joo-in.
Oh, sure.
Yu-jin, what brings you here?
I had to come on your special day.
Grab something to eat before you start.
[Please take good care of DJ Joo-in.]
When did you prepare all this?
It must have taken a lot of time.
I never regret spending time
on things I do for you.
-Did you draw this?
-Yes.
[Please take good care of DJ Joo-in.]
-I could have made you look cuter.
-It's cute.
Open it.
Thanks. It looks delicious.
Have some and then ace the show.
Joo-in needs to marry a guy
like Director Jeong to have a good life.
He's handsome, rich,
and has a nice personality.
Mr. Han is also handsome, rich, and...
His personality isn't great.
In the end, Joo-in will choose
Director Jeong because of his personality.
I think she'll choose
Mr. Han for some reason.
No. That won't happen.
She knew Director Jeong
for 14 years as a friend.
Which means she wasn't attracted to him.
That's a bad omen.
A love that grows on you lasts longer.
Oh, I see.
But you told me that you knew
I was your type the second you saw me.
You said you were smitten.
Smitten? Well...
Joo-in could be different from me.
It takes time to gain her attention.
You're being disagreeable today.
You keep countering what I say.
You're being a little touchy.
Enough.
I think we'll get into a fight
if we continue.
Okay.
Don't say anything.
I'm writing from Seogwipo.
["These days, I'm into collecting..."]
You always show up, don't you?
It's her debut as a radio show host.
I had to come.
It must be distracting to Joo-in
to have you tag along when she's working.
She liked it a lot that I'm here.
And what are you doing here?
Mr. Han, I'll give you a sign
when it's your turn.
Then go into the room.
Okay.
You heard her, right?
I'm an invited guest on the show.
Looks like you didn't know.
Joo-in probably told me,
but I wasn't paying attention.
You know the first guest on the show
is usually someone very close to
the radio show host.
But she asked me instead of you,
whom she's known for 14 years.
If she hadn't asked you,
you would've felt bad about it.
Since you live together,
that could create problems.
Keep thinking that
if it makes you feel better.
Should I ask her then?
If it turns out I'm right,
I don't think you'd feel good.
[On air]
Tonight is a time that makes me reflect
on things I tried for the first time.
In my first role, I don't know
why I was so nervous.
But sometimes, that intensity you feel
can be nice.
And that's how I feel right now.
Romantic Night.
I'm your one-day radio show host,
Oh Joo-in.
My sugar levels were dropping.
You came at perfect timing.
Here you go.
Ms. Oh got to a great start
on her radio hosting gig.
I knew she'd do great.
Thanks to Joo-in, I tuned in to the radio.
When I used to be a road manager,
I listened to the radio to stay awake.
I also listened to the radio a lot
when I was a TV producer.
One time, I was driving on the road
and was so drowsy.
So I put matches between
my eyes to keep them open.
I can show you how I did it.
You don't have to. Next time.
-Have some cake.
-Thank you.
You're very different from
the first impression I had of you.
-I feel the same way about you.
-Really?
What was your first impression of me?
A funny and pleasant person.
-But now...
-And now?
You're still pleasant.
You're also thoughtful.
And you also have a serious side.
[Nabom Nursing Home]
What is it? You came all the way here
to discuss something, right?
I'll sign the papers.
Thanks for agreeing to do it.
When I married you,
I wanted to be your protector.
But I don't think I did that well.
It weighs heavy on my heart.
[Nabom Nursing Home]
It's not you. I want this divorce
because of my illness.
Bi-soo still doesn't know?
No. Like I told you before,
don't tell him.
I don't want him to go through the shock.
I think he's stronger
than you think he is.
[On air]
Now our next segment.
It's time for Expert Advice.
I have a guest with me.
He's a TV writer who has
worked on TV thrillers.
-An award-winning writer.
-Yes, that's me.
I'm a TV show writer, Han Bi-soo.
It's your first time being on
a radio show. How does it feel?
I hardly ever get nervous.
But being on the show with you
is making me nervous.
Well, having you on the show
puts my mind at ease.
Let's take a song request from Writer Han
before we have our first caller.
My Love, Stay with Me by Kim Hyun-sik.
It's Writer Han's favorite song.
Here it is.
When we get our first caller,
you have to be very careful.
You have a bad image
for having a testy personality.
So you need to change people's minds.
I can't be self-conscious
about that constantly.
It's nice to have people
see your good side.
Why do you think I have a good side?
I only think about myself.
My feelings are important.
I do what I want.
That's also who you are.
But you're an authentic person.
Most people act in a certain way
for a reason.
But you're not calculating like that.
You really care when you talk to someone.
So that makes it special.
You're mistaken.
I'm nice to you for a reason.
What?
You know that reason yourself. The reason.
We just heard a song request.
Let's take our first caller.
Hello? Please go ahead.
[I'm in my 30s and gainfully employed.]
[I've been talking
to a fellow employee at work.]
[But she has a male friend.]
[I think she likes me, but when I see
how she treats her guy friend,]
[I think she's in a serious relationship.]
She's just checking out the pool of guys.
So quit hanging out with her.
You didn't ask her out yet, did you?
She could be thinking about
whom to choose between you two.
Excuse me.
I take back what I said earlier.
Take a wait-and-see approach
since she's not dating anyone.
You said you think she likes you, right?
[-Yes.]
-You also think about her
and want to be with her?
You get jealous and angry thinking about
what she's doing with her guy friend?
[Yes. Do you have a similar experience?]
Oh, I actually do.
I felt like I really
liked her.
If I'm not certain about a relationship,
I don't pursue it.
But I found myself breaking my own rules.
I don't understand what I'm doing,
but I can't hold back these feelings.
So I have to see it to the end
because these feelings won't stop.
So was that helpful advice to you?
[Yes. I'm going to take Mr. Han's advice
and go with it.]
Writer Han,
you were giving serious advice.
Any last words?
I'm glad I came on the show today.
-Ms. Oh, I hope we'll work together fine.
-What?
We're working on the same TV show.
Oh, the TV show.
Of course.
This is my first time hosting
a live radio show.
Every second and minute meant a lot to me.
By tomorrow, I'm sure I'll miss this show.
So I'm your one-day radio host,
Oh Joo-in on "Romantic Night".
I love
you.
You were terrific.
It was great.
The closing line was perfect.
You came up with that line.
So you have to like it.
You must feel lonely or else
how could you come up with it?
I don't have time to feel lonely
because I live with someone.
Joo-in, I don't feel like going home.
-What?
I don't feel like going into
an empty house.
-I know that feeling.
-Wait, what?
I'll stay over at your place tonight.
-Sure.
-Why?
Why aren't you asking for my permission?
I need your permission too?
No. I'm the homeowner.
Writer Han is just a tenant.
So don't let him bother you. Stay over.
Okay.
Come on, Writer Han.
I could wear anything.
This looks expensive.
I'm going to throw it away afterward.
I don't wear clothes someone else wore.
It fits me perfectly.
-Joo-in.
What's going on? You got up
and spoke at the same time.
I think Mr. Han is all right,
but he doesn't seem to like me.
Joo-in, come here.
Want to play?
I told you about this game.
Do you still play it?
I played it while in Paris.
And I would think about you.
I don't play kid's games. So have fun.
I'm going to work on the script.
You're still here?
Don't distract me.
We'll be quiet.
Wow. This is amazing.
You're still good at this.
That wasn't too loud, right?
-It's been a while.
-You're good.
You still have it, Joo-in.
-Nice.
-Jump. Go.
Go.
[-You must've played it all along.
-I know.]
[Very good. Go! That's terrific.]
[Jump!]
[I was almost there.]
Where's your plus one?
He went to get changed.
What is it?
-It's the script.
-Let's practice the lines.
I'll read the guy's lines,
and you'll read yours.
-Right now?
-Sit down.
How can I become your lover?
It's simple. Just look the way you are.
Your eyes seem to flicker with anger,
but they are deep and calming.
"It's like the world has frozen
when you look at me."
I like that about you.
-"Stop. Don't say another word."
-"Why?"
I might kiss you.
What was that?
You're making me jealous
by looking at him like that.
-Continue with the next line.
-What are you doing?
We're practicing lines.
Continue.
"I don't like guys like Gene.
He repulses me."
"He looks good-looking and cute,
but he's not my type. I don't like him."
But who is Gene?
I didn't see this name
on the character list.
He's a new character.
Anyway, your expression was perfect
when you said you were repulsed.
Now continue.
"He's just a friend.
I don't feel attracted to him at all."
-"He's in the friend zone."
-Mr. Han, it's interesting,
but do you think viewers
will like this scene?
Leave it to the professional writer
to make that call.
But do you know the viewers, Mr. Jeong?
Are you an expert?
I'll stop right here. I need a break.
Oh, it was getting fun.
I wanted to hear more.
But there's a mistake in this script.
My script is flawless.
You described me as being cute.
But you're a cuter guy than me.
What?
Should I add Gene to the show
to spite him?
I would like you to be more honest,
Mr. Jeong.
Okay. Go first. I wanted to talk to you.
You don't want to go into an empty home?
But you live alone.
-It's the truth.
-Just tell her you want to be with her.
On the radio show earlier.
What you said to the caller was
your true feelings, right?
It was meant for Joo-in to hear, right?
You're not as dumb as I thought.
As you know, I like Joo-in a lot.
I'm not going to let you
steal her from me.
Joo-in isn't an object that you steal.
It's up to Joo-in on whom she'll choose.
Mr. Han, memories are stronger
than you think.
They might not appear so at first,
but when people are under stress,
the power of memories becomes a factor.
I'm so sleepy.
You can sleep in the guest room
if you're tired.
The guest room.
You're not asleep?
I'm going to bed.
I just need some water.
We can't allow a special guest
to sleep on the couch.
I'll have to carry him to the guest room.
All right.
My gosh, this is...
I'm so sorry.
My goodness.
What are you doing?
You were sleeping
in a cramped position on the couch.
-And so?
-I got concerned.
I was trying to move you, but then...
You don't want to throw your back
by sleeping like that.
Were you really concerned?
Don't argue with me.
A couch isn't a bed, Mr. Jeong.
Go sleep in the guest room.
Leave that here.
Go. Hurry and go in.
Sleep on a bed. On a comfortable bed.
Why is he there?
Where did the blanket go?
What are you two doing?
I guess I'll go to bed.
It's time for you to be honest too.
What just happened?
I already told you that I like Joo-in.
Is that a problem?
So you'll do as you please
without any regard for me?
I'll do as I please from now on too.
Wait.
I have something to tell you both.
You said you had something to say.
Joo-in, you told me you had
true feelings for me.
That's true. I like you.
What about that kiss on the cheek?
That was my true feelings too.
I like both of you. Writer Han and Yu-jin.
-What?
[Oh! Master]