[Lee Min-ki]
[Nana]
[Kang Min-hyuk]
[Oh! Master]
But there's one condition.
[Room Rental Agreement]
While you live in my home,
you'll call me "master",
and I'll call you "writer".
Why are you the master?
Because it rhymes with my name. Joo-in.
Master... Master?
Is that correct?
Fine then.
Let's just call each other
"Writer" and "Joo-in".
I can't read the lines of a script written
by a writer who puts on
airs and acts special.
These are extreme terms.
I'm not comfortable with these terms.
Oh, well. Then let's scrap the agreement.
I feel like I'm signing a slave contract.
I'll tear it up then.
Fine. Give that to me.
[Han Bi-soo]
[Oh Joo-in]
-I'll move in tomorrow.
-Tomorrow?
Don't you need time to pack?
I want to work on the script right away.
The sooner, the better.
That way I'll be able to move out
before the lease ends.
The sooner you leave,
the better it is for me.
All right then.
House keys.
Tell me when you'll be finished tomorrow.
I'll come home after you're done moving.
See you tomorrow.
What was that?
[Oh! Master]
[Episode 3]
You did it. You'll be moving
into her house.
Most people would say no.
But Joo-in is so kind.
No, she's not kind.
She just knows what's best for her.
She needs me to keep writing
for the show. That'll help her career.
You really don't need my help tomorrow?
Just keep your lips sealed.
Don't tell Dae-young. Let him keep
thinking I'm staying at this house.
Okay.
I'll make space here for his stuff.
For just three months.
Where's my stuff?
In the storage room in the back.
Why do you ask?
Are you planning to move in?
I found a place.
I want you to move in with us.
Where are you moving to?
I can't tell you or else
you'll sell that place too.
If you want me to live here,
give me a convincing reason.
Stop being so stubborn.
It's my wish.
But why would you ask me to move in now?
It's hard to understand.
Sometimes, you don't need to
justify a wish.
Why is it so hard to grant me one wish?
I'm calling the movers.
Let's have dinner when I'm done moving.
Congratulations on being picked to
host the awards show.
I didn't expect this. It's great.
You've got star power.
That's why the producer picked you.
To maintain your popularity, we need
your new TV show to be a hit.
Then KT Cosmetics will extend your
ad contract. We need momentum.
-Now Joo-in.
-What?
Could you reconsider
not doing Han Bi-soo's TV show
just one more time?
I already made my decision to do it.
And I gave an interview saying
that I would be the lead.
Well, KT Cosmetics is planning to
sign Kim Ji-yeon.
That's fast.
What is their reason?
KT Cosmetics wants you to keep
appearing in romantic comedies.
But your decision to star
in Han Bi-soo's show
has forced their hand.
I'm sorry.
Well, you were their spokesperson
for five years. That's a long run.
So I won't say anything more.
I'll respect your choice.
I'll hold a meeting with Mr. Yoo Dae-young
and check the TV shoot schedules
and other matters.
Thanks a lot.
Don't mention it. It's my job.
After KT signs Kim, they'll inform us
that they won't renew.
But anything can happen in this business,
-so let's see how it goes.
-Okay.
Ms. Kim, Joo-in has to hurry.
All right.
-Do a great job.
-Bye.
It finally feels like home now.
Why is everything rearranged?
Where did my furniture go?
They're in storage.
What did you say?
You put my furniture in storage
without my permission?
Why are you mad?
The house is clean,
and I upgraded the furniture.
These are better furnishings.
What's the problem?
It's wrong to put someone's stuff
in storage. You know that, right?
My intentions were to
make the house look better.
But I see your point.
It won't be easy to
bring your furniture back right now.
They're safely stored in storage.
How about you just try getting used to it?
And if you can't, then I'll return
everything back to how it was.
First, apologize for moving my stuff
without my permission.
Do you really want an apology?
-Yes.
-Fine.
Sorry.
There wasn't a hint of sincerity in it.
I'm truly sorry.
Wait a minute.
Gwang-ja, why are you so late?
Jae-hwan, how do you like your new place?
It's a bit run-down,
but I like the rustic style.
Thanks, Gwang-ja,
for finding this place for us.
On your next TV project,
I'll try to find a better place.
I almost forgot.
[I love you, Jae-hwan. You're mine]
Here's a gift. Think about me
when you look at it.
Gwang-ja, how can I stop
thinking about you?
When will you become a lead writer
and I, an agency president?
Someday, it'll happen.
We just need to work hard.
Anyway, I'm worried about Ms. Oh.
From my experience,
it takes extra effort to bear with him.
Joo-in is as tough as nails.
To be a top TV star, you have to
work incredibly hard. That takes grit.
She didn't do it all by herself.
She had a road manager like you
who made it possible.
Since the two of them are living together,
they'll eventually develop
some feelings, won't they?
-Living together?
-Yes.
[2021 Asia Drama Awards]
[Safety guidelines when calling]
[Things to buy]
[When did he laminate these?]
[Floral therapy for flower-loving mom]
He's incredible.
I wonder if he had dinner.
Is it time for dinner?
Look at her.
Are you trying to blow our cover?
-What?
-What if I had walked by
[Hanjungsung]
when you opened the door
for the delivery guy?
That's why I told the guy
to leave the food at the door.
You saw me bring the food in by myself.
But you left the door open.
Someone could have seen me
through the opening.
I was trying to be careful.
I'll watch out.
This is your dinner.
I didn't ask you to order any food
for me, so why did you?
I prefer meeting at a halfway point.
[President Kim Yi-na]
Why did she insist on meeting here?
She's playing psychological games.
Have a seat.
I could hear you muttering
under your breath.
Oh, Ms. Kim. Well...
My gosh.
How much has Han Bi-soo written so far?
He finished the draft for episode 4.
And he's making changes to it
that Ms. Oh requested.
Indeed. Joo-in is on the verge of
losing her cosmetic contract
because she chose to appear
in Han Bi-soo's TV show.
-I see.
-I'm sure you're aware that the network
won't pick up the show
if Joo-in decides not to do it.
Yes, I'm very aware of that.
I promise you that the show will be a hit.
[Oh Joo-in]
Ms. Oh will be able to
boost her career too.
That has to happen no matter what.
Our agency will fully cooperate
with your studio.
Thank you so much, Ms. Kim.
Joo-in is our agency's top star,
and she's more than just that.
Right.
She's the first actor
I signed to our agency.
She was 18 when I scouted her.
Ever since then, I have always sought
what is best for her career.
I understand how much
she means to you and your agency.
I'll do my best in helping Bi-soo
to write his best work.
Let's try to make this a success.
Thank you, Ms. Kim.
At last, it feels like we're a team.
-Oh, Ms. Kim.
-Oh, gosh.
-That's enough.
-Oh, Ms. Kim.
She's got a lot of energy.
She could kill someone with her punch.
I tried to be thoughtful.
Why can't he say sorry or thank you?
He's got to fix that.
What a jerk. He's antisocial!
Maybe I'll punch him
the next time he acts like that.
She clearly wants to kick me.
But why is an actress like her
taking up boxing?
Darn it!
Hey, you've been in there for 30 minutes.
Life was better when I was living alone.
What?
Darn it.
Oh, gosh...
Excuse me...
Oh Joo-in!
Ms. Oh Joo-in!
No one's out there, right?
What are you doing?
-Why did you turn around?
-What is it?
Put on some clothes.
How can I wear this? It's soaking wet.
-Don't look.
-Who would want to look?
Then why are you looking?
Keep your eyes covered.
Now walk to your room.
I need to use the bathroom.
Don't move while I head to my room.
Don't peek, okay?
Could you hurry to your room?
I'm watching to see if you're peeking.
I think you sprained your back.
You need to exercise. Your muscles
get tight if you sit around all day.
Don't mind me. I'm fine.
I'm opening my eyes now.
Okay? I'm opening them.
Do you need a heat pack? Do you have one?
[No, thanks.]
Living together with someone
is a real pain.
Oh, gosh.
[Heat pack]
I told her I didn't need it.
Darn it.
[Sein Hospital]
I would rather have a strong espresso.
Pretend the green tea
is a cup of espresso.
Okay, Doctor.
For how long are you
not going to tell Bi-soo?
You should at least let him know.
He's your son.
What good would it be to tell him?
I'll delay telling him
as long as possible.
I think it'll be better to tell him
during my final days.
You need to give him time
to process this news.
I'll figure it out.
After I quit my job as a hospital director
and take care of a few things.
Speaking of which...
[Candidate for Hospital Director Position]
I'm going to recommend you
to be the new hospital director.
Dr. Jung. You're here.
You came at the right time.
[Candidate for Hospital Director Position]
What is this?
I'm going to quit my job.
So I'm planning to recommend both
of you as candidates for the position.
What do you think?
This will go bad by tomorrow.
Where did you go?
I had dinner.
You don't eat at home?
Why eat at home?
That produces food waste and trash.
It's better to eat out.
I'm eating the food I ordered for you,
which you refused to eat.
If nobody eats it, it'll go in the trash.
I didn't ask you to order food for me.
Nor did I ask you to eat that.
The same goes for the heat pack.
Sure. I made a mistake
by ordering food for you.
I just lost my appetite.
Darn it.
Unbelievable.
I need to talk to you.
What is it?
I can't do it like this.
You need to allow me to write
what I please.
Why do you want no character to be killed?
I'm a crime thriller writer.
We already had that discussion.
I let you lease a room here
so that you could write.
If you still can't write the script,
then you lack creativity.
I lack creativity?
How can you say that to me?
What?
Now you're getting on my nerves.
Did you forget our agreement, Han Bi-soo?
-What?
-You heard me.
I'll let it slide maybe once.
But we had an agreement,
so call me master.
Follow the terms, Han Bi-soo.
"Han Bi-soo"?
Oh, gosh.
What are you doing here?
You need to spend every second writing.
I want to, but I have writer's block.
You never had writer's block before.
I don't understand.
What's the problem?
I even leased a traditional house
for you to work on your script.
Oh, come on. It hardly helps.
Why are you being difficult too?
Dealing with Ms. Kim
is stressful as it is.
Bi-soo, I need you
to write terrific scripts.
Give me something
that I can show off to Ms. Kim.
Oh, gosh.
You're leaving so soon?
I'm going to work on the script.
You said you want a terrific one.
Hi, Joo-in.
Let me introduce you to your new stylist.
Nice to meet you. I'm Choi In-young.
What's wrong?
Well, you look kind of familiar.
-Let me show you your wardrobe choices.
-Okay.
-I'm going to talk to the hairdresser.
-Sure.
So I chose these outfits for you
to wear at the meeting
with the award committee members.
I kept it low-key with no frills.
Which one do you like?
I like them both.
That's my favorite look.
In the first romantic comedy show
you were cast in,
you played a clothes model
of an online shopping mall
who posed in dresses
with a minimalist style.
That was in contrast with
the floral dresses
Even though you had a small part,
you outshone everyone.
Thank you.
Wow. You remembered that.
Do you have any special fans
that you remember?
A fan that supported you
from the beginning.
I appreciate all the support
I get from my fans.
But it's hard to remember everyone.
It's not easy.
Could you excuse me?
I need to use the restroom.
-Sure.
-Okay.
[With Joo-in, the actress I love]
How could you not remember me?
-Hello, Chief.
-Oh, dear.
It's been a while, Joo-in.
Our network's top star.
Thank you.
Long time no see, Ms. Kim.
-How have you been?
-Great as always.
Let me introduce you. This is Mr. Jang.
He'll be overseeing the awards ceremony.
He's a trending variety-show producer.
You were his first choice to
host the awards show.
I asked the chief to recommend
an actress for the hosting duties.
And your name was
the first one that came up.
I merely mentioned your name,
but he made the call.
I won't let you down for choosing me.
I know you'll do a great job
in hosting the show.
Now when you're hosting,
make sure you promote
Han Bi-soo's new show, okay?
Oh, Chief. All you think
about are TV shows.
I skimmed the script
and noticed the promotional spots.
I'll do my best to promote it.
I'm not worried at all
about the drama's ratings.
Every show you do does so well.
Our main advertiser is KT Cosmetics,
which you're a spokesperson for.
Joo-in, how about we have some tea?
I don't have time.
I'm going to see my mom.
Okay.
Has your mom seen your new house?
She must've loved it.
Not yet.
I'll bring her to see it
when she's in stable condition.
I'd also like to see your house,
the one you were dying to live in.
Tell me what you want
as a housewarming gift.
Okay, I will.
[Resignation Letter]
[Private Investigator]
Did you find him?
And you have the address?
Okay, I'll check your text.
He lives so close by.
[Nabom Nursing Home]
Artificial flowers just don't look
as good as fresh flowers.
That doesn't matter.
I like anything you get for me.
But still. I'm disappointed.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
-What?
-You look troubled. Tell me.
I look troubled to you?
What is it? Is it something bad?
You can't even look me in the eye.
What? I thought you were...
Those are the lyrics to
a song that Dad liked.
The doctor said memorizing songs
is good for slowing Alzheimer's.
Really?
♫ Why won't you say anything? ♫
♫ Is it something you can't tell me? ♫
♫ You don't have anything to say? ♫
♫ You don't want to tell me? ♫
The lyrics are funny.
Why is it so hard to communicate
my feelings to other people
even though we speak the same
language and have a lot in common?
That will make you want
to know more about that person.
If you could know everything
about someone after talking a bit,
that would be a letdown.
You think so?
Joo-in, how about I stay over
at your place?
Really?
I'd love that.
You can come over right now.
Oh, not today.
How about tomorrow?
I'll come and pick you up.
Great.
-Have a good day.
-Thank you.
Can I ask you something?
I knew a guy who used to
play the guitar for me.
He was a philosophy major.
He always wore a Hawaiian shirt
and at church,
he wore sunglasses
when he performed with the choir.
He was a little strange.
Do you happen to know him?
Is your name Kang Hae-jin?
You remember me!
You're really Kang Hae-jin.
I couldn't stop staring at you
after you came in.
Chang-gyu, you broke a lot of picks
while playing the guitar.
-I still do.
-Really?
You haven't changed.
These are pretty.
That looks nice on you.
You always know how to make people smile.
How have you been?
-Did you get married?
-I'm divorced.
My ex-wife was a good person,
but we weren't right for each other.
So what else did you do?
I was a journalist, but I quit.
I don't like working in an office
and having a boss.
So now I run this record shop
and enjoy music.
-How about you?
-I have a husband and a son.
How did you find me?
I asked around to find you.
I'm touched.
I miss the people I used to know.
Coming here brings back the memories
of the songs you played.
It's a strange feeling.
-You want to listen to me play?
-Sure.
This living room is fine.
But what will I do about this room?
What on earth?
Writer Han.
Just call me Han Bi-soo.
Oh, come on, Writer Han.
I don't understand
what's going on, Master.
-What were you doing in my room?
-I have a favor to ask.
My mom is coming over tomorrow.
-Tomorrow?
-Yes.
She'll be staying for three days.
Could you stay somewhere else
during that time?
You just need me to be away?
What about my stuff then?
About that...
Could we change the room?
-How?
-We can change it to look like my room.
[Author Oh Hyun-chul]
Author Oh Hyun-chul. You like his works?
Of course. He's my dad.
Your dad was an author?
This room used to be my dad's study.
I wanted to put all his stuff back
and make it look like his old study.
But I'll have to wait until you move out.
Once we put this up, we're done.
You want to hang this?
It'll look like it's my room then.
I'm taking it down
as soon as your mom leaves.
Do as you please.
We're done.
-What were you so happy about?
-I was posing for the camera.
It's work. So you smile on cue.
You can do that?
You can with some practice.
And people like it when you smile.
It's good for my career to have more fans.
All I've seen is you yelling
and getting mad at me.
I guess I was like that.
Maybe it's because
we live in the same house.
Well, being around each other
all morning and all night
might be uncomfortable.
Writer Han.
You have another favor to ask?
Changing this room won't be enough.
I need to buy
some extra toiletries for my mom.
My mom won't be suspicious
about this room,
but you have personal belongings
in the living room and the bathroom.
All right. I'll go buy some boxes
to pack my belongings.
And I'll see you back here
after you buy some toiletries.
Okay.
Once we part here,
don't act like you know me.
Who are you? Why are you talking to me?
All right. 1, 2...
Oh Joo-in!
I saw a moving truck a few days ago.
I can't believe a top star
is living in this neighborhood.
I never imagined I'd see you
right before my eyes.
It's an honor.
-Please come often.
-Oh, I will.
I would love to get her autograph.
Oh, you're back.
Are you going to laminate more notes?
-No.
-Someone in your family
has Alzheimer's, right?
That must be tough.
A long illness can wear down a family.
My friend's dad is ill,
and it's really hard caring for him.
Sometimes, he wishes
he could forget about his dad.
It's a big headache.
I don't recall asking you to tell me.
Why do I have to listen
about your friend's situation?
I didn't mean it like that.
How could he consider
his dad's illness as a headache?
I know a person who acts
the exact opposite to him.
-Writer Han, you were impressive.
-What?
I didn't hear you. Say it again.
You said it was wrong to consider
a family illness as a headache.
I felt uncomfortable
when the storeowner said that.
I was uncomfortable with it.
That's why I spoke up.
Thanks for laminating
the notes on the fridge.
I laminated them because
the frayed edges were bothering me.
If something bothers you,
it's good for me, isn't it?
Let me carry some of your stuff for you.
That's okay. I'm fine.
We can't let people see us
walking together.
I'll pretend we met by coincidence.
It's a piece of cake.
I'll tell them that you're a writer friend
and that we met by coincidence.
Maybe not.
I'll say that we're very close.
Very close?
Don't get so close. It's too warm.
It's too warm?
On a chilly night like this?
Wait for me.
What are you doing?
You didn't notice I was back?
Oh, hi. You seem to be in a good mood.
You're smiling.
I am?
Because it's a full moon.
-What are those pills for?
-I have indigestion.
You've been acting strange lately.
You sold off the house
that Bi-soo was living in.
Then you tell me you're resigning.
I want to retire and enjoy life.
I want to smell something else
than sanitized hospital hallways.
Like flowers and
freshly-baked bread in the morning.
-Before it's too late.
-Why would it be too late?
We've still got a lot of years left.
Anyway, if you want to retire,
then I'll do my best to run the hospital.
I won't disappoint you.
I'll work hard in my new job.
So I need your full support.
You always achieve
what you set your mind on doing.
Recommending you to
the hospital board is all I can do.
You'll be able to get the job on your own.
Closing doors and drawers
is a habit of yours.
I thought you were doing that
out of anger.
The door exists to be closed.
No, it exists to be opened.
Absolutely not.
They exist to divide spaces,
so why would you leave them open?
I even caught you
closing the door to my room.
Why are you so obsessed
with closing doors?
When I see a door half-open,
I can't stop staring at it.
It bothers me, and I get
this uncontrollable urge to close it.
It's very distracting.
That must be stressful.
Writer Han.
What now? You have another favor?
No.
I suddenly told you
that my mom was coming over,
and you didn't complain at all...
I don't need a thank you.
I don't help people
just because they ask for it.
I am doing this because I want to.
All right.
Thanks to you, we're done.
Thank you, Tenant.
Thanks, Landlord.
[Bothersome]
If something bothers you,
it's good for me, isn't it?
[Bothersome]
Are you going out?
Obviously.
Thank you for agreeing to
stay somewhere else.
While I'm away, you can
keep the doors open if you like.
-Writer Han.
-Oh Joo-in.
You can go first.
The door....
Thank you for taking the time to close it.
Have a pleasant time away.
Good morning, Mr. Yoo.
-Oh, boy.
-What are you doing here?
Did you get kicked out?
I feared this would happen. Oh, no!
Focus on doing your job, okay?
Turn on your laptop. Let's start working.
Right now?
["Red Siren"]
["Red Siren", Episode 1]
[A crime thriller doesn't
have to be bloody all the time.]
[You know, boy meets girl,
girl meets boy. They fall in love...]
-Yes.
-You never call your mom first.
I was going to call you.
There's a lot I fell short as a mother.
Why are you saying that all of a sudden?
I feel bad.
Come out for lunch.
Thanks to you, I'm returning to
our old home for the 1st time in 14 years.
It's exactly the same.
It was nice to watch
the laundry dry in the front yard.
Hello?
[Are you the wife of Mr. Oh Hyun-chul?]
[This is Hanjoo Hospital's
emergency center.]
[Your husband collapsed
and was brought to our hospital.]
[He's in critical condition.]
Mom.
-Mom.
-Yes?
Let's go inside. You must be tired.
Okay.
It's so cozy and warm.
You even have a record player.
It would be nice to listen to a record
while sitting in the courtyard.
I bought it for that purpose.
How about taking a rest?
You can look around later.
I want to look around the house.
Don't treat me like a patient.
Why is the fridge so well organized?
Did you actually do this?
When I put my mind to it, I can.
You didn't have to do this
because I was coming.
Looks like you don't cook.
You don't have any food ingredients.
Because I usually eat out.
It's too much work to cook.
But cooking is fun
once you start doing it.
Cooking at home is healthier too.
The things that were a hassle to do
are what you remember the most.
Mom, hearing you nag like that
is so nice.
It's great.
I didn't have time to unpack.
So I read books and scripts here.
-Do you remember that time?
-Of course.
It feels like your dad could be here
writing at any minute.
I miss him.
Mom.
You worked so hard for this, Joo-in.
Thanks.
Why are you only eating vegetables?
My tastes have changed.
You don't crave any foods
because you've tasted
almost all fine cuisines?
Perhaps.
When will you tell me where you're living?
Why do you need to know?
I'll clean up the place
and organize your things.
Then I'll cook something for you there.
I'm curious to know what it looks like.
You know, do the things
that other moms do.
You're bored with running a hospital?
Doing ordinary stuff
that moms do doesn't fit you.
Are you seeing anyone?
I don't have time for that.
I'm too busy writing scripts.
Make time to date someone.
You made a lot of money.
I'll get around to it.
Stop nagging me.
I won't tell you to get married,
but you should date a girl.
-I'm going home, Mom.
-No, enjoy your food.
I won't hang out with you
if you keep this up.
Okay, okay.
-Start dating.
-Come on.
It feels like
I'm back at the nursing home.
You really don't have to.
I like doing this for you.
The oils smell nice,
and I'm able to be a dutiful daughter.
It makes me happy.
[She can stay for a short while with you,]
[but she might display erratic behavior
because she has Alzheimer's.]
[If there's an incident,
call us at any hour, and we'll help.]
I'm Park Gun-ho, and I've been
appointed as your aide.
Nice to meet you.
My sister told me a lot about you.
This is a phone you can use in Korea.
Thanks.
I need to call someone.
[Joo-in]
Hey, Yu-jin. It's been so long
since you last called me.
[You're even busier than me.]
How is Paris?
We visited the Eiffel Tower
and Montmartre together.
[Is it still nice there?]
Paris has the Louvre,
Eiffel Tower, and Montmartre,
but you're missing.
So it's no fun.
I'm so sorry that I missed
your exhibition.
I couldn't find time in my schedule.
That's okay.
Don't lie. It's not okay.
By the way, something great happened.
I bought my old home and moved in there.
Really?
I'm so happy for you.
You always wanted to live there again.
It took me 10 years to return here.
[Good job.]
It must've been tough,
but you never showed it.
You don't have to
hide your feelings around me.
Be yourself, okay?
I won't be annoyed.
Wait. It sounds like you're
in the neighborhood.
Did it sound like that?
I guess I miss Seoul a lot.
Then come back soon. Paris is so far.
I miss you, Yu-jin.
I miss you too, Joo-in.
When did you get here?
You have writer's block again?
No, I just came.
I see. Just because.
The girl I had a crush on in college
came to see me out of the blue.
What?
She was cute back then,
but now she looks so elegant.
Did she have a crush on you too?
I don't know.
I think she just considered me
as a funny college senior.
But it was so nice to meet someone
from my college days.
It brought back a flood of memories.
I felt young again.
Like I was in my 20s.
-You don't look young at all.
-Do you have to say that?
Stop talking about the girl
you had a crush on.
Any new records?
-Show them to me.
-You're so cold.
They're over there.
These?
Don't ever write a script about romance.
She must've been very tired.
Squash, green onion,
chili peppers, mushrooms.
Slice the chili peppers.
Split the mushrooms.
Slice the squash sideways.
Slice the onions into thick slices.
Make the tofu into cubes.
They're not that bad.
I bought them from a guy
who had no space to keep them.
There are a few gems in there.
Isn't this album a killer
Don't say that word.
I can't find a better word
than "sick" to describe it.
Stop it. I have to get it out of my head.
Are you getting stressed over someone?
Is someone giving you problems?
-To the point you want to kill them?
-Yes.
What?
Now she can't kill him herself.
She'll have to get someone else
to do the deed.
What are you talking about?
I can make her the killer
instead of the doctor.
It won't create any problems in the story.
Gosh, he's talking to himself.
What should I name her?
Cha Eun-kyung?
No, that sounds like a doctor's name.
A name...
Will Oh Joo-in be able to handle the role?
Guitar.
Guitarist Oh Joo-in. She uses
a customized rifle shaped like a guitar.
The female killer, Guitarist.
I got it.
I got it. The Guitarist is the killer.
I got it. A guitar shape.
Has he gone crazy?
[Part 1. Guitarist, Female Killer]
I knew it wouldn't work.
I'm a top writer. I'm Han Bi-soo.
No!
That's not it!
Do I have to go to such lengths?
Yes, I do. I have to do it now or never.
I'll just write a few pages.
["Guitarist, Female Killer"]
These pages are warm to the touch.
The smell of fresh printer ink.
Female killer...
I added some murder scenes that I like.
And introduced the Guitarist.
There are also some romantic scenes.
In the last mission, she pulls the trigger
but fails to kill him.
-She suffers from memory loss.
-What are you doing here?
Can't you tell? I'm working.
How can you be here right now?
My mom is here.
Oh, I forgot.
-Hurry before my mom sees you.
-Okay.
-Hurry up!
-I'm packing my computer.
-Hurry.
-Honey.
Honey, good morning.
[Oh! Master]