♪In the distant hills, a goose cries
with head bowed, walking alone♪
♪The river reflects
the shadow of longing♪
♪The grass beside me looks up,
searching the sky♪
♪Yet, even the eastbound spring water
cannot drown my heartbeat♪
=Burning Passion=
=Episode 21=
Shen Qingru,
who
am I
to you?
You
are...
Jiang Wei! Die!
Cheng!
Answer me.
What?
Answer my question.
At a time like this?
Focus on staying alive!
There are plenty of people
who want me dead.
If you don't tell me now,
there may not be another chance.
Jiang Wei.
♪A goose cries
with head bowed, walking alone♪
♪The river reflects
the shadow of longing♪
♪The grass beside me looks up,
searching the sky♪
♪Yet, even the eastbound spring water
cannot drown my heartbeat♪
Why not come out and kiss?
Father!
You...
You two...
Are you even a man?
Let him go!
Shen Cheng,
my biggest mistake
was letting you leave Chunshui Town.
Yan Jun.
Let my father go, and I'll stay with you
until the end of our days.
Excellent suggestion.
My father's dead.
I no longer have anything
to keep you by my side.
Ms. Shen.
I can give you everything,
including myself.
And I can destroy everything,
including you.
No!
Qingru.
Yan Jun.
If you don't let my father go,
I'll fight you
until the end of our days.
Point the gun
at me.
Qingru...
There is nothing crueler
than striking one's weakness.
I am no match for you
when it comes to having a stone heart.
I know exactly what you want.
And I also know what you fear the most.
Father!
Father... Father!
Sir.
After them!
Yes, sir!
Several groups of people
didn't get word about the ceasefire
and came for the bounty.
I left a few alive.
Kill them.
Understood.
Stop!
Marshal.
Mr. Song.
What brings you here?
Cheng?
Marshal?
Jiang Wei.
(Deputy Song, Jiang Family Army)
Grand Marshal Jiang is critically ill.
If you hurry,
you might still make it in time.
Didn't get that from the phone call.
If you could figure it out
from a phone call,
he wouldn't be Grand Marshal Jiang.
Mr. Song.
If you don't leave now,
I'll shoot the woman
that's keeping you here.
I'm taking her with me.
I will not aim my gun
at Grand Marshal Jiang's son.
Either you shoot me right now,
or you come with me.
There's no other option.
(Yan's Residence)
Yan Jun.
If she loses even a single hair,
in three days,
I'll return with my troops
and flatten Chunshui Town!
So, it was you and your brother
who destroyed everything
the Yan family worked so hard to build.
Tell me.
How do you think
this should end between us?
Only one of us will survive.
You're right.
As you wish.
(I sent you away)
(because I didn't want you
to see any of this.)
(I have no regrets in this life.)
(My only regret is that)
(I won't get to see you grow up.)
(Wei,)
(don't ever bring me up again.
Not at home,)
(not in front of your father,)
(all right?)
(You killed her!)
(I couldn't accept Mother's death,
so I left home without a second thought.)
(I kept my promise to Mother,)
(and for over ten years,
I never spoke of her again.)
(Until three years ago,)
(when I was separated from Qingru.)
Sir.
Marshal Jiang has returned.
♪I wish I could go back to that time♪
♪When a shooting star
brushed past the Earth♪
♪Waiting all night long♪
♪You said if time could freeze
at this very second♪
♪We would have the whole universe♪
♪When I start missing you again♪
♪I try to slow down time♪
♪That moment of brilliant fireworks♪
♪If only I could truly
do it all over again♪
♪Just once would be enough♪
♪With a sincere heart, I would♪
♪Say all the things I never said♪
♪At least I once loved you♪
♪In your life♪
♪Why has there been silence♪
♪After that day?♪
♪All the words we should've said
are now in a black hole♪
♪Along the arc of missing you♪
♪I slowly fall♪
♪And I'm lost on a lonely planet
without you♪
♪Please don't look back at me♪
♪I'll be fine♪