♪In the distant hills, a goose cries
with head bowed, walking alone♪
♪The river reflects
the shadow of longing♪
♪The grass beside me looks up,
searching the sky♪
♪Yet, even the eastbound spring water
cannot drown my heartbeat♪
=Burning Passion=
=Episode 20=
That's the full situation.
Ms. Shen really doesn't look well.
Why?
Cheng's already handed her the gun.
She should be doing just fine.
If Cheng hadn't meant to leave him
for her to deal with,
he wouldn't have gone to such lengths
to bring down the Yan family.
- What's the situation at the front line?
- Proceeding according to plan.
What about the roads?
At least another two or three days
to clear them.
Have them hurry.
Yes, sir.
The Yan family can't afford
to keep servants for you,
nor your illegitimate son.
He...
He's your brother...
My brother?
My mother's been dead for 12 years.
How could I have
a five-year-old brother?
12 years.
She should have reincarnated by now.
Maybe that's for the best.
She won't have to meet you again
in her next life.
I will bear
your sins and karma.
Jun...
Estranged from your son.
Fortune lost.
Your own flesh and blood scattered.
No one left to bury you when you die.
Misery doesn't taste good, does it?
You defiled my mother
and drowned her.
The day my brother died,
so did my innocence.
You brought this all
upon yourself.
(Yan)
Cheng.
You've had that map
spread out all afternoon.
But your eyes haven't been on it once.
Sir. The former clan leader is dead.
Ms. Shen has returned
to the Shen's Residence.
So she really was after revenge?
Second Young Master,
after what's happened to the Yan family,
is that even a question?
Women can be vicious.
Deputy Zhang,
clear the roads immediately,
so my brother can escape...
I mean, head to the front line.
Someone kept saying
this has nothing to do with Shen Qingru,
but now he's glaring at me.
What's that supposed to mean?
Haven't you been hurt enough?
Second Young Master.
Please say less.
Just wait for the military order.
Let's see if you leave or not.
Marshal! Emergency order!
Sir.
Yes, sir.
Cheng, I was just joking.
Didn't mean to jinx it.
Did something change at the front line?
Grand Marshal Jiang and Jiangbei
have reached an agreement
to resist
foreign invaders together.
That's great news!
I've been waiting for them
to unite against foreign enemies!
Withdraw the troops.
Yes, sir.
Father,
you go first.
I'll follow soon.
Old Master is kind man.
Yes, he is.
Have some more.
Thank you.
Cheng...
Even if your brother came back,
he'd only be five years old.
You're back.
I've avenged us,
Cheng.
You never actually left me.
You gave me the evidence
of the Yan family's collusion
with the Lu family, didn't you?
Answer me.
Only if you take your medicine first.
Your clothes are wet.
You should get changed.
♪When a shooting star
brushed past the Earth♪
♪Waiting all night long♪
Where are you going?
What?
Do you want to change in front of me?
♪We would have the whole universe♪
♪When I start missing you again♪
♪I try to slow down time♪
♪That moment of brilliant fireworks♪
Shen Qingru,
who
am I
to you?
♪I wish I could go back to that time♪
♪When a shooting star
brushed past the Earth♪
♪Waiting all night long♪
♪You said if time could freeze
at this very second♪
♪We would have the whole universe♪
♪When I start missing you again♪
♪I try to slow down time♪
♪That moment of brilliant fireworks♪
♪If only I could truly
do it all over again♪
♪Just once would be enough♪
♪With a sincere heart, I would♪
♪Say all the things I never said♪
♪At least I once loved you♪
♪In your life♪
♪Why has there been silence♪
♪After that day?♪
♪All the words we should've said
are now in a black hole♪
♪Along the arc of missing you♪
♪I slowly fall♪
♪And I'm lost on a lonely planet
without you♪
♪Please don't look back at me♪
♪I'll be fine♪