♫ My life has never felt regret for anyone ♫
♫ Accompanying you to combust with romance until we’re extinguished ♫
♫ I will cherish every tear in our lives ♫
♫ One day I will be strong and not choking with sobs ♫
♫ I’m blindly pursuing, not compromising, to protect someone ♫
♫ I want to wish for a tomorrow with you in it ♫
♫ I just want to live again ♫
♫ I can face every day proudly ♫
♫ There will always be opportunities in life ♫
♫ Are you ready for them? ♫
♫ To live again ♫
[HIStory 3: Make Our Days Count]
[Episode 2]
What do you guys want anyway?
Stop hassling me.
What do you mean it's none of my business?
Anything to do with Brother Chigang is something to do with me.
Do you also like Brother Chigang?
Let go!
He's mine.
No one can interfere or sabotage me!
I don't understand what you're talking about...
Sun Boxiang, what are you doing?
Bothering another student?
Student, are you okay?
I'm fine.
If anything's wrong, remember to tell teacher.
Thank you, Teacher.
Did he provoke a group that he shouldn't have?
Look at it now.
Xiang Haoting said you stood him up,
so he kidnapped your desk and chair.
He wants you to meet him in the engineering building.
Can you return my desk and chair?
Apologize.
Why do I need to apologize?
You didn't show up yesterday.
I never agreed to show up.
You got my brothers into trouble and they've been punished to sweep the schoolyard.
That's because they hit me.
They hit you because you were stealing my girlfriend.
I'm not stealing your girlfriend.
She sat down and asked me to tutor her with homework.
She said she didn't bring a jacket
and it was cold.
Are you a man?
Blaming the girl for everything?
A bookworm like you...
Do you think the world revolves around you?
I don't like her.
Then, why do you keep getting close to her?
I told you I'm not trying to get close to her!
All you can say is "I didn't," do you know how to say anything else?
I'm just asking for a simple apology, is that so hard?
I didn't do anything wrong, why should I apologize?
Say it again.
I didn't do anything wrong so I will never apologize!
Xiang Haoting!
Let go!
If you don't let go,
I'll ask your parents to come to school!
Okay, okay.
You get back to class right now!
You...
Come with me to the instructor's office!
Yu Shigu!
Are you okay? Did he hurt you?
You're the one that asked the school instructor to come?
Of course.
Because when Xiang Haoting gets angry, he's scary.
Stop meddling in my business.
I don't want to be wrongly accused of anything anymore.
You don't need to worry.
I already planned on breaking up with Xiang Haoting.
I don't like you getting so close to me.
Please stay far away from me.
Who likes you?
That's enough.
Get up.
There are still 32 minutes left.
You--
You really are stubborn!
Don't blame your father for making you kneel.
This time, it really was your fault.
You promised us that you would never beat up anyone again.
I remember!
So I only pushed and pulled him a little.
I didn't do anything else.
You're still so young.
Just a student... What's the need to make this into such a big deal?
Besides, you're a big kid!
You lifted the other person up. If he got injured, then what would you do?
Promise me!
Never again!
Mommy, this is a matter of principle.
So what if he's the valedictorian.
No sense of honor at all.
Blames the girl for everything!
And also likes to snitch! I despise these types of people.
That's easy then.
You go and get the top mark on the next exam
and make him angry.
Reverse psychology doesn't work on me.
I will find some other way to make him angry.
I really don't understand.
You--
What's the point of moving someone's desk and chair?
The instructor told you to move it back. Do you hear me?
You're really not getting up?
I really don't know what to do with you!
- Bye-bye.
You're mopping the place yourself?
Are you hungry?
Do you want to grab something to eat?
I've noticed that your training's improving lately.
How about if we…
We've known each other so long now.
Do you want to... go catch a movie with me?
Brother Chigang!
Don't be like that, okay?
Waiting is so boring!
Why did Old Sun take a leave of absence?
No need to wait.
I'm starving.
You're provoking us!
Are you my brother or not?
I'm here.
You're finally here!
I got your favorite.
You know me best.
Awesome.
Yours.
Thanks.
A-hao, why did you return his desk and chair?
Don't bring it up.
We can't just let this go.
Why keep hassling him?
Don't you feel that he's pretty self arrogant and really needs a good beating?
Don't forget what happened in the first year.
His eyes were way up on his forehead.
That arrogance.
All day, he would be with that Zhuang person.
Forget it.
Bookworms like to be with their same kind.
They look down on us.
Why say that?
He just studies harder and cares about his grades.
Not like us.
Why do you keep sticking up for that Gu guy?
I can't stand him.
Forget it.
I'll handle the bookworm.
What are you going to do?
Take care of him?
Me too.
I must find a way to piss him off.
Hey, don't joke around.
We're in the third year.
We need to think about what we should do after graduation
A-hao, what would you like to do after graduating?
Are you asking me?
Look at him being so cocky.
I know! Be in the mob.
You're going to be in the mob. I have my own plans.
You're not going to try to get into university?
Is university mandatory?
Guess not.
Sounds reasonable.
You have the guts to tell your mom and dad?
Of course, I have the guts to do so, why wouldn't I?
I don't have the guts.
Wimp!
Just eat.
He'll be okay!
His parents, teachers, girlfriend: he doesn't need to care.
He's not worried.
His worry (care) factor is zero.
That's true.
Could you be like him?
I'll just eat
Let me see!
I don't believe you!
I'm serious!
You're the one that made everything up!
Hi!
Bye.
Going back to class.
Baby, you haven't returned any of my messages.
You're still mad at me?
No.
You're clearly still mad.
Didn't you say you like Yu Shigu?
Are you serious or just pretending?
I said that only to make you angry.
Because you haven't even bothered to talk to me for so long.
I'm sorry.
I like you.
Going forward... I won't have much time to spend on you, either.
That's okay.
We can concentrate on preparing for the midterm exams.
But after our exams, let's plan a trip together. Okay?
I'm really sorry.
Baby, kiss-kiss.
Let's make up, kiss-kiss.
You!
They're really spontaneous.
Start kissing just like that.
You really want to, too.
What is it?
Can you buy me some soymilk?
What the hell's your problem? Asking me to come all this way just to buy you a cup of soymilk.
And then tell him sorry for me, I know I was wrong.
I didn't do it on purpose, can he forgive me?
And then can we be like we were before? Everything was okay--
Wait!
So you want me to be your sorry bag now to help you apologize to the girl you like?
No!
Then, what is it?
It's a guy.
You're joking!
You're the manly man! Tell me.
What are you really doing?
Why are you getting so pissed off? What are you mad about?
I really do like him!
Really, really, really like!
So you're being for real?
I thought you...
I thought you went to the gym to see those--
I got you, Brother!
Which one?
The one on the left or the one on the right?
The one inside.
The one inside is kind of old.
Are you going to help or not?
Brother, it's not that I don't want to help you.
If you want to apologize, you need to do it yourself for it to be sincere.
Asking someone else to apologize for you is totally insincere. Why would anyone forgive you?
I'm afraid he won't listen to me.
Scared?
Everyone is scared! That's why you need to go and do it!
To show you're determined.
Understand?
Did you bring your little mushroom?
Yup.
Then go!
You can do it.
I'll wait for you here.
Go!
Welcome.
I'm not here to apologize!
It's not wrong to like you!
You...
Keep it down.
I don't want to be quiet!
Lu Chigang, I like you!
Also, I don't regret what happened in the bathroom--
Can you act more mature?
This is my work place.
Do you know what you're doing?
Why come here to make trouble?
Did you think about what your actions would result in?
First, it was the gym. Now, at my place of work.
I'm sorry.
Let me tell you one more time.
Please don't come to make trouble anymore.
Okay?
Student Yu Shigu, you really did very well this time.
Teacher is very happy.
And here is an exam.
Take it home and work on it.
This summer if you're not too busy, practice more.
Because I believe that these questions will benefit you a lot.
What's the zodiac sign of people born on this day?
Raise your hand if you know the answer.
Okay, please speak.
Pisces.
That's right.
Here, next question.
People born on the day of Summer Solstice are what zodiac sign?
Here.
You.
Please reply.
Carry me a little, quick!
Carry me.
Didn't I carry you?
I'm out of blood, quick!
Lost again.
You're the worst.
These types of days, when will they end?
That's right. Every day it's exam, exam, exam.
I really can't stand it anymore.
Exams are good.
Concentrate on exams.
Then, you'll have no time to think about anything else.
Old Sun, you didn't do so well on the exam.
Yeah.
Lately, you've been acting kind of strange.
Speak.
That's enough.
Don't bother him.
This is us caring for him.
That's right!
You're all the same.
Why is school not over?
I really want to play basketball.
Midterm exams are tomorrow.
Xia De, didn't you prepare the exam questions?
Weren't we going to get together and go over them?
- No.
- No way!
Then I'm going to take off, I won't hang out with you guys after school.
I have something way more important to do.
Are you going to Chambers?
Why don't you take us with you?
That's right, together.
You'll find out soon.
Here we go again.
I'm going to get something to drink.
Being mysterious again.
Always keeps us in the dark.
Yu Shigu, this is for you.
No need, thanks.
Isn't that Xiang Haoting?
That's right.
Is it really him?
It's really him.
So handsome.
A-hao!
De!
Senior!
Last time the school editorial didn't get a chance to interview you. We really--
Don't have time!
Please, Senior, please. Just give us a little bit of time.
Then, how about if we add your LINE.
Add your LINE.
Can we get your LINE account? Senior, add our LINE, please!
Add LINE!
Thank you, Senior!
This is great!
It's so late, what are you doing still in the classroom?
I'm starving.
You don't need to eat?
No way.
Student Yu, it's about time.
Okay.
Be careful on your way home. Remember to turn off the lights and close the door.
Thank you, Brother Lin.
- Bye-bye.
How long do we need to walk? Why not take the bus when it's available?
Weird.
I got you
I'm leaving!
No way!
Who's there?
Hello.
Xiang Haoting>
Don't be a bother now. It's midterm exams today!
I know.
That's why I picked today.
Xiang Haoting, what do you want?
You want me to apologize, is that it?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Is that okay?
Get out of the way.
I want to go out!
Move!
What the heck are you doing?
Don't hassle me!
Why are you sleeping?
Reporting!
Teacher, I'm sorry I'm late!
I will go take the exam right now!
Student Yu, it's already too late.
You will need to wait for the make-up exam.
Teacher, in these three years I've only been late once.
I'm begging you, please let me take the exam.
What are you doing?
Teacher, I beg you!
Don't bother the students.
Come outside with me.
Xiang Haoting, what are you doing here?
You can see me?
What are you talking about?
Teacher, please!
Please.
I only need three minutes.
I'll be done in three minutes.
The rules are rules.
Begging me will be of no use!
That's right.
If you don't stop, I'll call for the school instructor.
Teacher, I'm begging you!
Yu Shigu, get up.
Please.
Teacher, please.
You, get up!
If you do that, I--
I won't get up unless you agree!
I can't agree!
You're really too much!
Everyone's watching!
Is this really necessary?
Auntie!
Shi-shi, starting today, you'll be living with me.
Okay, then how many days will I live with you?
For a very very long time, because Mom and Dad
went on an exploration with the stars.
What's wrong, Auntie?
Auntie, then is a very, very long time, one month?
When will they come to pick me up?
Can the rain stop just for a while?
I miss you guys so much.
Hi, is anyone home?
How did you come up with that one?
That was a really good one he pulled.
It was awesome!
Bang!
Bullseye!
Where're you going?
It's lunch time.
He's not happy.
Why?
I don't think what A-hao did was okay.
Was it that serious?
He just missed one of his exams.
I bet for that Straight A student,
this incident will be very hard for him to take.
You've really hurt the enemy this time.
I heard that he punched you pretty hard.
It was a fight.
It wasn't getting hit.
It wasn't a fight.
But what I heard was he didn't even care about the teacher trying to hold him back.
He almost got hit.
Also, he cried like someone gone mad.
No way!
None of that's real.
But that's what everyone is saying. Isn't that right?
Just to be able to take the exam, he begged the teacher.
Xiang Haoting was there, too.
If you don't believe me, go ask Xiang Haoting.
Really?
Tell us.
What really happened?
Hey!
Why don't you say it?
Let's think about where we're going for winter break, okay?
How about going to the hot springs?
Sure.
Can we really?
Then... this time, only the two of us.
None of your brothers can come.
Understand?
Let's go.
So he was looking at the grades just now.
For him, grades are really very important.
Let me see how you did this time.
It'll be faster counting from the last place.
Wow, 50 points.
How did you manage to get that?
Your dad's going to give you hell.
So that's why I wanted to ask Brother Chigang to help me out.
Don't you need to prepare for next January's GSATs?
I don't want to affect my studies either.
That's why I'm asking if Brother Chigang has any high paying part-time work.
I'm hoping you can refer me.
You're short on cash?
How can you not have enough money?
Don't be afraid, tell me the truth.
Brother Chigang, I really can't find any high paying part-time jobs.
Please help me.
Little Gu, if you're really in trouble,
you have to let me know.
Okay?
I'm not stealing your girlfriend.
I didn't do anything wrong, why should I apologize?
I won't get up unless you agree.
I can't agree.
Hi-Hi--
Why are you walking so fast?
How am I going to pretend to meet you by coincidence?
What are you doing here?
I... I...
- I was passing by.
- Passing by?
What am I saying?
Passing by?
Am I stupid?
What a lousy excuse.
You bought too much stuff.
Why did you come see me today?
I have something to ask you.
NT$300.
I'm trying to look out for your brother.
You're really looking out for him?
Of course.
Then add another NT$100.
Why are you Xiang's all alike?
What's the matter with him?
Lately, he's been in like a monkey state.
Monkey state?
Like this.
"Nobody bother me now."
Looks so much alike.
Every time he regrets something, he turns into this monkey state.
Regret?
Last time I saw him like this was in elementary school.
He made the whole class dislike another student.
Later, although he apologized and told everyone what really happened,
but no one wanted anything to do with that student anyway.
That's cruel.
Yeah.
So he's regretting something now?
Regret?
He knows how to regret?
Seriously.
What is he regretting now?
You really want to know?
NT$500.
You really are low!
What?
Xiang Yongching! Xiang Yongching! Xiang Yongching!
You really are something!
Immature!
You're immature.
Retard!
You're the retard!
Have you been waiting long?
Sorry.
I asked to meet you and had you come all this way.
The young guy you referred... is he really capable?
As long as you don't give him too many hours,
keep things simple and uncomplicated.
Because he's still a student, he'll probably need to keep a low profile.
Another thing...
If possible, I'd like to come by your workplace to take a look.
Is he your boyfriend?
No.
If not, then how come I haven't been able to get you to come out lately.
To have some drinks.
You, are always too serious.
Let's find a time to have a drink sometime.
Do you have anything else you want to say to me?
Right.
Thank you.
That's not what I was looking for.
Come pick it up when you make your delivery tomorrow.
It's nothing, you always take care of us.
Okay.
Owner Chang, bye-bye.
Little Gu!
Brother Chigang.
I found a job for you.
Thank you, Brother Chigang.
The pay's pretty good, too. NT$400 per hour
NT$400?
It's a bar owned by my friend.
A bar?
Don't worry.
The place is quite uncomplicated and clean.
I go there myself, too.
I go to get drinks, eat meals, and listen to music.
The only thing is that his place is open until very late.
Until 3:00 a.m.
So I already took care of everything.
You can only work on weekends.
Did you hear me?
Thank you, Brother Chigang.
Also, you promised me before to put your studies first.
Once you've saved up enough money, I don't want you to go there anymore.
Come.
This bowl of noodles, finish it right now.
Brother Chigang...
If you want to thank me, be good and listen to me.
Eat it while it's still hot.
Sad.
I can only see you through my phone.
You really haven't spent time with me lately.
Should I answer it for you?
No need.
Hello?
You get out of the car right now!
Get out?
Why do I need to get out of the car?
I'm coming to find you now!
Wait...
You're following me?
That's right!
Lu Chigang, get out of the car, right now!
Can you please pull over up there?
I'm sorry.
Don't say sorry.
If you have any trouble, call me.
♫ I still don’t understand why you left ♫
♫ I still don’t understand why I’m waiting ♫
♫ Waiting for who will remember their responsibility ♫
♫ I’m left at the original place wandering around alone ♫
♫ When the blue sky and white clouds disappear ♫
♫ When you take away the yellow sneakers and the red sweater ♫
♫ When all the colors are gone along with you ♫
♫ Only transparent tears that unceasingly fall accompany me ♫
♫ I still don’t understand why you left ♫
♫ I still don’t understand why I’m waiting ♫
♫ Waiting for who will remember their responsibility ♫
♫ I’m left at the original place wandering around alone ♫
♫ When one story becomes two regrets ♫
♫ Letting two hearts run towards two different futures ♫
♫ All those that can’t be forgotten can only become regrets ♫
♫ But I still can’t understand why the tears won’t stop ♫