♫ My life has never felt regret for anyone ♫
♫ Accompanying you to combust with romance until we’re extinguished ♫
♫ I will cherish every tear in our lives ♫
♫ One day I will be strong and not choking with sobs ♫
♫ I’m blindly pursuing, not compromising, to protect someone ♫
♫ I want to wish for a tomorrow with you in it ♫
♫ I just want to live again ♫
♫ I can face every day proudly ♫
♫ There will always be opportunities in life ♫
♫ Are you ready for them? ♫
♫ To live again ♫
[HIStory 3: Make Our Days Count]
[Episode 5]
What's up with you?
I'm sorry.
You're in a bad mood?
It's nothing. Seeing you makes me happy.
It's okay. There's no need to act for me.
If you're feeling sad then feel sad.
Everyone feels sad once in a while.
Do you want to hear a joke?
I don't know if you'll think it's funny or not,
but I think it's pretty funny.
Do you want to hear it?
Are you trying to make me laugh?
You succeeded.
But I haven't even told you yet.
Do you know what you can do to make me feel happier?
Say you like me.
Let me kiss you.
Or you kiss me.
The one that's not happy right now is me.
So do you want to hear the joke or not?
Do you know which performer doesn't eat lunch?
Mika Nakashima (Jung dao Mei jia).
Why?
Because she doesn't eat lunch.
(Taiwanese pronunciation means: doesn't eat lunch)
[Young Little White]
It's so late already, why haven't you gone home?
Still angry at me?
I know he's your closest brother.
I'm sorry for upsetting you,
but I really can't help him.
Do you like him that much?
I said, do you like him that much?
Touch his head. Give him a job.
Now, you won't even give permission for Xiang Haoting to go out with him.
Are you talking about Little Gu?
Who else?
I just found out today that you knew him much longer than you knew me.
But you already promised you would go out with me.
You should forget about him
and take whatever there is of him in your heart and get rid of it.
Our age gap is too big.
He's like a younger brother to me.
I'm the same age as him.
I don't like him in the same way I like you.
He's a little brother.
Do you understand now?
You kiss me out in the open like this...
Then I want another one.
Hurry and go home.
Quickly, hurry home.
I'm home.
Don't you have a test tomorrow?
Recently, a lot of unbelievable things have happened,
but it's all good things.
All very fortunate things.
I don't know...
What percentage is the ocean?
97.5%!
Good, very good.
Next, rivers are classed into four different categories.
What four categories are there?
Glacial, groundwater,
frost, surface water!
Next. This is an important point. Take notes.
Teacher Liu, can I borrow a student?
Sure.
Student Yu Shigu.
Idiot.
My heart's beating so fast.
As I said, this is an apology drink.
I'm apologizing for Brother Chigang.
I accept.
We're fine.
And please apologize to your Brother Chigang for me, too.
I was too rash and was really mean to him.
I'm sorry.
Also, I will need to ask him a lot about him in the future.
I really can't believe you.
So, just now, it was all about him?
Yup!
Fine. I know you really really love him.
But you have to consider him, too.
Why?
He's an excellent student.
So? I'm an excellent student, too.
If because of you, he gets reported because of rumors,
then what?
Would that happen?
That wouldn't happen!
I've never considered that before.
Don't look.
Just one more look.
Put it away.
I can't help it.
Come out!
Bad hands!
Bad!
How can you do that?
Not listening!
Somethings happened!
Yu Shigu's been asked to go to the schoolmaster's office.
- Why?
- Someone reported him going to a gay bar.
A-hao don't go!
What are you guys doing?
Where are you going?
What?
Why hold him back?
Why can't we hold him back?
Why?
Yu Shigu's picture has your signature!
Tell the schoolmaster! Did you really go into that place?
If you did, you did. If you didn't, you didn't.
Just tell us.
What do you have to say to the schoolmaster?
It's time to speak up now.
If not, you may be reprehended by the school.
Reporting!
Xiang Haoting, what are you doing here?
It's not your turn yet.
Since you're here, let me ask you.
You took this photo.
Did Yu Shigu really go into this place?
Why aren't you talking either?
Didn't you sign this photo and put it into the schoolmaster's mailbox?
Since I was the one that signed it,
then I was the one that did it.
Did he go into that bar or not?
He never went to that place.
What do you mean?
Explain.
I photoshopped this photo.
It's a computerized composition.
It really looks real.
Xiang Haoting, you–
What are you doing?
I really can't put up with you anymore.
Call his parents. I want to meet his parents.
What is going on?
Seriously, who was the one that took the photo.
The point is...
You're back!
Is everything all right?
Wait!
Was everything cleared up?
Tell us quickly!
Didn't A-hao go to the schoolmaster's office and deny it was him?
He even said he was going to speak for you, say you didn't go to the gay bar.
He said the photo was a digital mock-up.
How does he know it's a digital mock-up?
Answer me!
He has the same exact photo on his cell phone.
Impossible!
But if the photo is a mock-up,
then it means the whole thing is fake.
Yes.
Then, where's A-hao now?
He said he was the one that mocked up the photo.
That's impossible!
Please tell us exactly what happened.
What happened just now?
You're still so young and don't want to learn.
What are you doing mocking up photos for?
Okay, whatever it is, let's discuss it when we get home.
Schoolmaster Song, we're sorry.
Our Haoting has often caused you much trouble.
Thank you for showing so much patience in dealing with him.
Asking you to come today is to let you know the situation.
Yes.
I'll ask you one more time.
Where did the photo come from?
Didn't I say Liu Meifang from Class 5 gave it to me?
You. If you don't believe me, you can go ask her.
What's with your attitude?
Speak politely to the schoolmaster.
I don't really like him.
Xiang Haoting!
Because of him, Sun Boxiang and the guys had to sweep for a week.
I had to get back at him.
What's it have to do with you? Are you that bored?
If you wanted to get him in trouble,
then why confess now and say that you mocked up the photo?
Because...
my dad taught me
My dad said a man must take responsibility for his own actions. Right?
I was the one that signed the photo; of course, I have to take responsibility for it.
What are you being so arrogant about? So cocky!
You think you're in the right now?
Enough, Dad!
Let's not do this at school and hit him.
Let's talk about it when we get home.
I'm sorry, schoolmaster.
It's okay.
Are you confessing now all of this was done by you alone?
The school will have to reprimand you,
and it won't be light.
You better think clearly about this!
It was me.
Are you telling the truth?
I'm telling the truth!
It's because he was acting very arrogant, so I wanted to teach him a lesson. That's all.
You doing this. What are you being so cocky for?
Why do you do this all the time?
Dad!
Stop that.
Dad Xiang.
Such an embarrassment!
Since he's admitted that it was all done by himself,
the school will have a discussion to see what the punishment will be.
We'll contact you once it's been decided.
We're sorry.
Thank you, schoolmaster.
Dad.
Schoolmaster, I'm sorry.
Then we'll wait for the school to get back to us.
But our Xiang Haoting,
he's already in his third year of high school.
We hope that he can still graduate and continue with college.
So, I hope the schoolmaster will help us.
I will let the school know.
Thank you.
Teacher, I'm sorry for disturbing your class.
A-hao.
Please continue, all of you.
Okay, students. Let's continue with class!
That's way too much!
A major demerit along with five days of suspension.
Think about the good side.
A-hao is probably having a good time at home. He doesn't need to go to class.
No way!
Not wanting to come and not being able to come are two different things.
That's true.
If I see that guy,
I'll kill him for sure.
Think about it guys.
This whole thing could have been planned by Yu Shigu himself.
What you're saying is he's taking revenge for the mid-term exam?
You guys are overthinking this,
and blaming Yu Shigu for all of it.
You're not afraid that Xiang Haoting would come after you guys?
I'm going.
Yu Shigu.
- You...
- I just wanted to let you know,
this thing wasn't done by Xiang Haoting.
You have to believe what that fool said.
He wasn't the one that did it. That's all.
There is one thing that I need your help with.
No matter how much Xiang Haoting hates Yu Shigu,
he wouldn't do that to him.
This isn't his style of doing things.
But he signed his name on the photo.
It's not about the signature.
When he really hates someone, he would confront them directly.
He wouldn't bother going through the school or teachers
and relying on people snitching.
So that's why they all disliked Yu Shigu so much before.
But he really did ask me for the photo.
The schoolmaster even asked me down to ask me.
Why did you give it to him?
He tricked me.
Dumby.
Are you sure you're the only one that has that photo?
Of course. Even though we exchange photos often,
that one's so cute, it's for my personal collection.
And for Xiang Haoting.
Positive?
- Tingan.
- Tingan?
Zhang Tingan?
Really?
That time when we went to eat cake,
after you left, he asked me for it.
What did he want Yu Shigu's picture for?
I don't know.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Sorry for keeping you waiting so long.
Oh my, I'm so tired.
You mocked up the photo?
What photo?
- The one with Yu Shigu.
- What are you talking about?
- Did you see the letter from Xiang Haoting to me?
- Which one?
It's can't be Tingan. Didn't Xiang Haoting already confess?
Did you mock-up that photo?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You clearly saw that letter he wrote to me.
- The one that he signed.
- There are so many, they all look the same.
Don't lie to me. Zhang Tingan!
It was me.
It was me that mocked up the photo and forged Xiang Haoting's signature.
Why did you do that?
I was getting revenge for you.
Who asked him to treat you like that?
Let's go clear it up with the schoolmaster!
What are you doing? I'm not going.
What do you mean you're not?
If you didn't cry your eyes out like that and weren't that depressed,
I wouldn't have to do something like this!
You're really low!
What you just said really hurts.
Have you ever considered me a good friend?
Someone who would do something like this isn't fit to be my friend.
Li Shiyu, do you know that I have always liked you?
Forget it. Do whatever you want.
Tingan!
Speak. What do you want?
Got a beating and being suspended,
you still have the mood to sing and play with your phone.
What?
Who gave it to you?
♪ Hitting my children ♪
♪ Pain in my heart ♪
That's impolite; copying Dad.
Come on!
Wipe it down yourself!
That hurts!
What did you see?
Who is it? Why do you care so much?
Not telling you.
Who cares?
So mean.
Long time no see.
What is it? You're looking for me.
There's something I need to apologize for.
What thing?
The photo incident.
You're the one that did it!
Half-true.
How did you know about the bar?
I didn't know about the bar.
I was walking with Sister Meifang and just happen to see Yu Shigu walk in.
And then?
There's no and then.
We just saw it.
You scared me!
Good thing I'm quick to react!
I'm really something!
You're not mad?
Nope.
But I still want to go tell the schoolmaster--
Don't do that.
Yu Shigu is not a very good talker.
If you tell the schoolmaster, things will for sure...
When did you start to know Yu Shigu so well?
Are you protecting him?
Yes, I'm protecting him.
Why do you want to protect him?
Didn't you used to hate him before?
Now,
as long as he's doing well,
then I'm happy.
Isn't this what it's like to like someone?
Like before when you liked me and I liked you, that kind of like?
I like Yu Shigu.
I really like him!
Thank you.
After telling you just now, I feel so much better. YES!
Xiang Haoting, you really are crazy.
That's what my dad says.
Bye!
Good thing I broke up with him already.
That really hurts! What are you doing?
Who asked you to eavesdrop?
I'm going to close the door in a bit. When I open it and if you're still there,
what's going to hurt won't just be your ears.
Get out.
Take a seat on my bed first.
No need.
How do you know where my house is?
I asked Sun Boxiang.
I have something to tell you.
Agreeing to be with me?
No.
What I want to say is I know you didn't do it.
How do you know it wasn't me?
You're not that type of person.
You understand me so well.
I don't care if you believe me or not.
I know you had nothing to do with it.
It must be because of the mid-term exam.
They all thought you hated m,
so they used this to get back at me.
You could've not come to the schoolmaster's office.
- But...
- But I went.
And I said I did it.
I said the photo was mocked up by me.
Actually, you've never been to the bar.
Then I got a major demerit and was locked up at home.
I know you understand in your heart...
I like you.
I believe you understand.
Because I know...
that you have already started to like me.
I don't!
No?
Liu Meifang LINEd 132 of your photos to me.
How's that possible?
Don't deny it; I have proof.
This one.
You're looking right at me.
I used red circles to mark them.
You still want to deny it.
Yes, I was looking at you.
You're admitting it?
And you said you didn't like me.
It's not like, it's because I'm curious.
Curious?
About what?
Just... You know how much I care about grades?
So I will always go look at the school rankings.
After the 2nd year exams,
didn't you get the second highest mark in the school?
Yeah.
We were only 4 marks different,
so I thought you were my competitor.
Wait. No way!
So, you started noticing me because of this?
Yeah.
I thought...
But after that time,
you started to rank starting from the worst place.
So I thought you were pretty unique.
Do what you want to do.
Whatever your heart desires. No restrictions.
And don't even care what others think.
Just like you've got the whole world in the palm of your hand.
Don't flatter me too much.
I'm not trying to flatter you.
I really do envy you.
I can never be like you.
Why?
I don't want to be a burden to others.
I also can't be a burden to others.
You're not.
Doing what makes you happy, how can that be a burden?
This is what I envy about you the most.
I was raised by my aunt.
She later got married and had kids.
She got tired.
I needed to be independent, needed to be strong,
needed to learn to rely on myself.
I really wanted to be like you.
Laugh when I felt like laughing, be angry when I felt mad,
and be able to get along with everyone so well.
Getting punished, or getting demerits,
not needing to care about them.
That's how I saw you.
I felt like I gained a little freedom, too.
You know? After getting to know you,
I started to think and feel that
if my parents didn't leave me when I was so young,
would everything be different?
Would everything be different than it is today?
♫ Let yourself be fragile for once ♫
♫ I will be like this in front of you ♫
♫ At the time that you need it, gently say ‘Hey’ ♫
Starting from today, you have me.
I will give you my everything
Also, his sister told me, his dad slapped him.
And his face got all red.
If that person really wanted to frame him,
then it's pretty bad for Little Gu,
to get caught up in all of this.
It's true if you put it that way.
But Xiang Haoting kept protecting him.
I'm telling you. As long as Little Gu doesn't go out with him, nothing will happen to him.
Don't hate Xiang Haoting.
If you got to know him longer,
you'd know that he's a real man.
He's only in his teens, how could he be a real man?
Stop bringing up age all the time.
You're mad?
You get mad so easily.
This proves that you're still a young boy.
But you're my little boy.
Forget it.
This Sunday my cousin has me closing up the gym.
Could you come to work out later that day,
then be with me when I close up shop?
Sure.
That's perfect, I'm not working that day either.
Let's go.
Is this okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
Good morning.
Your breakfast.
I missed you.
Why did you sneak over?
I prepared breakfast already.
You're just eating that?
Don't eat that.
Eat what I prepared.
Thanks.
You came all this way to just give me this?
Of course.
Actually I have something else really important to ask for your help on.
It's just that my dad is still pretty angry.
I was thinking of doing better on the final exams,
so he'll be happier.
Currently the second from last ranking is begging you for your help.
The finals are next next week.
It's fine. You're great with your school work.
It's definitely not a problem for you.
Besides I'm pretty intelligent.
I... When I'm not working part-time, I'm at school.
But lately due to entrance exams,
I've taken on fewer hours for part-time work.
Especially on the weekends.
Then weekends it is.
That's good, right?
I'll come by your place at 1:00 in the afternoon on the weekend.
Yes, sir! Thank you, Teacher Yu.
Okay, hurry up and go home;
or else, you'll get yelled at again.
I'm heading to class.
You like this?
Don't you think it's very cute?
What's it called?
It doesn't have a name.
Then just call him Whitey.
Whitey?
Whitey
Whitey, have some jello.
Little Yu,
have some chocolate.
Yes, Mrs. Fu.
Yes, I know. Mrs. Lee's dog didn't do it on purpose.
Of course, I know.
You know that dogs are all like that.
Not very.
You're so beautiful today.
Yes, good.
I'll go speak to her. No problem.
It's time, I'm going to change.
That. Okay, I will take care of it.
Okay, bye.
What's gotten into him today?
He better not cause any more trouble for me.
He said he has a friend coming over to help him with homework.
He's trying to be studious?
Who knows?
I'll get it!
Friend's a girl?
If it's a girl, we'll have to keep the door open later.
- Yu Shigu.
- Uncle. Auntie. How are you?
I'm Haoting's classmate. My name's Yu Shigu.
He's good.
He's pretty amazing. From the first year until now,
he's always placed first in school!
He really is the legendary bookworm. He never fails.
Xiang Haoting.
That's so great. Welcome.
Our house has never had a guest with such good grades before.
Come, sit.
Dad!
He came to help me with my homework.
Don't take up his time.
Okay, okay.
Go and study hard. Make the most of your time.
Do you want anything to eat or drink? Auntie will prepare something.
Thank you, Auntie. We're okay.
Mommy,
I've seen this guy's photo in brother's phone before.
He wouldn't let me eavesdrop on their conversation last time either.
I think something strange is going on.
It's okay, it's a boy anyway.
Since it's a guest, of course, we'll have to prepare something to eat.
Right.
I've noted some main points.
Memorize them. I'll test you in a little bit.
Stay with me.
Teach me.
Stay with me. Teach me.
You said you wanted your dad to be happy.
You coming already makes my dad happy.
You said you really wanted to study and not waste my time.
I am.
Okay. Focus.
I'll read.
I finished reading.
Fine.
A disciple should treat their teacher with humility,
but when accomplishing things
modesty can be put aside.
When facing those that are younger,
- one must remember to be humble--
- Hello!
- Mommy.
- Here son.
- Here.
- Be careful.
The two of you worked hard.
If your eyes are tired or sore later,
just drink some water. Then there's some fruit.
Don't be shy.
How about eating some apples right now?
Here, this.
Come eat some.
Thank you, Auntie.
I really need to thank you. You're really great!
Don't be silly, you!
Auntie...
Your job is done here.
Yes, good. Then you guys continue.
Give it your all!
Mom, close the door.
That way I can concentrate better.
Reasonable.
Right. If you don't have anything to do later, stay for dinner.
Auntie, please, there is no need to trouble you.
It's okay.
He will! He will!
Fighting!
Okay. Keep going.
You, concentrate.
- I'll do my best, okay?
- Okay, okay.
Okay, I'll go and prepare.
Okay.
Love you, Mommy.
Xiang-xiang, you'll be okay by yourself?
No problem at all.
You go be with your girlfriend.
Okay. Make sure everything is clean. Also...
I know
All the machines have to be put back.
Turn off the lights, close the door, and turn off the air conditioning.
Security system!
Right! I remember.
Relax.
Hello, baby.
Yes, I'm already on my way. I'm almost there!
I'm downstairs now, another five seconds.
Five, four! Three point five.
Such a nag.
Are you being naughty again?
No.
Hurry up and clean up.
I'll take you to grab a bite to eat later.
Why are you here?
For you.
Working until now. You must be tired and hungry.
I'm sweet, aren't I?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas.
But I didn't prepare anything.
I have you
Yes!
What are you doing?
I'm happy.
Silly.
- Let's go.
- Go.
Wait for me.
What are you doing?
Getting a taxi.
No need. It's too expensive.
How do you usually go home at this hour?
Convenience store.
So I brought my books with me.
You just got off work, why study?
What you need right now is to relax.
Let me take you somewhere.
There are no buses now.
I have a ride.
Get on.
You can go anytime, anywhere.
Convenient, right?
Retard.
Let's go!
Keep up.
Wait for me!
Where are we going?
Can't tell you yet?
Why?
Where the heck are we going?
I'm almost done.
Wait for me to come out and help you.
Okay.
♫ I still don’t understand why you left ♫
♫ I still don’t understand why I’m waiting ♫
♫ Waiting for who will remember their responsibility ♫
♫ I’m left at the original place wandering around alone ♫
♫ When the blue sky and white clouds disappear ♫
♫ When you take away the yellow sneakers and the red sweater ♫
♫ When all the colors are gone along with you ♫
♫ Only transparent tears that unceasingly fall accompany me ♫
♫ I still don’t understand why you left ♫
♫ I still don’t understand why I’m waiting ♫
♫ Waiting for who will remember their responsibility ♫
♫ I’m left at the original place wandering around alone ♫
♫ When one story becomes two regrets ♫
♫ Letting two hearts run towards two different futures ♫
♫ All those that can’t be forgotten can only become regrets ♫
♫ But I still can’t understand why the tears won’t stop ♫