(This program is a story of girls of different worlds with one dream.)
(This program is the third story...)
(of girls of different worlds with one dream.)
(Republic of Korea)
(Canada, China)
(Japan)
(France)
To be a part of a K-pop girl group,
a total of 82 girls gathered in Korea.
Out of these 82 girls,
only eight girls will head to the final global stage.
Please get...
Tickets to our dreams.
- Tickets to our dreams. - Tickets to our dreams.
(Universe Ticket)
(If I get another chance, I don't want to make a mistake.)
(I want to show a proper performance.)
(I felt wronged.)
(I performed everything live.)
(She performed separately for dancing and singing.)
(I will definitely make sure...)
(to win the next battle.)
(The last hurdle of Battle Week)
(Revenge Battle)
Revenge?
(The Revenge Battle will be a team battle.)
(Winners versus Challengers)
Hold on.
(I'm so excited.)
(My head is full of spite.)
(Revenge)
(I love that title.)
(There's a chance I can get back at someone.)
(That revenge won't be easy.)
(I won't lose twice.)
(Bring it on.)
I'm sorry.
(Cute Challengers' "Tell Me" who dream of revenge)
(There's no main dancer.)
(There's no main vocalist either.)
(Cute Winners' "TT" counterattack with ace members)
(It was very successful.)
The winner of the Cute concept is...
(The first battle comes to an end with an overwhelming Winners win.)
(Team...)
(and me)
(The number of participants who can advance to the Universe...)
(Half of the winning team)
It's half of the winning team.
(Only 20 members can make it to the Universe.)
(Not everyone can survive.)
(It's not a team battle.)
(Should it be seen as an individual battle?)
(The movements don't match toward the end.)
(Jang Sua is quite slow when it comes to learning things.)
(A battle between the girls who want to be in the top 20)
("Why am I doing this?")
(I really want to go home.)
(A sudden act out of the blue by the girls?)
(Episode 3: Tears)
Enchanting Winners and Enchanting Challengers,
please come up on stage.
Enchanting.
I'm really curious.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Enchanting Winners)
(Enchanting Challengers)
They're beautiful.
Hello.
They're so pretty.
How enchanting.
We can see what they're going for with their outfits.
Exactly.
It's "Mister."
(They chose KARA's song that started the Korean wave in Japan.)
(The highlight of "Mister" is the enchanting hip move.)
One, two, three.
- Hello... - 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, boom it!
- Hello. - Hello. We're...
- Team "Mister." - Team "Mister."
- Hello. We're... - What was that?
I think they should do it again.
- My goodness. - Did you work on that?
In 2, 3.
- We are so perfect. - We are so perfect.
- We get a perfect score! - We get a perfect score!
- Hello. We are Team "DIVA." - Hello. We are Team "DIVA."
(Enchanting Challengers chose "DIVA" by After School.)
"DIVA!"
Challengers get a perfect score for the greeting.
- Oh Yoona. - Yes.
During the 1-on-1 Battle,
you were the only one on this team to lose by a point.
It was a close match as you lost 2 to 3.
Right.
(33rd Ahn Seungbi, 49th Oh Yoona)
(The 1-on-1 Battle was decided just by a single point.)
(Oh Yoona lost after a close match.)
(I felt wronged.)
(I performed everything live.)
(She performed separately for dancing and singing.)
(I will definitely make sure to win the next battle.)
(Reveal of the final battle)
The Revenge Battle.
(A chance for revenge has come upon the Challengers.)
(Hold on. I'm so excited.)
I'm so excited.
(Another girl dreams of revenge.)
(This is it.)
(Let me have my revenge.)
The fact that I had a chance to get my revenge...
motivated me with a bigger sense of passion.
We must start an uprising.
- We must get our revenge. - Right.
(The Challengers are determined for revenge.)
Do you remember who you're up against?
I'm against Anxin.
Anxin?
- She performed "Flower." - Right.
She looks really cute.
She's perfect for the cute concept.
She used the chair and went like this.
- Narumi? - Narumi?
She went with the enchanting concept.
- Enchanting. - Right.
I really have no idea what's to come.
(While the Challengers predict the concept...)
The songs will be revealed.
"DIVA" by After School.
"DIVA?"
"Mister" by KARA.
- "Mister." - "Mister."
(Everyone decides to choose "Mister" by KARA.)
We'll win.
- The results are obvious. - Yes.
- Seungbi is feeling energetic. - Right.
- Wait right there. - Let's go!
- We will win! - We're on top!
- We will win! - Wait right there.
(Which girl will smile at the end of Battle Week?)
Anxin.
You don't seem like a match with the enchanting concept.
She's so cute.
How did you interpret the enchanting concept?
To seduce everyone here,
I chose the enchanting concept.
(What do we do?)
That was hilarious.
(We're expectant to see unexpected charms through this battle.)
(How will enchanting Anxin's "Mister" look like?)
She's so cute.
Let's quickly decide on our parts.
Does anyone want Part One?
You do?
- Is everyone okay with that? - Yes.
- Then Seungbi will get that part. - Yes.
Raise your hand if you want Part Two.
All right then.
"My heart keeps pounding."
Let's hear this part.
Can you ask for the song to be played again?
She wants to listen to the song one more time.
Right. She wants to listen to it again?
Why is it so fast?
I'll go first.
Okay. Yuri first.
(Expressions and gestures full of confidence)
All right.
Anxin, next.
It's okay.
We still saw what it was like.
We'll start the vote.
Let's put our heads down.
We'll vote.
Raise your hands for Yuri.
You may put them down.
Raise your hands for Anxin.
Part Two...
- will be given to Yuri. - Thank you.
(Anxin lost the part she wanted.)
Here's the next part.
Part Four will go to Xiaoyu.
- Oh, me? Is that okay? - Yes.
- Yes. - Part Seven will be given to me.
Everyone else speaks Korean but I don't.
I can also only speak a little bit of English.
I couldn't get the part I wanted.
(That night)
(A place where the girls can speak their feelings)
Hello. I'm Anxin.
It's a bit disappointing that I couldn't get the part I wanted.
But it's okay.
This part might not have been a suitable one for me.
It could've been because I was lacking for it.
I will work even harder.
(2 days before the Revenge Battle)
All right. I'll show you the part.
- Twice here. And swirl. - Swirl.
(Peeking)
Everyone learns the moves really quickly.
In a blink of an eye, half of the first verse is gone.
Wait.
Like this.
- Go like this and then do this. - I heard...
how things were going for the other teams.
And it seems like we're being too slow.
(The other teams are almost done working on the choreography.)
- Go like this. - I have a lot on my mind.
It felt like we were a little off.
So I was nervous.
"Hey, there, mister." We're off the beat here.
(Smile smile, just smiling to you)
(Anxin has a hard time pronouncing the lyrics.)
- "I keep..." - "I keep..."
- "Gaining a bit of confidence." - "Gaining a bit of confidence."
(Yewon, the leader teaches them how to pronounce the lyrics.)
You should be able to do it by yourself during the battle.
Anxin, I know it's hard.
But...
you should try to memorize it.
Okay.
I keep falling behind while we practice.
I often forget the lyrics and stop.
(Anxin focuses on memorizing the lyrics alone.)
I'm upset that I caused the other members trouble again.
(That night, at the dorm)
Some of us haven't even memorized the lyrics yet.
Why is it so hard to memorize the lyrics?
- This is serious. - I mean...
That's because they're from other countries.
But still...
But it must be only about...
- 5 to 10 seconds at the longest. - They just need to memorize it.
And they're supposed to sing the "all" part together,
but they don't.
They can't even memorize the dance moves.
And they don't know the song.
You must be frustrated.
What if I don't get to do my thing?
I understand.
Today, when they were practicing the Korean song,
they kept missing the beat and sang off-key.
But that's what determines...
the result of the battle.
So I'm a little afraid.
(1 day before the Revenge Battle)
(They start practicing the lyrics early in the morning.)
(Anxin works harder than anyone else not to cause her team trouble.)
(The group dance is almost complete.)
(Some people are dancing to "Mister?")
(The girls are surprised to see the unexpected guests.)
My goodness.
Be careful.
(Universe Icon, Chaeryeong and Yeji)
(They're making a surprise visit to see how things are going.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Once you're ready,
- please show us. - Hello.
(They check Anxin's lyrics at the last minute.)
Anxin, you should...
(I can't memorize it.)
You can do this.
Just make sure to sing on the beat.
(Yewon and Yuri work together to train her quickly.)
I guess Anxin has a problem.
- Good luck. - Good luck.
They're good.
(She ends up making a mistake at the part that she worried about.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
- Anxin. - Yes.
I noticed that you got...
the lyrics wrong.
Was that because you were nervous?
I didn't practice enough yet.
You didn't practice enough?
But the battle is tomorrow.
You have...
only 2 or 3 parts to sing.
I think you need to practice more.
You have to hurry and memorize it.
Memorizing the lyrics is my biggest concern.
Wherever I go, I bring the lyrics with me...
so I can keep working on it.
Yes, it's you
Yes, it's you, mis...
Mister
(She recognizes her limits for the first time.)
(The burden of getting it done in 3 days weighs her down.)
I think I'm the eighth.
(I think I'm the 8th on the team.)
I don't sing or dance better than the other members.
I don't think I will be able to survive.
(I don't think I will be able to survive.)
I like him
I keep gaining a bit of confidence
First,
Enchanting Winners will perform.
- Yes. - Please go down and stand by.
Okay.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
All right.
Start.
One, two, three, four, five, six, boom it!
- They are so powerful. - Let's do this.
- Good luck. - Good luck.
- Good. - That's cool.
- Good. - They're tall.
That looks amazing.
- Good start. - They're tall.
They're tall.
- They look pretty. - Yes.
They're really pretty.
How can they look so pretty?
That's too bad.
She's cute.
There you go!
- Oh, dear. - Oh, no.
What kind of formation is this?
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- It's a little disappointing. - Yes.
None of them is memorable.
I don't think...
you performed in good harmony.
It felt like...
you didn't practice a lot together.
It looked like you all practiced individually.
And many of you made mistakes with the lyrics.
It felt like you failed to perform as a team.
I could tell...
Yewon and Seungbi were trying hard,
but it didn't feel like...
you were in harmony with the song.
You were just working hard.
I don't think you understood the concept perfectly.
I appreciate your hard work.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
What do we do?
What's wrong? Why are you crying?
I thought the opposing team would win.
I barely remembered the lyrics,
I didn't sing well,
and I didn't even remember the dance moves.
So I was sad.
I was very angry...
at myself.
And I was sad that I didn't take good care...
of my team members.
I'm really upset.
(I'm really upset.)
(Enchanting Challengers watched Enchanting Winners' performance.)
(They feel more nervous as Enchanting Winners get bad reviews.)
Take my heart
Try the part, "I love my boy."
I love my boy
Okay.
- Don't miss it. - Okay.
There's no beat, so you have to be careful.
Okay?
They weren't dancing in straight lines,
so I thought we'd be able to win if we did well.
(3 days before the Revenge Battle)
We have to do this with clenched teeth.
We should be wearing pink.
- Pink. - Right.
This is Revenge Battle, you know.
Hang on.
Wait.
I'm so excited.
I really wanted to get my revenge.
I think we have to finish the first verse today.
I felt bad for those who voted for me to make me first place.
(1-on-1 Battle. 1st Riel versus 54th Xiaoyu)
(Riel lost with a score of 1 to 4 and became a Challenger.)
I have to win this time.
- Let's decide on the leader. - Who should it be?
Does anyone want to be the leader?
Shall I do it?
- Yes. - Yes, good.
- Good. - I'll do it.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
I was upset that I lost.
This is it.
Let me get my revenge.
I really wanted to win.
So I said I'd be the leader.
We saw her during the 1-on-1 Battle,
so we knew she danced really well.
She taught us how to dance.
And she encouraged us and cheered us up.
I liked how well she led us.
It's hot.
- We should repeat over and over. - We should repeat over and over.
Let's keep doing it until we pass out.
I'll work really hard with clenched teeth...
to be a winner.
I'm so happy that the atmosphere of our team is so good.
Would there be a team with a bad atmosphere?
I don't know.
I think Enchanting Winners have a lot of members from abroad.
- Really? - So...
they are not moving forward because of miscommunication.
Are you serious?
That's too bad. What can they do?
They have to do well anyway.
- You're right. - Meeting a good team is luck.
(Meeting a good team is luck.)
(2 days before the Revenge Battle)
(Enchanting Challengers are busy getting a dance lesson.)
Shall we do it again slowly?
(They do the moves slowly again to the beat.)
(Jeong Huigyeong of Challengers)
(Look at my heart...)
- Take my heart - Take my heart
(They keep making mistakes.)
We were in a situation where we needed to move forward quickly.
But there were members...
who kept making mistakes and fell behind.
I found it frustrating.
I have to win this time.
- I'll tell you about my love - Okay.
I realized...
we shouldn't make things easy when we practiced.
- Hello. - Hello.
- We talked about this a lot. - Yes.
I think we will have to change your parts completely.
The parts are too divided.
(They rearranged their parts to build team synergy.)
I think we should put some of them together.
- Okay. - So...
Jinyeong will do this part,
"Promise me that you'll look at me."
- Okay. - And...
(They check the main vocal part again.)
All right. For this part...
- Yui. - Yes.
Can you give this a try?
- Yes. - All right.
(Idota Yui tries singing the main vocal part.)
Good. That's it.
Then the rest of the members will go, "Tonight, tomorrow night."
Okay?
Yes.
We changed all our parts.
Completely.
I was upset that I got fewer parts,
but I understand that it's for the team's sake.
(They practice their new parts again.)
(Their voices become unstable with the new parts.)
(Part 8: Idota Yui)
(Part 1: Jeon Jinyeong)
(Promise me that you'll look at me.)
I got more parts to sing.
So I was a little worried.
(The leader, Jinyeong, keeps making mistakes.)
We trusted Jinyeong, but she kept making mistakes.
That swayed me a lot.
What do we do?
Let's not eat today.
We have to practice.
I don't deserve to eat.
We don't deserve to eat.
We have to get things done within only three days.
(They have to memorize their parts within a short period of time.)
This sounds a lot better.
Why? What's wrong?
Why? No, you did well. It's all right.
- You were good. - Don't cry.
(The changed parts make her burst into tears.)
It's all right.
Don't cry.
(They feel bad that they are being burdens on each other.)
Come on. Don't cry.
Did we lose? That's not it.
- Don't be like that. - We will win.
- I'll get you some tissue. - We didn't lose yet.
- I didn't do well. - What? No.
- Why is everyone crying? - Why...
- What? - Hang on.
Oh, my. What do I do?
What should I do?
It's all right.
We just need to practice hard tomorrow.
Don't cry.
(Challengers are becoming stronger to win the battle.)
Poke, and...
(1 day before the Revenge Battle)
Lower your body now.
Seven and eight.
(Leader Jinyeong leads the members during the practice.)
Sua, your timing to swing your arm is a little off.
Try it again.
(Sua's moves are a little different.)
It becomes off as it goes on.
We have to let our team win in order for us to win.
So I helped Sua a lot.
Good. Do it slowly.
We were determined to win,
and it made us have good teamwork.
(Sua practiced hard with the members' help.)
I want to steel myself and work hard...
so I will do things right...
without making any mistakes.
You...
You go like, "Diva, diva."
What?
(Enchanting Challengers supported each other in the short time.)
Do this.
I will win with clenched teeth no matter what...
and get my revenge.
Our wish to get our revenge...
made us work even harder.
I will get my revenge and smash them.
- They look cool. - That's cool.
("DIVA" by After School)
That's it.
What? They are so good.
Let's go!
- They did well. - They were great.
That was great.
- They were great. Yes. - I got goosebumps.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- They were so good. - Oh, my.
The Challengers killed it.
Their teamwork was much better...
- than the Winners. - Indeed.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Amazing.
I would like to give a huge compliment to Yoona.
Thank you.
Despite the fact that this kind of concept didn't necessarily...
suit your natural style or anything,
you diligently worked to understand...
and study the concept from start to finish.
You kept working hard to the end not to interrupt the flow.
I could clearly see that in your performance.
In my opinion, you had the center position...
for this battle. You were so great that you made me think that.
- Thank you. - Well done.
Sua and Yui.
You guys were incredibly adorable.
Whenever you stepped forward to sing and dance,
Se Jeong who was next to me couldn't stop giggling.
She kept saying, "Oh, my." She couldn't stop adoring you guys.
But as for this battle,
I must be objective when giving my feedback.
Since you guys are new,
your performance came across as a breath of fresh air.
But you might be at a disadvantage as the show progresses.
I don't think this will work on us next time.
You will need to do something about that.
I thought that the Japanese Challengers...
did a great job in this battle.
Let me start with Yui.
You said you weren't much interested in becoming a main vocalist.
But you still did a great job, pulling off your parts.
Gosh. Good work.
- And... Goodness. - Gosh.
- It's okay. - Yui.
(She overcame the pressure of being the main vocalist.)
- Well done. - You were great.
She's crying because her hard work was recognized.
- And Honma Yuriko. - Yes.
I thought you were Korean.
It means that your pronunciation was perfect,
and you also stood out during the performance too.
Thank you.
Jinyeong. Actually, in my opinion,
it was only possible that your teammates were able...
to cover up their weaknesses thanks to your help.
I didn't get the vibe that you were trying to stand out alone.
I felt that you were truly trying to be a good leader for them.
- I wasn't trying to make you cry. - Oh, no.
Being a leader is tough.
Right.
So I think the rest of the team was lucky to have met Jinyeong...
as their leader.
As a leader, she was able to help everyone's strength shine.
I wanted to tell you that you did a great job.
That's such high praise.
Totally. It's such high praise.
I really enjoyed your performance. Good work.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Winners for the Enchanting concept, please come up to the stage.
It must have been tough. Everyone is crying.
It's really agonizing to be in that situation. Seriously.
- You speak from experience. - Right.
You're amazing.
How did you get through that to be sitting here now?
Here are the battle results.
(The Enchanting Revenge Battle results get revealed.)
The winner of the Enchanting concept is...
(Enchanting Winners)
Had I performed well,
I wouldn't have had regrets about my performance.
But we still did our best.
I thought we could beat the Challengers.
I was confident.
But I kept feeling anxious because...
I couldn't be certain.
It's the Enchanting Challengers.
(The Enchanting Challengers win the Revenge Battle.)
Good job.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
With a score of 5 to 0,
Team Enchanting Challengers takes the win.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Do you want a hug?
They got to choose neither the team...
nor the song, but they won.
Right. Exactly.
They're impressive.
This is the Revenge Battle for a reason.
- Right. - Yes.
Everyone ought to experience hardships.
You're right. That's true.
Hardships make you determined and try harder.
Winners, please wait for...
the Unicorn Ticketing that will happen soon.
All members of the losing team must earn tickets from the fans...
to be able to advance to the Universe.
(They must win an opportunity to advance.)
I thank all of you for your hard work.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Gosh.
We were teamed up because we lost the 1-on-1 Battle.
And this was my first victory.
- It gave me this sense of thrill. - Well done.
- Right. - It felt like I was dreaming.
I remembered all the hard work I did for the past three days.
Seriously. It made me tear up.
I got to take revenge on the other team.
Winning hit the spot.
I also felt proud of myself.
I was happy.
(I was happy.)
Pure Winners. Pure Challengers.
Please come up to the stage.
(Pure Winners versus Pure Challengers)
- Gosh. - Yes.
You guys look beautiful!
How beautiful.
- They look so pure. - How pretty.
How pure.
(Pure Challengers)
- Hello. - Hello.
- How beautiful. - Gosh.
- Goodness. They look so pure. - Oh, my.
They look so pretty.
Gosh. They look so pure.
Let's hear your introductions first.
Winners, you can start.
Gosh. They prepared an introduction.
Hey.
- Yes? - Yes?
In 2, 3.
- Hello. - Hello.
This song is the symbol of purity. We're the Pure Winners.
- We're Team "Into the New World." - We're Team "Into the New World."
I see. "Into the New World."
Gosh. That's a masterpiece.
(It's the debut song of Girls' Generation, )
(the girl group Unicorn Hyoyeon belongs to.)
(A must-practice song for trainees that want to be in girl groups)
(How will they reinterpret the song?)
In 2, 3.
- Hello. We are... - Hello. We are...
Ah-choo
- Pollen is surrounding my heart - Pollen is surrounding my heart
We'll take the victorious pollen. We're Team Pure Challengers.
(It's the most representative song of Lovelyz.)
(The song emphasizes the girlish charms.)
(How will their version of "Ah-Choo" look?)
- I have a question for you, Yunha. - Yes.
During the rehearsal,
you watched your opposing team's performance.
What did you think?
"I think we can beat them."
It was short but had a punch.
She's scary.
Yes, "Into the New World."
(3 days before the Revenge Battle)
Everyone is Korean. Awesome.
(They begin with an advantage as communication won't be an issue.)
I was confident that we wouldn't lose.
Let's hear from everyone...
and go over the parts they all want.
- Let's clear the overlapping ones. - Yes.
- Yes. Let's do that. - Okay.
Please raise your hand if you want the sixth part.
Two of you. Great.
Why don't you sing it? Okay.
(Candidate 1 for Part 6, Lee Huran)
(Candidate 2 for Part 6, Jung Jiwon)
Wait. I don't know the notes for that part.
(She wants the part, but she doesn't know the notes.)
They're lower than that. The notes are lower than you think.
- They're lower. - Your soft
Your soft breath
- That's it. - Yes.
All right.
Please raise your hands if you want Huran to take Part Six.
(Huran gets the majority of the votes.)
The sixth part...
- will go to Huran. - Thank you.
I thought I could express myself the best with the part.
I wanted the part.
Raise your hands if you want Jiwon to take the part.
The first part...
will go to Yunha.
- She'll take the part. - Gosh.
The fourth part...
- will go to Sooin. - What a relief.
Thank you.
- The leader and the main vocalist. - I can't wait to work with you all.
- You look great. - Thank you.
- The main vocalist. - Thank you.
It goes to Gyoryeon.
Thank you. I'll do my best.
- You got this. - Thank you.
I mean, look at her. That's how she'll start.
I tried out all the parts.
I felt that I wasn't good enough, and my style didn't suit the song.
I just took the part that no one took.
- Only we don't have any part. - You don't have any part, right?
- Right. - We have some parts left.
(Heo Sunbin also doesn't have any part yet.)
Which part do you want?
- The ninth part. - Okay. Take that one.
- I'll take the seventh part. - Are you okay?
- Jiwon will take the seventh part. - Yes.
Then Sunbin will take the ninth part.
- Okay. - We're done.
- Let's do this. - It suited Yunha better.
(They begin practicing the choreography right away.)
- This one. - One.
How...
- You don't have to move that much. - Me? Okay.
- Right. That's enough. - Okay.
- Five, six, seven, eight. - She's moving too much to the side.
- Me? - Yes.
- No need to move to the side. - Okay.
If you stand in front of me...
So if I can't see the camera, you'll block everyone here.
(She's unable to be on camera due to Jiwon's wrong movement.)
The three of us in the back won't be on camera then.
- Don't move too much to the side. - Okay.
- Let's try one more time. - Okay.
I didn't think that the score from the 1-on-1 Battle mattered.
(Kwon Chaewon, 2nd, Jeon Jieun, 42nd)
(It was a complete victory with a score of 5 to 0.)
Your lacking skills shouldn't be apparent on the stage.
You can't let people see them.
Do the two of you want to continue going in this line of work?
(The Unicorns gave her the hard truth.)
It's true that I am under constant pressure.
I want to prepare for this battle to the best I can.
I want to show them what I'm good at.
I want them to think that I must have had a reason...
for my previous performance.
(Chaewon wants to perfect the performance more than anyone.)
(Jiwon is slow at memorizing the choreography.)
I'm sorry.
- Oh, no. I couldn't do anything. - I think...
our intro needs a lot of work.
To be honest, I'm not confident.
Why not?
I'm really not confident. Earlier,
I even thought about running away a few times.
Seriously. This is...
so tough on me.
The seventh part. And...
Just thinking about the time we had...
Some of the girls didn't know the choreography.
So time-wise, I didn't think...
we had enough time to prepare for this performance.
I still haven't memorized everything.
- What do I do? - You can do it.
Let's practice with me.
This part...
Has it been 20 minutes?
- Should we start from the top? - Sure.
- Can you count the beats? - Okay.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
One, two.
- Your tempo was too fast. - What was it?
- You missed this part. This one. - This one.
- Then the tempo works out. - Okay. Sorry.
Five, six...
- That's right. - When I do this part,
do I stretch out my palms?
After this, you go like this.
Can you show me one more time?
- Like this. - One more time.
Like this. Then you go like this.
- One more time. I'm really sorry. - It's okay.
(Yunha keeps dancing the same part for Jiwon.)
- Okay. - Yes.
- After this... - After this?
(Pure Winners dance together as a group.)
(When they are practicing the choreography as a team, )
(why is Jiwon standing in the corner alone?)
Practice with me. I need to go over the choreography too.
I can't do it. I feel self-conscious in front of the cameras.
- Why are you so clingy? - Come again?
What time is it?
I really want to go home. Seriously.
"Why am I doing this?"
I've been questioning myself that.
This is really tough on me.
But everyone is working hard. They don't even seem tired.
So I'm doing my best while hiding the fact that I'm tired.
(That night, Jiwon is spending time alone in the dorm.)
(Glancing)
(She keeps looking at the camera as she feels self-conscious.)
(Not long after...)
(Jiwon turns off the camera all of a sudden.)
- Has anyone seen Jiwon? - Yes.
Jiwon hasn't come yet.
(Jiwon hasn't come to the practice room.)
Sunwoo.
Jiwon...
(The staff brings up Jiwon with the leader, Sunwoo.)
Can everyone gather up?
- Okay. - Okay.
Well,
- there's supposed to be nine of us. - Yes.
But Jiwon doesn't feel good.
So she can't join us today for this practice session.
I thought I had to share this news with you.
She can't come right now.
But we'll try to get her to come back.
That's why she's resting now.
- So please be understanding. - Okay.
- Okay. - Okay.
We'll be able to practice with us today, though. Right?
I'm not sure about that.
She shouldn't take this much time off.
She already needs a lot of help.
If she takes this much time off...
and we keep practicing as a group,
it will be harder on her.
I had no choice but to be more realistic.
Then...
let's go over our movements. Think of it as reviewing our spots.
Let's take it from the top and finish it.
- Sure. - Sounds good.
I think...
the left side is getting tighter compared to the right side.
- Can you move to the side? - But...
Jiwon is supposed to be here.
- Move a bit more? Here? - Yes?
- Up to this point? - Thank you.
So this should be the formation. Let's check one more time.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Is this good? - We should stop here.
- Jiwon. - Her spot should be in the front.
Should I move forward a bit more?
Don't I have to stand in between?
I'm not sure.
The other girls were getting exhausted too.
I was concerned that Jiwon's absence might cause...
the other girls to feel anxious or have doubts.
I was concerned more than anything.
Should the people on the sides spread out more?
How should I put it? Well...
The sides?
I'm not sure.
(Will they be able to perform on stage?)
(During dinner that day)
Are you stressed?
It's like...
What's wrong?
Jiwon...
is going through a hard time.
So I'm feeling all sorts of mixed feelings.
- I... - Soyul?
Me?
We can finalize the formations...
- once Jiwon comes back. - Yes.
- And the angles too. - The angles.
That might be why you're not visible on camera.
(As time passes by, they get more anxious.)
Sunwoo.
How close do you think you guys are to finish preparing for the battle?
We're working on it, but I'm not sure how close we are.
We finished up to the first verse. The details and the formations...
I did think that we were in trouble.
I don't know when this distress will explode.
I'm worried about that the most.
- Can we take a five-minute break? - Sure.
- Let's take a break. - My legs are killing me.
(When the members are reaching the limit...)
Just go over the details in your head.
- Jiwon is here. - Gosh, Jiwon.
- Jiwon. - Jiwon.
(Jiwon returns to the practice room.)
Why do you look so exhausted?
- Come here. - She looks so pale.
- Come here. - Come here, Jiwon.
- Our baby. - We missed you.
Let's give her a hug.
- Let's start with a hug. - Give her a hug.
- You just got here. - Our baby.
Why are you crying?
- We missed you. - What?
- We weren't worried, Jiwon. - Right.
- Right. - Of course. We believed in you.
- What's wrong? - You were doing a great job.
- It's okay. - Right. Seriously.
Right. This is just the beginning.
We can do it.
I used to do sports.
(Jiwon was a rhythmic gymnast for 11 years.)
- You got this! - You can do it!
- You can do it! - You can do it!
(She was alone most of the time as a gymnast.)
Please stand in the center.
(In-person Audition, May 21, 2023)
Hi. I'm Jung Jiwon, 18 years old.
As a former rhythmic gymnast, I'm very flexible...
and have a pretty body line.
(Jiwon has a new dream now.)
Everyone is amazing while I'm falling behind.
I feel helpless and feel the pressure.
To be honest, I want...
to stay here and keep trying.
I want to show others my stage, and a good stage, at that.
I want to become a person and a member...
who keeps growing one step at a time.
I lacked in skills, and yet didn't practice.
I hated myself for being in bed.
I just really wanted to go home. I'm sorry.
I'll give it my all.
Thank you for mustering up the courage to come back.
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
Why are you crying?
Stop crying, everyone.
- Let's give it a shot. - Yes.
I'm in.
Shall we do a cheer together?
Okay, let's do it.
Everyone.
We took this chance...
and decided to brace ourselves,
practice together with winning in mind,
and put more effort into the preparation.
I did it!
- I did it! - Really?
It's okay.
(She got it wrong again.)
I couldn't tell that Jiwon was absent.
What is it?
She said she couldn't tell you were absent.
- Yes. - Really?
Yunha has a really nice voice.
- Thank you. - So I think...
- we can add more cute vibes. - Then...
(The teammates help each others' shortcomings.)
- Perfect. - That was perfect.
- How cute. - You were perfect.
- I can't believe it. - Is this wrong?
We are competitors,
but we're currently teammates who have to prepare a stage together.
Simply being able to do a stage together with the others...
is a very valuable experience and a great memory.
I'd like them to know that.
- Okay. - Let's be happy.
- I can see it. - Smile.
- Okay. - Here we go.
Pure Winners.
- We can do it! - We can do it!
We can do it.
It's my first time watching someone else perform this song in person.
- Really? - Yes.
And with nine members, at that.
Is that so?
- They must be nervous. - They all look cute.
We can do it.
I want us to perform an incredible "Into the New World..."
that will shock everyone to the point...
their jaws drop when they watch it.
("Into the New World" by Girls' Generation)
- Isn't it your part, Hyoyeon? - Yes.
- Swirl it! - Swirl!
That was good.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
They were amazing.
Thank you.
You must've practiced as a group...
quite a few times.
- The group... - Yes.
The group was in sync much better than I thought.
This choreography requires you to stretch your arms and legs out,
which means you need a solid foundation...
to dance it out.
So if you're not in sync even just by a bit,
you stand out if you get the move wrong.
But you were much better in sync than I expected.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
If I have to describe "Into the New World..."
in one word, it's energy.
I could really feel that energy...
- from Gyoryeon the most. - Yes?
You understood the choreography really well...
and showed that energy the most.
Thank you.
And Jiwon, you did rhythmic gymnastics back then.
I was very impressed by it.
So I thought this song...
would suit you perfectly...
and had high expectations.
But it felt like you lacked confidence,
maybe because you might not have practiced...
as much as the other members. It was a bummer.
That's all.
Sunwoo.
- Yes? - Firstly,
even if you fail the first ad-lib,
I hope you don't give up on the next one.
When you made that mistake midway,
I could tell you were anxious.
I must scold you for this. It's not right.
Let's say you make a mistake.
If you're before your fans, your fans will think it's cute.
And that's understandable.
But before the general public, it's a big no.
Well, that's it.
Winners. Please leave the stage and stand by.
- Okay. Thank you. - Thank you.
Great job.
- All right. - Guys, don't get hurt.
- Let's do this. - Be happy and enjoy it.
- Trust in how much we practiced. - Let's enjoy it.
(3 days before the Revenge Battle)
(Only silence lingers in the Challengers Team.)
I'm getting nervous.
What now?
(Another silence)
I think everyone has their own anxieties.
Not being able to contribute to my team...
worried me.
I felt much smaller.
I had zero confidence.
(In the last 1-on-1 Battle, )
(Jang Minju was crushed.)
What bummed me out was the fact that my nervousness and mistakes...
ruined...
the stage I had prepared for a month.
Hi. I'm Jang Minju, 23 years old, born in 2001.
Please look forward to my last attempt at becoming an idol.
Are you currently an idol?
I was a member of the girl group MAJORS...
until I signed the dismissal contract last month.
That's why...
- this is your last attempt. - Yes.
(Girl group MAJOR's A-ki)
(After dropping out, Jang Minju)
How does your daily schedule go?
Before I applied for this audition show,
I worked part-time at an academy.
I worked part-time for a long time at a lamb skewer restaurant.
In the evening, I worked part-time.
During the day, I studied writing music and lyrics.
(She plucked up her courage and applied to Universe Ticket.)
How do you want to be remembered?
Someone who doesn't give up.
(Someone who doesn't give up)
I'm making an effort since I don't want to have regrets.
(2nd Kwon Chaewon, 42nd Jeon Jieun)
(They came together for the same dream.)
(But Challengers faced devastation.)
"I need to work harder."
I had that thought.
We can do it. Let's do well.
We only have three days.
Seriously.
We don't have much time. We have two days and a half.
Shall we practice the dance?
- As we sing, "Ah-choo," - Ah-choo
- the right foot will go forward. - Okay.
To the left. "Ah."
- "Ah." - "Ah-choo." Then grab the nose.
- "Choo." - "Choo." Boom.
- Do we show the palm? - Yes.
As we do this, let's have the fingers together.
- Okay. - Okay.
(Most of the members don't know the dance.)
Two, three.
- I feel like I am going - I feel like I am going
Is it one step...
- at "I am going?" - Do we kick?
- It isn't a kick. - Lift it up.
You need to do this to make the move look neater.
I feel like I am going Then you go, "Ah."
- I have a question. - Okay.
Do you stretch out your arms like this? Is it diagonal?
- It's straight. - It's straight.
As for the right foot,
do you lift it up like this? Does it touch the other leg?
It needs to touch the leg like this.
- The right foot. - Yes.
The supporting leg.
- The front foot... - Lift the back foot.
It's better to lift the back foot.
Okay.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
We will do this at "Ah."
Since none of the members know...
the song and the dance exactly,
we are full of worries.
We aren't even done with the first verse yet.
I thought,
"I need to finish the dance by tonight."
I heard about Winners.
They finished the dance without going over the details.
Seriously.
That's how it's supposed to be.
You work on the details later.
You memorize the dance before working on the formation.
Then you work on the formation and fix the details.
At "My lips," you will take a step.
(Challengers still didn't memorize the dance moves individually.)
- Drag it. - Like this.
- Yes. - Thank you.
Do you turn right away?
(They went over the details for every move.)
- Yes, you turn right away. - Okay.
After you do this, does the right foot go forward?
- Yes. - That's right.
Even if we work on the details now,
the girls will get a mental breakdown if the dance moves along too slowly.
We need to go over the entire song tomorrow.
(2 days before the Revenge Battle)
- Can I ask you a question? - Okay.
We have an hour and 15 minutes before dinner.
Shall we work hard...
and go over the entire dance...
- before dinner? - Shall we skip the details?
- Are you okay with that? - I love it.
- I think it will be better. - Let's learn the entire dance.
Seven, eight.
(They change their plans and go over the entire dance.)
(Challengers speed up in learning the dance.)
- You line up like this. - That's right.
Like this.
- We are nearly done. - We are nearly done.
You aren't used to the moves yet,
but that's how the dance goes.
We succeeded in going over the entire thing before dinner.
Shall we go and eat dinner?
- Let's go. - Go.
- Where shall we sit? - Here.
Let's sit together.
- Look. - Look behind you.
The sky is opening up.
- No way. - Oh, my goodness.
(A surprise event for the girls who are tired from the competition)
- It's so nice. - Oh, my goodness.
The weather is so nice.
The sky is so pretty.
- Shall we eat? - Thank you for the food.
- Enjoy the food. - Enjoy the food.
It's tasty.
It's so tasty.
- I can't believe it. - It has been grilled so well.
(They continue practicing even during dinner.)
You need to memorize everything. Make sure you do it.
You can do it, right?
Shall we go?
(Let's go and practice!)
Let's memorize the dance.
Practice is the way to survive.
I can really feel that everyone wants...
to work hard.
Shall we do a cheer?
(1 day before the Revenge Battle)
- Good luck. - Thank you.
- Good luck. - Okay.
How cute.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
I personally think the chorus is the most important part.
Perhaps it was because you couldn't hear the song,
- but you sped up a lot. - Okay.
You sped up together.
It will be nice if you can relax...
- and slow down during that part. - Okay.
- Okay. - Thank you.
The two of you need to practice more.
I can tell that you aren't done with the dance.
Except for that,
the performance was pretty okay.
Okay.
You need to practice more.
I was so anxious.
My thoughts became scrambled the more I thought.
(Jang Minju continues to make a mistake.)
- I am sorry. - It's okay.
What was the next move?
(She becomes shaken up after the interim check.)
I don't have enough time to practice,
so I am anxious.
I need to have confidence,
but so many aspects that make me lose confidence...
- are starting to come to me. - A bit more.
I might end up going home.
(Anxiety spread in everyone's heart.)
- Are you exhausted? - Oh, no.
You are exhausted.
Because I can't do well...
Why do you think that?
- Thank you. - Memories...
of making a mistake during the 1-on-1 Battle came back.
I made a mistake, messed up the performance,
and lost with a score of 5 to 0.
I felt so pressured.
I...
might do the same thing again.
I might make a mistake and feel bad for the members.
When we take the stage, we only get one mistake.
Usually, I mess up once every ten times.
If I mess up on the stage,
everyone will think I am just like that.
That experience will...
- You are scared. - So I am scared.
I am scared that I might make a mistake.
You are crying since you worked hard.
- That's right. - I know that it's upsetting.
(Their anxiety begins to grow. Will they be able to perform well?)
("Ah-Choo" by Lovelyz)
How pretty.
My goodness.
They look so pretty.
How cute.
My goodness.
I think she forgot the lyrics.
Hyemi is really good.
I don't know what to tell them.
I don't have anything.
Me neither.
Minju,
were you very nervous today?
I am sorry.
I lost my focus for a moment.
Your performance worried me.
It's okay.
I just...
I am sorry. My head went blank.
Teammates, I am so sorry.
It's okay.
Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
She had a mental breakdown when she got the lyrics wrong.
- Yes. After messing up the lyrics, - She had a mental breakdown.
She made a mistake with the formation too.
We didn't have much time to prepare for the performance,
so the weight on my heart was heavier than the last time.
When I made a mistake,
all other members had a mental breakdown...
and messed up the performance.
It's too bad.
(Announcing the result for the pure concept)
We will announce the result of the battle.
The winner of the pure concept is..
(To be continued)
(Which team won the pure concept?)
Pure Winners.
Congratulations.
Did we win?
(Pure Winners won.)
Why are you crying? Don't cry.
With a score of 4 to 1, Pure Winners won.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Don't cry. - Come here.
- Good job. - Come here.
My goodness.
- Thank you. - Well done.
Thank you.
We won thanks to you.
Thank you so much.
- Seriously. - Come together.
Hurry up and come together.
- Come on. - Everyone worked hard.
That's right.
We know that you wanted to do well more than anyone here.
- I am sorry. - Don't be sorry.
- I won't say sorry. - Seriously.
- Thank you. Seriously. - Thank you.
I am seriously grateful.
I don't have any regrets about myself,
but I feel so bad for the girls.
(I feel so bad for the girls.)
You know,
Minju will remember that...
- for her entire lifetime. - Losing?
"My team lost because of me."
"I made a mistake. What should I do?"
- No, she needs to overcome it. - Yes.
She needs to overcome it.
(It's the growing pain she must overcome for her dream.)
Sparkling Winners and Challengers,
please come up to the stage.
(Sparkling Winners)
(Sparkling Challengers)
- Hello. - Hello.
- How cute. - They are so sparkly.
It's red and blue.
They look refreshing in those outfits.
So sparkling.
One, two, three.
We will color the stage red.
- We are Sparkling Winners. - We are Sparkling Winners.
So sparkling.
Two, three.
- Hello. - Hello.
We will create waves in your heart. We are...
- Team Sparkling Dolphin. - Team Sparkling Dolphin.
(We are Team Sparkling Dolphin!)
- How nice. - They are sparkling.
- They look like a new group. - Yes.
Now, Winners need to defend,
and Challengers need to attack in this battle.
While Winners work hard and do well,
we are better.
So we think we will win.
- "Dolphin." - "Dolphin."
(The day the sparkling songs got revealed)
(Challengers chose "Dolphin" by OH MY GIRL.)
That's incredible.
What's your song?
What's your guess?
We don't know.
- Guess. - Guess.
Are you very curious?
- We are very curious. - Yes.
Check it out on the stage.
(Unbelievable)
My goodness.
It hurt my pride.
It made me boil up.
They must have chosen the style they are good at,
so they have an advantage.
There were "Dolphin" and "Red Flavor."
Of course, I chose "Red Flavor."
"Red Flavor" is a song...
that has a kick toward the end.
I thought "Red Flavor" has more impact.
A performance of "Red Flavor."
I think I can pull it off really well...
because it's a very refreshing song.
What should we do?
(Silence falls among Sparkling Challengers)
"Dolphin" is a calm song...
that doesn't have many ups and downs.
Winners' song must be full of energy.
I was worried about bringing out that energy.
During the 1-on-1 Battle, I made an unexpected mistake.
(During the 1-on-1 Battle)
Eunchae, it has been a while.
Hello.
She starred in my music video...
of "Stardust."
(Eunchae starred in Younha's music video 2 years ago)
(She sang "Comet" by Younha.)
(But she missed the beat due to nervousness.)
(She lost with a score of 4 to 1.)
Thank you.
Eunchae,
I think I pulled you down.
Had you picked another song, you would have done much better.
I couldn't even show half of what I prepared.
I was very sad.
Younha said,
"You..."
(You can't be a singer.)
It seems like...
you will need to steel your heart.
You will need to practice singing a lot.
It's not about the basic skills.
You made me wonder, "Will this be possible?"
I think you should think about...
if you must become a singer.
I lacked the skills and didn't practice hard enough.
I am worried about doing well in the future.
I was worried...
if I could raise the energy levels.
That was my concern.
Let's give this a try.
My dancing and singing is a bit lacking,
but I still thought about what I could do for the team.
(Winking)
That was cute.
Look at her.
Let's go!
That's so cute.
(With high energy levels, their practice goes smoothly.)
I was worried at first.
We all want to...
win through this Revenge Battle.
That's why we're all practicing with a great passion.
That's it!
Okay.
- Good work. - Good work.
- Bye. - Bye.
During the live performance, you have to dance even harder.
- Okay. - Okay.
During the 1-on-1 Battle, I was criticized greatly.
I thought I needed to work much harder than everyone else.
That's why I worked even harder during practice.
My loss hurt my pride.
That made me work harder.
I believe we could be at a disadvantage,
but our team is filled with people who want to prove themselves.
I think we still have a chance to win.
My head is filled with spite.
She has this easy-going charm.
(What are you doing, Sieun?)
Sieun gets a bit weird...
when it gets past midnight.
She becomes more energetic as time goes by.
At first, she's like this.
(During the day, she's quiet.)
Then, all of a sudden...
(Her energy levels shoot up at night.)
(Raise the energy levels!)
(1 day before the Revenge Battle, interim check with ITZY)
May we see the performance?
- Yes. - Yes.
That was great.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- What? - What?
They're great.
Are you really the Challengers?
- Aren't you the Winners? - I thought you were the Winners.
I thought you were the Winners.
Seriously.
Everything was spot on.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
It was spot on. You must've practiced really hard.
This song caught me by surprise.
I thought this song would be...
less sparkling than "Red Flavor."
It was this part.
(The perfect choreography boosted the sparkling levels.)
The team balance seems really good as well.
You all worked as a team.
That really impressed me, and you girls did really well.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
I'm serious.
They practiced really hard.
This is how practice should be done.
It was the Revenge Battle,
but it was done as a team.
I felt proud when she said we worked as a team.
We worked really hard and practiced a lot.
I think we can win.
I'm determined this time.
I will work 100 times harder than before.
I want to show Unicorn Younha...
a completely different performance from the 1-on-1 Battle.
- Hey! - Hey!
Let's do this!
With a perfect performance with my teammates,
I want to complete my revenge.
(What kind of performance will the Sparkling Challengers show?)
With a perfect performance with my teammates,
I want to complete my revenge.
I will get my revenge against Yeojin.
("Dolphin" by OH MY GIRL)
Seriously...
That's so cute.
(That's so cute.)
They're so good.
They're really good.
They're great.
How are they this good?
- This team was great. - Right.
They don't seem like the Challengers.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
I can't get my eyes off of her.
Who is she?
- The one with the bob. - Right.
She drives me crazy.
- She has her own charm. - She dances around like a robot.
But it's so charming.
I enjoyed the performance by Sparkling Challengers.
It made me think that they weren't the Challengers.
- Right. - Yes. They were great.
I loved Sieun's expressions.
- Thank you. - It was so bubbly.
You were just like a dolphin.
Why is she so pretty?
Minari.
I heard the gun move was for me.
(I got caught.)
You'll need to work on that gun.
It wasn't strong enough to go through me.
Well...
Wasn't Eunchae really good?
Why did you sing "Comet?"
This is your specialty.
- Exactly. - I was really surprised.
The singing was really stable.
- Right. - Even the dancing.
She really took her spot when she was in the center.
She was shining.
- Thank you. - You did really well.
Eunchae just did really well.
She was on another level.
I'm really excited for what is to come.
Eunchae hasn't shown us everything she has.
She still has a lot more to show.
Don't cry!
- Don't cry! - Great work!
- Thank you. - You should've cried...
while singing "Comet." Why cry now?
They already lost to us once.
I think we'll take the win.
They're great.
Gosh.
That was amazing.
They're a strong team.
It's a close match. They're so good.
Can our team win?
(Revenge or consecutive win)
(Which team will win this fierce battle?)
You did really well.
(What a shame. They both did so well.)
(I wanted to shine even more on that team.)
(I first got determined...)
(to advance to the Universe.)
Oh, no.
(To be honest, we weren't like a team.)
(If we were to carry on like this...)
(Can we beat the Challengers?)
(Sujin, can I talk with you?)
(I know you're really up for this.)
(It could look a bit selfish.)
(Can you match my position?)
(With the eagerness to win, )
(the leaders feel that much more pressure.)
(What will the girls' tenacity result in?)
(The Challengers' will shocks everyone.)
(The Winners must protect their title.)
I got goosebumps.
(I get why this is the last battle.)
(Who will become the winner of the last Revenge Battle?)
(Finally)
(The survivors of Battle Week)
(20 direct advancements and 21 top ticketing rankers)
(The 41 girls of the Universe will be revealed.)
The dream ticketing for the debut.
Vote for your favorite girl.
Participate now on the Universe Ticket homepage...
and Fancast app for the global vote, Fan Ticketing.
Make sure to reserve a ticket for the girls' dreams.
(Universe Ticket)