(This program is the fifth story...)
(of girls of different worlds with one dream.)
(of girls of different worlds with the dream of debuting.)
(Universe Ticket)
It's a new beginning.
It's another competition,
so I think I feel even more nervous.
(A total of 39 girls entered the Universe.)
The new stage for the debut in the Universe.
Road to PRISM.
When I first saw "Road to PRISM,"
I felt overwhelmed.
(Universe Ranks)
There are five ranks in the Universe.
You all are currently in Rank M.
Everyone starts at the same rank.
Only the eight contestants who make it to Rank PRISM...
will earn the PRISM Tickets and make the debut.
I really want to reach the top.
I really want to earn the PRISM Ticket.
(Road to PRISM, the first journey)
The start of the promotion battle.
Level Station will begin.
(The first step to promotion, Level Station)
This really is a battle of survival.
I will make sure to be promoted.
I will never lose.
- Awesome! - That's amazing.
No way! That was so amazing.
(Surprising performances of the girls full of spite)
I really didn't want to get eliminated.
(And...)
Through Level Station today,
there will be nine eliminations from the losing team.
(A total of 9 eliminations)
If your team were to lose,
who do you think will get eliminated?
Gabi.
Gabi or...
I think Gabi will be in a tough spot.
Someone I'm wary of?
I don't think there's anyone.
(Episode 5: Competition)
The start of the debut survival to become Rank PRISM.
Road to PRISM begins.
Road to PRISM.
The first Station to reach PRISM will be revealed.
- I'm so nervous. - Hold on.
- I'm so nervous. - I feel so nervous.
- Gosh. - Oh, no.
It's a new beginning.
My heart was pounding. I felt really nervous.
(What is the first Station?)
Look at that.
What? Level...
- Level Station? - Level Station?
The first Station is Level Station.
Is it a level test?
Your starting rank is M.
However, you may be in different levels in the same Rank.
There are different levels in the same Rank?
Through Level Station, with your own individual skills,
you will be placed in Levels high, average, and low...
and perform on stage.
According to high, average, and low Levels,
there will be different numbers of promotion and elimination.
- What? - What?
For high, there will be 4 promotions and 2 eliminations.
For average, there will be 3 promotions and 3 eliminations.
(Average: 3 promotions and 3 eliminations)
For low, there will be 2 promotions and 4 eliminations.
- What? - You have to go home then?
This is harsh.
I got goosebumps.
Being in low will be tough.
Reaching high is a must.
What are your Levels?
The method of deciding your levels will now be revealed.
Oh, no!
I feel nervous.
(The Unicorns make a surprise appearance for the level test.)
Oh, gosh!
- Hello! - Hello!
The first Station of the Universe.
Before we begin Level Station,
we have gathered to help decide your levels.
- Right now? - Now?
Your levels...
will be decided by the evaluation...
of the second signal song, "Ticket to You."
(The second signal song after "Want to Come With Me?")
("Ticket to You" is a song filled with the hopes...)
(of the girls wanting to earn the tickets to their debut.)
(The girls of the Universe have seen the choreography video.)
(Unicorn Rian of LACHICA worked on the choreography.)
The Level Test will begin...
in 30 minutes.
In 30 minutes?
Please get changed and return to this place.
Okay.
Wait. Thirty minutes?
I can't go back.
I must aim for the top.
I want to stay up high...
and get promoted.
I'm confident in avoiding elimination.
(The girls have returned after getting changed.)
What do I do? I'm so nervous right now.
I feel so nervous.
- I'm so nervous. - I feel more nervous...
- than the first round. - Really?
All right.
The Level Test will begin.
("Ticket to You" Level Test)
(After singing and dancing in groups of 2,)
(the Unicorns will decide between high, average, and low.)
- Gosh. I'm so nervous. - Seriously.
The choreographer of "Ticket to You," Unicorn Rian...
will tell you the standards of evaluation.
- It's an honor. - It really is an honor.
- LACHICA. - When will we get the chance to...
- work with LACHICA? - Exactly.
The creator of the choreography is watching.
What do I do? I feel even more nervous now.
In "Ticket to You," there are many parts...
that display bright energy.
I will be looking into those parts in detail.
As it has a bright energy, expressions will be key.
Rather than just looking pretty,
I hope it will be a performance that shows more than that.
- Okay! - Okay!
Seeing the current system, I believe those in the lower tier...
have a great chance of being eliminated.
You need to show your best...
and put on a perfect performance...
to get good results. You all know this, right?
- Yes! - Yes!
Losing here means elimination.
I just wanted to avoid the lowest Level.
If I grit my teeth and do my best,
I feel confident that I'll survive until the end.
I have that sort of confidence.
We'll start with the first round.
(Who will be the first to start the Level Test?)
I'm shaking.
Gosh, my heart.
Nana...
and Jang Sua, please come up.
(Nana and Jang Sua)
You can do it!
- Let's go. - Good luck!
If I go against Nana,
she'll be really talented.
There will be a big comparison.
I felt intimidated because of that.
(How will Nana and Sua's Level Test go?)
- Okay. - I'm excited for these two.
I'm really excited.
Thank you in advance.
(Impressed)
My ticket to you
(Sua starts offbeat.)
- Every day, every time - Every day, every time
- I've waited a long time - I've waited a long time
(Sua is a bit ahead in terms of the beat.)
(Struggling)
(There's a big difference in the beat.)
(Sua's mistakes continue.)
(Nana carries on without getting hindered.)
(Impressed)
- You're my ticket to you - You're my ticket to you
- You, you, you - You, you, you
- My fluttering heart - My fluttering heart
She's good.
The line is amazing.
(Nana gets everyone's attention.)
- You're my ticket to you - You're my ticket to you
Okay.
Thank you.
- Nana is really good. - Right.
Great job!
Even during the 1-on-1 Battle,
I remember admiring her lines.
Even today, her long arms and legs stood out.
- Right. - Her lines were distinct.
Sua, are you feeling really nervous?
Yes.
You need to work on the rhythm.
A lot.
Okay.
I expected to go down to a low ranking.
I thought I was in big trouble.
We'll meet the next contestants.
Lee Eunchae and Kotoko.
(Surprised)
I worked with Eunchae for "Dolphin."
(Lee Eunchae and Kotoko worked together in the Revenge Battle.)
(Talented youngest contestant, Lee Eunchae)
(Kotoko with cute charms)
- Thank you in advance. - How cute.
- The cute ones. - They're so cute.
It's a tight match.
- They're both so cute. - Right.
(How will their Level Test go?)
(Interested)
- My ticket to you - My ticket to you
- How cute. - They're so cute.
(Impressed)
(Hitting her hair)
- Every day, every time - Every day, every time
- I've waited a long time - I've waited a long time
- Now it's time - Now it's time
(They're stable with no mistakes.)
(Impressed)
- You're my ticket to you - You're my ticket to you
- You, you, you - You, you, you
- My fluttering heart - My fluttering heart
- You're my ticket to you - You're my ticket to you
- You, you, you - You, you, you
- Days that are like a miracle - Days that are like a miracle
- You're my ticket to you - You're my ticket to you
(Ti...)
(Oh, no!)
How cute! That was so cute!
(Kotoko's cute mistake makes everyone laugh.)
- She's so cute. - It's an act, right?
Gosh.
My goodness.
- She's so cute. - She's cute pulling her hair too.
- Well done. - Well done.
- Haven't they really improved? - Yes.
- They really have improved. - Right.
Especially with Kotoko.
In terms of singing and dancing, she really improved.
Right. She really has improved.
(Smacking)
Who are you?
- Who is she? - Who are you?
Goodness.
Why are you crying?
I didn't expect to hear compliments.
- Oh, really? - You did really well.
You have really improved.
You have to work even harder.
Okay.
I can do it.
- You can do it! - Yes!
- Eunchae did well too. - Eunchae did really well.
- She did well. - Right.
Shall I say you've learned your own groove?
Her expressions were really cute when she was dancing.
She had a stable balance.
That's right.
- She did well. - Well done.
Thank you.
They really improved.
- Right. - It really surprised me.
We're all moved by them.
Next up, Bang Yunha.
Elisia.
(Bang Yunha and Elisia are up next.)
The best live performer.
- They're both really talented. - Right.
They're both bright like the sun.
- You're right. - Right.
Okay.
(Winking)
(These two contestants catch the eye from the start.)
(Amazed)
- T, I, C, K, E, T - T, I, C, K, E, T
- Because I'm ready - Because I'm ready
(They pull off the high notes well as well.)
- You, you, you - You, you, you
- My fluttering heart - My fluttering heart
(Proud)
(Their live singing is spot on even with the dancing.)
- Days that are like a miracle - Days that are like a miracle
- You're my ticket to you - You're my ticket to you
Okay!
They're outstanding.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
You both are so good.
- Great job. - No. You did a great job.
- Look at those charms. - What?
Elisia is so cute.
Thank you.
Did you practice the expressions as well?
Yes.
I did acting when I was younger.
I focus on my facial expressions a lot too.
She's got feminine gestures too.
- I know, right? - Yes.
- It's perfect for the song. - It was very good.
Thank you.
- Yunha. - Yes.
Despite your young age, you have...
- a groovy voice. For a part like... - I see.
My fluttering heart
You sang it with a groove.
I think you're the first one who sang the part like that...
- among the contestants we've seen. - Thank you.
These two are...
- all-round artists, I think. - Right.
Thank you.
Next up are...
Kim Sumin...
and Aya Natsumi.
Aya.
Good luck.
- Good luck. - You got this.
I was very impressed by her "DDU-DU DDU-DU" performance.
Sumin's got many different charms.
She sings very well...
and also dances well.
She looks perfect.
So I thought she'd rank high.
(During the rehearsal of Revenge Battle)
(A good vocalist)
(A good dancer)
(Sumin pulled off everything perfectly.)
- Are you ready? - Yes.
Yes.
- Every day, every time - Every day, every time
- I've waited a long time - I've waited a long time
No more waiting
- Now it's time - Now it's time
- To the end of the universe - To the end of the universe
(The rhythm is getting faster and faster.)
- We shine brighter than anyone - We shine brighter than anyone
(They keep singing offbeat.)
Our starlight shining the whole world
- A step closer - A step closer
- A heart-fluttering miracle - A heart-fluttering miracle
(They aren't singing in sync.)
- Let's go to the new world - Let's go to the new world
- We can set off anytime - We can set off anytime
- T, I, C, K, E, T - T, I, C, K, E, T
- Because I'm ready - Because I'm ready
(Studying their faces)
- You're my ticket to you - You're my ticket to you
(Their voices become out of tune now.)
- My fluttering heart - My fluttering heart
- You're my ticket to you - You're my ticket to you
Okay.
The contestant who performed with me went sharp a little.
There were unexpected things...
that I had to take care of.
So I was the most disappointed.
Both of you danced...
- faster and faster. - Okay.
So I think...
you will need to work on that.
- Okay. - Yes.
In the latter part of the song, you went sharp.
But it was slightly higher in pitch.
It was a little uncomfortable to listen to.
I think you failed to control your breath.
And I'd like you to watch the others' performances carefully.
See how they are different from you.
I think, as Younha said,
Natsumi probably practiced alone looking in the mirror.
It's true that Unicorns...
have become stricter since the 1-on-1 Battle.
This is the real beginning.
They fell a little short of my expectations.
Next up are Kwon Eunhyung...
and Idota Yui. Please come on up.
- Good luck. - Good luck.
- You got this. - Good luck.
- Now it's time - Now it's time
- To the end of the universe - To the end of the universe
(They suddenly start singing flat.)
- A step closer - A step closer
(Kwon Eunhyung missed her part out of breath.)
- Let's go to the new world - Let's go to the new world
Yes!
(Idota Yui sings in a loud voice.)
(Kwon Eunhyung stops singing again.)
- You're my ticket to you - You're my ticket to you
- You, you, you - You, you, you
- My fluttering heart - My fluttering heart
- You're my ticket to you - You're my ticket to you
(It looks as if she's lip-synching now.)
(Yui is so into her song.)
- She's adorable. - How lovely.
So adorable.
She's so lovely.
She's so energetic.
- I like her energy. - Right.
But Yui was...
too excited.
- Right. - Yes.
Your moves were a little too much.
Things will be a lot better if you work on that.
- Okay. - That's what I thought.
- Okay. Thank you. - Thank you.
I could tell Eunhyung...
tried to lip-sync when she was feeling nervous...
or when she had to sing the parts she wasn't good at.
But...
it's not like you're performing on a TV music show now.
We wanted to see how you'd practiced.
Everyone here is shy.
But they all just try their best to sing even if it wasn't perfect.
The lip-sync...
wasn't a good choice.
- Okay. - Okay.
Eunhyung, when you sing,
you press every note like playing the keyboard.
But you need to practice...
connecting the notes like a wind instrument.
In falsetto...
(Younha gives a demonstration to give her advice.)
You should practice lowering the keys like this.
Then you won't be afraid to sing high notes.
- Okay. - You need to practice a lot.
- All right. - Thank you.
My singing ability isn't good enough.
So I thought I'd rank low.
I feel like I'm in an uncertain position.
Next.
Gabi and Lim Seowon. Please come on up.
What? Is it Gabi?
I was a little nervous.
(Gabi and Lim Seowon teamed up for the Revenge Battle.)
(They practiced together as a team.)
(They showed the textbook cuteness with their lovely chemistry.)
My gosh.
They met again as rivals.
It's a big match.
They both are high ranks.
I have to move up to a higher rank no matter what.
I was confident in singing.
They approved of me.
So I thought I had a good chance.
She's a good friend, and she's really good.
But I'm confident.
I will win and become a higher rank.
- Gosh. - What?
- Look how talented she is. - Gosh.
My ticket to you
They're good.
- T, I, C, K, E, T - T, I, C, K, E, T
- Because I'm ready - Because I'm ready
(Seowon's voice is ear-catching.)
- You're my ticket to you - You're my ticket to you
- You, you, you - You, you, you
Okay.
- My fluttering heart - My fluttering heart
- You're my ticket to you - You're my ticket to you
- You, you, you - You, you, you
- My fluttering heart - My fluttering heart
- You're my ticket to you - You're my ticket to you
- Okay. - All right.
Thank you.
- I like the energy. - I really like it.
- They are sparkling. - They really are.
I'm so excited now.
You, you, you I was excited when they sang.
You look excited.
You did really well.
- Thank you. - I have nothing to say.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- That was neat. - They both did well.
They're so good. What do I do?
- I think Seowon is perfect. - I see.
She's really good.
- Gabi fell a little short, right? - Yes.
- We can't help but compare them. - Right.
It's obvious.
Those who are good get even better over time.
Exactly.
(The Level Test continues.)
That's it.
- You, you, you - You, you, you
(Kim Soobin and Lee Huran showed a stable live performance.)
- Days that are like a miracle - Days that are like a miracle
- You're my ticket to you - You're my ticket to you
(Kim Sujin showed a different move alone.)
Thank you.
The ending.
- Like this. - The ending.
Did you intend it? Or was it a mistake?
I intended it.
You intended it?
Impressive.
- Thank you. - Okay.
Next.
Jayla...
and Gehlee Dangca.
It's a battle of queens.
- Unbelievable. - A battle of queens.
Are they doing it together again?
I think they were together during the 1-on-1 Battle.
(They first met at the 1-on-1 Battle.)
(Then they met again at the Revenge Battle.)
I have a good feeling about this team.
Hello.
(Gehlee Dangca says hello politely like a queen.)
She's adorable.
Good luck.
(Their graceful gestures and waves stand out.)
They are two princesses.
- Every day, every time - Every day, every time
- I've waited a long time - I've waited a long time
No more waiting
- Now it's time - Now it's time
(Groovy)
- To the end of the universe - To the end of the universe
- T, I, C, K, E, T - T, I, C, K, E, T
- Because I'm ready - Because I'm ready
- You're my ticket to you - You're my ticket to you
- You, you, you - You, you, you
- My fluttering heart - My fluttering heart
- You're my ticket to you - You're my ticket to you
- You, you, you - You, you, you
- Days that are like a miracle - Days that are like a miracle
- You're my ticket to you - You're my ticket to you
All right.
This is strange.
- They are giving us a hard time. - Right.
They all improved a lot.
- Yes. - Yes.
And...
did you see that Gehlee Dangca closed her eyes while doing this?
Yes.
(Closing her eyes)
I think she dances in a charming way.
It was nice to watch.
But you need to work on your dance moves a little.
Okay.
And Jayla, I remember that you showed...
more powerful moves.
I was disappointed I didn't see it today.
Your moves were precise though.
- Okay. - Thank you.
Next.
(The last Level Test)
Kwon Chaewon and Narumi, please come on up.
(Kwon Chaewon and Narumi, the last contestants)
- Good luck. - Good luck.
Good luck.
What I have shown here wasn't good enough.
So I really wanted to rank high.
I hope they will do well.
- Good luck. - Good luck.
(How will their Level Test go?)
- I've waited a long time - I've waited a long time
- Now it's time - Now it's time
- To the end of the universe - To the end of the universe
- I'll go with you - I'll go with you
- T, I, C, K, E, T - T, I, C, K, E, T
- Because I'm ready - Because I'm ready
- You're my ticket to you - You're my ticket to you
- You, you, you - You, you, you
- My fluttering heart - My fluttering heart
- You're my ticket to you - You're my ticket to you
- You, you, you - You, you, you
- Days that are like a miracle - Days that are like a miracle
- You're my ticket to you - You're my ticket to you
Well done.
- Narumi. - Yes.
I don't think you made good use of your body which is your strength,
- so it was a little disappointing. - Okay.
You need to use your fingertips and the tips of your toes well...
to balance your performance.
- Okay. - That's what you need to practice.
- Okay. - All right.
- Chaewon. - Yes.
To be honest, as a member of a girl group like you,
Yes.
I wanted to support you.
- I see. - And...
I think I can finally support you after watching this performance.
- Thank you. - I'm serious.
- Well done. - Oh, no.
Don't cry.
I was very excited watching your performance.
I liked your energy.
- Right. - I liked your facial expressions.
Have you improved?
Or did you finally manage to show your real ability?
I really liked it. You were great.
Thank you.
You got this.
I feel relieved now.
- Today... - I had a heavy heart.
I know.
I was afraid I'd have to say something bad.
I'm so relieved.
- You're the best. - You did well.
- You were amazing. - You're the best.
I finally won praise.
It meant a lot to me.
That's what I really wanted to hear.
(The Level Test is over.)
Let's go through them one by one.
First...
Let's say high, average, and low.
- Okay. - Jang Sua.
- Low. - Low.
Seriously,
- what do we do with her? - She lacks confidence.
Right.
And...
- Lim Seowon is... - High.
Right, high.
- High. - She's really good.
She must be tired too.
Next is Gehlee Dangca.
- I think she's low. - I agree.
- Low? - Yes.
She's very charming.
But her dance...
What if Gehlee Dangca gets eliminated because of this?
Won't you be disappointed?
I'll be a little disappointed.
(They are torn between her charm and ability.)
But when it comes to her ability,
I think she deserves low.
- Her ability? - Ability-wise.
That's true.
But her looks deserve high.
And she sings pretty well.
- This is too difficult. - Right.
So they are divided.
Are we done?
- Yes. - We're done.
(The results of the Level Test will be revealed soon.)
(High)
(Kim Soobin, Kim Sujin, Nizi, Bang Yunha, Bae Yeram)
(Elisia, Oh Daeun, Yuri, Lee Soovin, Lee Eunchae)
(Lee Huran, Lim Seowon, Jin Hyeonju, Hwang Sieun)
(Average)
(Gabi, Goo Gyoryeon, Kwon Chaewon, Kim Sumin, Nana)
(Nako, Bae Haram, Oh Yoona, Lee Sunwoo)
(Jeon Jinyeong, Jayla, Choi Hyerin, Kotoko)
(Low)
(Kwon Eunhyung, Narumi, Riel, Minari, Vanesya)
(Park Yewon, Aya Natsumi, Yona, Idota Yui)
(Jang Sua, Gehlee Dangca, Heo Sunbin)
(Average)
(Gabi, Goo Gyoryeon, Kwon Chaewon, Kim Sumin, Nana)
(Nako, Bae Haram, Oh Yoona, Lee Sunwoo)
(Jeon Jinyeong, Jayla, Choi Hyerin, Kotoko)
(High)
(Kim Soobin, Kim Sujin, Nizi, Bang Yunha, Bae Yeram)
(Elisia, Oh Daeun, Yuri, Lee Soovin, Lee Eunchae)
(Lee Huran, Lim Seowon, Jin Hyeonju, Hwang Sieun)
(The full version performances of each class...)
(and the surprising announcement of their levels...)
(will be revealed online.)
No, Gabi.
Don't worry about what already happened.
You should do well...
from now on.
Who do you think will be eliminated?
Gabi.
I think Gabi might get eliminated.
(I think Gabi might get eliminated.)
This is another new beginning.
I thought, "It's finally beginning."
I was very nervous.
(Universe Ticket)
(Level Station, D-day)
(Waiting room)
I think the contestants are more determined now.
Some of us will be eliminated.
So I have to try my best and give it my all.
I believe in myself,
so I don't think I'll lose.
The new gateway to the debut on Universe Ticket.
Road to PRISM.
The girls who have advanced to the Universe...
will get their first promotion opportunity...
to the PRISM Level...
in the Level Station today.
I'm nervous.
This is the first promotion.
Level Station will be...
divided into high, average, and low.
The same levels will compete against each other.
Who will win and lose...
will be chosen by the Unicorns.
I'm in your care.
Through the Unicorn Ticketing,
nine will get promoted from the winning team,
and nine will get eliminated from the losing team.
(Out of 39 participants, 9 will get eliminated.)
The fact that some will get eliminated makes me sad.
(Who will get promoted, and who will get eliminated?)
The official war of promotions,
the Level Station,
will start now.
- This day has come. - I know, right?
The two average teams, please come onto the stage.
(1st Level Station: Average Level Battle)
- Hi. - Hi.
How adorable.
Gosh, seriously.
They must be really nervous.
Good luck, guys!
Good luck!
Let's go!
(The 2nd average team appears.)
What's with their chicness?
The outfits are amazing.
For real?
It's almost like "Genie."
(Their outfit concept is eye-catching.)
This team is tall, while the other team is cute.
Right?
They have completely different concepts.
Yes.
Each participant is in the concept that they fit in.
They look different, like black and pink.
(14 days before in the afternoon after the Level Test)
- We're in your care. - Likewise.
I hope they recognize us. They will, right?
You're the MC today.
Why make me do this?
- Hi. - Hi.
(The average teams walk in.)
(Amazed)
Hi, everyone.
- Hi. - Hi.
I'm ADORA, a producer before you today.
(Producer ADORA has come for the Level Station.)
Hi. I'm Nano of VENDORS.
Nice to meet you.
- Hi. - Hi.
(They produced songs for major K-pop artists,)
(such as "Spring Day" and "Not Today" for BTS,)
("Round and Round" for NCT U, and more.)
(An all-rounder producing team specializing in K-pop, VENDORS)
Nice to meet you.
Hi. We're team PAPERMAKER.
I'm TENZO.
Hi. I'm EB.
I'm Samuel Ku. Nice to meet you.
("LILAC" by IU)
(They produced songs of all genres...)
(like GFRIEND's "Me gustas tu" and "Glass Bead.")
(A producing team making big hit K-pop songs, PAPERMAKER)
Meeting the people I had only seen on TV...
in person was really cool.
- They're our competitor. - Hi.
- As for me, - Yes?
I have watched your performances as a Unicorn...
and remember what each of you did.
Can you pull it off?
- Yes. - Yes.
The average participants who will be in our PAPERMAKER team are,
- firstly, Nana, - Here.
- Jayla, - Here.
- Gabi, - Here.
- Goo Gyoryeon, - Here.
- Lee Sunwoo, - Here.
- Bae Haram, - Okay.
and lastly, Jeon Jinyeong.
I can already paint a picture of our team.
They look good together.
Yes. I have a great feeling.
Visually-wise, they look good as a team.
VENDORS should be worried about this mix.
You mean us?
I have a good feeling about them.
Can't you tell just by looking at our team?
- That they will win. - They will win.
I wanted to be a team with Sumin.
But now that we're rivals,
I'm really anxious.
"I should give more of what I have."
That was what I thought.
She was my competition.
Jinyeong and I were a team during the Revenge Battle.
She had great leadership...
and killed the stage back then.
So I held her in check a tiny bit.
Let's do our best.
- We can do it! - We can do it!
(Full of tension from the start)
The song we, VENDORS, arranged is...
I wonder how they arranged it.
"Superstar" by Jewelry.
- I know the song. - You do?
(It's a fast-tempo song with a rock-style flashy performance.)
"Superstar" is a dance song that made...
the whole nation do the shaking dance.
- I know the song. - You do?
- I do. - Really?
You are a superstar
We reinterpreted the song with VENDORS' band sound...
and brought out a charm different from the original.
Shall we listen to it?
- Yes. - Yes.
(A preview of "Superstar" by Jewelry)
(VENDORS' band version of "Superstar")
Oh, my gosh.
(Shocked)
The song suits that team.
I like it.
It's really nice.
- It's good. - Listen to the vocal.
That's it.
I want to hear our song.
Me too.
She did the guide of the song.
That's right. As I sang the guide of the song,
I was nervous to play this song.
What do you think? Can you do it?
- Yes. - Yes.
- I love it. - Great.
I also think you'll pull it off really well...
in your own style, so I'm feeling confident.
- Let's do this! - Let's do this!
The song we, PAPERMAKER, arranged is...
"Girls On Top" by BoA.
It's a song highlighting...
its powerful performance and neutral charm.
Befitting to it,
please execute a cool performance.
Let's listen to "Girls On Top."
(PAPERMAKER's version of "Girls On Top")
It's already over.
Don't you think Nana will look cool?
Yes, she'll look really cool.
It's your song, Nana.
- It's so good. - She did the guide.
She sang the guide.
(Producer EB sang the guide!)
(Is it an unexpected guide showdown?)
When I heard "Girls On Top,"
I knew that was it.
It was my song.
I thought our team would win.
The song was great.
It was a style of song I liked.
But I could tell the kind of performance they would do.
So I thought our team would do better...
and our team's song was better.
Well then, we look forward to your amazing performances.
- Okay. - Okay.
(Which teams will win and lose?)
The two average teams. Please introduce your teams to us.
Two, three.
- We are Twinkle. - We are Twinkle.
Hi. We are the most sparkling stars in the universe,
- Team Twinkle. - Team Twinkle.
(Team Twinkle)
Twinkle.
Attention!
- What? - That was cool.
- Girls on universe top. - Universe top.
Hi.
- We're Team Attention. - Attention.
(Team Attention)
- They have good energy. - I agree.
This performance will change...
the fates of half of the average team members.
Yoona.
How did you feel after receiving the average level?
Honestly, I was upset when I received...
the average level.
However, I felt like I had a chance to win as this battle...
was among participants in the average level.
The confidence.
Now then, Team Twinkle.
Get ready to perform first.
Team Attention. Leave the stage...
and stand by.
- I'm nervous. - Oh, no.
It's finally starting.
All right. The producers are with us right now.
- Unicorn ADORA. - Yes?
You're here as a producer today.
How do you feel?
Hi. I should be over there with them.
To be frank, I liked...
how I could meet all of them more closely.
I could feel their passion more.
And as mentioned, we added a new melody to the song.
The lyrics of that melody go like this.
"Try to listen to the song of dreams at the end of this universe."
That's the message of the song.
Just like the lyrics,
I hoped that the girls would be able to make a debut...
at the end of this show when I worked on the song.
I was wishing them luck the whole time.
I hope you will perform well with this positive energy from me.
(Universe Ticket)
By the way, it seems to me...
that you guys are feeling a bit down.
- I hope we work hard together. - Yes.
- All of us are dying to debut. - Right.
Our level is average.
- That's upsetting. Isn't it? - You bet.
- Darn it. - Let's be honest.
"Average?" Seriously?
One more thing. Does anyone want to be the leader?
No one?
None of you?
I had never been a leader in my group. So...
This is the perfect chance for you to be the leader then.
So...
since no one wants to do it,
I'll take the position gratefully and do my best.
I'll try to fulfill my responsibility as your leader.
- Yes! - Yes!
I wanted to be more ambitious from here on out.
To tell the truth, I now want to be the leader and the main vocalist.
All right. We'll divide the song to assign your parts today.
- Okay. - Okay.
Actually, this is the most important agenda today.
One of you has to improvise singing high notes.
Is there anyone who would like to sing these high notes?
If you sing high notes, you'll stand out at the end.
Getting noticed one more time might be better.
My name is Kwon Chaewon.
- Yes. - I'd like to try out...
- for the main vocalist position. - The main vocalist?
Let's hear it then, Chaewon.
Don't forget it, you're a superstar
(This is the part with high notes which ADORA emphasized.)
- Okay. - Okay.
Okay.
- The way you sing your last note... - Yes.
makes the song sound outdated.
If you sing dance songs with vibrato, they sound outdated.
Chaewon,
- you tend to elongate your notes. - I see.
Does anyone else think they can sing these high notes?
- I'll try it out. Yes. - Sumin?
- At last. - Gosh.
This is getting interesting now.
- Can I sing on my feet? - Sure. Of course, you can.
That's even better.
Actually, I want to sing the highlight of the song.
I kind of want to be the main vocalist too.
I'll be different
- Nice. - She's very nice.
- Very nice. - Your singing is very stable.
That's your biggest strength.
Thank you.
Gosh, this is...
It's hard.
I didn't want to lose this part to another girl this time.
The main vocalist is...
Sumin.
Sumin, you're great.
You can keep performing like that.
(Sumin becomes the main vocalist.)
I was really disappointed, so I did feel a bit angry.
- I want... - Who else?
- to be the lead vocalist. Yes. - The lead vocalist?
Get rid of everything that tires you out
Such gestures, such gazes
Aren't you sick of this old style?
- Okay. Let's stop there. - Okay.
(Hyerin tries out to be the lead vocalist after Yoona.)
The lead vocalist is...
- Hyerin. - Okay.
(Yoona wasn't chosen for the lead vocalist.)
Next. The sub vocalist will be...
- Chaewon - Okay.
That's what we decided.
(Chaewon who wasn't chosen either becomes a sub vocalist.)
What's wrong?
- No. Why are you crying? - What's wrong?
- Why are you crying? - Why... You're...
I'm sorry.
- Why did you do that? - Seriously.
- It's okay. - Things didn't go...
- the way she wanted. - Then...
I really want to make an impression on the Unicorns.
So I wanted to become the lead vocalist.
It was upsetting.
I really worked hard when I practiced singing the song.
But I might have practiced way too much.
When I woke up this morning,
I felt that my voice was a bit hoarse.
I shouldn't have practiced too much yesterday.
Next, we have the highlight. Does anyone want to try it out?
(Everyone is surprised when Kotoko volunteers.)
Kotoko.
- Yes. - Kotoko.
(This highlight was added as the song was newly arranged.)
I'll be by your side
To you
She looks like a studious student.
Great. Nice.
Well done.
You were flipping through the pages to sing. I found that so funny.
It was so cute, so I laughed.
(When the rest of them practiced with the printout,)
(only she studied with her notebook.)
I listened to the song carefully.
Then I wrote down the pronunciation of the lyrics in my notebook.
Okay. Right here like this.
I studied the lyrics until 3am.
The highlight goes to...
Kotoko.
Thank you.
Kotoko. In my opinion, she is...
one hardworking girl.
She doesn't have a booming voice. But given her voice,
she was very close to pulling off the highlight.
I thought that she'd excel a lot if we taught her a bit.
I saw infinite potential for her to grow as a singer.
(Kotoko is also working hard to practice the choreography.)
You're a superstar
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
I'm a Pilates instructor. My name is Baek Ji Yeon.
It's nice to meet you all.
(This is a special class for those with a lack of foundation.)
I'm going to analyze your body types today...
to find out what you lack and what you need to improve.
I'll take a look at everyone's body types one at a time.
Sua. It's your knees. On top of that,
I bet you have internally rotated hip joints too.
- I do. - You do.
You too, Kotoko. Your weight is on your heels.
- Yes. - Your ears...
Kotoko, you have rounded shoulders.
Kotoko. You have rounded shoulders.
Step on the middle of this.
(Their focused sessions differ based on their body types.)
All right. Standing on top of them...
on your own like this will be enough for an exercise.
One. Bring your legs in.
(They build their foundation to improve their performances.)
Your calves are being stretched.
Think of it as rolling down the foam roller.
All the way. You can feel...
your left side getting stretched, right?
Come on. Hurry.
All right. This is the last one.
Okay. The last one.
Let's finish the last one.
(She works harder than anyone to build a strong foundation.)
(After strengthening their foundation,)
(Team Twinkle starts their vocal lesson.)
- Chaewon, let's start with you. - Okay.
Forget it
Can you sing without the vibrato?
Instead of bending your pronunciation,
- keep it simple and plain. - Okay.
- That will suit you better. - Okay.
Lose yourself from time to time
That too. Why don't you sing without bending the last note?
(Chaewon's singing method is holding her back.)
I thought that it didn't sound that awful.
To tell you the truth,
I didn't fix my singing habits. So I have bad singing habits.
- All right. - Chaewon.
I'll be completely honest about her.
- She has a lot of bad habits. - Yes.
I'm not sure if she'd be able to fix those habits.
How should we help her fix that? Gosh, Chaewon.
Someone has to sit her down and fix her habit.
- It's really hard. - Yes.
- We'll do it after five minutes. - Okay.
(In the end, the vocal coach separately calls Chaewon.)
I mean, I had been singing like this for the past several years.
It wasn't easy to fix my singing style.
Let's try one more time.
- Forget it - Forget it
Let's try it again. Go.
(She still couldn't fix her habit the next day either.)
Not yet. Fix the first note. You can do this. Try it again.
- You can do this! - Are you okay?
I thought I had to fix this habit, so I really worked hard to fix it.
I tried to remove all of my habits and sing it...
like it was a children's song.
I shouldn't have cried in there.
But I kept finding myself in situations that made me cry.
One, two, three, four.
Do we start on 5 or 6?
(After losing her confidence, she can't focus on the practice.)
- One. - We probably did that on one.
- Four, five, six. One. - One?
Forget
- Your difficult days - Our positions aren't aligned.
Our positions aren't aligned correctly.
But we should...
We...
Our leader seemed to be struggling a lot.
At first, I thought, "What are we going to do?"
Should I move here? Or...
- Is this it? Aren't they different? - You have to move in.
- I have to move in? - Nako has to step out.
Why do I feel like nothing is working out?
I showed my weak side to the members of my team.
I pretended not to be affected by that.
But to be honest, I was very angry at myself.
(They begin the dance lesson when they're not fully ready.)
You guys have to look cheerful and energetic.
But all of your dance moves look sloppy.
If this is all the energy you can show them,
you're bound to lose.
This might look like a talent show at some school.
- You know? - Yes.
It felt like we might end up losing if we didn't change things around.
If we lose, I might get eliminated.
So I'm scared.
By the way, I was meaning to ask you this.
When we do this dance move...
As we circle our arms one and a half times,
we should slow down our arms...
and then do a bigger body roll.
That way, our move will stand out more.
Nako, you face forward when you do the body roll.
- You do it like this. - Yes.
Don't let your chest face forward.
Don't adjust the angle of your shoulders.
Just lean back when you do the body roll.
Yes. But there's no need to make the movement look so big.
I thought, "What's this?"
The body roll...
If I were to volunteer to be the leader from the get-go,
we could have fine-tuned the choreography faster.
I could have spoken up faster. That crossed my mind.
For some reason...
Getting eliminated?
I really don't want to be eliminated.
I can't go back now.
This is the only path I have left.
I don't want anyone in my team to get eliminated.
(They get on the stage, unable to wash away their anxiety.)
Yes, some people will be eliminated today.
But today's performance won't be your last one.
We will see each other again on another stage, right?
So make sure you leave no regret for today's performance.
Fully enjoy the energy of the performance.
So what if you need to improve?
Think of it as your last chance on this show.
I hope you will fully express yourself on stage today.
Don't lose your energy. You got this.
- Okay. - Good luck.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Good luck. I mean it.
Here they go.
- With a lot of energy. - Let's do this, everyone.
Are we in the center?
- Yes. - Okay.
We are.
I'm nervous for them.
I'm so nervous.
(Universe Ticket)
(Show us everything you've got, so you won't leave any regrets.)
Her blond hair is shining.
They look beautiful.
("Superstar" by Kwon Chaewon, Kim Sumin, Nako, Oh Yoona,)
(Choi Hyerin, and Kotoko)
She's so cute!
They're so cute.
Oh, my!
She's good!
I think I'm going to tear up.
I'm tearing up.
This is so emotional.
- That was so cool. - That was cool.
- I'm getting teary-eyed. - I loved it.
- Seriously. - By the way, was it live?
- It was live, right? - Yes.
- They did well. - They were great.
- They must've practiced a lot. - Totally.
They were determined.
How much longer will you hold the ending pose?
I guess they have to keep holding it.
All right. Get up. It's okay to get up now.
You can get up now.
Well done.
The group energy was great.
- Right. - Their energy was great.
- Seriously. - Indeed.
You didn't have to feel insecure.
Your performance was great. I mean it.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Sumin. You started off the performance.
Your facial expressions and singing were solid.
Thanks to that, you kept grabbing my attention.
I noticed that you grew a lot as a performer.
Thank you.
Yoona. First of all, I know that...
you're a great vocalist.
To have a more suitable voice to rap,
you must have a strong vocal foundation.
That's what I heard.
That must be why. Even the rap part suited you very well.
- You nailed it. - Thank you.
Sure. You pulled it off nicely.
- Kotoko. For this performance, - Yes.
you were responsible for more parts than expected.
Right.
(Kotoko was in charge of the highlight.)
Of course, I can't say that you were perfect.
But it didn't look like...
you were struggling or hesitant to perform.
I could tell that you worked as hard as you could...
for this performance.
I wanted to tell you I was proud of you and impressed by that.
Actually, I have a lot to share.
Just to add to what you said about Kotoko,
I should mention the day we assigned the parts.
She wrote down the pronunciation of the lyrics...
in Japanese on her notebook...
and practiced the pronunciation until late the night before.
She diligently prepared for this performance.
So for her, this performance was...
Why are you crying?
Don't cry. You did a great job.
- Kotoko. - Don't cry.
She cries like a baby.
- Don't cry. - Okay.
Kotoko.
You have this charm...
that puts people in a good mood when they simply look at you.
It's something neither you can buy with money...
nor work hard to get.
Of course, I see some improvement...
in terms of your dancing and performance.
But I did think that you would benefit a lot...
from practicing your breathing technique.
It will be great if you can practice that too.
I choked up when I was watching you, Chaewon.
I'll just share what I felt. Earlier before the performance,
I told you to fire it up...
even if this were to be your last performance on the show.
You did what I asked better than anyone on your team.
That must have been why I felt emotionally connected.
Gosh, she's crying again.
Don't cry.
- Don't cry. - Don't cry.
I noticed you a lot during this performance.
- Okay. - I did.
Thank you.
I wanted to give a round of applause...
to everyone here for a job well done.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Well done.
- Well done. - Well done.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Well done. - Thank you.
"Has Kotoko's singing always been this solid?"
- That crossed my mind too... - Right.
- even if her pitch was a bit shaky. - Right.
Actually, here's why I said I was proud of her.
I was proud of her because I noticed that she improved...
- even after this. - Right.
- I agree. Right? - Yes.
Next. Come up to the stage, Team Attention.
- Gosh. - Really?
(Let's go, Team Attention.)
- We'll finally get to watch them. - It's their turn at last.
I can't wait to watch their performance.
- Hello. - Hello.
- They look cool. - Gosh.
I'm getting really curious.
(Producers from PAPERMAKER: Samuel Ku, EB, TENZO)
Team Attention.
- Yes. - Yes.
What did you think of the performance of Team Twinkle?
Well,
I was really looking forward to it,
but their performance may not have been...
as impressive as I expected.
We'll give a more powerful performance...
and make you forget all about it.
(That's bold.)
- Oh, boy. - That's intimidating.
Let's say you guys have won.
Who among you think you'll win a Unicorn Ticket?
(All of them raise their hands.)
All of them raised their hands.
(They seem very confident.)
- Their hands went straight up. - That's cool.
People like us are in the average group?
I mean, I think we're the kind of people that others would...
wonder why we were put in the average group.
And I'm not worried about anything,
such as the job assignment.
No matter who takes which part,
we'll all be able to pull it off.
(They're a group of talented girls.)
So you know, I'm not worried.
Frankly, we don't belong in the average group.
We all feel like we were underrated.
(Gabi took the Level Test together with Lim Seowon.)
Gabi fell a little short, right?
- Yes. - Yes.
"Was I that bad?"
"What did I do wrong?"
I had questions like these.
When I was put in the average group,
I wasn't satisfied.
I'm going to try and make them regret putting me...
in the average group.
What I'm actually worried about is...
who will get the promotion.
That's more important to us...
because I'm sure we'll win,
and the competition for the promotion is going to be...
- You're right. - really tough here.
- Everyone here is so good. - Yes.
I thought I should pull out all stops to do a good job.
I don't think I will be eliminated.
I feel really confident.
Who do I find intimidating? There's none.
I think we'll be able to give a great performance as a team,
but what do I need to do to make sure I stand out?
That's my biggest concern here.
Let's go around and say which part of the song we want to do.
Well, I...
want to do the highlight.
- The highlight? - The highlight.
Part number one.
Part number one or...
Number 1 or 3.
Same. Number 1 or 3.
Number 1 or 3? I see.
(The highlight is where the song begins.)
I guess there's going to be a fierce competition.
I really want to do the highlight.
I know I can do the dance really well,
and I think I will be good for the part.
I think singing is my strong suit,
so if I'm lucky, I might be able to get the part.
I think I can do a better job than anyone...
with the dance for the intro which is the highlight.
I feel pretty confident.
(Who will get to do the highlight?)
(The next day at the PAPERMAKER studio)
Have you guys checked out the song?
- Yes. - What did you think?
- We love it. - We love it.
Is there a certain part you want to do?
Anyone?
- Yes. - We all have one.
- You all have one? Good. - Yes.
Let's hear you sing 1 by 1 then.
- Okay. - Okay.
(Nervous)
I'm nervous.
- All right, are you ready? - Yes.
- Let's give it a try. From the top. - Okay.
(Candidate number 1 for the highlight, Jeon Jinyeong)
(Candidate number 2 for the highlight, Bae Haram)
(Candidate number 3 for the highlight, Goo Gyoryeon)
(Candidate number 4 for the highlight, Gabi)
(Candidate number 5 for the highlight, Nana)
(Who will be assigned to the highlight?)
All right.
We've assigned you to your parts through discussion.
It was the most difficult to decide who'll do the highlight.
I really want to do the highlight.
The highlight.
(The highlight is assigned to...)
Gabi will do it.
Thank you.
I got the highlight,
and I was really happy.
I was sad I didn't get it.
Gabi. You're a good singer, but you're young and inexperienced.
If you put in more work, I'm sure you'll be amazing.
- I like your voice. - Thank you.
Nana.
I hear you're a good performer,
but you didn't sound so confident when you were singing.
If you work on that,
you'll stand out more in your performance.
- Okay. - I hope you'll work hard...
- until the recording. - Yes.
We've been assigned to our parts for "Girls On Top."
The part I wanted to do was the highlight,
but they assigned Gabi to it.
Yes. So...
when I went back to the dorm,
I cried.
Although I didn't get the highlight,
I'm going to work really hard...
to turn my own part into the highlight.
You can do it, Nana.
Let's go.
- Hi, I have a question. - Yes?
- When the rhythm changes, - That's right.
I have trouble keeping...
- my balance. - You do? Okay.
(She also asks the vocal coach for advice after the lesson.)
(After hearing that she lacks confidence in her singing,)
(Nana is working hard to improve her weaknesses.)
Can anyone do the kick?
The kick. Can you do it?
Seven and eight.
That's it.
(Nana got herself a new part too.)
- You've got long legs. - That's cool.
I didn't get the Unicorn Ticket before,
and I was really sad about it.
So as for the next performance,
I really want to own it.
I want to impress everyone with my performance of "Girls On Top."
We saw our practice video, and from Nana's facial expressions,
I could see that she's really going all out for this.
She's more determined than anyone...
to work hard and pull this off.
She's probably the most tenacious person on the team.
(Their practice continues until late at night.)
("Girls On Top," the day of recording)
(Team Attention is at the recording studio.)
Gabi, you're doing the first part, so let's start with you.
- Okay. - Let's go, Gabi.
- We'll go in this order. - Gabi.
All right, Gabi. Let's start.
Yes.
Everyone's telling me I should be somebody I don't want to be
Somebody I don't want to be
Want to be
- Want to be - Want to be
- Don't bend the note in "want." - Want to be
Yes, let's try again.
Everyone's telling me I should be somebody I don't want to be
It has to be all short.
Short.
- All the same. Okay? - Okay.
- Be more confident. - Yes.
Everyone's telling me I should be somebody I don't want to be
You're going faster. Don't feel rushed.
Listen, Gabi.
You're probably doing what you can in there,
but from here,
it sounds like you're standing still with a blank look without dancing.
You sound emotionless.
Everyone
(Stuck in the first part, they can't proceed with the recording.)
I don't think she's a good fit for this part.
- Gabi, you can come out. - Okay.
(They stop the recording.)
The problem is that if Gabi can't do the intro,
she won't be able to do this part either.
It's not like she doesn't understand the lyrics.
She clearly can't do the intro.
It doesn't sound right.
Want to be
"Want to be."
Here's the thing. This is not an individual performance.
- Right. - It's a group performance,
and you should do well as a team.
To improve your performance, you'll have to switch parts.
Some of you don't really sound good for your parts.
We're only doing this so you'll do a better job.
The lyrics for the intro are repeated later, right?
I want Nana and Jayla to give it a try.
I think you have better voices for it.
- Nana, let's start with you. - Okay.
- From "Everyone's telling me." - Okay.
(Nana gives the highlight a try.)
- Great. That was nice. - Good job.
It was good. The vibe and everything.
The intro, the part I really wanted to do,
was reassigned to Nana.
I couldn't help but wonder if I had done a bad job,
and I was upset...
that I blew my chance.
It already happened. There's no going back.
Just try and do a good job with your new part.
That's the part I wanted the most,
and I...
was really happy to get it.
Some of us were reassigned to different parts unexpectedly.
I was a bit scared.
Another change might bring chaos.
We have to compete against one another within the team as well.
I have to make myself stand out to survive.
All I could think about was that I have to do...
everything in my power to give a good performance.
(The competition for the promotion has become even fiercer.)
(While everyone is busy practicing,)
(Gabi looks at her phone the whole time.)
Since Gabi was reassigned to a different part,
she's been looking a little demotivated.
Sometimes,
she just ignores us and looks at her phone.
Does anyone want to have some snacks?
Let's have them later, Gabi.
She was looking at her phone while having a snack.
(During the practice)
Everyone was tiptoeing around her.
(The dance practice begins,)
(but it's soon put to a stop.)
And stop.
Gabi, you need to turn on the spot.
She seemed distracted when we were practicing together.
- Let's try the chorus, shall we? - Yes.
Gabi got it wrong.
(She got the moves wrong, but all she does is smile.)
(She even walks out of the room in the middle of the practice.)
- What's taking her so long? - Gabi.
Where's Gabi?
(Everyone is waiting for her.)
(They had to proceed without Gabi.)
If you lose and somebody had to be eliminated,
who do you think that would be?
Gabi.
Gabi or...
I think there's a good chance it'll be Gabi.
She was very enthusiastic at first,
but she clearly started to lose her motivation,
judging by the way she acted in the last ten days.
I wonder what she's thinking.
Well, it's...
I'm not tired, but I guess I'm upset.
What are you upset about?
It feels like...
people won't be able to notice me.
I'm upset about that.
I'm not demotivated, but it's just that...
I try to work hard,
but I can't help but feel sad.
I guess I might've looked demotivated in their eyes.
All right then.
Team Attention, let's see your performance.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Let's go. - Let's go!
- We got this. - Good luck!
I'm nervous.
- Me too. - Why am I nervous?
I hope they do well.
- Break a leg. - You guys look great.
They're all so tall.
I can't wait to see it.
It already looks like they'll win.
In terms of appearance, they already won.
I already feel blown away.
How cool.
I'm excited.
("Girls On Top" by Gabi, Goo Gyoryeon, Nana,)
(Bae Haram, Lee Sunwoo, Jeon Jinyeong, and Jayla)
Awesome.
I got goosebumps.
That's good. Very good.
That's insane!
They killed it.
Oh, my gosh.
Nice!
- That was incredible. - They killed it.
- I got goosebumps. - That was amazing.
They were awesome.
They totally killed it.
How are they in the average group?
They're really good.
- That was insane! - Their energy.
- They killed it. - I got goosebumps all over.
They killed it.
Gosh, that was great.
- I'm overwhelmed with emotions. - I know.
- That was cool. - The ending.
They were amazing. What do we do?
What are we going to do?
What did you think of their performance?
- I'm overwhelmed with emotions. - Same here.
They almost made my heart explode.
What do we do?
They performed like they were a group that has released...
- a few albums together already. - Yes.
They had such great teamwork,
and each of them expressed their energy so well.
It was a wonderful performance. You were awesome.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
We haven't seen the high level group's performance yet,
but I don't think it'll be better than this.
Wait, they're not the high level group?
I thought they were.
It was amazing.
Their singing was just flawless.
They seemed more professional than any other experienced artists,
and they also had incredible teamwork.
Their individual performances were great,
but they also did a terrific job as a team.
They were perfect as a team, but there were...
some members that caught my eye in particular.
Nana, you performed in the center...
- during the intro. - Yes.
You were way more charismatic than I expected.
During the dance where you shake your shoulders,
you just looked fabulous.
It was great. I really enjoyed it.
Thank you.
Gyoryeon.
Your singing was nice and steady in the middle.
Thank you.
I thought...
you were really good at controlling the vocal dynamics.
It was so pleasing...
- and easy on the ear. - Thank you.
For me, it was Haram.
I thought she wasn't playing a major role...
- You're right. - in this performance,
but she totally knocked my socks off during the dance break.
She was on fire.
It was so powerful. I was very impressed.
Thank you.
Producers, what did you think of their performance?
It took us a lot of work...
to finish this song, and the recording took a long time.
It wasn't easy,
but they gave a perfect performance as a team, and I loved it.
I have to talk about Gabi.
Gabi had to be reassigned to a completely different part.
She cried a lot during the recording,
and I was really worried about her.
But she did her best to complete her part,
and I want to thank her for that.
It was a great performance overall.
Well done.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(It's time to decide the winner and the loser.)
This is going to be tough.
We will now announce the Level Station levels.
The winner of the Average Level Battle is...
(Team Attention)
(Team Twinkle)
I can't believe three members will be eliminated.
I can't watch this.
The winner of the Average Level Battle is...
(Who is the winner of the Average Level Battle?)
(To be continued)
The winner of the Average Level Battle is...
Team Attention.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Team Attention won.)
(3 members of Team Attention will be promoted.)
(3 members of Team Twinkle will be eliminated.)
Thank you.
But they did well. They did well.
- I don't like this. - I lost my energy.
Now,
the winning team members' fates will be decided.
How did they pick three members among them?
We will now announce the three promoted members...
of the winning team that were chosen by the Unicorns.
(All members of Team Attention had incredible talent.)
The promoted members are...
Nana.
Thank you.
(The first promoted member, Nana)
Goo Gyoryeon.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Lastly...
(Who is the last promoted member?)
I was determined to get promoted.
I didn't get the Unicorn Ticketing last time,
so I was more desperate.
(Who will get promoted last on the average level?)
Bae Haram. Congratulations.
(The third promoted member, Bae Haram)
- Thank you. - They wouldn't be entirely happy.
I am more worried about the three eliminated members.
From this team,
three members will be eliminated.
That's right.
Firstly...
This is really hard.
What would be the right way to explain our decision?
Hyerin didn't catch my attention...
- like I said earlier. - Yes.
- Yes. - I think she lacks talent.
- I agree. - It isn't something...
she can improve in a short amount of time.
One thing is certain.
She was someone who never caught my eye.
But she showed potential during this performance.
(It's hard to make a decision since there are many aspects.)
Chaewon is the one who did well today.
I agree.
- She let things go. - Yes.
I feel like she can only pull off a limited number of songs.
I feel like she can only shine...
when she performs a song like "Superstar."
Unless she does much better,
- we can't keep Kotoko much longer. - That's right.
I agree.
I think there is a reason why...
the producers gave her more parts.
That's right.
- I can see that she is improving. - She continues to improve.
She does improve very quickly.
- That's right. - That's right.
It might be better to pick people we want to keep seeing.
Shall we go with this decision?
- Yes. - Okay.
I feel bad.
We will now announce...
the eliminated members of the average level.
The three eliminated members of the losing team are...
(Who are the 3 eliminated members of the losing team?)
- Please. - Oh, no.
I was very anxious, to be honest.
I thought I might be 1 of the 3 eliminated members.
The three eliminated members of the losing team are...
(Who are the 3 eliminated members of the losing team?)
(To be continued)
The three eliminated members of the losing team are...
Nako.
(The first eliminated member, Nako)
Choi Hyerin.
(The second eliminated member, Choi Hyerin)
Kwon Chaewon. Thank you for your hard work.
(The third eliminated member, Kwon Chaewon)
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
There is something...
I really want to say to Chaewon.
On the stage today,
seeing you...
and being able to call your name...
made me very happy.
I thought, "This is the performance Kwon Chaewon can show."
I was very happy to see it today.
- And Hyerin... - Yes.
- and Nako. - Yes.
You already have shining potential.
So you should think, "I am someone who shines."
"How can I shine brighter?"
I hope you will find the answer.
You have been doing very well. You did well today as well.
- Thank you. - Thank you for your hard work.
To me, Universe Ticket was...
a good stepping stone...
on my way to become an idol singer. Thank you so much.
I will leave Universe Ticket now,
but I experienced many things...
through this show.
I was happy to show my performances to the fans.
Thank you.
(Before leaving Universe Ticket,)
(what does she want to say to the Unicorns?)
Hello,
I am Kwon Chaewon.
Thank you...
for giving me a good experience and great advice.
I am going home after learning and feeling...
many things.
I will come back...
as Chaewon who is cooler and maturer.
When that happens...
When that happens,
please just accept me as a younger sister...
and a junior singer.
Thank you.
(We are both teammates and rivals.)
(The war of nerves becomes heated up due to their competition for parts.)
(I can't help but become a bit wary.)
(When you let you guard down and become distracted,)
(your rival will move up quickly.)
(Where did they bring someone like her?)
(Seowon's part...)
(should go to Elisia.)
You need to practice singing a bit harder.
(They win and lose parts amidst their struggle to survive.)
It wasn't a coincidence
(This could be your last chance.)
(To survive,)
(they need to be more desperate.)
(That was amazing.)
(I don't want to lose my part.)
(At the crossroads of promotion and elimination,)
(which girls will survive?)
(That was insane. That was incredible.)
(We will announce the eliminated members.)
It wasn't like Seowon did badly.
You know that you did well, right?
You know that, right?
The dream ticketing for the debut.
Vote for your favorite girl.
Participate now on the Universe Ticket homepage...
and Fancast app for the global vote, Fan Ticketing.
For the third Fan Ticketing,
you can cast up to 2 tickets to 1 girl.
Make sure to reserve a ticket for the girls' dreams.