[English subtitles are available]
[Destined]
[Episode 2]
Little Yuru, are you buying rouge?
Sir,
I'm afraid it'll be inappropriate
if there's a male customer here.
Young Master,
this is a rouge shop.
As soon as you came in,
my customers...
Don't worry.
I won't affect your business.
I'll buy all the rouge
in the store today.
Well...
Little Yuru,
if any rouge takes your fancy,
just pick it
and ask Jiusi to buy it for you.
Young Master, please mind your language.
My young miss
is a decent lady
from an eminent family.
You being like this...
Y-You being like this...
What's wrong with me?
Girl, tell me.
Young Master Gu,
I have no idea
why you're looking for me today.
But we are poles apart.
We never had much interaction.
If my family
offended you,
Young Master Gu,
please be magnanimous
and forgive them.
I apologize to you on their behalf.
Please stop
making things difficult for me today.
Don't believe her. She's just pretending.
That's right. She's very scheming.
Little Yuru,
I'm not giving you a hard time.
I like you.
Young Master Gu,
please don't joke around.
This is not a joke.
I fell in love with you at first sight,
then fell more deeply at second sight.
From now until I die,
I won't marry anyone but you.
Young Master Gu.
I apologize to you
for what happened at Ye Mansion today.
I had no choice.
Ladies always value reputation the most.
But even so,
it's my fault
for displeasing you.
Today, you've already
fooled me once.
We should be even now.
Young Master Gu,
please let me off this time.
Didn't you say
if Jiusi
took a liking to you,
you'd kill yourself by drowning in the river?
That's right.
Now, he has proposed to you.
Time waits for no man, Little Yuru.
The moat is over there.
Go quickly and jump into it!
Go and jump!
Are you trying to drive her to a corner?
You bully a young lady like this.
It is way overboard.
Young Master Gu,
must you force me to jump into the river
to end all this?
Jump! Jump!
How about this?
You just have to say,
"Ye Shi'an is a bastard.
He isn't as good as Gu Jiusi, who is very handsome,
elegant, smart,
and upright."
This will put an end
to the matter.
Young Master Ye... is not as good as you,
who are elegant,
h-handsome...
Cool.
Handsome and cool.
Not as smart as you.
And also not...
Upright.
Louder.
He's not as upright as you.
All right, you may go now.
Wait.
Everyone,
take a box of rouge.
Consider it a gift from me.
Thank you, Young Master Gu.
Thank you.
[A Godsent Marriage]
What?
Are you looking down on me?
If you don't take it,
it means you don't want me to spend money.
You are concerned about me, and you fancy me.
If you marry Ye Shi'an in the future,
teach him a lesson for me.
[A Godsent Marriage]
[Gu Mansion]
That little brat.
Young Miss Ye is so courteous and good-looking.
Not only did he refuse,
but he also went to her house
and made a fool of himself.
We were so eager to get him engaged.
Guess what he said.
He said
he wants to make his own decisions on marriage.
He wants to marry
someone he likes as his wife.
Otherwise, he'll pack up his things and rove all over the world.
Listen.
What nonsense is that?
Jiusi's got a point.
After all, this is
his own marriage.
He should marry
a girl he likes.
We took the liberty of
getting him engaged.
That was indeed not appropriate.
What do you think is appropriate?
Is it appropriate to marry the princess in Eastern Capital?
We're not in the same league as the royal family.
If anything goes wrong,
it will
cause the whole family to be exterminated.
The emissary who is going to bring up the proposal of marriage
will arrive soon.
What should we do?
Master.
Madam.
Young Master has a crush on someone.
Jiusi has a crush on someone?
Young Master said
he would marry no one but the young lady.
Did Jiusi really say that?
Of course.
He said it himself.
Many people heard it.
Then...
Which family is she from?
Well...
Go and find out.
Yes.
So she is the legitimate daughter
of the Liu family which owns a clothing business.
Her family is indeed a little low-class.
No wonder Jiusi didn't mention it.
Although her family is a little low-class,
it's a decent family.
The most important thing is
Jiusi likes her.
Thank goodness.
He's always wandering around outside.
I thought
he would marry
a prostitute.
How about this?
We will bring up the proposal of marriage tomorrow.
My husband and I have heard
what happened yesterday.
Madam.
My eldest daughter
was so impolite yesterday
that she offended your son.
My master will surely teach her a lesson
after he finishes checking the ledgers.
I sincerely apologize for the inconvenience caused.
Don't say that.
We're here today
to propose to Young Miss Liu
on behalf of my son, Jiusi.
Let's have a seat to talk about it.
This is the list of betrothal gifts from the Gu family.
It includes 100 mu of farmland in the western suburbs,
15 shops in Guangling East Street,
15 houses,
seven fishing villages in Zhuhu,
pleasure boats...
Ten pleasure boats?
Ten pairs of coloured glaze lamps from the Western Regions,
and ten pairs of mutton fat jade.
Please give the list to Master Liu
so that he can have a look.
But we heard that
the Ye family and your family are going to be united by marriage.
Is that true?
Madam,
you've misunderstood.
Here's the thing.
My eldest daughter
and Young Miss Ye
are close friends.
So she naturally gets along well
with the Ye family.
But they never mentioned
marriage.
Those
are just rumours.
If Master agrees,
I wonder
when we can get the betrothal gifts.
If he says yes today,
we'll give you the betrothal gifts tomorrow.
We also think that the sooner the better.
Madam.
You can't be
tricking us, can you?
A noble family like the Gu family
is not something
we can be in the same league with.
My son, Jiusi,
has a crush on your daughter, Young Miss Liu.
We sincerely came here to propose marriage.
I was even worried that Young Miss Liu would disagree.
I see.
If so, it's a godsent marriage.
Yuru
often said that Young Master Gu,
who is good-looking and warm-hearted,
is a rare young talent.
Did Young Miss Liu really say that?
Of course.
Yuru has always
praised Young Master Gu
for his literary talent and personality.
That's great.
But the most important thing
about marriage is sincerity.
Although I'm an illegitimate mother,
I always treat Yuru
as my own daughter,
like the flesh in my hand.
All these years,
many people came
to propose marriage.
But I think the most important thing
is to marry her
off to a family full of sincerity.
Of course,
we sincerely came to propose.
These betrothal gifts
are precious
for ordinary people.
But the Gu family is noble and wealthy.
These are just a drop in the ocean.
I'm afraid
I can't see much sincerity in these.
What is your opinion about it?
I think 100 mu of farmland
and 15 shops
are not enough.
At least,
120 mu of farmland
and 18 shops.
In this way,
it also shows that our daughter
has prestige.
Moreover, it will earn respect
for the Gu family.
That's no big deal.
But your master isn't here today.
Also, Eldest Madam is feeling unwell.
We'll come
once again tomorrow.
Madam,
the matter is of great importance.
I'm afraid Master will blame me
if the matter is held up.
How about this?
I'll now send someone to Maritime Trade Superintendency
to deliver the message
and ask for the Master's opinion.
The Maritime Trade Superintendency is not far from here.
When you arrive at your mansion,
you will have received the reply.
Good.
By the way,
you have to ask for an opinion
from Young Miss Liu's birth mother,
the Eldest Madam, too.
Of course.
We'll now take our leave first.
Take care, Madam.
Madam.
Maritime Trade Superintendency is under strict supervision when checking the ledgers.
Aren't we not allowed to deliver messages to Master?
Are you stupid?
Who would really ask for his opinions?
It was just an act.
After twenty minutes,
you go and reply to them
that Master has agreed.
Young Miss.
Young Miss, bad news!
What's wrong?
Our family has made an engagement with the Gu family.
You are married off
to Gu Jiusi.
No way.
What nonsense are you talking about?
It's true.
Madam Yue ordered you
to be grounded in your room.
She also said
no one is allowed to tip you off.
Fortunately, the carter who went to deliver the message to the Gu family
was Eldest Madam's dowry servant.
That's why he told me secretly.
Well...
No matter how rich and powerful the Gu family is,
they should care about their reputation.
Old Madam Ye
already fixed her mind on me.
She even asked a matchmaker
to inquire about my Eight Characters.
Go!
Go to Ye Mansion to find Yun.
Ask her to think of a way.
If Old Madam Ye
can speak for me,
maybe there's still room to turn things around.
Go now.
Yes.
Grandmother!
Grandmother.
The Gu family wants to forcefully marry Yuru.
Please help her out.
Grandmother.
Say something.
Don't you
like Yuru very much too?
Don't you also want
my brother to marry Yuru?
We can't stand by and do nothing
while watching her jump into the fire pit.
Grandmother!
Yun'er.
We can't help her.
Why can't we help her?
The Gu family
took a fancy to you at first.
If she doesn't jump into the fire pit,
you will be the one who has to jump.
Even so, I can't stand idle by
watching her jump into the fire pit.
Yuru and I are as intimate as sisters.
I don't want her
to suffer for me.
She's smart, stoic,
and thoughtful.
Even if she encounters adversity,
she can somehow
find a way out.
But...
Can you do it?
I...
Girl,
you've been spoiled since young.
If you marry a playboy,
can you endure those hardships
and sufferings?
Yuru has already
had a hard life when she was young.
No one could protect her.
So she's now stoic,
capable,
and thoughtful.
But if
someone could protect her,
wouldn't she be just like me?
Just because
she has been suffering since she was young,
she should keep suffering in the future?
This is not fair, Grandmother.
I'd rather marry the Gu family
than have her
suffer for me.
Girl,
do you think
I didn't try to think of a way?
No matter what,
first come, first served.
If the Gu and Liu families
had not issued official documents,
I would have gone to the Gu Mansion
to set the record straight.
But...
it's too late.
This morning,
the marriage
was certified by the official documents.
There's no turning back anymore.
Yuru.
Grandmother said
the Gu and Liu families
have issued the official documents.
There's nothing she could do anymore.
How could it happen?
It was...
Everything was fine.
You almost
married my brother.
Brother...
Oh yeah.
Yuru.
I'll now write a letter to my brother
and ask him to come back soon.
So he can help us think of a way.
Yun'er.
The die is cast.
If you tell him now,
you're just causing him more trouble.
Yinhong,
send Yun back home.
I need to think about it alone.
Go.
Yuru.
Perhaps
it might have been my wishful thinking
from the beginning.
Eldest Miss.
Something bad happened.
Your father was detained by the Maritime Trade Superintendency
and is now in prison.
They said he transported
several ships of cloth
but evaded the tax.
He will be severely punished.
If he evaded the tax,
you would just have to pay the overdue tax.
Easy for you to say.
It's different this time.
This time, the commissioner
intervened and said
if someone evaded the tax,
the person would either be executed
or pay 100 times the fine.
100 times the fine.
Do you know how much it is?
To pay 100 times the fine,
just sell the shops,
houses, and the land we own,
that'll be enough.
Are you crazy?
If we sell them all,
what else can we rely on
for a living?
That's why you want to sell me
to the Gu family?
Eldest Miss.
What are you talking about?
Are you trying to
hurt my feelings?
I tried so hard to help you get married to a rich family.
How could you say
it's my fault?
Besides, the Gu family has already given us the betrothal gifts.
If you are reluctant to get married,
no decent family
will dare to accept
a girl who has broken off an engagement.
The reputation of the Liu family will be ruined.
And you will also
implicate your younger sisters by doing so.
Guixiang.
Close the door.
Hurry up.
Look out the land deeds and farmland deeds
we own.
Yes.
Mother, what's wrong?
I'm afraid the Liu family will be in trouble soon.
In these few days,
we should trade
these valuable things for money first.
If anything happens,
we'll leave
Yangzhou immediately.
We can't be implicated
by them.
Okay.
Young Miss,
do you really want to
marry Gu Jiusi?
For the time being,
do I have another choice?
The Gu family is of great influence.
For the sake of dignity,
they won't allow their relative by marriage
to stay in prison.
To exempt Father from punishment
is just a piece of cake for the Gu family.
From now on,
the Liu family will be safe and sound.
Isn't that
what Madam Yue expected?
How despicable.
Not only is she satisfied
with this,
but she has also been coveting
the betrothal gifts from the Gu family.
After I get married,
Mother will still live under her thumb
and depend on her for a living.
To support Mother
to live in the Liu family,
I have to ask the Gu family
to register the shops and farmhouses
under my name.
Young Miss, if you do so,
will the Gu family look down on you?
Now, there's no time for me
to care so much.
Besides,
what if Gu Jiusi
is not as bad as
the rumours?
What if...
What if he's willing to help me?
Here you are. Go
and ask a trustworthy servant
to send this letter
to Gu Jiusi.
Remember,
ask him to open it himself
and tell him what I mean.
Yes.
[A Godsent Marriage]
Cheers.
Come on.
Jiusi.
Let me ask you something.
Go ahead.
You...
Young Master Gu.
My young miss
asked me to send you a letter.
She also asked me to deliver you a message.
Your young miss?
Who is it?
My young miss said
since you are going to be husband and wife,
please give her a little protection.
Did you get the wrong person
or are you making fun of me?
What husband and wife?
So it's true.
What do you mean?
I heard
your family has given betrothal gifts.
They are going to
marry you to a young lady.
I thought it was
an untenable rumour.
So it's true.
I heard about it too.
But the news came so suddenly.
I didn't take it seriously.
Right? Me too.
Since it's true,
I should congratulate you, Jiusi.
You're getting married soon.
I didn't expect that
you are the first person
to get married among us.
Yes.
Young Miss Liu
even wrote you a love letter
before you get married.
Wait.
Young Miss Liu?
Which Young Miss Liu?
Who else?
Liu Yuru.
Gu Langhua that old man
simply ignored my words.
Take it.
Young Master Gu.
The land deeds.
What deeds?
How could she say yes to such a thing?
Was Liu Yuru
out of her mind?
-Young Master.
-Look.
He's shy.
Keep up.
After all the detours,
we have to arrive in Yangzhou today.
[Gu Mansion]
Now that the marriage of Jiusi is settled,
I truly feel
at ease.
Gu Langhua.
You old man.
I knew you'd be hanging around here.
Little brat,
you haven't been home for days,
and now you're talking nonsense.
Why am I getting married?
What's wrong with Young Miss Liu?
What are you doing
behind my back?
Hold on. What do you mean?
Do you really want to go to the Eastern Capital
with the emissary of Lord Liang?
Besides,
isn't Young Miss Liu
the girl you like?
Who likes Liu Yuru? I...
You don't like her?
You don't like her,
but you said in public that
you would marry no one else except her.
I...
I was just joking.
How could you joke about your marriage?
You got me engaged without my permission.
Anyway, I won't marry Liu Yuru.
I want to break off the engagement.
You little brat.
The betrothal gifts have been given and the wedding has been confirmed.
The bridal sedan chair will
fetch the bride from Liu Mansion tomorrow.
If you break off the engagement now,
what do you want her to do?
But if she marries
someone she doesn't like,
it will ruin her whole life.
Master.
Father.
Go away.
No.
Liu Yuru and I
dislike each other.
She looks down on me,
and the same goes for me.
I hate
hypocrites like her the most.
Besides,
she already has someone she likes.
If we get married,
neither of us will feel good.
I know
you are in such a hurry
to protect me from the misfortune.
But if I really
break up the couple who likes each other,
it... it's not so appropriate.
What should we do?
In my opinion,
just break off the engagement.
It's easy for you to say.
Even if we do not consider Lord Liang,
the engagement has gone through all the procedures,
and the government has also issued the certificates.
You can't just break it off.
Then, what do you think we should do?
Master.
Lord Liang's emissary is here.
Madam asked you to go to the main hall
to discuss something important.
Go, go, go.
Hurry up.
Little brat.
What have I done wrong
to have such a son?
Why was he so agitated all of a sudden?
This old man...
What?
Young Master Gu is already engaged?
When did that happen?
Unfortunately,
two days ago,
the procedures and official documents
have just been completed.
We didn't expect
you would come here today.
That's really a pity.
His Majesty has approved
the marriage proposal of the princess.
Is this
really a coincidence?
Yes, it is.
The wedding of my son and his beloved
is known to everyone in Yangzhou City.
He is going to escort the bride tomorrow.
What beloved?
Don't tell me he is getting engaged hurriedly
to disobey His Majesty's order
and fool His Majesty.
Listen.
If you lie to me,
it'll be a crime of deceiving His Majesty.
That makes no sense.
We, the Gu family, have always been upright
and loyal.
Everything I said is true.
If I lie to you,
I'll accept the punishment.
Master is here.
If you don't believe me,
you can ask him yourself
whether my son, Jiusi,
has a crush on someone
and is getting married.
Exactly.
My son is getting married tomorrow.
You must be tired from the journey.
How about you stay here and join the wedding dinner tomorrow?
We tramped over mountains and through ravines
and rushed to Yangzhou every moment.
But it's still too late.
Before the wedding,
we have a lot to do.
Please have a seat, sir.
I'll get back to work.
Sir, please.
Father, how is it?
When will we break off the engagement?
Master.
Why are you here?
It hurts.
I'll forgive you if you let me go now.
Master has issued an order.
Don't blame me.
I'll get you
a lamb leg tonight.
Why do I need a lamb leg?
It hurts.
Lock him up.
Keep a close watch on him.
Yes.
Father,
you can't force me to get married.
Lock him up.
Don't let him run away
before the wedding.
Take him away.
Yes.
Gu Langhua, you old man!
You broke your promise!
Just you wait. Once I am released,
I'll water all your flowers
with hot water.
It hurts.
[Liu Mansion]
Young Miss.
What did he say?
Gu Jiusi said
you were out of your mind.
Out of my mind?
He is out of his mind.
Young Master Gu is so unreliable.
You're going to be husband and wife soon,
but he's still so heartless.
It's just marrying a playboy
who has no sympathy.
Even if the Gu Mansion is hell,
I'll keep my eyes closed
and get rid of
all the obstacles.
[Escort the bride]
The weather is so nice today.
It's really auspicious.
Yes.
[Liu Mansion]
The bride
must have been blessed.
Yes.
She must have been blessed.
Don't worry, Mother.
After I marry into the Gu family,
I'll take good care of my family affairs
and be filial to my parents-in-law.
I won't embarrass you.
Put the sedan chair down.
[Liu Mansion]
[Escort the bride]
[Gu Mansion]
Sir, please have a seat.
I'll go and greet the guests.
Master.
Do entertain him.
I will.
Madam, you want to see me?
Where is Jiusi?
Young Master...
Young Master is putting on his wedding outfit.
It's been an hour.
I'll get him myself.
Madam.
Master specially ordered that
today is a big day,
so we'd better not force him.
If we provoke him
and he talks rubbish at the banquet,
won't that make things worse?
T-This is what Master said.
[Gu Mansion]
Put the sedan chair down.
The bride, please get off the sedan chair.
Young Miss.
What happened?
The bride is shy.
It happens all the time.
She hasn't gotten off the sedan chair yet.
The bride, please get off the sedan chair.
Yuru refuses to get off the sedan chair.
Is she unwilling to marry into the Gu family?
If she is reluctant,
Master, why don't we...
Ridiculous!
If she doesn't marry,
do you want them
to put me in prison again?
[A Godsent Marriage]
The auspicious time is around the corner, isn't it?
The bride has also arrived.
The wedding will begin soon.
The bride is here.
Come out and take a look.
The bride marrying into the family
brings good luck and blessings.
May the family grow and prosper like spreading melon vines.
Be united and harmonious.
Now is the auspicious time. The groom, please show yourself.
Why isn't the groom coming out?
It's the auspicious time.
The groom, please show yourself.