[English subtitles are available]
[Destined]
[Episode 13]
There are so many
beautiful stones in your pond.
Can I take some home?
You like pretty stones?
Thank you.
What's your name?
I told you to keep an eye on him,
yet he messed with
the granddaughter of Scholar Su next door.
He didn't mess with her.
That naughty girl
climbed over the wall to play with him.
What's the difference?
Don't you know he can't be seen?
If word gets out
that my only daughter
was sullied
and then abandoned
before getting married,
and have a son out of wedlock,
the whole Luo family
will be disgraced because of you!
He can't
go to the garden again.
His existence
should forever be a secret.
Guards!
Yes.
Lock him up.
I have to go to the garden.
I promised
to give her Yuhua Stones!
-Fire!
Mother!
What's your name?
You can have the whole piece.
These are my treasures.
I'll share them with you.
Miss,
why did you sneak out alone?
You shouldn't sit with a beggar.
He's my new friend.
Go home now.
Her Ladyship is waiting for you.
Liu Yuru.
Why did she happen to be you?
Unfortunately,
even if she's you,
now that you married Gu Jiusi,
you have to go down
with the Gu family.
[Wang Mansion]
Congratulations, my lord.
On what?
Lord Liang
is about to rise up.
Just as you expected.
Everyone has the right
to execute a traitor.
Yangzhou is the bread basket of the country.
It's too critical to be lost.
In the current situation,
even if you take the whole Yangzhou
into your control,
it'll be seen as a justifiable
and patriotic act.
By the time Lord Liang is brought to justice,
every state will have been weakened by the conflicts.
By then,
whoever takes over the Eastern Capital
will have to
welcome you into the new court.
Mr. Luo.
You have a remarkable mind.
It's my honor to have your advice.
Go back now.
It's been long since you came out.
They may be worried.
Mother.
Have a good rest after going back.
Wait for my news.
One more thing.
Tomorrow is your birthday.
I planned to ask Yun
to send it to you,
but since I met you today,
I'll give it to you myself.
Mother, you embroidered this again.
This pattern
must have taken you lots of time.
I told you so many times
not to embroider these things.
You never listened.
Will they celebrate your birthday tomorrow?
We're about
to leave Yangzhou soon.
There are so many things
waiting to be done.
My birthday is not important.
No one will remember.
Right.
I just think that Jiusi cares for you
and may remember it.
The result of the Provincial Examination will be out tomorrow.
He's too busy
worrying about himself
to remember my birthday.
It's okay.
Birthdays
don't matter much to me.
It's enough that you remember it.
So far.
Come on. Do it again.
Great!
I'll give it a shot too.
You threw it very far too.
Right?
Wait.
This stone is so beautiful.
It surely is.
Could it be a gem?
It must be a gem.
Let's go
hide it in the secret spot.
Okay. Let's hide it there
and tell no one about it.
-Let's go.
Hurry. No one's here.
Hurry up.
That's where I hide my treasures.
Keep it between us.
There are many pretty stones in my pond.
I'll pick them out
and give them to you.
Okay.
But I'm leaving tomorrow.
Y-You're leaving?
Where are you going?
I'm going home with my mother.
I live in Yangzhou.
Will you forget me after you leave?
I'll come back to visit my grandpa again.
But maybe it'll be years
before you come again.
Then tell me
your name.
If I know your name,
I won't forget you.
I really can't tell you.
Well,
with those colorful stones as reminders,
you'll remember me forever, right?
Then I'll go collect them today.
Tomorrow morning,
let's meet here again.
I'll give you all the pretty stones.
Would you like that?
Yes. It's a deal.
Deal.
I'll be here tomorrow.
Pinky swear.
Master,
100,000 boxes of fireworks are ready.
They can be ignited at a moment's notice.
Where is she?
Master?
Liu Yuru.
Where
is she?
Happy birthday, Fairy Yuru.
[Happy Birthday]
Wish you happiness and longevity.
Yinhong.
What's wrong with you?
Why did you join them
to make such a fuss?
We're not making a fuss.
According to Young Master,
we're having a celebration
to give you all our best wishes.
Exactly.
No one mentioned anything about it
because we want to surprise you
and make you happy.
You want to make me happy?
You just want to embarrass me!
Put it down, everyone.
Drop the act.
You're elated inside, aren't you?
Let's do it again!
Happy birthday, Fairy Yuru.
Wish you happiness and longevity.
Yuru.
Mother.
Save the etiquette.
Today is your birthday.
You deserve more respect than anyone else.
I've told the stores
to put everything aside today.
Don't worry about anything.
Just have a good time
celebrating your birthday.
Thank you, Mother.
Here.
This is your birthday gift.
Mother, as your daughter,
I haven't given you and Father any gift.
How can I take a gift from you?
We want to give you a gift.
Just take it.
This old man is loaded.
Don't be shy.
Take a look. Do you like it?
Take a look.
Yinhong.
What a heavy gift.
Thank you, Father, Mother.
You're welcome.
We're glad that you like it.
Yes.
We've been so busy recently
and today the result
of the Provincial Examination will…
Today is your birthday.
How would you like to celebrate it?
How to celebrate it?
How did you celebrate it in the past?
In the past,
my mother
arranged everything for me.
It was lots of fun too.
How about this?
I'll take care of everything this year.
I promise you'll have a great day.
The kitchen has been preparing
for the birthday banquet since two days ago.
Where are you taking her?
Just eating is so boring.
I'll take her out for some fun.
To where?
You love watching
cock fights and dog races,
but Yuru may find them too uncouth.
You're right, old man.
I'm taking her to watch cock fights and dog races.
You're messing around again.
Yuru is an elegant lady.
Unlike you,
she can't fool around
and draw attention wherever she goes.
But when she replenished stocks,
kept accounts, and talked business,
she's already received lots of attention.
Aren't you the same?
That's for business.
Business is serious.
They're different!
What's the difference?
Remember our family motto?
Women are equal to men.
Women should be allowed
to do things that men do.
Are you saying that the women in our family
can only work hard to make money
and can't go out for fun?
Is it fair?
He's insane.
I want to take you out for fun.
Do you want to go?
I…
It's her birthday.
She has the final say.
Come back, you brat!
He's misbehaving again.
Why didn't you stop him?
It makes sense.
What makes sense?
Why is it that the women in this family
can only go out to make money
but not for fun?
When I have my birthday next year,
you have to take me out
for fun too.
Why are you…
I knew I couldn't count on you.
I'll go by myself next year.
No.
I'll go tomorrow.
Rou.
I didn't say you can't go.
[Gu Mansion]
Good morning, Mrs. Gu.
Mrs. Gu,
happy birthday!
I've told you how to address her!
Call her Second Brother!
What's the point
of calling her that?
We're not fools.
We've been
your brothers for so many years,
but you never treated us like this.
Why have you
never gone through so much trouble
to celebrate our birthdays?
Get lost.
We'll wait for you.
So much for our friendship.
They're just jealous.
Let's go.
Let's go to the Examination Hall first.
The Examination Hall?
Why?
To check the ranking, of course.
It's too early.
No.
The result will be out at seven.
If we go late, we won't be able to get to the front
to see the ranking clearly.
We agreed
to watch cock fights first.
You meant it?
Of course. Let's go.
Go get him! Come on!
Go. Go. Go.
Place our bets
on that Black Wind.
Black Wind.
No, no. On General Danding.
On the General.
Wait.
Let me think about it.
Hurry up.
They'll take no more bets soon.
General Danding.
General Danding?
You've made up your mind?
Black Wind.
No take backs.
I'm placing the bets now.
Wait. Give me one more second.
What if we lose?
Trust me. We won't lose.
Hurry up.
General Danding it is!
General Danding.
General Danding!
Black Wind!
General, hit him!
Beat him up! Hurry!
I don't dare to look.
Beat him!
Beat him up!
How's it? How's it?
See for yourself.
Beat him, General!
Yes. Beat him hard!
Get him!
They're fighting!
Beat him up!
We won!
We won! We won!
Mrs. Gu.
Young Madam, here are your winnings.
Why are they double?
General Danding
is Mr. Gu's cock.
If he wins, you'll get a bonus.
Therefore, the winnings are double.
Alright. Put them away.
Here.
Fortunately, General Danding
is yours.
Black Wind
was very fierce.
is his cock too.
No wonder you said we wouldn't lose.
They're both your cocks.
He splashed out
on all the best cocks here.
Jiusi, if you play this way,
you'll always be the winner.
Do you still find the games fun?
Of course.
I love winning.
Mr. Gu,
your General Danding,
Black Wind,
Marshal Jin, and Lan Caihe
won a total of
472 taels of silver this month.
Later, the manager
will seal the money
and send it to your mansion.
I'll keep the streamer.
It's auspicious.
Today is my wife's birthday.
Use the money
to buy yourselves a celebratory drink!
Thank you, Mr. Gu.
Happy birthday, Young Madam Gu.
Wish you happiness and longevity.
One more time.
Happy birthday, Young Madam Gu.
Wish you happiness and longevity.
Are you happy?
Yes.
Yinhong said you liked playing with little animals
when you were a kid
and were good at climbing walls.
That's not true.
Yinhong.
Why did you tell him everything?
It's not a big deal.
It looks good on you.
You bought out half the shops on the street.
Where are we going next?
Stop complaining.
I'll celebrate
your birthdays too.
Munan.
Send my friends home.
I…
I didn't know we were still friends to him.
Let's go.
Yinhong.
Yuru.
What else do you want to do?
I've had a wish for years,
but it was never fulfilled.
What's it?
I want to learn to ride a horse.
When I was young,
I envied boys who could ride.
That's easy.
Come up.
What are you doing?
I'll take you to ride.
Come on up.
Let's go riding.
Tighten your legs.
Lean forward.
No, no, no.
It's so wobbly.
I'm scared.
Let me tell you something.
It'll become steady
when the horse runs.
Should I make the horse run?
No, no, no.
I-I want to come down.
You asked to learn to ride.
I don't want to learn it now.
Help me dismount.
Try again.
Now, get me down.
Okay.
You…
Hold the horse steady before getting me down.
I didn't expect to see Boss Liu
so scared by riding.
You'll be laughed at if word gets out.
No one will laugh at me.
Only you saw it.
Actually, you're almost there.
You just need more practice.
We'll see. It's too scary.
You promised
to ride and sing with me.
You can't go back on your word.
I will keep my word.
I'm just taking a break.
I'll definitely master it in the future.
Unfortunately, your birthday is only one day.
It's too short.
There are lots of interesting things
I haven't shown you yet.
Then let's save them
for my next birthday,
shall we?
Why next birthday?
I'll show you tomorrow.
No.
I want to
save them for my next birthday.
Gu Jiusi.
Will we
celebrate my next birthday too?
Are you a fool?
Your every birthday
will be celebrated.
What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
No one
celebrated my birthday like this before.
But you said
your mother arranged everything for you every year
and you had lots of fun.
I lied.
When I was still a maiden,
only my mother
remembered my birthday.
Every year, she made a bowl of noodles
with an egg for me.
That was all I got for my birthday.
I was fine with that,
but you made me so happy this year.
I'm afraid
I won't settle for just a bowl of noodles in the future.
Don't think too much.
In the future,
we'll celebrate your every birthday.
I'll take care of everything
and make you happier every year.
We'll celebrate it in different ways.
I give you my word.
♫I forgot the things in the world all of a sudden♫
♫Everyone thinks life is like a dream♫
♫I looked back inadvertently♫
♫A stranger impressed me♫
♫We've been with each other for another day♫
♫Another spring and autumn came♫
♫Who will deliver letters to me?♫
♫I'm listening to you♫
♫I forgot the things in the world all of a sudden♫
♫Everyone thinks life is like a dream♫
♫How much do I miss you?♫
♫I've seen you here before♫
♫One night, we sat together to write poems and drink alcohol♫
♫Another spring and autumn came♫
♫I saw the sun, the moon, and the stars outside the window♫
♫The wind blows and the moon sways. My heart is beating♫
♫I forgot the things in the world all of a sudden♫
♫Everyone thinks life is like a dream♫
♫How much do I miss you?♫
♫I've seen you here before♫
Jiusi.
♫One night, we sat together to write poems and drink alcohol♫
Did you prepare that too?
♫Another spring and autumn came♫
Well…
♫I saw the sun, the moon, and the stars outside the window♫
No.
Who's doing that?
♫The wind blows and the moon sways. My heart is beating♫
So vulgar.
I can afford fireworks too.
Our fireworks are better.
Let's keep playing.
Let's go.
Move! Move!
Move!
Get out of the way!
[Gu Mansion]
Take this too.
Get it loaded
and take it with us.
Yes.
Also,
bring enough Yangzhou's soil with us.
I'm afraid these plants won't survive
after we arrive in Youzhou.
Yes.
My lord.
Let's go to bed now.
Arrange these things tomorrow.
We've gotten enough time.
We're leaving soon.
I feel uneasy.
We've been very careful
in the past few months.
Yuru is meticulous.
From applying for the pass, loading the boat, to sending scouts out,
she arranged different people
for different tasks.
No one knows about our plan.
Hasn't that brat come back?
It's so late now.
Yuru is with him. Nothing will happen.
We'll spend lots of time on the ship.
Traveling by ship is tiring.
Let's go to bed now.
Master, Madam.
Bad news.
Wang Rong is coming this way
with troops.
So the Wang family has heard about it.
They won't go easy on us this time.
We have to leave tonight.
I'll stall them.
You'll take the others
to the dock through the secret tunnel.
If I don't meet you
in two hours, you'll sail.
We can't leave you behind.
You'll head out of Huainan
and wait for me at Moon Dock.
Don't worry.
I'll go meet you there by road.
You…
Trust me.
[Gu Mansion]
Know the score here
and get out of my way.
Otherwise, I won't ask so nicely again.
Mr. Wang.
What a surprise.
Gu Langhua,
plead guilty now!
In years of doing business,
the Gu family has always abided by the law
and never evaded our taxes.
What am I guilty of?
Stop playing dumb.
Lord Liang colluded with Jiang He
to plot a mutiny!
The Gu family
delivered military supplies for them secretly,
which made you traitors too!
Treason
is a very serious offense.
Do you have evidence?
Evidence?
I'll find some
after searching your house.
I dare you!
Gu Langhua!
I was ordered by the commissioner
to search for evidence.
You wouldn't let me
because you feel guilty!
Do I look guilty?
Mr. Wang.
The unspoken ambition
of the Wang family
is no longer a secret.
In Yangzhou,
you amassed ill-gotten gains and imposed unjust taxes.
You covet our wealth
and use the demotion of my brother-in-law
as an excuse to rob us
in the name of the court!
How dare you!
Mr. Wang,
there's no need to posture and yell.
You're too young
to accuse anyone
of treason.
Get your father here.
I'll wait for him here.
I won't budge an inch.
Madam.
The carriages are ready.
Good. Go tell all the managers
to hurry to the dock
with their families.
Find Ship Xuan 3 of the Cao Sect
and tell the crew they're there to ship Mr. Jiang's jewelry.
They'll let them on board.
Understood.
Let's go.
Send a carriage to the Liu family
to pick up Yuru's mother.
Hurry.
The rest of you, follow me.
[Liu Mansion]
Don't let anyone escape.
Don't be afraid.
Search!
Officer! Officer!
Officer!
Officer.
Go. Go. Go.
Go.
Eldest Madam.
You have a way out, don't you?
I beg you.
Please help us.
I know
I was very mean to you.
But now,
for the sake of the children,
I beg you
to take us with you.
Eldest Mother, please help us.
Please.
Eldest Madam.
-Please.
-Please, Eldest Mother.
Okay.
Let's leave together.
Thank you, Eldest Madam.
After them!
Hurry up!
Move, move, move!
Yun, leave with us.
Come on!
Yun, leave with us!
Yun.
Go, go.
Yun, leave with us!
Eldest Madam, go!
Go!
Yun! Yun!
Let's go. Hurry.
Is everyone here?
Yes.
Everyone, come with me!
Grandmother!
Grandmother, what's going on?
Has something bad
happened to us?
Go back now.
No matter what happens,
don't leave your room!
As long as I'm still part of the Ye family,
nothing will happen!
Let's go!
Grandmother.
All right. My birthday is over now.
Let's go check the ranking.
Fine.
I can't escape this moment any longer.
Let's go.
Jiusi.
-Jiusi.
Mrs. Gu.
We need to borrow Jiusi for a sec.
Come.
Just a sec.
What's wrong with you guys?
Your house is surrounded
by Wang Rong's men.
What a scumbag!
I have to go back now.
Chen Xun.
Stay here with Yuru.
Don't let her get suspicious.
If I
don't come back in two hours,
take her
to hide in your place.
Wenchang,
go home now
and leave Yangzhou with your family.
The sooner the better.
Is it that serious?
There'll be chaos in Yangzhou.
After Wang Shanquan deals with the Gu family,
other aristocrats and rich merchants
will be next.
As my close friends,
you two will definitely be watched.
Chen Xun's father is a scholar
and you live outside Yangzhou.
You may be safe for now.
But your family does business too.
They won't let you go.
Do as I say.
No matter how powerful
Wang Shanquan is,
he has to abide by the law.
If Darong is thrown into chaos,
there will be no law.
Do you mean…
Enough. We have no time for this.
When the dust settles,
we'll drink together again.
Deal.
You owe us
a dinner at Cuiming Restaurant.
Sure.
You can drink as much Jolly Spring as you want.
Yang Wenchang got into trouble again.
I need to help him settle it.
Chen Xun will stay here with you.
After I come back,
we'll check the ranking together.
Wenchang.
Chen Xun.
What did Wenchang do?
Why are they in such a hurry?
Yang Wenchang…
Boss Liu.
My master wants to see you.
Mrs. Gu.
Who is he?
I made business with his master.
Please tell Mr. Luo
that I'm busy today
and we shall talk business
another day.
You may read the letter first.
Chen Xun.
Something urgent happened
in business.
When Jiusi comes back,
tell him
not to worry about me.
I'll be back soon.
Mrs. Gu.
It's so late now.
You can't go alone.
I'll go with you.
No need.
Some business secrets
may be involved.
You'd better not come.
I often
go out alone for business.
Jiusi knows it.
Don't worry.
Let's go.
Mrs. Gu.
Stay safe.
Before tonight,
375 ships have left Yangzhou
from Changfeng Dock.
The whole Gu family
is relocating
but no one knows about it.
You did a great job, Boss Liu.
But now that I found out about it,
I can't let you go
without saying goodbye.
How did he know?
He even knows
how many ships we used.
Has he
been watching the Gu family?
What's his purpose?
Is he going to
ask for hush money?
Boss Liu.
We'll reach the shore soon.
Master.
Yes.
Boss Liu.
Please.
The fireworks in Yangzhou
are my birthday gift for you.
It's so kind of you, Mr. Luo.
It's too generous a gift.
I can't accept it.
Mr. Luo,
just tell me what you want.
I just landed a deal
and feel very happy,
so I invited you here for a talk.
I'll leave Yangzhou
for another deal soon.
Have a nice trip, Mr. Luo.
You're a mysterious man,
but I never probe into things
that are not my business.
I hope you can do the same.
Stay out of the matters
that have nothing to do with you.
Life is unpredictable.
We may need each other's help in the future.
Boss Liu,
would you leave Yangzhou
with me?
You're talented and resourceful.
Staying with Gu Jiusi
is a waste of your acumen.
It's a great pity.
Mr. Luo,
I respect you.
Please deserve my respect.
I respect you too
and never take you
as a woman
who only knows about housework.
I asked you to leave with me
because I cherish your talents.
So don't get me wrong.
If you work with me,
sooner or later,
you'll become a great success.
Mr. Luo,
I run the Gu Business
as the Young Madam of the Gu family
and Gu Jiusi's wife.
I don't know you personally.
I'll forget what you said tonight.
Yangzhou is in chaos now.
Don't be afraid.
Leave with me.
You're just
an innocent person dragged down by the Gu family.
You don't deserve
to die like this.
I've told you this before.
I'll never betray the Gu family,
let alone Gu Jiusi!
But after tonight,
Gu Jiusi
will no longer live in this world!
Young Madam.
Where is Jiusi?
Young Master asked you to go to the dock.
Quick!
Has Jiusi gotten on board?
Let's go.
[Guazhou Dock]
Madam.
Coming.
The soldiers are headed to Changfeng Dock.
Guazhou Dock was poorly guarded.
All the guards have been taken down.
Good.
You may leave.
Yes.
We usually
exchange goods at Changfeng Dock
but are now leaving
from Guazhou Dock.
You're so clever, Madam.
Yeah.
This is the last smoke screen.
It's Yuru's idea.
Young Madam.
Madam, Young Madam is here.
Mother! Mother!
Yuru.
-Young Madam.
Mother.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Good.
Where is my mother?