[English subtitles are available]
[Destined]
[Episode 33]
To be brave enough to accept punishment
and seek justice for your husband,
I can see that
you are righteous
and won't stop
your husband from improving.
I'm sure
there won't be any conflicts
when you spend your days with my child in the future.
My child and Deputy Minister Gu
have an engagement.
I was thinking of
fulfilling this marriage
and allow you to divorce.
But my son pleaded for you.
He said that you and Deputy Minister Gu
have been through thick and thin together
and you are willing to be a commoner's wife.
So I agreed.
Thank Her Majesty.
Your Majesty,
I refuse.
How dare you!
I dare not
lie to Your Majesty about my feelings.
Gu Jiusi
is my husband.
I
am unwilling to share him with anyone.
How dare you say such ridiculous words
and talk back to the Majesty?
Fine.
Just continue kneeling here
and come to your senses.
Liu Yuru.
Do you think putting on an act here
can prove that
your relationship with Brother Jiusi is
tougher than gold
and can stop this marriage?
I thought
you were a smart woman.
you were a great pillar of support for Brother Jiusi.
I didn't expect
you to be so stupid.
Do you know
you are the only obstacle
between Gu Jiusi and
his bright future?
Your Highness is a noble lady.
You have the Empress Dowager's help.
If Jiusi becomes a consort,
it is his blessing.
In the future,
in the court,
it will be a smooth road for him too.
But I just refuse.
Gu Jiusi
is my husband.
And the man I love.
I have him in my heart.
I also wish that in Gu Jiusi's heart,
by him,
will always be
just me, Liu Yuru.
You...
How ungrateful!
Whoever wants to marry Gu Jiusi
will have to step over
my life.
I'll grant your wish.
Mother, save me!
Mother!
How dare you, Gu Jiusi!
How dare you wield a sword at someone above you
in the palace?
Do you want
our lives?
Empress Dowager.
You have achieved your goal.
You can target me,
but please let Yuru go.
Fine.
I promise you.
[Loyalty and righteousness]
Guards!
Imprison Gu Jiusi!
-Yes.
Jiusi!
Take care of yourself.
Go!
Jiusi!
Your Majesty!
[Changgeng Palace]
Your Majesty.
Lady Liu, a commoner,
talked back to me and I can let that slide.
But a mere Deputy Minister
broke into my palace
and wanted to kill me.
Your Majesty,
you misunderstood.
Actually Gu Jiusi...
He already had his sword
pointing at my throat.
If the guards hadn't stopped him,
I would have
already died.
Your Majesty.
I know.
Gu Jiusi
is your favorite subject.
But I was alone with my child
when I opened the city
and presented Darong
to Your Majesty.
From then on,
the world became Da Xia's.
The only hope I have
is to get His Majesty's protection.
So that I can spend the rest
of my life in peace.
Can't you fulfill such
a humble wish?
Your Majesty,
you're exaggerating.
When I ascended the throne,
I promised you and your daughter
that I will give you
infinite glory and wealth.
I am a man of my words.
I have already
put Gu Jiusi in jail.
He has suffered a lot
in that prison.
I am very grateful that Your Majesty remembers
the promise you have made.
But
I was scared to death.
If Gu Jiusi is not
executed,
I
will never have peace.
I will live in perpetual fear
that I will die sooner or later.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
if anything happens to you,
what would people think of His Majesty?
Please take care of your health
and just forgive this mere subject.
Your Majesty...
Fine.
Since you are so afraid
of Gu Jiusi,
then I shall...
I...
I shall just exile him from the Eastern Capital.
Your Majesty.
Between Gu Jiusi and I,
only one can be alive.
If Your Majesty decides
to let Gu Jiusi live,
I will go back today
and hang myself to death with a white ribbon
so that Your Majesty won't have to be so conflicted.
Your Majesty!
What are you standing around for?
Stop her!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty!
Is he stupid?
He finally escaped from danger
yet caused such a disaster again.
Do you know Her Majesty
is seeking death now?
Those old ministers of the previous dynasty
are also on her side.
Everyone is very agitated,
asking me
to execute Gu Jiusi.
Your Majesty...
Please approve what I have requested
just now.
Have you made up your mind?
Your Majesty,
my husband worked his way to the court
all because of me.
I should be the one
to take all the blame.
For the sake of my husband's
contributions to the court,
please grant my request
and exempt my husband from execution.
You lass...
Wang Hong.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Go get a cup of poisonous wine.
Your Majesty.
♫Tear stains on the letter♫
How long will it take...
♫The blurred contour of your face♫
For the poison of this wine to take place?
♫Looking into your smiling eyes♫
♫I lose track of time♫
About an hour.
♫The sound of snow falling♫
Will it look ugly...
♫The beacon fire on the vast desert♫
when I die?
♫Don't get lost on your way back♫
♫If by some twist of fate♫
♫We'll part ways in the end♫
No.
♫Remember you'll always be missed♫
That's good.
♫The world is so big♫
That's a relief.
♫You're my sun and moon♫
♫Lighting my way through the dark♫
♫How can I forget you♫
♫Forget us, and forget the days we spent together?♫
♫How can I move on as if you were never in my life?♫
♫I miss you♫
♫I still love you♫
♫But I can't hold you in my arms again♫
♫I reach out but only feel the wind between my fingers♫
Your Majesty.
♫When the wind picks up and the moon shines♫
♫I see you everywhere and nowhere♫
♫Memories of you flood back to me♫
Please allow me...
♫If I still love you the same♫
To let me meet
Jiusi.
♫Will we meet again in my dreams?♫
♫Will it be like the first time we met?♫
I want to
speak to him.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Jiusi...
Why are you so stupid?
How could you wield a sword at the palace?
Jiusi...
I made you suffer.
Do you like me very much?
You like me so much that you don't even want your life?
Jiusi...
From now on,
like me less, okay?
Okay?
[In loving memory of the late wife Liu Yuru]
Your Ladyship,
take a rest.
You haven't slept all night.
Go visit Mother-in-law.
She passed out
after hearing the news last night.
Didn't the doctor say
this shocking news
might threaten her health?
[White clouds to one's liking]
Sister Jiang.
Sister Jiang?
Sister Su.
Why are you up?
Go back and rest.
I'm here.
I can't lie down.
Isn't Yuru
returning soon?
I need to make some preserved fruits for her.
She
has liked sweets since she was a child.
I'm worried that her teeth might rot.
So I have to
make these preserved fruits for her personally.
So I can rest assured.
Yinhong,
why are you crying?
Are you missing Yuru?
She's returning soon.
Let's go.
Go pick more fruits with me.
[White clouds to one's liking]
Yuru.
Yuru!
Yuru! Where are you?
Yuru?
[In loving memory of the late wife Liu Yuru]
Yuru!
My child...
Wake up and take a look.
Look what happened to your mother.
How could you bear to
leave us like this?
Madam!
Hurry! Call the doctor!
Madam.
[In Mourning]
Yun'er.
Did I do something wrong?
I obeyed the Ye family's teachings firmly
and acknowledged His Majesty
as a wise founding ruler over the world.
I acknowledged Gu Jiusi
as a virtuous minister who can help govern country.
I followed them closely
without a doubt.
But what did I get in return?
Luo Zishang, the treacherous official,
stirred up trouble in court.
Yuru was wronged and died.
The situation is bleak.
When can we see the light again?
Young Master.
You're back.
[Memorial Tablet of the Late Wife, Liu Yuru]
Go and see
what you've done.
She drank the poisoned wine
to take the fall for you.
You told me
you would protect her forever.
That's why I
entrusted her to you.
But what have you done?
Do you deserve to be her husband?
Brother.
It's not all his fault.
I will kill that Empress Dowager
to avenge my Eldest Sister!
That's a crime serious enough to get your whole clan executed.
I, Shen Mingchi, am all alone in this world!
What family is there to speak of?
My sister was my only family.
I don't care about my life!
Step aside!
What about her?
You don't have to care.
What about her mother
and her family?
She chose to die
so that
we could live safely,
not for you
to act like a reckless brute.
[In Mourning]
♫It's like a dream♫
♫Feelings of lovesickness♫
[Correct and Clear the Origins]
♫Love once begun, will never end♫
♫Spring breeze passing by♫
♫Like the smile of youth on your face♫
♫Drops of lovesickness immersed in days and nights♫
♫Nowhere to be found♫
♫You once said I'm heartless♫
♫I didn't know I wouldn't stop missing you♫
♫Love once begun, will never end♫
♫Follow you everywhere you go♫
♫Days and nights, I can't help myself♫
♫What is love and what is anticipation♫
♫Our hearts collide♫
♫If only one person understands the hopes I wouldn't give up♫
♫You are the one I hold on to♫
♫If only one person can get me through the storm♫
♫You're the home I come back to♫
♫If only one person can protect me through the long nights♫
♫You're the peace of my life♫
♫Hoping the hands that I'm holding tight are yours♫
Young Master.
Young Madam left this for you.
♫If I can make a wish, I hope we can be like this for the rest of our lives♫
[A Godsent Marriage]
♫You once said I'm heartless♫
♫I didn't know I couldn't stop missing you♫
♫Love once begun, will never end♫
♫Follow you everywhere you go♫
♫Days and nights, I can't help myself♫
♫What is love and what is anticipation♫
♫Our hearts collide♫
Jiusi.
I love your dignified character
♫If only one person understands the hopes I wouldn't give up♫
and your sincerity.
I know
♫You are the one I hold on to♫
the person I love
can't stand by and watch
♫If only one person can get me through the storm♫
as the people suffer,
and do nothing.
♫You're the home I come back to♫
You want to become a grand tree.
♫If only one person can protect me through the long nights♫
Just like what you promised me,
you want to protect those you want to protect.
♫You're the peace of my life♫
Jiusi,
♫Hoping the hands that I'm holding tight are yours♫
thank you for giving me
a new beginning,
and a real,
tumultuous,
and uninhibited new life.
We didn't manage
to complete this lifetime together.
We'll continue
in our next lifetime.
Promise me.
Don't be silly.
♫If only one person understands the hopes I wouldn't give up♫
Keep living.
♫You are the one I hold on to♫
♫If only one person can get me through the storm♫
♫You're the home I come back to♫
♫If only one person can protect me through the long nights♫
♫You're the peace of my life♫
♫Hoping the hands that I'm holding tight are yours♫
♫If I can make a wish, I hope we can be like this for the rest of our lives♫
By the Heavens' will,
the Emperor speaks.
The way of governance
is to be cautious.
Now,
Gu Jiusi, Deputy Minister of Revenue,
has been lax in disciplining his family
and transgressed the honor of the Emperor.
Considering his previous achievements,
his family will not be implicated.
He will only be removed from his position in the six ministries
and demoted 600 li
to the position of the Waterways Supervisor of Yongzhou,
and placed in charge of hydraulic engineering of the Yellow River.
He shall depart today.
Such has the Emperor decreed.
Jiusi.
Accept the decree.
Your official
accepts the decree.
Third Sister.
I've come to see you.
It's my fault.
I failed to protect you and Jiusi.
Don't worry.
In the future,
I will definitely protect Jiusi
as a consolation to your spirit.
Brother Zhou.
Jiusi is a meritorious official of Da Xia.
Even if he did something wrong,
my eldest sister has atoned for it with her death.
Why did His Majesty still
demote him from the Eastern Capital?
And why a place like Yongzhou?
Have you asked His Majesty?
Brother,
I know
you just suffered the pain of the loss of your wife,
and you were just demoted to such a poor place.
It's natural to be depressed.
After finding out Yuru had passed away,
I couldn't sleep all night.
I was devastated.
But there are some things
that must be said by me.
Now,
the Yellow River is the most pressing issue at hand.
This year, both Qingzhou and Yongzhou,
which are situated along the coast of the Yellow River,
had no harvest.
The population was displaced.
Many people
became beggars,
roving bandits,
and rebels.
Some people even...
some people even exchanged their children for food.
If this continues on,
Da Xia is doomed to follow the footsteps of the previous dynasty.
The people will definitely
be plunged into the abyss of misery.
Brother,
His Majesty sent you over
because he recognizes your abilities.
He didn't ask you to become the Directorate of Waterways
to punish you,
but he wants to entrust the whole Yellow River
to you.
Please tell His Majesty
I will definitely repair the Yellow River.
Before you leave,
His Majesty wants to see you.
Some words are more appropriate
for you to tell him in person.
[Memorial Tablet of the late Liu Yuru]
Demoted to Yongzhou
for such a serious crime?
[To be benevolent and honorable]
His Majesty is willing to
take it so easily on Gu Jiusi.
Isn't that being too biased?
Mrs. Gu has died as a scapegoat.
Empress Dowager,
you should
spare him where you can.
I'm just worried that
if the court is not in order, it will damage your reputation.
That will also be a disgrace to you, Your Majesty.
My dignity is secondary.
The people that are most hurt by the matter of Gu Jiusi
are the Empress Dowager
and Princess Yunchang.
You have previously said that
I will have the final say
in the Princess' matters.
These few days, I have been considering
the marriage alliance
that was raised by the Northern Liang's emissary.
Your Majesty.
Empress Dowager,
the matter of Gu Jiusi
is just a small issue when compared to
the safety and security of our borders.
Empress Dowager, you are an understanding person
who cares about the world.
Why don't you first
discuss about the marriage alliance with the Northern Liang
with me?
[All-embracing Walls for Worldly Matters]
Your Majesty,
you must take care of yourself.
How is Gu Jiusi?
It seems that...
He is lucky that he has the company of two young generals,
Zhou Ye and Shen Ming.
Those two
are good kids.
Have you told Gu Jiusi that
I want to see him
before he leaves?
Well...
General Zhou
has sent the message.
But...
Tell me the truth.
Gu Jiusi said
he is unsure exactly who wants to see him.
If it's the Emperor's son,
then...
he is just a sinner
who is undeserving of any honor.
If it was
Commissioner Fan of Youzhou back then,
he asks for your understanding
for he is unwilling to meet anyone
as he mourns the death of his new wife.
If the Commissioner were to be angry about this,
then there is nothing he can do about it.
Calm down, Your Majesty.
What's there to be angry about?
In terms of playing with words,
if Gu Jiusi ranks second
in Da Xia,
no one dares to be the first.
Then
I'll go invite him again tomorrow.
No need.
He's upset at me now.
It's better not to meet.
It's getting late.
You may leave.
Tomorrow morning,
ask Zhou Gaolang to come see me.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Master.
Why?
When I used her as a bargaining chip,
I should have known
she would lose her life.
I knew she was stubborn.
I thought I could
keep myself from
sympathizing with her ever again.
But why does it still hurt
now that she's really dead?
Liu Yuru.
You've been smart your whole life.
But why are you always
so stupid
when it comes to Gu Jiusi?
I set this up
[Fragrant Lanzhi]
to get rid of Gu Jiusi.
Not you.
Master,
should we kill Gu Jiusi
on his way to his new post?
No need.
Yongzhou is my territory.
When Gu Jiusi reaches,
his
every move
will be under my control.
I can easily do away with him
anytime I wish.
But for now,
I want him to live a little longer.
I want his heart to be in piercing pain everyday.
I want him to wish he were dead.
I want him to rot in Yongzhou
and become a good-for-nothing.
Become a good-for-nothing.
Zhou,
you don't want to even
talk to me now?
I dare not.
I just
don't know
what to say to Your Majesty.
Fine.
I don't want to hear it either.
Go.
Your Majesty.
I don't understand.
The Crown Prince was the one who committed a serious crime.
Yet Gu Jiusi was the one
exiled to Yongzhou.
Gu Jiusi is a rare talent.
That's not true.
This is just a plan
I had devised
and have yet to discuss with you about.
Only because the Empress Dowager was being stubborn
and forced me to make a choice.
I had no choice
so I could only think of a win-win situation.
So,
I had to sacrifice Liu Yuru
to pacify the Empress Dowager
and save Gu Jiusi.
Only by asking him to be away from this chaos
can I keep him alive.
This was also
a suggestion of his earlier on.
Now,
although he is resenting me,
it doesn't matter anymore.
When I'm gone,
Yu'er will ascend the throne.
By then, he will still be an important subject
by Yu'er's side.