[English subtitles are available]
[Destined]
[Episode 25]
I'm here to save you.
Let me help you put it on.
Did Sister Yuru send you here?
Yes.
What?
Are you hurt?
This is not my blood.
It's Wang Shanquan's blood.
I killed him.
Impressive.
My sworn sister's sister
is indeed extraordinary.
Don't be afraid.
The first time killing people
is like this.
It's normal that you're not used to it.
Wipe that bad guy's blood,
and you'll be fine.
Let's go.
My sworn sister is waiting.
Young Master Luo.
You're finally back.
I knew it.
Father shouldn't
have quarreled with you
and driven you away.
Now, Father is gone.
However, Young Master Luo,
you can help me.
We can share Yangzhou.
Young Master Luo.
I'm different from my father.
I'm also very different
from my other brothers.
You know, Young Master,
I'm the commander of Yangzhou.
I'm in sole charge of
Yangzhou.
Young Master Luo.
I'll definitely treat you
as my welcomed guest.
Go spread the word.
Commissioner Wang Shanquan's
third son, Wang Ai,
maintained an army and defied orders from the central government,
and intended to rebel like Lord Liang.
He has been executed.
The one who killed the rebel
is Luo Zishang.
Yes.
What's wrong?
It's Luo Zishang.
When did he return to Yangzhou?
And when did he appear at the dock?
It looks like
he's seeing us off.
Boss Liu.
Thank you for your help.
See you.
My Lady.
Have a bite.
Put it down.
Ever since you heard the news from Yangzhou,
you haven't eaten anything
or slept.
You've been sitting here all night long.
If your condition gets worse,
when Young Madam comes back,
she'll blame me.
My Lady.
The more serious the situation is,
the more you should take care of yourself.
This...
This will be for the good of them.
Yuru and Jiusi
made a written pledge
in order to save the Gu family.
Today is the last day.
If Yuru
couldn't make it back,
I'll definitely
go
with them.
My Lady!
Ruixue.
You're a good girl.
You never left,
even though the Gu family had ups and downs.
If this fatal calamity
really happens to us,
just leave.
I've prepared the travel expenses
for you.
My Lady.
Don't say that.
Heaven will help a good person like Young Madam.
She will be fine.
You will be safe too, My Lady.
If...
If it should happen,
no matter where you go, My Lady,
I will be with you
and take care of you.
♫I implore the moon to be bright and the wind to be gentle♫
♫Lightly shine on my beloved♫
♫Listen gently to my vision and your willingness♫
♫Grow old quietly♫
Yuru.
Mother.
You're finally back.
All is well now that you're back.
Madam Yue.
Yuru.
You're back.
How have you been, Madam Yue?
Can you sleep
at night?
I'm okay.
Not bad.
Yuru.
I've been worried about your safety.
I've cut out meat and prayed for you every day.
It's great that you're back.
I'll go burn incense and thank the gods for answering my prayers.
No need.
Someone wants to see you.
Who is it?
Yinhong.
Let's go.
Help!
Eldest Madam!
Help me, Zhao!
Zhao, help me!
Mother, save Eldest...
Help me, Zhao!
Eldest Madam, take my hand.
Zhao!
Get Yuzhao back.
Take care of yourself!
Let's go!
Zhao!
-Let's go!/N-Eldest Madam!
Eldest Madam!
Zhao!
Let's go!
Eldest Madam.
Can I
have a few words with you alone?
You gave up on a dying woman.
It's no different from killing her.
We have nothing to say to you.
Save your words for the court.
Zhang Yue'er.
I will interrogate you personally.
Although you don't deserve to die,
exile and servitude
will be inevitable.
Eldest Madam.
I'm begging you.
For the sake of
us both being mothers,
give me a chance.
I'll just say a few words.
Just a few words.
Let me finish,
and I'll be willing to die.
Just say it here.
Eldest Madam.
I know that
I deserve to die.
I made many mistakes.
But no matter how bad I am,
my heart for my children
is the same as yours.
Yuzhao, Yuying, and Yumao.
These three children
were brought up
solely by me.
Maybe for them,
having a mother like me
is the most unfortunate thing
that could happen in their life.
But from today on,
even a mother like this
won't be there for them anymore.
Eldest Madam.
You are kind-hearted.
I beg you.
Please take them in
and take care of them.
From now on,
you'll be their real mother.
Consider me dead.
No.
Just take it as
I've never existed in this world.
OK?
OK.
I promise I'll take care of the three of them.
But it's not because you begged me.
It's because I'm also a mother.
I watched
the three of them grow up.
Although some of them
have been misled by you,
they're still young.
They are not hopeless.
Thank you, Eldest Madam.
Mother.
I beg you to
teach them well.
Don't let them
become someone like me.
From now on,
listen to Eldest Madam.
Take me to the court.
Mother!
-Mother!/N-Mother!
Eldest Sister.
We're guilty too.
We've been holding out on you.
We should be punished too.
To be honest,
if my mother didn't make it...
But now that I know the truth,
I will never forgive you.
In this world,
not everything
can be turned around
and made up for.
But fortunately,
my mother is still alive.
As long as you
repent sincerely,
and be honest
and kind,
I'm willing to be your sister again.
But the three of you
are different.
Mao is still young.
It's forgivable that
a little kid
didn't want to disobey his mother.
Yuzhao is repentant.
I can forgive her, too.
As for Yuying.
Your personality
is the most similar to Madam Yue.
You've always been
mean and duplicitous.
I can keep you here
and let you learn to do business
in Huarong,
and learn the way of making your own living.
Or, I can give you a dowry
and find you a good husband.
Whether you'll follow me or not,
you have to
choose the right road
in the future.
You and Yuzhao
were both given birth by her.
You've been eating and sleeping together since childhood.
Everything has been the same for you,
but you have completely different temperaments.
It shows that a person's origin
is not important.
The road
is completely chosen by themselves.
Got it.
Eldest Sister.
[Commissioner's Mansion]
[Clean and Sharp]
His Majesty passed away?
Yes.
There was supposed to be a solemn funeral.
But that rebel Lord Liang's army
is still besieging Eastern Capital,
and fighting intensely
with the Youzhou Army.
Other prefectures
can only observe from the side.
They're waiting to choose sides
when the situation is clearer.
Not to mention a solemn funeral.
In troubled times,
people can only take care of themselves.
But now,
the Crown Prince is regent.
The Crown Prince is narrow-minded
and useless.
Knowing that Lord Liang was coming,
he has been terrified.
Once His Majesty
passed away,
he ran away overnight.
Now Eastern Capital's trouble
is both internal and external.
I'm afraid my father and Uncle Fan
are deeply distraught.
But Lord Liang's army
already approached Eastern Capital last year.
Now it's already spring, but the city hasn't been taken down yet.
Even if he has a strong army,
he won't last long.
Looks like
Commissioner Fan and General Zhou
are about to have a great victory.
Thanks to Yuru,
who went south to raise military provisions
to provide
a steady flow of military provisions for the front line.
If it were not for her,
I'm afraid the front line would have been in critical condition.
If so, Youzhou
would be in trouble, too.
By the way,
I just checked.
The last batch of grains has been stored too.
I'm reporting to you
on behalf of Yuru.
Why is it you this time?
Where is Yuru?
She's with my mother-in-law.
She and her mother finally got together after her mother almost died.
They have a lot to catch up.
That's right.
When I have time,
I should prepare a welcome dinner
for Yuru.
This time,
she made a significant contribution.
The welcome dinner can be put on hold.
Now that you're in charge of Youzhou's affairs,
I want to ask you for a position
in the name of
Yuru.
It's not for me,
but for
an extraordinarily talented man.
By the way,
the commissioner and General Zhou
led the army to fight out there,
and they transported so many provisions out.
But the grain price
in Youzhou
has been dropping.
Don't you know?
Boss Liu of Huarong,
Magistrate Gu's wife.
She went to Jiangnan alone
and raised 15,000,000 kilograms of provisions.
It's all thanks to her.
No wonder.
The couple also made a great contribution
to bandit suppression on Heifeng Mountain last time.
The couple is
really Youzhou's heroes.
Yes.
It's a blessing to Youzhou.
Brother Gu.
Why are you here?
You came at the right time.
I have some good news for you.
Let's talk inside.
No need.
I'm here to say goodbye.
Goodbye?
My sister is a weak girl.
It's not appropriate for her to travel around with me.
So I want to
entrust her
to you and Yuru.
I can also rest assured.
When I have the chance,
I'll come back to see her.
Where are you going then?
To be honest, I haven't decided yet.
But in this vast world,
there must be a place for me.
I just
got you a position
to be my secretary
and work for Youzhou together.
Why are you leaving?
I was born in a scholars' family.
My grandfather was a famous scholar in Jiangnan.
And I
have been well-read since I was little.
However, I accidentally
got under the rebel Wang Shanquan's command
and worked for him.
I've ruined the reputation
of myself and my family.
And now,
Commissioner of Youzhou, Fan Xuan,
is deeply conscious of righteousness
and sent troops to save the emperor.
He shouldn't have
a traitor like me
work for him.
Otherwise,
he won't be able to convince the people.
Ye Shi'an.
I've always looked down on you since childhood.
It's exactly because of
your pretentious attitude.
What are you holding onto the
pretentious reputation
for?
You are well-educated and knowledgeable.
Why are you still
so dumb and stubborn?
So in your eyes,
what's said in the classics,
like worrying about the country and the people,
is all cynical and empty talk?
Thank you for being frank with me, Brother Gu.
Goodbye.
Do you know
when I changed my thoughts of you?
It was when you surrendered to Wang Shanquan
to protect your family.
It was when you endured the humiliation
under Wang Shanquan's command, and planned secretly
to save so many people
and the literati of Jiangnan.
I suddenly felt like
you, Ye Shi'an, are really something.
You are a loyal
and courageous person.
Many people may not know
what you did.
But you know it yourself.
Your family knows it.
God knows it.
Ye Shi'an.
You've been studying all your life.
Isn't it for the world
and the people?
Can you really bear to
hand the country and the people
over to someone
like Luo Zishang
to wreck
and degrade?
No, I can't.
Young Master.
I didn't expect that
as a scholar,
you have calluses from archery practice all over your hands.
In troubled times,
scholars are the most useless.
If I'm defenseless,
so what if I'm knowledgeable?
I need to have the real ability
to protect our country.
You've been with me all day.
Don't you have things you need to do?
Even if I do, I won't go.
I finally found my mother.
I just want to be with you all day.
You're already the hostess of the Gu family
and a big boss.
Why are you still acting like a child?
Those who have mothers are supposed to be children.
Is Yuying's dowry ready?
Yes.
I also put in
an extra gold bracelet for her.
You are so kind.
You married her into a good family,
and added to her dowry.
She asked to get married far from us.
I think
she's too ashamed to see us.
We won't see each other again.
Our kinship is over.
It's okay if I
gave her some more money.
It's good that she's gone.
This child
is a bit more scheming
than Zhao and Mao.
What worries me the most now
is Yun'er.
Since she came to Youzhou,
she's been staying in seclusion all day.
I visited her several times,
but she didn't even open the door.
She was wronged badly.
It's understandable that she'd take things too hard for a while.
I've asked the maid
to keep her company.
Shen Ming
is keeping an eye on her outside the door all day, too.
I won't let her do anything stupid.
How about
I visit her again today?
Sister.
You're finally here.
Can you appoint me to something else?
I'm
bored to death here.
Do you have any grudges against someone,
or did someone offend you lately?
I can go fight them for you.
Or, can you
let me out for a walk?
No.
Just stay here.
Keep an eye on Yun'er. Don't go anywhere.
Take care of it immediately
if anything happens.
I'll hold you accountable
if anything goes wrong.
Okay.
What's this?
It's not for you.
Yun'er.
I'm Yuru.
Open the door.
Let me come in
and talk to you.
Sister Yuru.
I'm not feeling well today.
Maybe another day.
Didn't the doctor give you a checkup yesterday?
What did he say?
Let me in
and tell me.
It's nothing.
By the way,
I brought you a pot of plum wine.
I made it myself.
I remember
you liked
the plum wine I made the best.
Keep it, Sister.
It's bitter in my mouth.
I won't know how it tastes.
Fine.
Have a good rest.
If you want to talk to me,
come to me anytime.
Take care, Sister.
Yun'er.
I want to tell you that
when we were leaving Yangzhou,
you killed our enemy.
You are resolute, smart,
and courageous.
I was really impressed.
If Old Madam Ye were still alive,
she would be very happy
and want to make a toast to you, too,
saying that you're truly her granddaughter.
Kid.
As long as I'm still in the Ye family,
nothing will happen.
Let's go.
Sister.
Sister, take care.
What's that sound?
Why does it sound so bad?
Young Master Shen.
Miss Ye sends her greetings to you
and asks you to stop blowing the leaves.
Why?
I'm bored, so I blew the leaves.
What harm did I do?
Go again.
Young Master Shen.
Miss Ye is upset now.
Please be kind
and stop blowing.
She keeps herself
inside the house all day long.
How can she not be upset?
She doesn't feel bored,
and she won't allow others to do things to ease the boredom.
So domineering.
Besides,
my sister simply asked me to guard her.
She didn't ask me to listen to her.
If she wants to say something,
let her come out here and say it herself.
Can you stop blowing?
You were out of tune, don't you know?
I thought
you wanted to
keep yourself inside the house forever
and never come out.
But you're out now.
This is great.
Turns out
it's not that hard
to get out of this room.
The story of raising provisions in Yangzhou
is so good that it can be included in the story-telling script.
The timing, place and people
are all so favorable.
I didn't expect that
it would go so smoothly.
It's just...
It's just what?
It went too smoothly.
Maybe I'm overthinking.
Sister.
You're smart and resourceful.
Young Master Ye worked from the inside.
Plus, I'm brave and capable.
And Young Master Ye's sister,
a weak woman,
made an epic move
and assassinated Wang Shanquan.
Of course it went smoothly.
Wait a minute.
Who killed Wang Shanquan?
Young Master Ye's sister.
Yun'er has never even dared
to look at the scene of a chicken or fish being killed.
I didn't expect that either.
But the version I heard is that
it was Wang Shanquan's staff,
Luo Zishang, who killed him.
After Luo Zishang killed Wang Shanquan,
he also killed
the military commander of Yangzhou Army,
Wang Ai.
Wang Shanquan has
19 children in total.
They either died or escaped.
Now,
Luo Zishang is in sole charge
of Yangzhou.
It's a rumor, right?
Wang Shanquan
wasn't killed by him.
It can't be a rumor.
The military information I received
couldn't be wrong.
If it was really Young Master Ye's sister
who killed Wang Shanquan,
Luo Zishang
must have deliberately made up this lie
to tell the world.
During your stay in Yangzhou,
Luo Zishang wasn't there the whole time?
Right until the end,
when I was leaving.
He came to the dock to see me off from afar.
He only brought one attendant with him.
He looked
very calm.
So when did he
leave Yangzhou?
After the chaos took place in Yangzhou,
you all ran away.
The city
completely
got in the hands of Wang Shanquan.
He started to feel like Luo Zishang is an eyesore.
I was forced to get under his command.
One time,
I overheard
them quarrel.
Luo Zishang thought
Wang Shanquan should
be far-sighted.
But
Wang Shanquan only wanted
to be the local emperor.
Gradually,
he also started to feel like Luo Zishang
is ruthless.
He was afraid that he'd be killed if he kept Luo by his side.
So not long after that,
he expelled Luo Zishang from Yangzhou.
Everything went so smoothly in Yangzhou.
I think Luo Zishang
must have helped from the side.
He claimed to want to become
the top merchant in the world
and help Wang Shanquan dominate Yangzhou.
Now it seems
it was just a guise
to confuse Wang Shanquan.
What he wanted from the beginning
is the entire Yangzhou.
So Wang Shanquan
was something he abandoned
at this point?
It's very likely.
So what?
He's not
a legitimate commissioner.
Now,
Eastern Capital is temporarily in chaos.
So he's taking over the city for now.
When the world is stable again,
what should he do?
I don't understand it either.
Luo Zishang is treacherous.
When he takes a step, he has thought about five steps further.
But there must be something bigger
behind this.
She needs no loud red on common green boughs
to be found her blossoms blessed with the best.
I've traveled all over the world.
She's not a beauty of beauty.
But in this world,
no woman can compare with her.
Master, you have great ambitions.
Will you be tied down by a woman?
Of course not.
I'll get
what I want in the end.
When I own the world,
she will naturally be mine as well.
[Commissioner's Mansion]
Brother Zhou Ye.
This is a military letter from the front line
sent by Father.
Take a look.
[Ten days ago, the rebels led by Lord Liang were completely wiped out in Eastern Capital.]
Ten days ago,
the rebels led by Lord Liang
were completely defeated in Eastern Capital.
Father is about to win.
In the future,
he'll be a meritorious official since he saved the emperor.
Maybe we can all become officials
in Eastern Capital.
[Ten days ago, the rebels led by Lord Liang were completely wiped out in Eastern Capital.]
Something's wrong.
What's wrong?
Lord Liang's army was defeated.
The main force is still there, and the provisions are not used up.
At this time,
how could they
give up Jingji?
I think
there must be something wrong.
We can't act rashly.
Indeed.
It has been ten days since
Lord Liang's army was defeated in Eastern Capital.
But there hasn't been any news about
any of the prefectures fighting against them.
This means
they are very likely
to be heading towards...
Youzhou.
That's right.
They couldn't conquer the front line.
So they want to use the lives of Youzhou's Young Master
and the people of the city
to threaten Commissioner Fan to retreat.
This...
I'll write a letter right away
to notify the front line.
Report!
Young General.
Lord Liang has led a force of 100,000 soldiers
across the border of Youzhou,
and they're heading to Wangdu.
100,000?
Yes.
What should we do?
How many soldiers do we have in the city?
The main forces of Youzhou
are all saving the emperor at the front line.
Now there are only 10,000 soldiers left
in Wangdu.
This...
With such a large gap in military force,
aren't we destined
to lose?
Yu'er.
Pack your things
and get out of here.
But...
But what?
Now, we have to focus on the big picture.
Go!
OK.
Brother Gu.
Take care.
Jiusi.
I'll find someone reliable
to escort Fan Yu
and the letter of help-seeking.
At this time,
I can't leave Youzhou.
Brother.
You should go in person.
Think about it.
What if they don't come
after receiving the letter?
It's a long journey to Wangdu from Eastern Capital.
Lord Liang's army is approaching the city.
Even if they receive the letter,
they'll think it's too late,
and Youzhou is already a dead city.
Jiusi, don't worry.
I will go at top speed.
You must hang in there
until the reinforcements arrive.
No matter what it takes,
we must get them back.
Don't worry.
Yun'er.
Are you feeling better?
I brought some peach gum.
It's good for your health.
Thank you, Sister Yuru.
I'm all right.
You don't have to worry about me.
Why are you being so courteous to me?
The city has been in chaos lately.
I've asked
the wives of the soldiers guarding the city
to move to the charity halls.
For one thing,
they can take care of each other.
For another,
the soldiers
fighting at the front line can be assured since
they don't have to worry about their families.
Your brother has been busy
out there with Jiusi.
I'm really worried
that you're here alone.
Move
to my place as soon as possible.
There are many people there.
I'm good
living here alone.
My condition
is unstable.
It'll be bad
if I infect anyone.
It's nothing.
The current situation is special.
No one will care about that.
Besides,
I'm here.
It's still inappropriate.
If you need my help for anything,
Sister,
just let me know.
It's peaceful for me
to live here alone.
Everything's good.
Fine.
After all,
I want you
to live comfortably.
Take care and get better.
I'll come visit you tomorrow.
There is a prescription
for cooking peach gum
and the food that works against with it inside.
Take good care of her.
Don't worry, Boss.
I will take good care of
Miss Ye.
Yun'er.
No matter what happens,
we are sisters.
We're like actual sisters.
Of course.
I'm leaving.
Take care, Boss.
Did you call Sister Yuru "Boss"?
Do you work at Huarong?
No.
I'm a refugee from Qingzhou.
I almost starved to death.
Boss donated her family fortune
and built many charity halls in Youzhou.
Boss saved my life.
Although I'm not good at accounting,
I'm quick
and good at taking care of others.
Usually,
I do flower picking and drug pounding
at Huarong.
Sister Yuru
is still so kind.
Miss Ye.
Boss is worried about you.
The city
is in complete chaos right now.
The charity halls are the safest place.
You should move there.
Those living in the charity halls
are all wives of the soldiers.
Who are they?
And who am I?
You're Boss's sworn sister.
I know that
Sister Yuru treats me well.
But the better she treats me,
the more I can't take it for granted and
drag her down.
I'm a jinx
who has already lost my reputation.
If she
spends a lot of time with someone like me,
I'm afraid others will gossip about her.
[Liang]
[Getting Ready for Battle]
The rebels led by Lord Liang are intruding.
A major battle is coming.
Today,
I will go back to Eastern Capital in person to ask for reinforcements.
Therefore,
I'm handing the military power of Youzhou
over to Gu Jiusi.