♪Unknowingly, my gaze falls on you♪
♪Your eyes are filled with starlight♪
♪Yet only my reflection remains♪
♪The warm sea breeze kisses you♪
♪Longing holds my breath still♪
♪My heart is quietly unwavering♪
♪This feeling, in silence♪
♪Circles the path of the stars♪
=Ten Years of Unrequited Love=
=Episode 10=
Mrs. Cen.
You seem quite relaxed.
Where's Mr. Cen?
Isn't he worried that you're here?
Let me introduce you.
This is the wife of Mr. Cen from Mirui.
Mr. Cen's girlfriend?
Isn't that actress Su Peipei?
I've never
seen her before.
So what if she's an actress?
You don't get men.
What makes a man?
We get bored fast.
Men
always cheat.
No way.
Miaomiao.
If Mr. Cen ever leaves you,
just let me know.
I'm here for you.
I can give you
whatever he can offer you.
Who even are you?
What's wrong with him?
What a jerk.
Don't waste your energy on him.
I'm never
coming back here again.
I paid for the car.
She just sped off without a word.
How carefree.
She left me alone in the parking lot.
Seriously, does she have no heart?
Mr. Cen, just stay calm.
Are you upset about that?
Are you kidding me?
Why would I get upset about that?
Let me break it down for you.
Your mom slapped you once.
Secretary Lin slapped you once.
Su Peipei slapped Secretary Lin.
Secretary Lin slapped Su Peipei.
Secretary Lin gave two slaps in total.
Stop counting.
What's that for?
Look.
Secretary Lin gave two slaps in total.
Didn't she put in the most effort?
What kind of logic is that?
- It's raining.
- Yeah.
Come on, let's go this way.
Chang Qixing?
Why is he still here?
What's going on?
What are they doing?
(Bar and Night Market)
Let's go.
I told you.
You'll see weird stuff
when walking at night.
Better be careful next time.
Miaomiao.
He was drunk and got beaten.
Could he pass out for good?
Let's go check on him.
Is he okay? He's not dead, is he?
Are you all right?
Lin Miaomiao.
What are you trying to do?
Did you hit me just now?
- What? Are you crazy?
- No.
When I walked over, someone covered me
with this and hit me. Was it you?
I came to check if you were okay.
It must be you.
It wasn't me.
Don't move.
What are you doing?
The more I think, the angrier I get.
I won't bother helping you again.
(Zhou Wan)
Hello.
Hello, Cen Siyuan.
Miss Lin...
Your wife is with me now.
What wife?
You have ten minutes.
Hurry to the Second Hospital.
Or I'll propose to her.
It's up to you.
Mr. Cen.
- What happened?
- Let's go.
Chang Qixing got beaten up.
Miaomiao thought he was gone,
so she went over to check it out,
but Chang Qixing grabbed her,
saying Miaomiao was behind it.
So what if he was dead?
Why get involved?
Mr. Cen is here.
Mr. Chang, who did you upset this time?
You brought this on yourself.
She showed up too conveniently today.
It makes me think she set me up.
It wasn't me.
So why did you call me here?
Mr. Cen.
We've known each other for years.
You know me.
I'm not unreasonable.
Admit she's your wife,
and I'll let this slide
for your sake.
How about that?
I'm the one who did it.
You said it yourself.
- Yes.
- Fine.
- Yu Yang, call the police.
- Got it.
She hit me. Arrest her.
Mr. Chang,
Miaomiao would never dare hit you.
She's just saying that to annoy me.
If she really goes in,
my mom will tear me apart.
Do you admit she's your wife now?
I'm right here.
Answer me.
Do you?
Yeah.
I've always seen her as my wife.
Alright.
Very good.
So, who is this?
Not talking now?
You can't answer, huh?
You say she's your wife.
Then, who is Miss Su to you?
A mistress? A homewrecker?
Family matters are hard to judge.
Mr. Chang, no need for you...
It's not hard. It's simple.
This is Yu Yang.
This is Yu Yang's girlfriend.
Easy, right?
Look.
Everyone's being reasonable.
It's getting late now.
Rumors are everywhere.
Just tell us one thing.
Who is Miss Su to you?
An ex.
An ex?
Girlfriend,
mistress,
or a homewrecker.
What do you mean by "ex"?
Mrs. Cen, you spoil him too much.
He sneaks around with someone else.
Cen Siyuan.
You jerk.
Sorry about that.
Since you're Mr. Cen's wife,
I trust you.
I know it wasn't you.
You can leave.
I'm still shaken.
I need a moment to rest.
Can you think before you act?
I didn't hit him. What's wrong?
Don't I know what you're like?
Stop pretending with me.
We're in the hospital.
Why are you yelling?
Plus, did I ask you to come today?
Fine, I was just being nosy.
That's exactly it.
Great, now I'm a woman
who stole someone's boyfriend.
Happy now?
How can someone cold and heartless
like you exist in this world?
How ungrateful.
Yeah.
I'm ungrateful.
Alright, that's enough.
Go find her.
I've broken up with her.
Let her be.
♪You'd rather gaze into my eyes♪
Jerk.
♪And you'd treasure every moment♪
♪And try your best to stay with me♪
Who turned me into a jerk?
♪Unforgettable pain♪
Well...
♪Warm winds and drifting clouds♪
♪Could never match your deep affection♪
♪Even if one day♪
♪Time would start to turn back♪
♪As we part ways♪
♪I can't help but want you to stay♪
♪But in the end,
you still have to leave♪
♪But in the end♪
♪The moon hides in the dusk♪
♪Kept my troubles inside♪
♪Snowflakes drift like clouds♪
♪Mingling into the river of dreams♪
♪Each of our frames♪
♪Bittersweet memories linger♪
♪Meeting you broke my lonely drift♪
♪The cloud kisses the sea,
gently expressing love♪
♪Sunset lingers in your eyes,
refusing to leave♪
♪I borrow the wind to hold you close♪
♪Wherever my gaze falls♪
♪All I want is to follow you♪