Episode 2
We only hired Nanami and Kashiwagi.
I can't believe the two top players are out.
The president is still complaining.
Kashiwagi is different from me.
He's independent and has his own way of doing things.
He's amazing.
He's not that special.
No, no. He's a real rich kid.
How much did he make in the last six months?
That's not what we're talking about today.
It's Nanami.
The real estate agent is now a police officer.
Huh?
Huh? Huh?
Ah!
I'm still a low-level criminal.
I'm still running around the scene.
I'm talking about you.
You'll get the result and get out of jail.
I'm not here to get out of jail.
What are you saying?
Go where you can.
I'm expecting you.
Oh, you're sending an A to your former rival.
My rival?
I didn't think that.
When Nanami quit his job,
Kashiwagi was missing Genta.
That means he's lost his rival.
That's right.
He's capable of this.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
What's wrong?
Hey.
Ah!
Nanami.
Hey.
Sir.
Police Agency.
Investigative Support Analysis Center.
S.S.B.C.
Collecting and analyzing video footage.
Data analysis of smartphones and computers.
Profiling of suspects.
The department supports all investigations.
And this time,
the investigation team that handles
murder, robbery, and robbery,
has been selected to support the special investigation.
The name is
S.S.B.C.
S.S.B.C. Confiscated.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
S.S.B.C. Confiscated.
A month's worth of heart.
What do you see?
Yes.
Do you have a wallet or a license?
I can't see my phone either.
These gloves.
I thought it was the driver of that car.
The memory card was stolen.
The culprit took it out.
He stopped the car here,
chased the driver who was running away,
and stabbed him there.
Is it a robbery for you to have no wallet?
That's what we, the Ikka, are thinking about,
so S.S.B.C. is...
I'll look for the video.
I understand.
Let's go.
Yes.
You too.
The car was a car of the president
who was arrested for the theft of the car.
When we checked the company,
the driver of the car was
the driver of the car, Moroboshi Katsuya.
His name is Tomita Hideaki, 53 years old.
What about the video?
We found only one video of S.S.B.C.
This is it.
The culprit is probably a man.
We don't know anything else.
You don't know?
Just this?
Yes.
I'm really not used to it.
I'm sorry.
Chief Ichikawa,
there is one thing that doesn't fall into the sea.
What is it?
Tomita-san was sent to Haneda
by Moroboshi, the president of overseas business,
last night,
and was attacked after that.
However,
the scene of the incident is not the way from Haneda
to the company,
but the route to the president's home.
What does that mean?
To say that the vice president of the Moroboshi security department,
was Tomita-san,
was he mistaken?
Misunderstood?
Tomita is sent to the president's home every day.
Last night,
I thought he was on the president's car.
You just sent it to Haneda.
No.
Well...
I'm sorry.
I was so upset when I heard that Tomita had died.
I felt that the vice president of Araki-dani was a little strange.
That's suspicious.
Ask more.
Yes.
Don't think that the SSBC has finished its work.
Find out more thoroughly if the video of the fire escape is missing.
Understood.
Do it thoroughly.
What's so strange?
I always feel bad when I hear that I was threatened.
I feel refreshed today.
Where is Nanami?
Huh?
Nanami!
You're not here.
Nanami is in the hospital.
He was sent to the emergency room last night.
Why?
I don't want the vice president to be here.
Please sleep, Nanami.
I'm fine.
I heard that Nanami was attacked by the emergency room.
I came here without saying a word.
It's natural to have a vice president in the future.
I'm sorry.
The surgery was successful.
I'm glad.
This is a fruit basket.
I'll put it here.
You're so considerate.
This is a jasmine flower.
I'll leave the flower words with you.
I'll leave it here.
Do you have a vase?
I'll ask the nurse.
I'll leave this here.
Thank you.
You must be busy, Chief Ichi.
I just have one murder case.
Murder?
I've started the investigation.
I'll start the SSBC.
Don't worry.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
What are you doing?
Take a rest.
You look good in anything.
You look great.
Yesterday, there was a theft case in a house in Seijyo,
which is a big city in the Aoyama area of Minato Prefecture.
A theft case?
The jewelry store was closed.
The back door was broken and someone broke in.
The people who stole the precious metals from the 8,000 yen bill were taken.
The house in Seijyo was broken through the window of the living room.
The national clock and cash were stolen.
The whole house was destroyed.
The police were arrested.
The police stole the national watch and cash,
and the total sum of 15 million yen.
The police were sleeping on the second floor of the junior high school in a big house.
Is that related to us?
We're a group of people.
If it's a theft case, the SSBC will be responsible.
Neither of them have a video of the fire.
They don't have a video?
It's a video of the fire at the jewelry store.
Originally, the video for a week should be saved,
but at 0 am...
It disappeared.
And...
4 am...
It's back.
It was destroyed during this time.
And the security company that this store was contract with was the Moroboshi Security Insurance.
Moroboshi Security Insurance?
Moreover, the house in Seijyo was also contracted with the Moroboshi Security Insurance.
What?
There too.
During the time from 0 am to 4 am when someone broke in,
there was no sign of anything in the fire alarm.
Tomita-san was murdered last night.
He was the driver of the Moroboshi Security Insurance.
And the next night,
the Moroboshi Security Insurance security system was not working in Aoyama and Seijyo.
The gold bottle was stolen.
I don't think it's a coincidence.
It has something to do with it.
What kind of relationship?
It's a family business to investigate that.
I know that even without you telling me.
Then investigate it quickly.
Shut up.
I'm really sorry.
I don't think our security system had any errors.
Errors?
We're still investigating the cause.
Is this common?
It's ridiculous.
It's the first time.
There were only two errors in Aoyama and Seijyo last night?
That's right.
There was a thief there by chance?
That's what it is.
Inaba-san is responsible for the security system, right?
Yes.
Last night, this driver, Tomita Hideaki-san, was murdered.
Do you think this system error has anything to do with it?
I don't know.
I'm really sorry.
Is he hiding something?
Like the vice president,
he may be involved in a company gang including a murder case.
A company gang?
Call the vice president. I'll ask him directly.
Araki-dani-san.
Yes.
It's strange to think that there was a thief in the two cases where the security system was not working.
The system error was actually more than 10 cases.
What?
The person in charge of the two cases was wrong.
More than 10 cases.
That's a big problem.
I'm really sorry.
Araki-dani-san.
Yes.
Isn't the case connected to the criminal?
What?
This is a crime that was helped.
That's not true.
Really.
The fact that Tomita-san was murdered is actually related to the criminal.
No.
What's the difference, Araki-dani-san?
Are you hiding something?
Listen.
The chief of police, Masao Yaegashi, is being watched.
Tell me the truth.
Tell me, Araki-dani.
The president...
What about the president?
The president of Moroboshi...
was kidnapped.
What?
Kidnapped?
Are you serious?
I'm bored.
Nanami.
Kashiwagi?
He came to see you?
He came to see me?
He's a police officer, but he's also a chief of police.
I said I could stay in the big room.
Criminal psychology, 2025.
The FBI's original report finally came out in Japanese.
Can't you leave?
What?
You're not a chief of police, right?
Don't be so spoiled. Get back to work.
I want to, but not yet.
When I heard you were transferred to the police, I was so excited.
I can compete again.
Compete?
Tell the doctor you're going to retire.
It's not the time to sleep.
What's wrong, Kashiwagi?
You're a police officer, right?
That's why I can't be so selfish.
I can't see.
Even if I go back like this, I'll just be a burden.
I'm disappointed.
You started this company when you were 32 years old.
I was sending guards to construction sites.
It was during the bubble, so there were many
I feel like I'm in trouble.
On August 9, President Moroboshi went to Haneda for overseas business.
But this is a lie that Vice President Araki Dan thought.
On that day, he took the car that Mr. Tomita Hideoaki was driving and went home from the company.
What's going on?
Probably the culprit is more than two people.
President Moroboshi was kidnapped.
Mr. Tomita was murdered.
The person who called President Moroboshi's home was at 9.25 pm.
This is Moroboshi.
I kidnapped Moroboshi Katsuya.
Look at your smartphone.
What is this?
If you tell the police, Moroboshi will kill you.
Call Vice President Araki Dan.
This is a picture sent to your smartphone.
Mr. Araki Dan.
The driver's door is not connected.
What happened?
It's Moroboshi.
Is Araki Dan here?
Yes.
I'm Araki Dan.
I will tell you the situation.
From tomorrow night from 0 am to 4 pm,
turn off the security system at the place you are going to say.
What?
Write down the address.
Yes.
Minato-ku Aoyama 4-1-13 Jeweld Wars Jewelry Shop.
4-1-13 Jeweld Wars Jewelry Shop.
Setagaya-ku Seijou-Nishi-3-4-22.
Seijou-Nishi-3-4-22.
Ohori-kenzaburo-otaku.
I wrote it.
If you don't follow the instructions, President Moroboshi will kill you.
I think it's a joke.
I've already killed one person.
What?
Oh, wait.
What's wrong?
The driver of the president, Mr. Tomita, was found dead.
What?
I got it.
The next day, the vice president of Araki Dan called the officials.
I should have called the police.
If you call the police, the president will be killed.
If that happens, we're done.
We're done.
There's no replacement for the president.
What are you going to do, Vice President?
I can't decide.
I'm consulting you.
Even if you're consulted.
What else do you have other than doing what you're asked?
If you do that, will the president come back?
That's...
You'll give it back to me.
Absolutely.
Even if you say absolutely.
It's already noon.
I have to decide.
Vice President!
Are you really going to cut it?
I'll cut it.
You're going to cut it?
Yes.
You should have told the contract to the contractor in advance.
I can't say that.
It's going to be a problem.
The vice president has already been decided.
I'll cut it.
Come.
Yes.
As a result, Aoyama's jewelry store and Seijyo's house were invaded.
Of course, the security camera doesn't show anything.
I'm sorry.
The vice president of Araki-dani also...
There was a system error.
Actually, it's more than 10.
He was trying to deceive us.
It's probably because of the life of President Moroboshi.
But even now, 39 hours after the kidnapping,
President Moroboshi has not been released.
All the decisions of Moroboshi's security insurance are behind the scenes, right?
That company has been decided by President Moroboshi so far.
The employees can't respond to emergency situations.
No.
There's something behind this case.
Behind?
Why was the criminal convinced that the security system was cut as requested when he entered?
Isn't this the internal human being?
Even though the president was kidnapped,
the security company cut the security system.
It's a suicide.
Who made that decision?
In the end, the vice president.
That's right.
It's Araki-dani.
Kidnapping?
The criminal group, please search for the car used by President Moroboshi when he was kidnapped.
It's possible that the same car was used in the invasion of Aoyama and Seijyo.
Kidnapping is a high-risk crime.
Even the driver was killed.
It's not about paying for the body, it's about cutting the security system.
Why is it so complicated?
Since President Moroboshi is not coming back, the criminal's request may still be met.
Next, let's cut the bank's security system.
Bank robbery?
That's too inefficient.
SSBC doesn't have to think about that.
What the hell does the criminal want to do?
Hurry up and find the car.
Chief Ichi, is it true that kidnapping is a crime?
Chief Ichi, please calm down.
The victim is not released yet.
So please keep the truth to yourself.
Is President Moroboshi's identity card confirmed?
It's confirmed.
What did the criminal request?
I'll tell you the investigation situation.
So there's no information about the criminal?
No.
Actually, I have information.
What?
But I can't tell you now.
So I think I can solve this case in no time.
Then I'll tell you.
Wait a minute.
Chief Ichi.
What are you doing?
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm telling you.
Why are you always like this?
Please stop.
The market just closed.
Can I call you?
I'm bored to death.
I'm tired of reading books.
Kashiwagi came to see me.
Kashiwagi?
He came to see me because he was worried about me.
But he's not in a good mood.
Worried?
No, no, no.
He's in trouble.
I'm in trouble.
You fell down at that store.
Are you okay?
Nanami.
I'm okay.
I'm coming.
The ambulance is coming.
Yes, it's a man.
He's holding his right stomach.
What are you doing, Kashiwagi?
Nanami, are you okay?
He'll be back in five minutes.
He sent us that video after that.
You don't understand the meaning.
What are you doing, Kashiwagi?
Nanami, are you okay?
He'll be back in five minutes.
The ambulance is coming, Nanami.
At night, at this time ...
At this time ...
Tell the doctor that you're going to be discharged.
It's not time to sleep.
When I heard that you had been transferred to the police, I was excited.
I can fight again.
Same car.
What's up?
Are you working, Mr. Aigaki?
I'm working.
I'm investigating.
What are you investigating now?
You're in the hospital, right?
Be quiet.
I'm free.
What's the matter?
Murder and kidnapping.
Kidnapping?
The president of the Moroboshi Police Department was kidnapped.
Really?
The driver was killed and the intruder was set up.
It's a big deal.
Kill ...
What?
The intruder set up?
The Moroboshi Police Department's security system didn't work.
That was the request of the kidnappers.
What do you mean?
It's a little ...
Right?
If the president was kidnapped, he should have asked for money.
It's too efficient to enter the thief by breaking the security system.
When I think about the effort to lock up the stolen metal ...
It's like playing a game.
Game?
It's a game that creates unpredictable stories and chases the opponent.
I found it!
I found the car.
Nanami, let's go.
Moroboshi Police Department?
Is it the same car?
It's a video of a bat that was 150 meters away from the scene of the murder.
And a bat that is 200 meters away from Aoyama's gemstone.
The same car!
And a bat that was 300 meters away from the victim's attack.
There is no doubt. It's the same car.
What's the number?
I'll zoom in.
I don't understand.
I'll try using Presley.
Low resolution.
Number estimation program.
I'll try.
Moroboshi Police Department?
Wasn't that company our client?
It's not a company.
Moroboshi is our personal client.
Oh, I see.
Kashiwagi has been in charge of it all the time.
Kashiwagi ...
But in the end, that's why he quit the company.
He lost 4 billion yen in the company's share of the company.
4 billion?
He built a portfolio that was too strong.
And the president is a big hit.
Why are you coming? You idiot!
You're such a useless person. You took my place.
I'm sorry.
Hey, you, too, lower your head.
Lower it!
I'm sorry.
So Moroboshi was pissed off and cut off.
He hit the president with a
He may not have known, but it's actually a pile of pride.
Especially you were a rival.
The criminal group is thought to have a leader and an executor.
Moroboshi's president, Yuukai, Tomita's murder, Aoyama and Seijyo's invasion,
and all the other members of the criminal group who have committed crimes.
What?
And that friend may have been gathered at the Yami-Bait.
Yami-Bait?
Either way, the most evil is the leader.
And this time, the most evil is the executor.
And only a person with the authority to do such a vicious crime can do it.
Director Ishida.
Haragitami.
Yes?
A little more evidence.
Isn't it you? The executor.
What?
What are you talking about? Why me?
You lied to us many times.
That resulted in the investigation.
That's the president's life.
It's a criminal company.
They're in charge of the crime.
It's a crime to cut the security system.
So that's...
You were cornered and couldn't make a proper judgment?
That's right.
It's a company that's a security company, but it has zero ability to play.
What did I do wrong?
What?
That's how you became the vice president.
I just became the hand and foot of President Moroboshi.
I just thought about being interested in President Moroboshi.
I can't do that.
I can't blame the vice president for what he did to me.
Well, what about that?
Director Ishida.
The SSBC stopped the car of the criminal group.
Really?
All right.
Yes.
It's a matter of time before you can be fooled, Haragitami.
I'm also thinking of becoming my own hand and foot and working for it.
I'm just thinking about being interested in it.
There's a SSBC.
President Moroboshi was kidnapped.
Moroboshi was so angry that he hit the vice president with a
It's a matter of time before you can be fooled, Haragitami.
I'm also thinking of becoming my own hand and foot and working for it.
The ambulance is coming.
By the way, at a time like this...
Ouch.
If you kidnap the president, you should ask for money.
It's too efficient to cut the security system and enter the thief.
It's like the criminal is playing a game.
Create a story that is unpredictable and chase the other person.
4258.
It's the car number of the criminal group.
There's no doubt.
I'll chase him with the N system.
If I find the destination, I'll get a vocal image from there.
What the hell?
Hello?
The criminal in this case may be someone I know.
What?
If it's him, the target should be a little further ahead.
But wait a minute.
What are you talking about?
At the moment, the case is not bright, so the stock of Moroboshi Security Insurance is stable.
A stock?
If I'm the criminal, I'll put a lot of the sale of Moroboshi Security Insurance stocks on the line.
And then, I'll ask for more aggressive conditions for the president's release.
Moroboshi Security Insurance will not be able to do that.
If I do that, what do you think will happen if Moroboshi Security Insurance cuts the security system and spreads it to the world on social media?
It's a big deal.
The stock price of Moroboshi Security Insurance is very low.
That's right.
If I look at the bottom and buy the stock again, I will make a huge profit.
How many billion?
It's a empty sale.
And when I get the money, I run away abroad.
I gave the president Moroboshi a fear, crushed the Moroboshi Security Insurance, and made a big profit.
Isn't this the story of the game the criminal drew?
Who is he?
Ask the attorney general and the board of supervisors to find out who is selling the stock of Moroboshi Security Insurance.
If it matches the name I'm thinking of, he's the culprit.
I found the car.
Nishitama-gun Hino-demachi.
Nishitama?
Next to Akiruno.
This is the last image of the N-system installed on the Todo 184.
Leave the SSBC.
Don't let me check all the documents.
I'll put it in Araki.
As long as he's here, he can't do anything.
This is Moroboshi.
Come to Araki.
Where is Araki?
He's at work now.
You told the police.
I didn't tell them.
Fine. I'll tell them what you want.
Will you return the owner?
From tonight until 4 p.m., remove all the security systems in Tokyo that the Moroboshi Security Insurance has contracted.
If you don't do as you're told, there's no life for Moroboshi.
Hello? Hello?
Chief Gyaku.
It didn't work.
Damn it!
All of Tokyo?
They told me to remove the security systems. That's what they want.
Wait a minute. Araki was in the investigation room the whole time.
Maybe Araki isn't the culprit.
What do you mean by that?
Is he?
He said he was.
I told you he wasn't the culprit!
I didn't think you were the culprit.
You did? You suspected me?
I didn't suspect you.
But how do we respond to the culprit's demands?
The chief's life is the most important thing.
So you're going to remove all the security systems in Tokyo?
If you do that, the criminal group will do whatever they want.
What if the chief gets killed?
The police won't accept the help of a criminal.
Murderer!
What?
Really? I understand.
I'll leave it to the police.
You decide, Mr. Yaegashi.
How? No, no, no.
This is where the car was last confirmed.
There's a convenience store ahead.
Let's go.
Yes.
It's not there.
Where are the security cameras?
I don't know.
We have to find them.
Yeah.
We found a guy who sells a lot of Moroboshi security insurance.
His name is Ryo Kashiwagi.
I knew it.
Who is he?
He's my colleague from the insurance company.
He's made a huge loss to the company's assets.
He's been hit hard and has quit.
You have a grudge against Mr. Moroboshi?
I joined the police and implemented a criminal plan.
You did?
He had a strong rivalry with me.
So you had a match with him?
A match?
Yes, that's what I said.
But that won't get you anywhere.
Kashiwagi is a murderer.
I don't think I'd be involved in such a violent act.
I don't think he's using a dark horse to give orders.
It's around here.
He's awake.
4258.
What's ahead of us?
There's only Akiyama.
Akiyama?
Yes.
Hino-demachi, Nishitagawa.
O-Aza-O-I.
2980.
5258.
O-Aza-O-I, 2980.
I think Mr. Moroboshi is locked up here.
Chief Ichikawa.
Send SIT.
Report him without the criminal noticing.
Yes, sir.
Wait.
Wait?
There's no one to give orders to in that house.
Someone to give orders?
There's a powerful suspect.
Kashiwagi Ryota.
He was a witness and is now a private investor.
What?
He's a colleague of Nanami's former company.
He hates Mr. Moroboshi.
He's a challenge to the police.
Now.
He's been in the Moroboshi Security Security Department.
You're doing this again?
How could you keep quiet when you knew he was there?
Why didn't you tell us?
Because we didn't have a criminal notice.
You could've reported it without a criminal notice.
We don't have time.
I'll get Nini.
No.
I'll set a trap.
A trap?
What?
Let's go.
What's the matter?
What are you doing?
I'm going to kill you.
The laser mic is set.
Hello?
The voice is back.
Shall we use the police?
Yes.
10 minutes left.
If we don't do as requested,
there's no life in Moroboshi.
There's no life in Moroboshi.
I refuse.
You can't cut all the security systems in the city.
I refuse your request.
Kill Moroboshi.
You want me to kill Moroboshi?
It's Kashiwagi.
It's the police.
Kashiwagi.
Don't run.
Kako.
11 o'clock, 51 minutes.
Hurry.
Kashiwagi.
It's about two hours before the time.
We have protected Moroboshi Katsuya
in the Akiya in Hinode-machi,
and also the one who was there
was Kawasaki Yuma, 26 years old,
Iwata Hikari, 30 years old,
and Kurosaki Kensuke, 22 years old.
It's me.
Is it Moroboshi?
I'm fine now.
Boss!
What is it?
It's the phone that was contacted by the commander.
Also, the victim who was seen as the commander,
Ryo Kashiwagi, 39 years old,
was arrested last night at 11.51am
at the home building
in Nanpei-dai, Shibuya.
Moroboshi was
quite exhausted,
but he was still alive.
Is it okay to think that
the same criminal group
killed the driver, Tomita Hideaki?
We're considering that possibility
and we're doing it at the police station.
What was the request of the criminal group?
Hmm...
I don't know.
Well,
Moroboshi Police Station
is going to
remove the security system.
What?
What do you mean by that?
What do you mean?
Please explain.
I was going to explain
all the details of the contract.
Do you want to do Aoyagi?
Come on.
I'm a member of the police.
Do it.
I'm a member of HOPE.
HOPE is a long name.
I'm sorry.
Do it.
It's okay.
Moroboshi Police Station
is in a bad shape.
But the president
made an apology meeting
so he might be able to stop it.
If we cut the security system
that company would be over.
It's your fault, Nanami.
I didn't do anything.
You were the one who fell down.
What?
You wouldn't have doubted
the cashier.
I see.
The cashier came to watch
the video
because I was hospitalized.
I see.
Anyway,
this is the first case.
It started with revenge.
And it's going to be a nightmare.
If we make it a cashier
even the kidnapping
and murder
are just the materials
for that.
If we use the dark bite
we'll be able to do it without
getting into trouble.
It might be a kind of psychopath.
I don't understand.
I don't even
have a book.
A book?
I'm going to go back to school today.
Today?
I'm going to go back to school now.
What are you going to do
after you retire?
I want to work.
I see.
Come on.
Yes.
I want to be in the pool.
You came down from the sky?
You're going to the half-moon.
You're a hot iron teacher.
I'm scared.
You're going to lie to me
while you're teaching me
to find the person who's doing the medicine?
I want to find the evidence.
I'm going to be caught
by the teacher.
You can't lie.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
I don't think I'll see you again.
That incident made me who I am now.
You weren't a teacher, Chief Ichikawa?
What?