If they say
travel
is about encountering new stories
then I feel
this trip
just maybe
will help me find something
Usually
in my world
it's mostly just me
and these
drawings from my imagination
I am a
fantasy romance comic artist
But right now
I have zero inspiration
Even my editor said
I should go out for a walk
go out into real life
and look for a romantic feeling
Telling me to find romance
someone like me
Phayao Province
It's my first time hearing this name
Even for me, from Hong Kong, China
I'm not sure if the pronunciation is right
I really hope this place
can give me some inspiration
and give me the energy
to go back and finish the comic
Sorry!
Phayao Province's welcome ceremony
is actually quite interesting
Our hotel is hosting an art event
We also have some cute works by children on display
If you have time, we invite you to visit the art exhibition
Please excuse me for a moment
Excuse me
How can I help you?
where is the restroom?
The restroom?
Mm
Uh
You go out
then turn left
walk to the back and you'll see it
Oh
Thank you
Okay
Breakfast starts at six in the morning
You can go rest for a bit now
and then have some free time
Thank you
Sigh
Where did it go?
It was definitely here just now
Hello
I am the manager here
Nilan
May I ask
is there anything I can help you with?
I lost my passport
I don't know where it went
Maybe I dropped it somewhere
Think back for a moment
where did you just walk?
I...
I walked straight here after getting off the car
and then...
Oh
the restroom
How about this
you go check the restroom first
I'll help you look around here
I'll go to the restroom
Okay
Let me take a look
Where is it?
Eh?
Found it.
So it was here.
Hey.
Found it.
I found it already.
Oh.
Found it.
Okay.
So...
I can check you in now.
Alright.
Go ahead.
The reservation is under Meilin.
Okay.
Please come inside.
Miss Meilin.
Check-in is complete.
Your room is Room P1.
Here are two key cards.
The Wi-Fi password for the room...
...is already on the desk.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
Oh.
By the way.
Actually, I came to Phayao...
...to participate in the art exhibition here.
To find some artistic inspiration.
Oh.
Then...
May I ask...
Have you already...
...confirmed your registration via email?
Do I need to confirm?
Yes.
If you haven't confirmed...
...according to the rules, you cannot participate.
But...
...I came here specifically for this event!
Those are the rules.
If you haven't confirmed...
...it's hard for me to help you.
Is there really no way?
But you're an employee here!
But confirmation must be done by the registrant.
If you didn't do it, how can I help you?
I don't care.
I want to speak to the person in charge of this event.
I am the person in charge of this event.
If...
...you want to participate in the event...
...then please answer a question first.
What question?
In your understanding...
...what is art?
To me, art is the voice of the heart.
It follows no logic, nor does it need to be perfect.
But it...
...can make you feel something.
Whether it is...
...sadness...
...loneliness...
...or happiness.
Art is what lets me know I am still alive.
Next time, I hope...
...you can take your own matters more seriously.
This time...
...I will keep...
...your spot in the event.
Thank you.
There.
That's the title.
Trouble Upon Arrival.
Just you wait.
Ni...
...lan.
Hungry again.
Excuse me
Can I rent a bicycle here?
You
It's you again
Hotel guests...
...can use them for free.
Oh
It's very nice around here
Cycling around the lake...
...the scenery is beautiful.
Or...
...you could visit Wat Si Chun Kan.
Wat Si Chun Kan?
How would I know the way?
I don't know how to get there.
Uh...
Actually, the hotel has a guide service
if you need it.
Then you be my guide.
Well...
Uh...
I...
Just do it for a bit.
Mmm
All right
This is Wat Si Chun Kan.
Phayao people also call it The Great Buddha Temple.
It's one of the most important temples in Phayao Province.
It has a long history.
Wow
It's so beautiful
And so bright
You can make a wish.
How do I do that?
Pray and make a wish.
Just follow what I do.
Hands like this.
Then...
From here...
Three
Make a wish.
I hope I can bring back good inspiration.
Let me draw as well as I used to.
I hope I can pursue my dreams.
Uh...
Let's walk around the area.
Okay
Have some water.
Consider it...
...for what happened before...
...as an apology.
Thanks
I'm sorry
It's okay
I was at fault too, being so careless.
I should be the one apologizing to you.
So...
...are you tired?
Shall we go back to the hotel?
Sure
I've taken up too much of your time.
It's fine
It's my pleasure
Let's go
Mmm
This Meilin I just met...
The me in her drawing...
seems...
...compared to what I see...
...even more...
...real.
Did you find drawing inspiration today?
Yes
I found some.
If you have time...
...could you take me around Thailand...
...to find unforgettable experiences?
I want to be with you...
...to complete this...
...trip full of inspiration.