SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Subbers: Archanfel, Toki
Princess Nirvana
Episode 4
You mistook it.
I missed you so much
that my heart hurts bitterly
if I couldn't see you.
As for them,
they came with me because they worried
about my health.
Right?
His Highness is ill,
so we worried about him
and insisted on coming.
Please punish us.
It was barely a mistake,
so no need to punish you.
Besides,
you cared about my husband's health
and...
This lecher knows
how to take advantage of me.
Since you
didn't wrong me,
I
am relieved.
There are many houses for me to see,
so
I'm taking my leave.
All right.
Laifeng, Laifu.
Yes.
Check the study
to see if there is something missing.
Also see if the decoy secret letter
is touched.
Yes.
Your Highness.
Nothing in this room
is missing
and the secret letter isn't touched, either.
Did she find that place?
It should be a coincidence.
How could she be interested in that?
It was so close.
Catch her.
There must be something confidential
in that secret room.
No.
I have to go there again.
Let's go.
Everything here is related to Zhao Qing and me.
Why does he
keep them so well?
This umbrella is so tattered,
to think he still keeps it.
It was my fault.
If I listened to you before,
I wouldn't have sprained my ankle
and you wouldn't need to carry me laboriously.
Don't speak like a fool.
I'm so glad
to carry you.
Thank you for holding the umbrella for me.
You are comforting me again.
Is must be so hard to carry me.
Look, you are sweating.
It's not hard
to carry you.
Then
I will hold the umbrella for you always.
All right.
It settled.
Crying like a pear blossom in the rain.
I wait for your return.
On a broken bridge is remained snow.
There is no you.
The sounds of the music instruments.
Enter my ears.
The clear rhythms
swells and subsides.
A qin win with a broken string
talks about the brilliant thing.
I play pipa in the rain.
The catkin dances in the wind.
The shy voice of qin
lifts up the jade screen.
A silk dance.
Crying like a pear blossom in the rain.
I wait for your return.
It's for you.
Do you like it?
Yes.
I wait for your return?
It's just a fool's dream.
Qian.
What are you doing?
I heard
that if two love birds
bind their hair together,
they may be together for many lifetimes.
This is mine.
Fool.
Only a couple
could bind their hair together.
I don't care.
I want to be with you always.
Qian.
Stop it.
The promise of binding hair
is no joke.
Whatever.
Qian.
Who the hell are you?
Why did you come here?
How did you know this secret room?
Your Highness.
Did my wife go out?
She didn't feel well,
so she slept after having supper.
There is an assassin here.
Keep my wife safe.
Yes.
Qing.
It hurts me each time
I see the falling flowers.
I don't want you to be hurt.
What did you say?
Nothing.
YoYo English Channel    YouTube