SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Subbers: Archanfel, Toki
Princess Nirvana
Episode 6
Hurry up.
Come on.
Mister Qin.
Tell me how he is.
The wound isn't deep.
I have applied the medicine.
He will be fine
after resting a few days.
It wasn't my fault.
I was going to bear it for you,
but you chose to stand in front of me.
Qian.
Come down.
Qing.
Don't worry.
I can do it.
Qing.
Impressive?
Does it hurt?
I'm sorry.
I have got you hurt.
It's fine.
It doesn't hurt.
Qing.
Will you always protect me?
Trust me.
I will
always keep you safe.
Mister Qin.
Take a look at His Highness.
Huh?
Why did he spit blood?
That stroke
didn't hurt his internal organs,
why is the wound so severe?
Was it
a toxic blade?
It wasn't,
but
His Highness was badly wounded
in the last war
which became an uncured illness.
Recently,
it keeps coming back frequently,
I'm afraid he may be at stake.
An uncured illness?
Why haven't I heard about it?
His Highness has kept it
a secret.
I think he doesn't want
others to worry about him.
That illness
can't be cured?
I
can only
use all the rare medicines
to try to prolong his life.
His Highness
is supposed
to stand a chance,
but...
But what?
But
the person who could save him is dead.
Forget it.
Impossible.
There must be another way.
No.
Why is there
a crucial herb missing at this critical moment?
What is it?
I'll go buy it now.
It's a rare one,
so I only have a few at my old house in Lingjiang.
But
His Highness must take it within six hours,
otherwise...
Lady.
Huh?
I haven't told her the specific location.
Go to tell her
that the herb
is in the third drawer of the right cabinet
in the second house of the west yard.
Okay.
May His Highness
survive it.
Ya.
Zhang Qing.
Hang in there.
Don't you die
before I take my revenge.
Ya.
Mister Qin.
Lady.
Is this Revival Herb?
Yes.
This is the Revival Herb.
I'll decoct if for His Highness now.
Great.
Mister Qin.
Her Ladyship passed out.
Look.
Easy.
Mister Qin.
How is she?
Don't worry.
She is just too fatigue
and she will recover after resting.
It must be too hard for her
to ride 150 km in a day.
His Highness
has married a nice consort.
Fantastic.
I'll go decoct it.
Your Highness.
You are awake.
What happened?
Last night,
your old disease came back.
Her Ladyship rode 150 km
to take the herb to save you.
Then
she fainted due to tiredness,
yet she still called your name.
Mister Qin and I thought
since you were married,
we made the decision to...
Nonsense.
Don't you
know her identity?
I'm sorry.
Please punish me.
Leave.
Yes.
Zhao Qing.
You can't die.
Look,
I didn't...
Don't mistake it.
I know
Thank you
for last night.
Well,
if there is no business else,
I'm taking my leave.
It's good you made it.
He saved me,
so I had to take the herb
for him.
Besides,
he won't suspect me
for going to Chunxiang Pavilion
because of that.
What's more,
since he is still alive,
I can still ...
Yan.
YoYo English Channel    YouTube