♪Chasing wind, I set out afar♪
♪The road ahead lost, my voice unheard♪
♪I've tasted joy and sorrow♪
♪Laying low, I plan every move♪
♪With a mortal heart and lingering ties♪
♪I'm roaming far and wide♪
♪A twist of fate in desperate times♪
♪A bond that outlives the dust of life♪
♪Still chasing what immortality means♪
♪Even eternity flashes by in a blink♪
♪Don't mock my ordinary life♪
♪I fight alone as chaos shakes the world♪
♪Don't scorn my humble roots♪
♪Kind at heart, ruthless when I must be♪
♪Fate stirs with joy and grief beneath♪
♪I hold the tide between life and death♪
♪Faith carries me through endless dark♪
♪And I return with a heart refined♪
♪Forged by trial, I rise through three realms♪
♪Reborn in the wheel of fate♪
[The Immortal Ascension]
[Adapted from the webnovel, The Immortal Ascension by Wangyu]
[serialized in www.qidian.com under China Literature Limited]
[Episode 21]
Caught you.
Are you fleeing the battle?
Meng,
cut it out.
Han,
I got these pills on my last mission
to help with recovery and strengthening.
Take them.
Just in case.
You've all heard.
The Master trusts us the most.
Here.
Take it.
Thanks.
Han,
why not ask Master
to let me go with you?
It's not easy
to find a good sparring partner.
I haven't had enough fun yet.
The war is in full swing.
You trying to dodge the fight?
Who said I was dodging?
Han,
come here a second.
I heard
there's a new cosmetics shop
in the capital.
The Moxiang Abode.
They sell all kinds of skincare and perfumes.
Pick some up for me, will you?
I made a list.
Just follow it.
Don't let Senior Liu find out.
Things look lively.
That brat.
Let's see how he acts
when he sees me on my ark.
If she doesn't want to see me,
then I'll just pretend
we're strangers, like she said.
What's that supposed to mean?
He didn't even say hi.
Where are you going?
Aft cabin.
You brat.
You didn't even look at me.
Who do you think you are, huh?
Nangong Wan.
You're already in the Core Formation Stage.
Why are you still mad over some nobody?
It's not worth it.
I'm not mad.
Calm down.
Who he's with,
who he's buying rouge for,
has nothing to do with me!
He's not even worthy.
This is maddening!
I'm going to forget him.
I have to forget him!
Back to my cultivating.
Han Li...
I'll never forgive you.
She wouldn't
really kill me, would she?
That should be Yuanwu Kingdom.
A good chance to find Qi Yunxiao
and the array master he serves
to ask about the teleport array.
Mr. Han,
we're not in the capital yet.
I have a mission.
I'll take my leave.
Right.
One more thing.
Please pass this to Senior Nangong.
What is it?
Ageless Pill.
Ageless Pill?
Grandmaster,
that guy in the back cabin left.
He left?
Looked like he headed toward Yuanwu Kingdom.
He didn't even come to see me.
He told me to give you this.
Give me what?
It's a pill.
He said it's the Ageless Pill.
Ageless Pill?
What for?
Does he think I'm old?
You may go.
Yes.
Wait.
Don't tell anyone about this.
Especially not my senior Nichang.
Forget it.
I'll let you off this time.
[Yunxiao Pavilion of Yuanwu Kingdom]
Shouldn't you be minding the shop?
Where did you go?
[Out at the moment. Leave a message.]
Top-grade artifact,
the Flamecloud Sword.
It has fire-element techniques.
Personally refined
by a Core Formation cultivator.
Starting bid.
Two hundred gems.
Any takers?
I'll bid three hundred.
Three hundred.
I bid four hundred.
Four hundred.
Four hundred gems!
Any more bids?
Five hundred.
Five hundred gems!
Anyone going higher?
This auction's on another level...
Five hundred, once.
...These cultivators are all
- Early Foundation Establishment. - Five hundred, twice.
Five hundred, thrice.
Sold!
Congratulations to the bidder.
Alright.
Next item.
Let's bring it up.
High-grade pill,
Ageless Pill.
Two pills.
Ageless Pill?
Ageless Pill!
I want one too!
This pill
- comes from the Joyful Union Sect. - I want it!
- I want it too! - It's rare in the market.
If you know, you know.
Starting bid.
One hundred gems.
This stuff is good.
I want this one.
I bid one-thirty.
You're a grown man.
Why do you need the Ageless Pill?
Do you have no shame?
One fifty.
One fifty!
Two fifty.
Two fifty!
Three hundred.
Three hundred gems!
Five hundred.
Five hundred gems!
Any higher offers?
Looks do matter in cultivation.
These two Ageless Pills might sell
for as much as a top-tier artifact.
Five hundred, thrice.
Sold!
Congratulations, cultivator!
Excellent.
Please collect your item at the counter.
Esteemed guests,
next up,
the twenty-eighth item of the night.
It's also the final item this month.
Golden Glow Ganoderma.
Now that's rare.
A millennium-old one.
A thousand years old!
No starting bid set.
Smells amazing...
Isn't that the one I sold
to Treasure House?
Is that shady merchant
actually backing this auction?
Eighteen hundred!
Two thousand!
Twenty-five hundred!
Anyone higher?
Twenty-eight hundred!
Thirty-three hundred!
Thirty-eight hundred!
Thirty-eight hundred, once!
Hold it!
Qi Yunxiao?
This Millennium Ganoderma
shall be mine.
Stop causing trouble!
Guards, throw him out!
- Not this again! - Who even are you?
- I'll trade an array for it! - Still haven't learned, huh?
-This time... - Wait!
...he even dropped the disguise.
Esteemed elders,
I am Qi Yunxiao, an Artifact Crafter in this city.
I truly need that Golden Glow Ganoderma
to save a life.
I'm willing to offer
two high-grade arrays
in exchange for it.
Where did this guy come from?
Two arrays, you say?
I have eight myself!
Throw him out!
- I'm just trying to... - Kid,
stand down!
Get lost.
Hold on, wait!
Young man,
come back next time.
- Come on. - Elder, please!
I really need it to save a life.
Elder, wait!
A Qi Refining rookie?
An Artifact Crafter?
Move it.
- Four thousand! - Elder!
- Four thousand! - To save a life!
Four thousand!
Anyone want to bid higher?
Forty-five hundred!
Forty-eight hundred!
Any higher than forty-eight hundred?
Blade Arts?
You're from the Fu Clan?
Now that you know,
even if you hand over the array,
we still can't let you live.
Han!
[Yunxiao Pavilion]
[Xin Ruyin]
Yunxiao.
Ruyin?
How did you get hurt?
I let my guard down for a moment,
and some thugs mugged me.
Is this girl...
Han saved me.
...the one he cares so much about?
Han,
come in.
The Millennium Spirit Herb you took earlier
was the one he traded to us.
Yunxiao often mentioned you.
You saved me once.
I, Xin Ruyin, am deeply grateful.
Senior Han,
come inside.
Han,
you might not know,
those two
are from the Fu Clan, the top family
in Yuanwu.
They are trouble.
My advice?
Leave here soon.
You stepped in to protect me.
I don't want to get you involved.
Just now,
I wiped out all their traces.
I won't stay long.
However,
I think you two
should find somewhere quiet
and lay low
just to be safe.
Ruyin,
did you hear that?
Han says
we should find a quiet place and stay a while.
Yunxiao,
we're not even married yet.
By the way, Han,
thanks to Ruyin's help,
the upgrade for the Five Phases Reversing Array went smoothly.
Its defense is stronger now,
plus it now has
an illusory trap to restrain enemies.
I'll go get it.
Qi,
no rush.
Since Miss Ruyin is here too,
I actually came
to ask for your help
to appraise something.
Teleportation,
stabilization,
acceleration,
spiritual channeling,
amplification.
I can't believe
this ancient teleport array
actually exists.
Once this array
is infused with spiritual power,
it can teleport
across great distances.
It seems
you also need a Greater Teleport Command Seal
to withstand spatial turbulence.
Judging by your expression,
that shouldn't be a problem for you.
Unfortunately,
this array isn't complete.
A part is missing.
It may no longer be usable.
Do you think you can
restore it?
This array
is very ancient,
and part of it is broken.
To fix it
would take rare high-grade materials.
It also involves a secret art.
Right now,
I'm still unwell.
I'm afraid we're not able
to help you with it.
We're truly sorry.
If it's about the cost,
don't worry.
I'll handle all of it.
I still have
Golden Glow Ganoderma.
I can trade it.
Ruyin,
your illness can be cured.
Let's just agree to it.
Don't worry, Han.
I'll figure it out.
Yunxiao,
my condition
comes from being born with the Dragon Roar Body.
As I cultivate,
my meridians
gradually wither.
No medicine can cure it.
To have lived this long
is already a blessing.
I shouldn't
leave you disappointed
and waste
Senior Han's spirit herb.
Besides,
the demonic sects are on the rise.
The ancient teleport array
is bound to attract attention.
She must think
I'll betray them when they are no longer useful,
then silence them for good.
Looks like
I'll have to put her doubts to rest.
Hear me out.
I'm a free soul
with no interest in power.
But with the world in chaos now,
a great conflict is brewing.
We can't just idle away anymore.
This time,
it was pure chance
that I came upon this ancient teleport array.
Naturally,
I planned to use it as an escape route.
Though I'm no expert,
I've studied a bit of medicine.
The ancients once said
this world is vast and full of wonders.
No disease is incurable.
We only think so because
of our limited knowledge.
Miss Ruyin,
don't ever give up hope.
Han is right.
With this array,
nowhere is
out of our reach.
Ruyin,
stop saying
it's pointless to find a cure.
With Han and this array,
we'll definitely find a way to heal you.
Senior Han,
if that day really comes,
would you take us with you?
Of course.
Come to think of it,
this is my first time in the capital.
The cultivation world is in chaos,
yet this place stays lively
as if untouched.
I just wonder
how long this peace
will truly last.
Grandpa!
Grandpa, come chase me!
- Cui'er! - Sweet sugar hawthorn!
- I'm over here! - Fresh sugar hawthorn!
Sweet sugar hawthorn!
Watch where you're going, little girl!
Cui'er!
Don't run, Cui'er. Slow down!
Careful! Slow down!
Cui'er!
[Xiao Zhen, Qi Refining Stage]
Qi Refining Stage?
I can't detect his cultivation.
Did he use Aura Concealment?
[Mind Control Spell]
I was a fool
for not knowing your might.
I offended you, Master.
Please forgive me!
Calm down.
Your technique
is rather interesting.
I've memorized your aura.
Once I'm done here,
I'll come find you again.
Come take a look!
Painted umbrellas!
Sir,
where is the Qin Residence?
Thank you.
Fresh and fragrant buns here!
Grandpa, what's wrong?
[Xiao Cui'er]
- Did someone bully you? - Run!
Run!
Wait, what's going on?
Hurry, let's go!
Who are you?
[Qin Gui]
You trespassed into the Qin Residence.
That's a crime!
Sir, please...
Who are you calling "sir"?
Handsome,
it's an urgent matter.
I must see your master.
Please inform him.
My master isn't
someone you can meet on a whim.
[To Qin Yan]
That's our lord's name...
Come with me.
Qin Yan greets the Master.
I failed to recognize you
and showed disrespect.
Please forgive my offense.
Master,
take a seat.
Please sit.
Have a seat.
Please.
Calm yourself down.
As the letter stated,
I, Han,
came on my master's orders.
I may have to
stay for a few days.
[Qin Yan]
Thank you for your generosity.
You bring honor to our humble home.
Before my father passed away,
he once said that if disaster ever befell the Qin family,
Master Li would surely lend us a hand.
May I know
if that's the reason you've come, Master Han?
You need not ask further.
But indeed,
my master sent me here
to ensure your family survives
this coming disaster.
A disaster...
In that case,
the lives of the entire Qin family
are in your care, Master Han!
No wonder he's a man of power.
Much more sensible than the gatekeeper.
We are in your hands.
Please protect us.
At ease, Lord Qin.
This is my sect's duty,
so I will
do my best.
However, for this mission,
I was ordered to proceed
in secret.
From now on, we shall
address each other as uncle and nephew.
Uncle and nephew...
As you wish, Master.
- As you wish, Master. - That's enough.
Please, have a seat.
From now on,
we're uncle and nephew.
Did he say he's the descendant of the old Master's friend?
Yes.
Sounds like another freeloader to me.
Young Master, Madam,
while I was observing in the hall,
The Master was rather indifferent at first,
but after reading the letter,
his expression turned grave.
He even dismissed all the servants
to speak with him alone.
How old is he?
[Madam Qin]
And what does he look like?
Tell me everything.
Madam,
his looks are very ordinary.
His clothes were plain and shabby.
At first, I thought he
was another penniless fool trying to make a connection.
But I've served Master since childhood.
He's never treated anyone
[Qin Fei]
with such respect.
Come!
The Master actually poured tea for him.
I want him dead.
Qin Gui!
Throw him out!
Madam,
I wouldn't dare!
Calm down.
Please calm down.
Grandpa!
Cui'er, hide quickly!
Who did this?
It's a complete mess in here!
So much blood...
The mark
on the old man from yesterday
vanished here.
The trail is still fresh.
It must have just happened.
Rogue cultivators,
welcome to your paradise,
the Black Fiend Cult.
Everyone here
has been cast aside by the Seven Sects.
- Da. - We're...
Quiet!
- ...not overthrowing the Seven Sects. - Let him finish.
And we won't make you die for us either.
We just want you to know
the so-called Foundation Pill
is a lie by the Seven Sects!
Without that pill,
you can still break through Qi Refining
and reach the next stage!
Seriously?
The Master of the Black Fiend Cult
is using a secret technique.
Soon,
he'll break through to Core Formation.
What the Seven Sects keep hidden,
our Black Fiend Cult
shares with all of you.
Now,
the Black Fiend Cult
is willing to share
our secret arts with you all
so we may cultivate together.
Da,
this sounds sketchy to me.
What should we do then?
Sharing secret arts!
- Cultivating together! - What is this place?
- Who are these people? - Sharing secret arts!
[Meng Wu]
Cultivate together!
Share secret arts!
San.
You alright?
I'm fine.
How do you feel?
I'm all itchy.
It has nothing
to do with me.
Sir,
save my grandpa!
Let go!
If you save my grandpa,
I'll give you
this book that holds the Aura Concealment.
No.
I'll even serve you if you want!
I already told you,
I can't help you.
Stop bothering me.
Leave now.
If you won't help me,
then I'll just die right here!
then kill me yourself!
We rogue cultivators
are all being hunted anyway.
They got my grandpa yesterday.
Last month, a boy from the Li family.
Three months ago, it was Miss Zhao.
Next time, it might be me.
How is it my concern?
Grandpa was right after all.
You are all two-faced hypocrites.
You don't care if rogue cultivators live or die!
If it weren't for that Aura Concealment,
Grandpa wouldn't have left the city.
And if I hadn't
insisted on seeing the Lantern Festival...
If it weren't...
What is it?
Young Master,
The Master has asked you to come to the front hall.
He says it's something important.
Alright.
Understood.
Hold on a sec.
Sorry about this.
As for you,
we'll settle this later.
They were all taken,
but not killed on the spot.
Seems like they're still useful.
It's no easy task to control so many rogues.
They must be locked up separately.
There are
different locations too.
Did Uncle Qin say what it was about?
Young Master,
Prince Xin's estate sent an invitation.
The Master thinks highly of you.
Perhaps he wants
to take you along.
You'll know when you're there.
Greetings, Mr. Qin.
Steward Wang, how have you been?
[Steward Wang]
Thanks to you, quite well.
Please.
Yes.
Qin Fei,
you sit here.
Han Li,
Please, Young Master Han.
What a strange wave of spiritual power.
The demonic sects?
Young Master Qin,
please.
Prince Xin has arrived.
[Prince Xin]
Tonight's family banquet
is an opportunity
for me to share
a once-in-a-lifetime chance
with all of you.
Steward Wang,
invite the cultivator.
Amazing!
Incredible!
[Wu Sanxing]
It may just be a basic Fireball Technique,
but the control was remarkably precise.
Quite interesting.
Good.
Excellent.
So impressive.
- Amazing. - Truly spectacular.
Honored guests,
this cultivator
shares a connection with the Prince.
He has
accepted the Young Prince
as his personal disciple.
All this fuss,
and he's just a Tier 5 Qi Refiner?
He's also seeking
others with spirit roots and potential
to guide them onto the immortal path
and teach the way to eternal life.
He is indeed a cultivator,
but his cultivation is weak.
He won't stir up much trouble.
Master.
Can you take a look at me?
Look at me, please.
Please, look at me!
Aside from this Steward Wang,
no one else here
has any spiritual power.
Miss Mo?
Why is she here?
You caused the commotion last night.
How did it end up like this?
[Young Prince]
We got the old one. The girl escaped.
No idea what spell she used,
but she hid her aura well.
Master will soon return.
No mistakes are allowed.
You're being too flashy.
If this causes trouble,
and Master gets upset,
he might use us
as dummies!
Understood.
Protector.
Lately,
I've told those five idiots
to search the capital
for rogue cultivators.
Miss Mo?
Why are you here?
You're here too?
You're tailing Steward Wang?
He's the one I told you about.
He wiped out my clan,
Sect Leader of the Five-Color Sect.
He's dangerous.
Way out of your league.
Is he a cultivator?
More or less.
But he reeks of dark aura.
Clearly a demonic type.
Not a righteous man.
I should've figured.
Everything he said,
and all those shady dealings...
How are there so many cultivators in the world,
and I just happen to meet them all?
Miss Mo,
this place is dangerous.
Before anyone sees you,
go back.
Don't come again.
Li.
I thought
I'd never see you again.
On the day we parted
at the Yan Clan Stronghold,
you didn't say anything.
But I knew
a mortal like me who can't cultivate
could never walk the same path as you.
Our lives are far too short,
like morning dew
that will be gone in a blink.
All love, hate, longing
will turn to dust.
But even with such a fleeting life,
I still want to make it count.
Even if it's like a moth to a flame,
even if
it ends in nothing,
I still want to try.
But you...
Li!
All these years,
you haven't changed
a single bit.
Don't worry.
Today,
I won't kill him.
I won't go head-on with him again.
I'll do as you and Father taught me.
I'll do it
one step at a time,
find his weakness and trap him,
until the day I can kill him.
No matter how it's done,
no matter how long it takes.
Farewell,
Li.
Miss Mo.
If I told you to stop,
you wouldn't listen.
Very well, then.
You've been compromised.
Do you admit your guilt?
I was too blind to see your powerful presence.
Please, spare me!
Senior,
I am just
a newcomer here.
All I've done is enjoy
some mortal offerings.
I don't know
what crime I've committed.
Whether you have or not,
that's for me to decide.
I'll ask the questions.
Answer truthfully.
Yes!
You may rise.
Thank you, Senior.
Many thanks, Senior.
What is your name?
Who is your master?
That Fire Control Technique you used
back in the hall,
where did you learn it?
Senior,
I'm Wu Sanxing.
I have no sect or master.
I'm just a rogue cultivator.
As for that spell,
I developed it
through my own practice
and knowledge.
It was a simple trick
to fool the mortals.
I meant no offense.
If you like it,
I'm willing
to offer it up with both hands.
A smooth talker.
Clearly used to dealing in the mortal world
and very street smart.
Quite impressive.
♪Shards of dreams inside a dream♪
♪A pale moon falls into mirrored skies♪
♪Years slipped by as I lingered on♪
♪Old scenes rise again♪
♪Too hard to forget♪
♪Easier just to miss♪
♪They say the past fades like smoke♪
♪But looking back still stirs the ache♪
♪This noisy world, this lonely page♪
♪Swept away by time♪
♪Eyes once looked far♪
♪Now lost in the shift♪
♪Autumn winds stir♪
♪Smoke curls once more♪
♪Like clouds on the edge of sky♪
♪Returning to my eyes♪
♪Looking back from the mountaintop♪
♪Time lost its name♪
♪Was it yesterday♪
♪Or tomorrow?♪
♪The world has changed♪
♪Beyond recall♪
♪Time will fade♪
♪All the words ever spoken♪
♪Only this longing remains♪
♪Crossing centuries and days♪
♪In a fleeting moment we call eternity♪
♪In a fleeting moment called eternity♪