=Childe Xie's Wine=
=Episode 4=
Does it feel good to be pretty?
But soon, I'll regress.
What do I do to maintain the face?
Find Five-additive Wine.
Don't go.
I have a question for you.
I'm not going anywhere.
I've been waiting for you.
What are you doing in my room?
Ask yourself.
You've been holding my hand
since last night,
forbidding me from leaving.
And…
Last night?
What happened last night?
Did we…
What you did last night
was eye-opening.
I think I've found a treasure.
So…
So
I'd like
to ask you this bold question.
Could you…
What?
What is he going to do?
Is he going to propose to me?
But I'm not ready.
Did...
we do that thing
last night?
(Application for Mentorship)
Please
accept me as your student!
What?
I'll be honest with you.
I don't go to the House of Art
to see the girls.
I just want to learn
their singing and dance skills.
It wasn't until
I saw your performance last night
did I know
that they are nothing
in comparison with you.
So why don't I learn
from a good teacher around me?
When I saw you for the first time,
my heart raced
like I had cardiac disease.
Saw me for the first time?
It's a wonderful night.
Let's take a picture.
What is this glowing
little box?
A cellphone.
What is a cellphone?
How come we're in it
but not so quite?
Don't be daft.
It's a cellphone.
Just treat it like a mirror.
Come on. Come on.
Mirror? Mirror?
Come and take a picture.
Mirror?
Say cheese.
So
he just wants to learn
how to dance from me.
Meng Xiaofan,
you were being delusional.
So,
what's in it for me?
You'll get paid for sure.
And the broken vase,
we'll write it off.
Write it off?
This is good.
And
once I'm Xie Xun's tutor,
I can stay by his side.
It'll be easy for me
to steal Five-addictive Wine.
She'll name a big price.
It's obvious that she is
a greedy woman.
But
as long as
she's willing to teach me the skills,
it's all worthwhile.
To show my sincerity,
I'll leave the blank lines
in our contract.
If you agree to tutor me,
you can fill in whatever you like.
But I'll make one thing clear.
This tavern
is a family heritage.
The treasure of our family
is the Five-addictive Wine
made by my grandfather.
The winemaking method
is not to be known by others.
You can choose anything else
that your eyes can see.
Deal.
Cousin.
Teacher.
Do I
have to do this?
It is your fingerprint
on the paper.
Plus,
I'm only trying to maximize
the effect of your practice.
With all the clothes on,
how do I observe
the movements of your muscle?
Gosh.
Do I get to see such a beautiful scene
for free?
No, no, no.
I need to be serious.
Um…
No, no.
Your hands.
You're doing it wrong.
They…
Your hands…
Your arms…
You need
to try your best to…
Open your arms.
Teacher.
My foot…
It hurts…
Um…
Stop dancing.
Fulfill your
second duty.
Yes.
It hurts.
This is the first time I do this.
I'll try another spot.
My student.
You need to change your name.
Or it'll be awkward for your fans
to support you.
They can't hold a board
with "Xun" on it, can they?
That would be lame.
You need a stage name.
But I am Xun.
How can you belittle yourself?
My father gave me the name
hoping that I'd be
polite and modest.
And that's
what I've been trying to live up to.
I'd like
to be more and more humble.
No, no, no.
You can be humble
when doing something else.
On the stage,
you have to be dynamic.
Do you feel me?
I've made my decision.
From today on, your name will be...
Xie Tingfeng.
♪Lingers between my fingers
and in my world♪
♪Farewell to your heart♪
♪Enter the emptied room
my tears can't help but♪
♪Blur my vision♪
♪I still remember
through the window on my right♪
♪That I see your smile♪
♪On the day of our reunion
it appears again♪
(Right of communication
through information network)
(reserved by Shenzhen Tencent
Technology Co., Ltd.)