=Childe Xie's Wine=
=Episode 5=
I've made my decision.
From today on, your name will be...
Xie Tingfeng.
You'll have many fans.
I mean listeners.
Audience.
Xie Tingfeng.
A pavilion by the river,
breezes swing by.
What an elegant and unique name.
I didn't expect
that other than
your dancing and singing skills,
your brilliance in literature
is amazing as well.
Thank you for the name.
Nah, nah.
Xie.
Ting.
Feng.
Xie Tingfeng.
Um,
enough.
Let's move on.
Keep practicing.
You'll have
a basic footwork test tomorrow.
Sure, Teacher.
See you tomorrow, Teacher.
Goodnight, Teacher.
(Wuti Tavern)
Murong,
what is this about?
Miss Meng,
it's been nice knowing you.
Farewell.
Where are you going?
I'm going to leave this tavern,
this obscene den,
for another livelihood.
Obscene den?
Now,
the House of Art isn't enough
for Xie Xun, the lewdster, anymore.
He even
brought girls to the tavern.
What?
Last night, I personally heard
those nasty sounds
from his room.
Last night?
Last night, it was me
in Xie Xun's room.
Does
he think Xie Xun and I were…
Murong,
the owner went to bed very early.
Before that,
he asked me to kill some mosquitos.
So
you must have misheard it.
Miss Meng,
you're a good person.
Can't believe you're defending him.
I suggest you
get out of here as well.
He doesn't care about this place,
this tavern.
This tavern
is going to be closed for good
sooner or later.
It will be closed?
Then I won't be able
to drink Five-addictive Wine again.
I will get my old look back.
And I can't have a relationship
with Xie Xun anymore.
No.
I cannot
let that happen!
No.
It mustn't be closed.
I'll manage the tavern.
You always wanted
to learn how
to make those chips, right?
I'll teach you.
Chips?
The small golden bars?
Those are yours?
There are quite some techniques
when making the chips.
Would you like to learn?
These potatoes are nice.
I can tell they were grown
in good soil.
While we clean it,
we cannot damage its character.
Use this brush.
Gently
clean all the crevices.
Gentle
but make sure you clean it.
When you grill,
don't turn them over
until one side is golden brown.
Off the grill, sprinkle some salt.
So that
you get the low-fat, low-salt,
crispy and crunchy chips
of the perfect flavor.
Your invention of that…
That chip thing
is amazing.
The texture is crunchy,
and aftertaste is pleasant.
Tomorrow
I'll try the recipe, too.
Sure.
If you have any problem,
just ask me,
and I'll teach you again.
Um,
I'm going back to my room.
Okay.
Keep it up, Shang.
Keep it up.
Meng Yufan!
Get over here.
What's wrong?
You have four hours.
Chop all the firewood.
Four hours
to chop so much firewood?
Are you messing with me,
Xie Tingfeng?
Hold on.
Don't call me Xie Tingfeng.
You're my dance teacher,
but in normal times,
I'm still your boss.
Start working.
Xie Xun,
you're the worst!
Thank you.
I like you.
When I saw you for the first time,
my heart raced
like I had a cardiac disease.
You said you like me,
but you make bodily contact
with someone else.
I didn't know
you're such a duplicitous woman,
Meng Yufan.
Why did I think that way?
I won't speak to you again.
You're fired!
Disappear!
Leave right away!
You don't want me to get tanned?
I don't want the firewood to burn.
I knew it.
The firewood you chopped
is crooked
and in different sizes.
It won't
pile orderly in the firewood room.
You're going to burn it anyway.
I can chop it
however the way I like it.
I'll chop it into the shape of you.
Show me
if you can.
Look at this one.
Short and thick.
That's your boy Shang.
Shang?
He's like 30 years old.
Is everybody endearing to you?
I thought
you only gave me a stage name.
He's only 19 years old.
He just doesn't look youthful.
You're jealous, right?
You are.
Nonsense.
No way I'm jealous.
That's what I distaste the most.
Then why do you hold
the umbrella here?
You don't want me
to get a heat stroke.
Still in denial?
It isn't for you.
I, uh,
read the weather,
and I think it'll rain.
Ridiculous.
Look how bright the sun is.
Unbelievable.
It's actually raining.
Thankfully, I was quick.
Or the firewood would be ruined.
Just take your time chopping more.
What's wrong with your hand?
Let me see.
I'm okay.
More firewood is waiting for me.
You can beg for my mercy.
I didn't say you had to finish all.
And
it's just a bunch of firewood.
Why so serious?
Em…
Shang
said the tavern
is in deficit again.
If the firewood got wet,
it'd make things worse.
If it goes on,
the tavern is going
to be closed for good.
Fine.
I don't mind.
I've been meaning to ask you.
You said the tavern
is a family heritage,
why don't you manage it properly?
It isn't where my aspiration lies.
And this tavern
can't help fulfill my aspiration.
Plus, I hate drinking alcohol.
You never drink?
My grandparents and parents
made their living
through winemaking.
I learned winemaking from them
since I was little.
When I was older,
I became their wine-taster.
But I never tasted any good wine.
It was either sour
or extremely bitter.
I never tasted the so-called
sweetness in wine.
No.
Five-addictive Wine is sweet.
I mean…
Five days.
Five days later,
you'll get some sweet liquor.
What I'm trying to say is,
five days later,
you'll finish your dance lessons.
By then, I'll have a way
for you to realize your dream
in this tavern.
♪Lingers between my fingers
and in my world♪
♪Farewell to your heart♪
♪Enter the emptied room
my tears can't help but♪
♪Blur my vision♪
♪I still remember
through the window on my right♪
♪That I see your smile♪
♪On the day of our reunion
it appears again♪
(Right of communication
through information network)
(reserved by Shenzhen Tencent
Technology Co., Ltd.)