52 DAYS UNTIL ASTEROID COLLISION
JANUARY 1, 2026
No, that's not it.
Why are you speeding up?
You have to follow my hands!
-You were too quick.
-Jang-beom, Dae-han!
I was looking at the lyrics.
-What is this?
-What? Mi-ryeong!
I heard this ragtag bunch was at it,
so I had to show support.
So what if we're a ragtag bunch?
You sounded good from outside.
Hear that?
We're not hearing from those who left.
It was frustrating to stay at home,
so we came here.
And it's nice.
I heard singing is good for your lungs
and your brain too.
You and your wife should keep coming.
Use this chance to sing your heart out.
You bet we will!
Hey, you're good!
No need to applaud her.
Go on. Sorry, Sister.
Singing makes all your worries go away!
-Yeah.
-You all lack confidence.
-Right.
-Sing louder!
-Okay!
-Jang-beom, Dae-han.
-What?
-I saw you mouthing along.
-I wasn't!
-Put in some effort.
-I put effort into mouthing--
-Be serious.
Ready, go.
Are we starting from the top again?
Oh, okay.
Here we go.
I felt like coming back.
After three days with my family,
I was tired of them.
Are you back for good?
For now.
But I quite liked traveling around.
Play a game of soccer before you go.
Sounds good.
Wait.
Do they know I'm coming?
-No.
-Wait…
Get the scarf off of me. Everything.
Father!
What is it?
Goodness.
-Hello, Father.
-Hi.
Okay, that's enough.
-Will you be okay?
-Yes, I'm fine.
He said he wanted to come,
so I brought him here.
I didn't know
so many of you would be here.
What's going on?
Don't worry.
Thank you
for greeting me
with such reverence.
I am thankful to the Lord
for his grace and lofty will.
Now that Christmas has come,
let us reflect on…
He's not in his right mind.
Christmas was days ago.
…our foolishness, which led us to doubt…
Just wait.
…and neglect his intricate plan
that we couldn't dare fathom.
Do repent for such mistakes in your past.
We are here on earth
while the Lord is high above us…
Wait, where are the altar boys?
And why are there
no liturgical objects here?
Heavens.
Who's reading the Bible today?
-Man, it went out again.
-Don't worry about it.
Yun-sang, why don't you take
Father Baek and leave?
You'll catch a cold, Father.
Yeah, hurry up and go.
It's cold here even with the heater on
because the ceilings are high.
Take him home.
Patients are extra vulnerable this winter.
With no medicine,
there's little we can do.
Yeah, we don't want him
to get terribly ill.
Go.
My wife beat COVID.
Now she might die from a simple cold.
Come on!
Why is it so noisy outside?
I heard the prisons have failed.
Are the rioters here?
Someone go and take a look outside!
Father, let's go.
Okay.
I mean, what's all the commotion?
I heard the prisons have been destroyed.
Are the rioters barging in?
Goodness, Father.
-Call Mr. Cho, the chief of staff.
-Okay.
Tell him to maintain the security
of Woongcheon, okay?
Where on earth is Mr. Cho right now?
Call him right away.
Tell him to secure the safety
of Woongcheon, okay?
-It's a mess here right now!
-Okay!
END OF THE WORLD
ASTEROID COLLISION IN 200 DAYS
ASTEROID COLLISION IMMINENT
MARTIAL LAW DECLARED
199 DAYS LEFT
CHANCES OF SURVIVAL?
NO INTERNET CONNECTION
198 DAYS LEFT
TOGETHER TO THE END
140 DAYS LEFT
COLLISION CRISIS ALERT
CHEONDONG MIDDLE SCHOOL CLOSED
DO NOT APPROACH
130 DAYS LEFT
SUPERMAN AND WONDERMART
MISSING
BASED ON THE NOVEL SHUMATSU NO FURU
BY KOTARO ISAKA
80 DAYS LATER, OUR ETERNAL LIFE BEGINS
EXPERIENCE THE ETERNAL LIFE
50 DAYS UNTIL THE END
FLOATING BUNKER PRESENTATION
Dear citizens of Woongcheon,
there are only 20 days left
until the asteroid collision.
Though it cannot be confirmed
and we hope it is not true,
the kidnapping and trafficking
of children and adolescents
appears to be occurring again.
It may be best to refrain from
going outside at night, and…
The asteroid will arrive…
in 20 days.
May you find happiness
in the remaining days.
Thank you.
Great job, ma'am. You were amazing.
So that was our last broadcast.
I know.
See you on the outside.
Damn, I'm done with this now.
APPLICATION FOR BIOGRAPHY
MATERIAL DESCRIPTION: WEDDING VIDEO
Aren't you pushing yourself too hard?
Hey, this is private information.
I won't look, okay?
By the way, have you moved in for good?
Yeah. We have a bunch of stuff
we need to do together.
You mean this? Your bucket list?
WRITE A SHORT STORY
TAKE 100 AWESOME PICTURES OF SE-KYUNG
COOK OUR BEST DISHES FOR EACH OTHER
GO ON A CAMPING TRIP
MAKE PEOPLE COFFEE
BEAT SUNG-JAE AT TENNIS
YS BUCKET LIST
NUPTIAL MASS WITH SE-KYUNG
You're gonna be really busy.
I'd appreciate your cooperation.
What should we do first?
Not sure.
Thank you.
I didn't know what to do.
They won't even think
to look for you here.
No one looks twice
at the neighborhood nutcase now.
Um…
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
Do you have any meat?
Meat?
Well, Jin-seo can't eat meat.
Why not?
Because you quit meat.
He ate it all, so there's none left.
I'll get some the next time you visit.
Careful. It's hot.
Is it okay?
I haven't tasted it yet.
How is it?
-Not bad, huh?
-Good.
TAKE WHAT YOU WOULD LIKE
Goodness.
Goodness me.
We are never going to…
end our lives this way.
Oh dear!
Hey, why did you come out?
You said we should starve ourselves
and wait until we die.
Well, it's harder than I thought.
Bibim-guksu.
What?
I want to eat bibim-guksu.
They probably went somewhere safe, right?
-Should we pile it up?
-Yeah.
-It's hard now.
-Hard.
You can't expect me to send them away
to some strangers.
I know.
I know, but…
This city is getting
more and more violent.
It's more dangerous for them here.
We don't know what it's like there.
No one has been there.
What if they're forced into labor
or sexually assaulted…
What if they experience
something terrible?
And, honestly,
I don't know if they'll agree to go.
Hae-chan, Woo-chan, aren't you cold?
-No!
-No.
You have to play together, not alone.
Yes, that's it.
I'll scold them if they bully you.
Don't bother the others like that, okay?
Only authorized personnel
are allowed here!
You should go!
They've got to be kidding me.
Ms. Jin, you can't come here. Go!
Okay.
Men and women alike,
they are crazy over these chickens.
It's cold, huh?
Somehow, this thing kind of feels warm.
-Although it isn't.
-Yeah.
We have no fuel.
-There you are.
-You startled me!
I was just in the area.
What, this works?
-No. The military ran out of gas too.
-No.
I'll give you my warmth.
So how did the candidates react?
Well,
they're not exactly thrilled.
We're trying to send the kids away
since it's dangerous.
But, Se-kyung,
I've been informed
that the terms have changed.
They've gotten stricter.
So I was hoping
Capt. Kang could make it public
and help us in this matter.
People here listen to you
more than they do me.
Is anyone in our neighborhood eligible?
From our neighborhood,
Woo-chan and Hae-chan.
Let's do it.
Let's send them.
We might be letting our own fear
make us worry over nothing.
They could actually be sent
to a good place!
We can't let them live like this,
waiting for death.
Young-ji, I said
you don't have to help out anymore.
14 DAYS UNTIL ASTEROID COLLISION
Goodness, it's cold.
Sister.
What would you do if you were to die
tomorrow and not in two weeks?
I'd do the exact same thing.
The same thing? And what's that?
Well, all I know how to do
is pray and serve.
Come on, that's just church stuff.
Would my life be any different
if I died tomorrow?
I'll just have to do what I can.
What's wrong?
You don't want to go to volunteer work?
You're being really strange today.
The weather is cold, and so is my heart.
Hi there.
Where did you come from?
You can't eat that. You're hungry, huh?
It's a good thing
you didn't get eaten by people.
They say that if dogs love you,
that means you're a good person.
If I die first,
I'd love for this dog to eat me.
What an audacious thing to say.
But I don't have the courage to die
and be your food right now.
If you really die,
the scarier dogs will come for you.
Don't you hear
the asteroid coming to get us?
That kind of joke isn't funny at all.
Let's go.
Let's play soccer!
Why are you here alone?
Se-kyung overslept.
Let's play, guys!
Ma'am!
Mess unit, get in there.
We have no one left to…
-Feed anyway!
Let's go!
Here we go! We're playing soccer!
I'm sorry.
I know it's meaningless at this point.
Captain.
In-a.
They probably won't send a replacement.
I'd like you to take over.
I hope nothing happens,
but keep an eye on the troublemakers
so they don't cause any trouble.
You'll find live ammo in there.
SNACK STORAGE
It's enough to arm all the soldiers.
All thanks to Mess Sergeant So.
The missing ammunition incident--
It's a long story.
But don't worry. The ammunition is clean.
I'm sorry
for dumping all this on you.
You're the commander of this unit now.
So do a good job.
Captain!
Please work.
Hang in there.
In-a.
You look different today.
Where's Se-kyung?
"This is goodbye."
In-a, what are you…
You seemed to like running into operations
and shooting guns.
Why didn't you become a soldier or a cop?
I don't like the uniform.
After venting on my mom,
I came to a decision.
Where do you get the energy?
From all the squats you do?
Come on!
Just listen. I'm serious.
I realized that I've lived
a dull life until now.
Why are you looking back
on your life all of a sudden?
I wanted to get recognized so much.
That led me to think I had to
take responsibility for everything.
Please stop. What are you trying to say?
And I…
did get overprotective
and overanxious about you at times.
You're not apologizing, are you?
As if.
Instead…
You have the gun, right?
Yeah.
You do the protecting.
I hereby report
that I was formally discharged
on February 8th, 2026.
In-a!
You've done well…
this whole time.
10 DAYS UNTIL ASTEROID COLLISION
Not that.
You crazy-ass junkie!
You said you knew some kids, right?
This is your last chance.
Three kids for one boarding pass.
Okay.
What's it gonna be?
Just three kids, right?
Of course.
You crazy bastard.
Your eyes look ridiculous!
Three will do.
-Hey, let's go to the den.
-Yes, sir.
Good job.
Good work.
It looks like those bastards
are putting kids in containers
and shipping them off again.
Since this is their last job,
they're just bent on hitting the number,
so they might be careless.
It's the last ship they will send
before the asteroid hits.
Woo-chan, what should we pack?
This and this.
Let's see.
-Okay.
-The penguin?
-You'll take the penguin too?
-Yeah!
-And the dinosaurs.
-Okay.
Let's pack everything for now.
Bring them here, Woo-chan.
Woo-chan…
Hae-chan, do you need help?
So-min, I don't want to go.
I'm scared.
Don't worry too much.
There'll be lots of food there,
and it won't be cold.
You and Woo-chan will make
a lot of good friends.
Hae-chan.
You and Woo-chan need to go
and live a happy life there.
But why only us?
What about So-min? What about you?
You know what?
I'll come visit you two no matter what.
Liar.
Hae-chan, let me hug you.
Let me hug you. Woo-chan, you too.
Let Auntie give you a hug!
And my daughter. Come here.
That's my girl.
The world falls into ruin,
but with you by my side,
I'd sacrifice everything--
Just go and move our stuff.
What shall we eat for dinner?
Don't know.
Really?
HI, THIS IS SUPERMAN AND WONDERMART
THE TIME HAS COME FOR US TO CLOSE UP SHOP
I'll carry that.
It's okay, but thank you.
Are you doing okay?
Yeah.
Are you going out to work again?
No, I'm taking the older ladies
for a drive.
Do you want to come too?
Should I?
Goodness, I guess our soccer team is done
now that Ji-eun and Mi-ryeong are leaving.
Come on, they're not leaving for good.
Don't you worry.
When the time comes, they'll all return.
Isn't that right?
Yes, that's right.
I'll come back again.
But will you really be okay
when you're with child?
Yes.
But
there's a chance we won't come back.
Where are you heading? Take me with you
if you're going someplace nice.
It's nothing like that.
Sister, there are no nice places
left in this world.
This church is the best place to be
to find your way to heaven.
Yes, that's true.
What is all this?
Oh, Father.
I brought some stuff here
after cleaning out the supermarket.
Sister, you're leaving again?
Sung-jae.
Oh my.
Were they that close?
Mi-ryeong!
You should call him "Father."
Dae-han.
Keep lying to yourself, and you'll go
to hell alone when the world ends.
You do have a face
that's well-suited for hell.
Let's go to heaven.
I'm leaving this guy behind.
I'm off to see Ms. Kim.
Need a ride?
I'll keep the chatter short.
Is In-a going to come back?
Why is the door open?
For ventilation while I'm cleaning.
Have a seat.
Is Se-kyung going somewhere?
She's going to visit Bo-ae.
So she went out to work.
Too bad. I came to offer some prayers
for you newlyweds.
You brought out the homemade liquor.
Shall we drink it all tonight?
You know, a while back…
Yeah?
You said
that I only saw Se-kyung
as a cheerful and generous person, right?
Did I?
I think I did see her that way
at the time.
And it's true I liked her for that.
But it's different now.
I don't feel like I need to be by her side
or I need to protect her.
She's just…
someone I'll be with to the end.
That is very special.
We'll all die together in ten days.
Does that mean…
we're all special to each other?
Help me if you want to be special!
Why, yes, sir.
I'll take special care in cleaning.
How much have you cleaned so far?
Can't you tell?
Following you, sir.
Follow my lead, sir!
I don't want this.
Please stop it.
You're pretty.
Ms. Jin.
I don't want to get married.
Then you don't have to.
But, Ms. Jin, you got married, right?
I did get married,
but I can't say that it's great.
If you got married,
why are you telling me not to?
I know, right?
Why did I tell the kids
not to do so many things?
Are you crying, Ms. Jin?
Don't cry.
I know why you're being like this.
No.
No one knows. No one.
Even I don't know anymore.
If I had killed your son,
would things have turned out differently?
What if I followed my students
after they had died?
No, what if I pursued my studies
like my boyfriend did?
For both you
and me…
if this is the result of our choices…
I imagine a world…
where we make different choices.
Even though it's meaningless.
I don't want that.
These are the only things I have left.
The ones you can actually use.
You know how to use them, right?
Those guys are badasses.
They have no mercy.
I know. But I brought this on myself.
But the end is near. Why bother…
It was you?
Why are you so surprised?
Where's Ha-yul?
Ha-yul…
Ms. Jin.
Did you see any rough-looking men
on your way here?
Do you see men like that out there?
It's crazy these days.
We're so scared
that we can't even go outside--
You didn't see…
Sergeant Kim nearby, did you?
I didn't.
SERGEANT KIM
You guys can live if you leave.
I'll treat you nicely
and give you a gun too.
Jeong Ha-yul, bring both of your friends.
Don't do anything dangerous, Ms. Jin.
You'll really die if…
Why would I die?
I'm not going to die, okay?
If I have to die, I will die…
after I see you guys
grow up into adults.
Then…
I don't want to become an adult.
I didn't know.
Everything kept passing by,
but I didn't even realize it.
Take me there.
To my grave on the mountain ridge.
Wait.
Goodbye
to this world.
Goodbye, my neighborhood.
Goodbye now,
mothers and fathers.
The spontaneous musical clock.
And the garden we all tended to, farewell.
The delicious food and coffee.
The freshly ironed clothes
and bathhouses steaming with hot water.
Falling asleep
and waking up.
Dear Earth,
that no one knows the true value of
for it is so beautiful and magnificent…
goodbye.