I poured some homemade liquor.
Would you like a glass?
Se-kyung.
I have something to show you.
With this,
we can leave this place.
Let's go.
We can leave together with this.
Se-kyung.
Let's leave.
END OF THE WORLD
ASTEROID COLLISION IN 200 DAYS
ASTEROID COLLISION IMMINENT
MARTIAL LAW DECLARED
199 DAYS LEFT
CHANCES OF SURVIVAL?
NO INTERNET CONNECTION
198 DAYS LEFT
TOGETHER TO THE END
140 DAYS LEFT
COLLISION CRISIS ALERT
CHEONDONG MIDDLE SCHOOL CLOSED
DO NOT APPROACH
130 DAYS LEFT
SUPERMAN AND WONDERMART
MISSING
BASED ON THE NOVEL SHUMATSU NO FURU
BY KOTARO ISAKA
80 DAYS LATER, OUR ETERNAL LIFE BEGINS
EXPERIENCE THE ETERNAL LIFE
50 DAYS UNTIL THE END
FLOATING BUNKER PRESENTATION
192 DAYS UNTIL ASTEROID COLLISION
-Hey, this place is huge.
-It is.
You could fit 200 soccer fields in here.
You reckon?
Do you think
the US troops left anything behind?
I bet they did. They left in a rush.
-You think the bike might get stolen?
-Yeah.
We still have 193,
no, 192 days left, so I need it.
Right, some eager idiots out there
might want to steal it.
Whatever.
That's So-min's number one treasure.
No, that's number two.
Whoa, then what's number one?
Ms. Jin.
Are you serious?
-Yeah.
-Your number one was a person?
I'm worried.
About what?
Ms. Jin's acting a bit strange these days.
She looks down for some reason.
Like when?
She didn't seem happy
when they caught the bad guys.
The Ms. Jin we know
would've been crazy happy about that.
Strange, huh?
And Yun-sang came back,
so why is she like that?
Let's sweep the place.
I'll go that way!
-Me too.
-I'll go this way.
You go.
Great people of Woongcheon.
Good news.
The rescue operation from the brothel
was a success!
But it wasn't done
by the Joint Investigation Unit.
And just because
that one place was swept clean,
it doesn't mean that the neighborhood
will become an amazing place
that befits the class of this city.
But for now, attention.
A salute
to our proud Special Warfare veterans!
We salute you!
At ease.
The JIU must be
pretty bitter right now, huh?
Drop and give me 50!
By the way,
did the actual owner
of the brothel really just vanish?
Something smells fishy.
Real fishy.
They say the owner vanished.
What about it?
You checked properly, right?
Did you?
In-a.
In-a, wait.
Wait up. Just a second!
I need some water.
Wait here.
I'll give you ten seconds.
"Vanished." That's all you need to know.
What?
My bike.
Use it.
How much longer will you run?
Wait for me. I'm dying here!
Wait for me!
I forgot this was your place.
Wow.
Let me go and wash up.
I'll see you.
A gang that imprisoned underage girls
and exploited them for prostitution
has been arrested.
Most minors who went missing
after the asteroid announcement
were speculated to have been funneled
into adult entertainment establishments.
Through this incident,
we confirmed this to be true.
Next.
Migration to safe zone countries
has been completely suspended.
For those who have received news
from family or friends
who migrated to a safe zone…
Here.
You can share these
with your friends or sell them.
They were in storage.
I remembered how much Jae-won liked them.
It upsets me.
They left so they could survive.
They are in a safe place.
Some say we're all going to die anyway.
That again!
You know, I had a dream last night.
-A dream?
-I turned on the television.
And the president came on.
What do you call it?
The satellite broadcast or something.
The US president was speaking
into a bunch of microphones.
Well, what did the president say?
"We have done some recalculations
and discovered
that the asteroid
isn't going to hit Earth."
"I apologize
for all the trouble we have caused."
The president's face was all red
as they kept bowing to the audience.
You're so optimistic, even in your dreams.
Right, there's no way the US president
would speak a word of Korean.
I miss Jae-won so much.
I don't know what to do.
We're going all the way to the top today.
Hae-chan, can we have a break here?
But you have to find the gems.
Look, you found another one.
Woo-chan, you have so much treasure.
You're a rich boy now.
Let's go.
Hello.
Hey, So-min!
-So-min.
-Yeah?
Hey, why don't you take the kids
and go play at home?
They seem to be straying
too far from home these days.
Hae-chan's not home again?
That's right. So get moving and find them.
You go!
Don't you see I'm making money right now?
Stop petting the dog
and go look for the kids.
-Fine.
-Go.
The same goes for you too.
Don't wander around, okay?
-Okay.
-Yeah.
Check the playground first.
If they're not there,
check the alleys too.
Good morning.
I understand,
but I'm still upset.
If you understand, why are you upset?
Even if you forgot that I was back,
shouldn't you be happy to see me?
You looked surprised
but not in a happy way.
You were startled out of your skin, as if…
"As if"?
As if…
In the year we spent apart,
which felt like 100 years,
we each went through a different hell.
So it's okay to be a little startled.
Yun-sang. Se-kyung.
-Se-kyung, get in the car.
-Hey, forgive me.
Hey, wait!
Yun-sang.
I have an important proposal to make.
You have to listen to me.
-What's that?
-Where?
What? Hey!
It's like he sniffed you out or something.
How did he show up right away?
I know, right?
-Se-kyung.
-This is crazy.
Are you going to talk to him?
Can you forgive that jerk?
-No.
-Se-kyung.
Let's go. Yeah.
It's a huge proposal.
You have to listen to--
Hey, Yun-sang!
Yun-sang!
Yun-sang, I have an important…
One, two, three!
Wow, there's so much to eat!
-Do you like it?
-Yeah!
Hae-chan, I miss Mommy.
Me too.
This is yummy.
Hae-chan.
Auntie, sorry. So-min, sorry.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
Are you okay? You're not hurt anywhere?
Woo-chan, are you okay?
Dear Lord, thank you.
Thank you, Lord.
I'm sorry, okay?
I've been so distracted with gold
and all the panic talk going around
that I didn't even know where you play.
I mean, how?
How did you
think about taking shelter here?
I actually came here with Mom before.
I said I wanted to live
in a place like this, and she…
Okay, why don't we sleep here
for the night?
Come here, everyone!
Ga-eul, you too.
-What is this?
-"I have butterflies."
-It's scary.
-What was that?
"I have butterflies."
Have you?
Have you got butterflies?
At this rate,
we won't last 100 days, let alone 200.
What we need more than ammunition
is food and snacks.
You all keep saying that,
but there's nothing I can do.
Are you saying
you don't have any solutions?
We commanders spend our days
running around begging for food.
Isn't this just wrong?
That's why we told you to let your men go
and hire mercenaries instead.
-Hey, fuck this shit, man.
-What?
Kim Gyu-tae, what did you just say?
What? Do you think
we're just a bunch of idiots?
You suck-ups gave all we had
to those who fled the country,
and now you tell us to let our men go?
You're asking for it!
I can shoot you for insubordination!
Go ahead, shoot me!
That asteroid will fucking kill me anyway!
-Tired, huh?
-No, ma'am.
You seem tired.
Shall we stop by the rest stop?
Yes, ma'am.
Drink!
OUT OF FUEL
DO NOT DAMAGE THE GAS PUMPS
-One more glass!
-Who cares about life?
Bottoms up!
Who made this? It's so good!
What a waste.
Ma'am!
We leave in 15 minutes.
Leaving in 15 minutes. See you, ma'am.
Ma'am.
Thank you for your service.
I was discharged just two months ago.
Come grab a bite.
We're having budaejjigae.
No, thank you.
It's a woman.
-She's badass.
-The combat support commander, right?
-That's her?
-Yeah.
That's right. She leads a trash unit.
That's not true.
I heard that girl's different.
She's a goner now.
A former Special Missions Unit member.
Really?
During the civil war,
her boss was fired for insubordination.
-Oh dear.
-The unit was disbanded.
And they all scattered.
She was sent here
because she's from Woongcheon.
-Goodness me.
-Really?
Excuse me. Someone's in there, right?
I think I heard a cat. Am I right?
I'm a soldier, by the way.
I couldn't just pass by.
Step on it!
Hold this.
-The Mass?
-Did you hear about it?
-The SMU raided the brothel.
-I get what you're saying.
-Ms. Joo, is that your daughter's unit?
-You can't change things suddenly--
Father!
That was no mean feat.
They are an amazing team.
My thoughts exactly!
Father Woo is here.
The deputy mayor swore she'd get rid of it
but couldn't do a thing.
The Martial Law Command and the JIU,
those higher-ups were somehow
related to the brothel.
A symbiotic relationship!
You're so smart!
So good with words.
Father.
They'll go to hell, right?
Well, it's a huge relief.
The missing kids were rescued,
and above all,
I'm glad I can speak of hope
at the joint memorial mass.
Hope? Yeah, right.
Father, that's not
what's important right now.
What?
The deputy mayor wants the memorial Mass
to be much bigger, for the entire city.
What?
She changed the venue
to the city hall square.
City hall?
That makes no sense. How can I--
No, Father.
It seems like the success of the mop-up
has inspired the deputy mayor.
She must be having a surge of motivation.
You have to do it.
Believers and non-believers alike,
we've all been waiting for this.
Think of all the hardships
we went through.
-Yeah!
-You're right.
We just want to get together
to remember the deceased.
Okay. Excuse me.
You haven't given us your answer!
Do it!
-Let's just get ready for the Mass.
-Yeah.
The memorial Mass will be at city hall.
OKTOKKI
First things first,
we have to get the rehearsal down right.
It's your first time
leading a big event by yourself.
So this is how God tests me.
Just thinking about it
makes my legs shake.
Oh no. What do we do?
In the afternoon, a truckload of people
will be coming in for confessions.
Why, thank you for the morale boost.
It's really encouraging. I mean it.
It is what it is.
To be honest,
for the people left here with no options,
the only thing they can do
is confess their sins.
Right.
You can do it.
I have to do it.
-It's so hot here!
-Okay.
The AC isn't working well.
-I'll look into it.
-We're fixing it.
Hello.
Ma'am!
Having the joint memorial Mass
at the city hall square is a huge task.
We've never done it before,
and we have no time.
I know. I'm aware of it,
but the raid was successful.
Right?
We gave the citizens hope that
we could accomplish something on our own.
-Yes, that's right.
-One more thing.
The president's chief of staff said
he'll be attending the Mass.
What?
Is he still in the country?
He couldn't leave.
He said he would be leaving together
with the president and the prime minister,
but the truth is, he didn't make the list.
Mother.
How are your knees? You're seeing
the oriental medicine doctor, right?
Mother, I think you should refrain
from going out for the time being.
Things are chaotic here too.
Don't you worry.
Hey, In-tae!
Cho In-tae!
Enough with this!
You can't avoid your father forever!
Come out!
Just let him be.
We should be thankful that he stays home
and doesn't wander around outside.
It's because you always side with him
that everything just goes to his head,
and he acts like this.
Well, that's what kids are like.
Hey, In-tae!
Cho In-tae!
Cho In-tae.
It's your father. Come out.
Let's talk.
I know you're in there!
When will you grow up?
Are you gonna stay in there forever?
Come out!
Cho In-tae! Come out!
No.
If I come out, you'll beat me!
Just what in the hell
are you doing in there?
You punk!
Come out and eat,
or you can starve to death in there!
I'll behave.
Don't beat me.
I'm sorry.
Eat before you go.
No, I have to leave right away.
-Please take good care of my mother.
-Of course.
Thank you for everything.
Oh, and there will be good news soon.
Trust me.
The plants need water.
They're wilting.
Yes, well…
By the way,
despite the migration ban
for high-ranking officials,
your family must be escaping soon,
seeing how relaxed you are.
Without my money, he'd have nothing.
He's probably looking for
an immigration sponsor
because he's afraid
I won't offer up my money.
Excuse me?
Being a former prosecutor
and high-ranking official
may mean something here.
But for safe zone countries,
they're free to choose
which immigrants they take in.
What use would they have
for a former prosecutor from South Korea?
They will want people with the skills
they need, like scientists and engineers.
Don't you think?
Yes, ma'am.
You're right.
SONG, JIU
Meet me at the memorial Mass.
There's someone you need to meet.
I was with my family
when I entered the facility,
but then I suddenly got dragged away.
Is there anything else
you'd like to tell me?
Confessions will begin soon.
SISTER REGINA - CONFESSIONS AT 2 P.M.
I live in Seoul,
so I don't know this place at all.
Ma'am, I'm safe here, right?
If this is too hard,
you don't have to say any more.
-I can't talk about the training center.
-Training center…
SEPARATED FROM FAMILY AT TRAINING CENTER
Training center.
ADMITTED TO THE TRAINING CENTER
WITH HER FAMILY LAST JUNE
TRAINING CENTER MANAGER IM?
CAPTAIN KANG IN-A
In-a.
Hey.
What's all that stuff?
You should be asking about her instead.
She has a number of injuries.
Take care of her. I have to get back.
Okay.
I'll get going now.
You can direct your questions to her.
She knows a lot of people who can help.
Okay.
Hey, that's it?
You should at least introduce us…
Let me. It'll be better if I carry it.
It's okay.
Let's head inside.
Captain?
Yeah?
I think I saw her picture
in the central lobby.
-The school lobby?
-Yes.
"Proud alumni of Cheondong.
Chae Young-ji."
Private Na, you are one of them too.
She went to an elite university.
It's 20 minutes to base, right?
I'm gonna get some shut-eye.
Yes, ma'am.
The results are good.
No diseases to worry about.
Drink up.
Ms. Jin, this is her ID card.
I'll take a quick look.
PERSONAL MEDICAL RECORDS
CHAE YOUNG-JI
How did you get all these injuries?
I just fell.
Unit 306, Building 12?
I live in Unit 305.
You live next door to Ms. Jin.
But how come we've never met?
I've rarely visited home
since I went to high school.
I guess we missed each other.
I was here until I finished university.
I moved out when I started working.
I was assigned to Cheondong Middle School
two years ago.
Two years ago…
Those who have been saved
will live in a dazzling heaven on Earth.
Give us our money back!
After the flames cover the sky
and the ground melts from the hot fire,
under a new sky promised to us,
we will find a new land
where there's no death or pain…
Where did you hide the kids?
Chae Young-ji.
The system of order on Earth
has been destroyed,
and now we must follow the principles
of the universe to return to our roots.
All life on Earth will cease to exist.
After the flames cover the sky
and the ground melts from the hot fire,
we will start a new life
in a beautiful place.
You are all standing
in the dominion of salvation.
Come this way.
Come in. It's okay.
This way.
It's fortunate that you don't have
any dead or missing family.
I guess some are meant to leave
and some come back.
Capt. Kang used to serve in Icheon,
but returned as part of a supporting unit.
Sit down here.
You have to report your return
to get your ration card.
Se-kyung!
Yun-sang, did you come
to get your ration card?
Who is that?
Woongcheon's second returnee
after Ha Yun-sang.
In-a brought her here.
I'm helping her report her return.
-She lives next door to me.
-Next door?
Yeah, Unit 306.
Young-ji.
This man lives in Unit 205.
He's our neighbor.
It's nice to meet you.
I came back recently too.
Then I guess there's hope.
Hope? Is there someone you're waiting for?
Ms. Jin.
You can get your ration tickets here.
I'm telling you this because Capt. Kang
wanted us to keep an eye on her.
Those cuts and bruises
aren't from an accident.
-She was assaulted.
-What?
She denies it.
But I looked up the physical exam records
for graduates of Cheondong Middle School.
-And her parents--
-You found her parents?
Her mother, Do Jeong-a, went missing
in the pyramid scheme incident.
REMAINING FAMILY MEMBERS
CHAE YOUNG-HAN
CHAE YOUNG-JI, 22ND ALUMNI CLASS
ADMITTED TO POSTECH
We have a new student from Ulsan--
My name is Na Hyeon-jae.
I'm an idol trainee.
Quiet! Let's see, you can sit--
That seat's empty.
Next to Chae Young-ji?
Open your books.
Hi.
Are you Young-ji?
I told you
to clean the board before class.
She has a cat.
Awesome!
It's a cat.
I hope we can be good neighbors.
Thank you for everything.
Have you had dinner?
It's okay. I have some food left.
You should have a home-cooked meal
now that you're home.
This guy's a great cook.
Yes, he is!
We'll leave some food out here
and ring your bell twice.
Thank you so much.
Get some rest.
Ms. Jin, was that really a cat?
-Quiet!
-I wanna stroke it!
Let's let the girl and the cat rest
so they can settle in.
-Be quiet.
-Can we really stroke it?
It's so cute!
Yeah, it was really cute.
But you guys are even cuter. Go!
-Ji-eun!
-Hey.
Hey, you're here.
All right.
JOINT MEMORIAL MASS - AUGUST 17
CITY HALL MEMORIAL SQUARE
I assume we all have things
to confess before we die.
Ji-eun, what sins have you committed?
It's nothing like that.
You know, it's the least I can do
to get through these times.
Yeah, that's right.
Mi-ryeong.
Where's Se-kyung?
In the hideout, with the Three Musketeers.
About Min-ho…
Are you okay…
No one is okay.
But
we can't just go on feeling sorry
for each other until the end.
Is that why Se-kyung can stay so strong?
You should leave.
I know that's why you're here.
The two of you should leave quietly
to a safe place right now.
Mi-ryeong!
LIFE SCIENTIST HA YUN-SANG
13TH ALUMNI CLASS, CHEONDONG MIDDLE SCHOOL
-Captain.
-Yeah?
Do you know him or what?
Dr. Ha Yun-sang.
Cheondong Middle School's hero
and a Nobel laureate in the making.
He's cute.
-Mess Sergeant.
-Yes?
Why do we only have seven fertilized eggs?
Captain, seven eggs is an awful lot.
I used the salt water trick.
You put all the eggs
in concentrated salt water,
and then you pick out the ones that sink.
I'll have to monitor these ones
for another eight days.
-Salt water?
-Yeah.
Is that method scientifically proven?
Now, that's something
I never really thought about.
But if these babies hatch later on,
grow up, and start laying eggs,
then they'll provide us
with some protein, don't you think?
Look at the boys' faces.
They're all malnourished.
The command sergeant major said sausages
will be coming in to the supply depot,
but there's no way we'll get any.
-Fuckers.
-Sergeant First Class So.
Yes?
Tell me,
why is my name on this--
Hush now, Captain.
The babies can hear you.
Why don't you name it "Hush"?
You need to be careful
when changing names, Captain.
Why is that one "Chun-sik"?
That's my father's name.
So Chun-sik.
IN-A, MIMI, PUPPY, KISS
Father, I'm just asking. If I were to say…
that I am pregnant…
should I keep the baby?
All life…
is the will of the Lord.
Thank you, Father.
I am jealous of those who abandoned
this neighborhood and left.
If I could, I would take all the money
I could get my hands on and leave.
Father, are you listening?
Yes, please go on.
So…
I…
For two years, when Father Baek was here,
I made donations
to the church extension funds,
and now I keep thinking
that I want that money back.
I can't stop thinking about it,
and it tortures me
that I'm even thinking such things,
and I feel guilty.
Sister.
Yes?
What you have to remember is
that the Lord
is always by our side.
No. I think he's only with the rich folks
who've got it all.
Goodness, I…
I'm having these thoughts again.
I will repent of my sins.
Good job, Father.
I've been waiting for so long.
Don't tell me you're here to confess.
Of course not.
I'm a law-abiding citizen, you know.
Sure.
What's up?
Hong Gi-pyo.
That bastard showed up.
What?
Man, that guy's as shameless as ever.
He got on his knees
and said he was sorry, but…
I think he's plotting something.
What are you…
Lord,
please forgive these poor little lambs.
What could he be up to?
If he was really sorry,
he shouldn't have come to you.
Are you going to rehearse
for the memorial Mass?
Is Jin-seo not here yet?
I told him to come too.
Oh, right.
There he is.
Hi, Father. Hi, Sister.
-Hi, guys.
-Hello.
Yun-sang, can you wait?
Okay.
Don't ring that now, Andrea.
What?
I mean, this memorial Mass
isn't going to be at the church.
It will be at the city hall square.
We can't afford any mistakes, Father.
What if I make a mistake?
The audience will laugh at you.
Please, call them "believers."
Yun-sang.
In my sermon, should I say something
about international politics?
You know about that stuff.
Forget it. Stick to what you know, Father.
Okay.
Oh, and about the liturgy that day,
is Sister Sophia from Group 8
going to handle it?
Yes. Someone from Group 8
will be the lector as well.
I'm not sure
if the choir could get together.
They won't even have time to practice.
I think I'll have to meet
Brother Kang Joseph.
Can I help you?
I came for a confession.
Sung-jae.
-Are you a member of the church?
-A member? No, I'm not.
If so, please go to the education center
and register for a catechism.
We offer a fast-track course now.
There's a fast-track course?
Sister's got sales skills!
Oh my, Jesus!
Yun-sang!
Come out.
No one here
is going to hear your confession.
Don't you really wanna know
what the big proposal is?
You think I'm here
just to ask for forgiveness?
You know what it's like.
Seniors in any lab are bound to be evil.
I went through the same thing myself.
That's what you came to tell me?
No.
Right.
I shouldn't have done what I did.
Okay, fine.
When Prof. Hong told me
to set up the new project,
I pocketed 300 million won from the funds.
I framed you for it, and I know
you went to the US to avoid me.
It was truly persistent slander.
It's why Se-kyung suggested I leave.
Yeah.
I wronged you.
What, do you want me to get down
on my knees again?
Hey.
You're still naive, aren't you?
Our entire lab is moving
to a class-one safe zone.
But in order to get there, we need you!
Do you even know
why you had to go through all that grind?
You were nothing but a lab nerd.
I bet you had no idea
how your experiments were being used.
See? You've got to be kidding me.
You don't know, do you?
But I know exactly how you can be of use!
Global funds have their eyes
on this project.
It's organized by one of the Vatican's
asset management companies.
And it's made a fortune
during the asteroid crisis,
so funds and foundations in Korea
are dying to hop on this train!
They're all going crazy over this!
I have no idea what you're saying.
How do I even trust you?
This is the backdrop behind
all the missing public figure cases!
Those in charge of big public funds,
where did they run off to?
What?
You want an example?
The mayor of Woongcheon.
No. There's another one.
How about your godfather?
Father Baek Sang-Hyeok!
Hey, In-a!
Open the window. Open it!
You were going to pass by me, weren't you?
You and that temper of yours.
Just tell me what you want.
I mean, you came all the way here,
right in front of your mother's house.
How can you not drop by once?
Because it's your house, not ours.
I can't believe that brat is my daughter.
They don't provide medicine,
but they give out a lot of these.
Why don't you drink one?
I'm okay.
Has anyone seen
the mother of the girl in Unit 306?
I don't think
I've ever spoken to the mother.
I live next door,
and I've never even seen her.
I heard her son left school in first grade
to go to an alternative school.
Her daughter went to
a science high school.
Maybe that's why
their mother was never at home.
You all have such big mouths.
So the word is out already.
Unit 306 is the family that got caught up
in that pyramid scheme mess.
That's right. I remember the father
coming to our church to meet Father Baek.
Min-ho was so excited to have a friend
who was good at math and science.
But he suddenly transferred.
It was rumored that the mother
ran the pyramid scheme herself.
But I had no idea
that they had a daughter that old.
Even Hong Gi-pyo knew about it.
You're a priest of this church,
and you didn't know?
Sung-jae.
Has Father Baek really gone missing?
You can't reach him,
but that doesn't mean he's missing.
What's wrong with you? You're scaring me.
I don't know anything about that stuff.
You really don't know?
Or are you hiding things from me?
Hey, Yun-sang. You shouldn't…
Hey, you can't just barge into his room!
Please calm down.
Look, I wish I had something to hide!
If I knew something,
why would I hide it from you?
What is it that you do know?
Hey, Ha Yun-sang!
Listen.
Do you think I enjoy being in the dark?
If Father Baek were alive, if he were
still in this world, as you say,
do you think
he would've left us like this? Do you?
Tell me!
It's In-a's bike.
Se-kyung.
Look at this. She ate it all.
"Thank you for the delicious meal."
What a relief.
I'm glad. You were worried about her.
Exactly.
Good night.
I'll see you in the morning.
Well done today.
Bye!
Yeah, bye.
Damn it!
-Father!
-Damn!
No one can open that door.
Unless there's a fire.
Father Baek was the only one
who knew the passcode.
What do you think happened, by the way?
What?
"Father Baek has already passed away."
Or "He has already fled to a safe zone."
Maybe I've been too oblivious,
as a priest and as a human being.
May I ask
what you are on about all of a sudden?
I was under a big umbrella
by the name of Father Baek,
so maybe I thought that…
I didn't have to know about
all these problems.
It's good that you didn't have to know.
You know what?
That, too, is power.
Ignorance. It's a privilege for the few.
Yes, ignorance.
I really hope
that tomorrow never comes!
What's with him?
Throwing a fit won't stop it from coming.
This is the Martial Law Command
of Woongcheon.
The curfew has been lifted.
The current time and date
is 05:00, August 17, 2025.
Father.
-Disaster brings new beginnings.
-Once the darkness passes, a bright light…
Chae Young-ji.
Tae-mi.
WOOYANG TRAINING CENTER
Young-han's playing
is getting better by the day.
I wanted to see Young-ji too.
She says she's not feeling well.
We can't take them all with us.
But we have to take Dr. Ha Yun-sang.
Yes. Of course we do.
I'm counting on you, Father.