Yun-sang, come here.
Huh?
What is it?
It's okay.
I'm okay.
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
No, never mind.
It's nothing.
END OF THE WORLD
ASTEROID COLLISION IN 200 DAYS
ASTEROID COLLISION IMMINENT
MARTIAL LAW DECLARED
199 DAYS LEFT
CHANCES OF SURVIVAL?
NO INTERNET CONNECTION
198 DAYS LEFT
TOGETHER TO THE END
140 DAYS LEFT
COLLISION CRISIS ALERT
CHEONDONG MIDDLE SCHOOL CLOSED
DO NOT APPROACH
130 DAYS LEFT
SUPERMAN AND WONDERMART
MISSING
BASED ON THE NOVEL SHUMATSU NO FURU
BY KOTARO ISAKA
80 DAYS LATER, OUR ETERNAL LIFE BEGINS
EXPERIENCE THE ETERNAL LIFE
50 DAYS UNTIL THE END
FLOATING BUNKER PRESENTATION
The next glass is for all the people
who loved Café Moira.
When the asteroid hits,
pretty much everyone will die.
They will all die anyway.
It's the express train to death.
Okay, everyone.
First, we're going to give you
a health checkup here at the hospital.
And then… You're here!
Evening, Father.
-Then we'll let you rest and play.
-Are you okay?
So listen to the doctors,
and be good during the checkup.
-Hi.
-Hello.
-Let's go inside.
-Young-ji!
Just follow the doctor.
Se-kyung.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Thank you.
I'll get my brother examined.
Se-kyung.
Please look after Yun-sang.
In-a and I are a bit busy.
-Stay in line.
-Okay.
This way.
No, you have to go inside.
-Director Ri.
-Yes?
I know you'll do well, but if the parents
or the investigators show up,
please call the base.
Their safety comes first.
I'll keep an eye out.
Thank you.
Things are pretty much wrapped up here.
How on earth did those punks
find out so quickly?
It doesn't look like you're hurt.
Capt. Kang.
Come with us.
Bring Private Na Hyeon-jae too.
Also, she's an accomplice,
he's a witness from the scene,
and the shooter--
Excuse me.
Can we do this tomorrow?
Why do you think
we're here in such a rush?
Do you seriously think
they're gonna run away?
-Ma'am.
-I mean, you--
I'll handle this.
Private Na is receiving treatment
right now.
And these two civilians
have no involvement in this incident.
Well, whatever.
You stay here.
Keep an eye on the one who got shot.
You can come alone, then.
I'll wait out front.
In-a.
I'm sorry.
Did you find the gold bars?
What?
I can't disclose that to you, Sister.
I'll see you later.
If Father Baek was still here,
he would've called them and said,
"I heard some of the members
of my church are being investigated."
"Will it take long?"
Just one call would've helped us.
Who are you?
You.
Put down the gun, or I'll open fire!
Who the hell are you?
Na Hyeon-jae?
Yes, sir.
Where exactly were you hurt?
You shot someone.
A man involved in the case
was aiming at a civilian--
"Involved"?
How did you know he was involved at all?
It seemed so, given the situation.
Did your captain order you to shoot?
That's not…
I see.
So you shot him for no reason.
MARTIAL LAW COMMAND, WOONGCHEON
JOINT INVESTIGATION UNIT
The curfew has been lifted.
The current time and date
is 5 a.m., September 4th, 2025.
Due process?
As it was an urgent situation,
it required an ex post facto approval.
The circumstances
of child confinement and abuse--
So you decided to trespass
onto private property.
On top of that, a civilian was shot.
In what universe would that be approved?
The gravity of the situation
called for an investigation.
A report was made by a victim,
and Clause Three, Section Two
of the martial law says--
That's not why martial law exists!
Capt. Kang.
Reverted to the national treasury.
If one person had that much, there must be
a lot more where that came from.
Funds for the escape, I guess?
I wonder how much the total cost would be
for a chartered plane,
investment, and settlement.
I did my own calculations.
Since it was a pyramid scheme,
I have no idea how many people signed up.
But most of those people
must've been scammed, don't you think?
In-seong was so handsome.
According to the kids,
Capt. Kang brought the military
to the scene and helped Ms. Jin,
which is why they were able to escape.
Since they were kids, In-a's always
been there to help Se-kyung when needed.
Right.
By the way, is your daughter okay?
Yes.
I felt like my heart had stopped.
But you know how kids are.
They're just playing
as if nothing happened.
Goodness, that's a relief, then.
With the way things are now,
you never know what's going to happen.
Oh my, careful!
Well, even so,
who could've guessed that the kids
would do something like that on their own?
Anyway, the kids said they saw gold bars.
Have you heard anything from the church?
I knew there was a reason
you suddenly volunteered to help.
No, it's…
Don't get me wrong.
The church was burned,
and the extension funds disappeared,
but now there's talk of gold bars, so…
Well, Sister Regina seemed curious
about that too.
Hey,
if we had just one of those gold bars,
we could all escape--
Start wiping.
-Okay.
-Careful.
How do they manage the gold?
What has the Board of Audit been doing?
Where did the gold found
at the training center come from?
I'm curious as to how the gold exchange
is viewing this situation.
So, usually,
gold ETF operators are supposed to have
gold in their actual possession.
They pay a fee and store it
in the vault of a trust bank.
This is insurance for any contingencies,
but it's only partially guaranteed. Why?
Because no thief would be able
to carry it all out anyway.
It is the responsibility
of the Board of Audit
to check if the gold ETF operators
have gold regularly.
So how did this happen?
All the money that disappeared
from the church was turned into gold,
but I don't find that surprising. Why?
When the stock markets are volatile,
people prefer safe assets like gold.
But here's the problem.
How on earth did they manage
to amass the massive pile of gold
that was found at the training center?
Gold is meant to be thoroughly managed
by ETF operators and the gold exchange,
yet a pile of it has just been found.
There's only one way to explain all this.
That all of this was planned in advance!
Eternal life!
This plot was in motion
a year before the asteroid was announced.
The gold management regulations
are already a mess.
I am deeply concerned
about the impact this situation will have
on the global economy in the future!
But don't forget, everyone.
I say we're stronger than gold.
We're stronger than gold!
Eternal life!
When the asteroid hits,
eternal life begins!
Do not doubt.
Our future selves are waiting for us.
-Do not doubt.
-Man, what the heck?
-A new, inextinguishable sun burns.
-I thought he was onto something.
Though the asteroid might end the world
Walk toward the center of the light
You will find no death or extinction
The theory of promise is forever true
There's this woman I know.
She says she's pregnant.
And she's not sure
whether to keep the baby or not.
But if the baby's born now,
it won't make it to its first birthday.
Hey.
Who is this woman?
Is it Se-kyung?
It's not Se-kyung!
It's just
someone I know.
Meanwhile, here we are
just digging spinach!
And some bastards out there
are planning on escaping with gold.
Right?
I hope the gold bars are
a good sign for the new baby.
Those darn gold bars.
I wish I could just have a look at them.
Maybe we'll find some if we keep digging.
Is that never going to happen?
You're a greedy woman!
Se-kyung told me
to get you to sleep before leaving.
It's just as you said.
What?
Every day, I'm learning new sides
of Se-kyung I never knew about.
All the things I didn't know about her.
The way you see her is finally changing.
She's not just a cheerful girl, you know.
I didn't have to know all this.
If it wasn't for the end of the world,
you wouldn't have found out.
In a world like this…
do we all just end up becoming fools?
Se-kyung, me.
All of us.
The end of the world…
and the fool.
As you may know,
I'm a famous media figure
who spent many years
hosting an eponymous program
for an influential media outlet.
For your migration plan
to progress smoothly,
you need to turn
the public's eye elsewhere.
If you were to put me to good use…
Excuse me, ma'am.
Director? Chairwoman!
We don't want anyone's devotion.
Devote yourself to your family instead.
If they come with you voluntarily,
touched by your devotion,
then I'll reconsider.
That's not hard at all.
I'll come back with my family!
So you approve, right?
There was a slight hiccup,
but our migration plan
will go ahead as planned.
After completing payment for the plane,
we will board on the scheduled date.
I think you should show us proof.
I will give you proof
as long as you make a pledge of secrecy.
If this gets out,
the children may be in danger.
It could also provoke the public
and lead to a second riot.
-I'll make that pledge.
-Me too!
Yes, I pledge too!
So do I!
We…
will be flying
with the leaders and officials
of the shadow cabinet.
Here they are.
That's…
-Right?
-Yes!
Show us too!
In other words,
the entire process of our migration plan
is top secret
and is being meticulously supervised.
Code blue.
Surgical critical care unit, second floor.
Doctor.
Make way.
Code blue.
Surgical critical care unit, second floor.
Manager Im died while receiving treatment.
One, two, three.
Nurse Kim, bring me the LUCAS.
Yes, Doctor.
What are you doing without notice?
All the children from the training center,
including Chae Young-han, are witnesses.
I'm following orders--
From whom? Who gave those orders?
You're just repeating the same words!
The JIU investigation is the priority.
But
I'm Young-han's family, so please.
Family visits are also not allowed.
"Not allowed"?
Under whose authority are you doing this?
No, Manager Im. From the training center.
He's dead!
Yeah.
Cardiac arrest?
Just as expected.
They have no creativity at all.
Those are for you. Eat up, okay?
Hey, pass me the ball!
-It's coming.
-Salute!
Good work.
-Get some rest.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Are you okay, ma'am?
-I'm fine.
Manager Im is dead.
Yes, Ms. Deputy Mayor.
They banned all visitations
for the children.
Yes, out of the blue.
-Yes.
-Hey.
Young-han meant to tell you this
during his counseling session.
It's about Father Baek.
Young-han saw him.
Young-han did?
He saw Father Baek?
-Yes.
-When? Where?
He went to the place where Father Baek was
a few times to perform.
The training center owns
several prayer houses.
The place Young-han went to
was probably one of them.
WOOYANG TRAINING CENTER OPENS
WOOYANG TRAINING CENTER
ACCESSORY BUILDINGS - ADDRESS
Someone saw Father Baek…
at one of these addresses.
Let's go…
FATHER WOO SUNG-JAE
CAPTAIN KANG IN-A
Do not be deceived,
not by the wiles of someone
who hides in the--
Father!
Perhaps you should reconsider.
If this goes wrong…
I'll take responsibility, no matter what.
Did you hear that?
Why didn't you turn the lights on?
You should get some rest.
The more desperately I want you…
the more I seem to ruin things.
No.
It's my fault.
I should've thrown it out.
I found the real deal.
WOOYANG TRAINING CENTER
This is a safe organization
that prioritizes the value of family.
This time, it's for real.
I don't intend to drag you there.
Ha-yul.
I'll be good to you, okay?
I'll lead by example
so you can trust me and…
Yes.
I'll do this. How's this?
-What's up with this?
-The power's out.
-Huh?
-The power is out.
Really?
Okay, then.
Ha-yul, anything you want to eat?
I'll get you whatever you want. Like…
Seriously, what is wrong with him?
We've got instant noodles!
Packet or cup?
When a person changes too much,
it's creepy.
You know my younger brother,
Seok Tae in Pyongyang?
Yeah.
His family was dragged to Chŏngju
to mine for gold.
My other sibling in Dandong told me.
Pyongyang is a mess right now.
It's completely empty.
Everyone's been taken away to mine
for gold, zinc, and rare-earth elements.
They work 12-hour shifts
so all the rare minerals can be mined
before the asteroid hits.
It's just like the Chollima Movement.
Don't even talk about that stuff.
They're not being fed,
and I only get word that they are dying.
Hey, just eat up.
Don't think about anything else.
Okay? Eat your fill.
The engineering building is empty.
All the guys in the lab are…
They left.
I get to have the lab all to myself,
which is nice.
It's good to see you again.
For me…
it feels a bit awkward
to even ask how you've been.
So… why did you come back?
Why didn't you leave?
Young people are the useful ones.
Who'd want a withering old man like me?
-Professor.
-Yes, Gi-pyo.
I was able to get hold of the dissertation
you mentioned last time.
You should come with us
and see Yun-sang win the Nobel Prize.
There will be good news soon.
Dr. Ha.
The director of the lab
would really like to see you.
Stop by before you leave, okay?
Gi-pyo came looking for you
multiple times, right?
I don't know
what Gi-pyo has in store for you,
but, as for me, I feel bad for you.
At my age,
it doesn't seem like a bad idea
to witness the end of the world firsthand.
But
you're different.
Designing genetic variation
will be a key project in the safe zones.
You can't let it go to waste.
From what I heard,
apparently…
this will be the last opportunity
to get out of this country.
STATEMENT
NAME: NA HYEON-JAE
Fuck.
Hey.
Hey!
Hey, I heard you killed someone.
You're a murderer. A freakin' psychopath.
I can't sleep at night
because of you, you damn psychopath!
Kim Hyeon-sik.
Look at you!
I'm genuinely surprised
at the crap you just said.
Hyeon-sik.
You see, the real psychopath
is me.
Come here.
Come here. It's okay.
I'm not gonna bite you.
This is a great spot. A VIP seat.
Sit.
Cackle?
Why don't you give this bastard
a peck on the lips?
One, two, three!
Fuck!
Rip out his snout!
That idiot is dumber than a chicken.
Man, I'm tired.
-Ma'am!
-Hi.
Ma'am!
-Captain!
-Yeah?
Hey, guys! Hurry!
They laid eggs.
-They did it.
-They laid eggs.
Good job, Cackle!
Yes, ma'am.
You were only carrying out your mission.
Now focus on your duties here.
-Yes, ma'am.
-That's right!
You went through a lot.
-Hey, Ji-su.
-Yes, ma'am?
Take a break with him.
Come on.
And how would you know
that he went through a lot, Sergeant?
Bang!
Someone's been busy.
Ma'am.
Sergeant, the JIU is here looking for you.
-They're looking for her?
-Yes.
Please excuse me.
Ma'am.
-Bye, ma'am.
-Ma'am.
-Understood, sir.
-This way.
-Does this go here?
-Yeah.
Hey, bring that one here.
Sir.
Is Capt. Kang getting canned?
Stop picking on the others and leave now.
I'll put you on the discharge list.
Sorry?
The disciplinary action isn't an issue.
It was internal anyway. I won't stop you.
Nothing but a load
of oxygen thieves here anyway.
Bunch of duds.
Shut it!
I'll leave now.
Check all the firearms.
Seize all the ammunition,
including that used for guard duty.
Yes, sir.
Hey, you don't want to mop?
Then get discharged, asshole!
Yeah, that mop smells like shit.
Fuck this shit!
That bastard's pissed off.
-He's pissed.
-Stupid morons.
Kim, you poor bastard.
-I have better places to be.
-Seriously, I want him gone.
-What's on the menu today?
-When is he going to leave?
Hey.
-First Sergeant Park, sir.
-What is it?
This is Sergeant Kim.
-I'm deleting this too.
-Everybody's busy talking about gold.
They don't even care that Capt. Kang
and Ms. Jin saved the kids.
Well, it's exciting news.
It wasn't a whole ton,
but it's still 500 kg of gold.
With that, any country would accept you.
Do we have to live like this
until the very end?
Deleting disgusting videos.
I'm so sick of this.
Yeah, the asteroid
will wipe all this stuff out anyway.
Gross!
It's a tragedy that I'm reminded of my dad
every time I do this.
I think I'm going crazy!
Now he wants to talk to us.
Whoa.
Is that even possible?
What do you think?
Father.
How did you come out of there?
Did you know about this passageway?
No, I just found out now.
The footage showed me.
The church extension funds
must be in those suitcases, right?
Where have I seen that driver before?
The man stood next to him is Manager Im,
the man who died of a heart attack.
Isn't this shocking?
I mean, where was Father Baek going
with all of that?
Abandoning us too?
You're glad, aren't you?
Father Baek might actually be alive.
Father,
can you send this to your phone?
It doesn't work on mine.
My phone's too old.
It won't work, no matter how hard I try.
So I was about to rip this out and--
Where are you trying to send this?
To whom?
Don't tell me you're…
Don't you worry.
I may talk a bit too freely sometimes,
but I'm not that thoughtless.
Give me your phone.
Dear Lord…
today,
I couldn't help but think of this quote
from the Book of Psalms
that Father Baek would often cite
and give us as topics for contemplation.
"Remember…
how frail…
the sons of man you have created."
-Why are you coming so late?
-I'm sorry!
-Oh no, we're late!
-Yun-sang!
Hi there!
Look here.
Say cheese! One, two, three!
Eat now.
Don't spill your food!
-Hey, that's mine.
-Get out of here!
-Don't do that.
-Seriously, Ji-eun!
Take this!
-Leave them be. They're in love.
-Having fun?
So you're not closing
the supermarket for good?
Of course not. We have Ji-eun here.
And Sister Gye Hyang over there
is about to bite the dust…
I mean, since her days are numbered,
she said she wanted to try something new.
But you're going to keep Moira open?
I love coming here
and listening to music once in a while.
Of course, madam!
Of course we'll keep it open.
But why isn't Sister Chae-hwan here yet?
Speaking of which,
why isn't our dear In-a here yet?
-Stop it.
-Hey.
Isn't In-a dating anyone these days?
-Zip it now!
-But why not?
Hey, Se-kyung! Yun-sang!
Listen, the two of you.
Go to the bishop
and have your nuptial Mass.
-That's right! Yeah!
-Yeah, do it already!
-Do it now!
When will you do it?
I'm leaving soon!
Hey, wait.
-Take our picture. Do it now.
-Oh my!
-Me too!
-Go away!
-Hey!
-This is our picture.
-Let's take it!
Smile and say cheese!
Cheese!
Yeah, this is great.
-Did it come out good? Not yet?
-We have to wait!
Right, next up,
a parting word from Mi-ryeong!
I hate you!
All right, then.
We'll hear two words from her!
Go on, say it.
This is so embarrassing.
Come on, now.
Please don't cry!
This country is about to go down,
and our end is drawing near anyway,
so why am I doing this?
I guess I just want to do something
I wouldn't usually do.
Gee, I don't know!
Come here.
-Hey, why me? What?
-Just…
So, ever since
we came to Woongcheon together,
we've been running Wondermart and Moira.
Well, as for Wondermart,
Ji-eun will take good care of it.
And I'm sure you'll all keep
cherishing Moira, right?
As for me,
since this man right here says
he'll stay by my side…
I really didn't want to cry.
What's wrong with me?
-I really didn't…
-Don't cry.
-Don't cry!
-Mi-ryeong!
-Don't cry.
-Don't cry!
Don't cry.
Myeong-ok, come here.
-Let me get a hug from you.
-Yeah.
Oh dear.
Don't go! Just don't!
Don't go.
Goodness, they're all crying.
-Stay healthy.
-I'm telling you not to go.
Hey!
Let's take a group picture
for the Woongcheon FCC, okay?
-Come here.
-Let's not cry, okay?
FFC. It's "FFC."
The camera is ready!
-FFC.
-Yeah, the F whatever.
-You have to come together.
-Gather around.
-Woongcheon FFC.
-Got a war cry?
Fine, then. Forever Woongcheon!
-Woongcheon!
-Woongcheon FFC!
This must be the last picture
we'll take together before we die.
Together to the end!
TOGETHER TO THE END!
D-154
You got discharged? Bastard!
Hey, when did you get here?
Wait. Get out of the way.
You haven't eaten, right? Let's eat.
Come here, kid.
Say hi. You'll be working together now.
Sit.
Sit down.
Forget the army chow. Let's eat real food.
You know Manager Jeong's boys, right?
You'll be in charge of them.
You said you'd hook me up with a broker
who would get me to the US.
Drink up.
Wait, what are you doing?
Wait just a second!
There is no gun.
He doesn't seem like the one.
Why do you keep looking for a gun on me?
This fucking sucks.
-Hyeon-sik.
-Sergeant Park.
Aren't these supposed to be sent
to the Special Missions Unit?
So Ju-yeon.
A soldier must do what they're told.
Keep your mouth shut.
-See? I told you.
-Hyeon-sik, take this.
God, I'm exhausted.
-Did you check that?
-Of course we did.
The ammunition we had hidden there
disappeared without a trace.
It wasn't you, and it wasn't So Ju-yeon.
Sucks for you, eh?
Well, it sucks for me too.
Of the boys who played
with the guns, one's dead,
one's gone missing,
and one's had a heart attack.
Anyway, be careful.
Things aren't looking good.
For whatever shady stuff they did,
they want us to lay low.
Fuck, we have to make a score somehow.
Hey, call Manager Jeong.
Hey, good job.
-Same food for the late-night snack?
-Yeah.
Hyeon-sik, the food's getting cold.
Hurry up and eat.
Man, you're one hopeless grunt,
wearing that uniform around.
We got big rooms up on the second floor.
Pick one and use it.
You look even uglier without your uniform.
Shut up.
What do you want?
I have to ask you something.
What? If I have a girlfriend?
Snap out of it, dude.
Well…
can you get me a gun
or something like that?
Hey. What are you talking about?
You were a soldier.
I'm sure you didn't leave empty-handed.
Not even the officers
can do stuff like that.
But instead…
Get over here.
What?
Give it some thought, okay?
Where did everyone go?
They didn't even eat their meals.
What is that?
Goodness, that little…
Father.
Father, open…
Father Woo Sung-jae.
-Let me.
-Okay.
Damn!
Hey, Sung-jae!
Fasting won't change anything!
You have new data in your head,
so come out and start utilizing it.
Are you praying again?
Does praying change anything?
Woo Sung-jae, open the door!
We should make a plan together!
Woo Sung-jae!
Open the door, Woo Sung-jae!
Sung-jae.
We have to find the link.
Like how Father Baek is connected
to those people.
As you know, my hands are tied right now.
If I do anything, I bet…
Just focus on feeding your soldiers.
Yun-sang, let me use your car.
Where are you going?
Yun-sang, I brought the director with me.
Dr. Ha.
I heard you came by a few times
but never once visited us.
How could you do that?
Well, I'm sorry.
He's not blaming you, okay?
Of course not.
Now's not the time to be nitpicky.
Dr. Ha.
I happened to get my hands on
a bottle of fine liquor.
Using this as an excuse,
I came to you first
to settle any bad feelings.
What do you say?
I'll come visit you at the lab.
Right now, Se-kyung is--
Right, she's welcome to join us too!
Yeah, how about it?
I'm really sorry, sir.
-Yun-sang!
-Dr. Ha!
Is he…
He still doesn't understand the situation.
The kid's too naive, you know.
Yeah, right. He's not naive.
Come on!
Se-kyung! Hey!
Kang In-a!
Se-kyung!
This is Ha Yun-sang.
Well…
Mr. Song.
Here. It's a bulletproof vest.
Put it on first.
I'm going solo this time for real.
What are you saying? Just put it on.
It'll only take a minute.
You don't even have bullets.
Soldiers have a duty to protect civilians.
I'm just going to check
and come right back.
Se-kyung.
Do you believe that finding Father Baek
will lead you to a solution?
I wish.
We all saw the video on the dashcam.
Father Baek ran away and--
No, he's still here.
Young-ji's little brother saw him
at some kind of country house.
What?
I thought there was nothing I could do
after the church had burned
and the money had vanished.
-But--
-Se-kyung.
In the end, we're all going to--
But there are things we can still do now.
If I find him,
I'll beg him if I have to.
Beg him?
To send the remaining kids to a safe zone?
You should all join me, then.
Yun-sang, Sung-jae, you.
Everyone.
Me alone won't be enough.
Don't worry. I'm just going to check
and come right back.
At least wear this while I can see you.
It's an older model, so it's a bit heavy.
But it's the least you can do
to reassure me.
Hurry.
I'm really busy right now,
but I'm putting this on for you.
Hey!
Waiting won't kill you.
-I put it on.
-But a bullet will.
Or an asteroid will?
Seriously, that mouth of yours.
Don't worry. I'll be back, okay?
Don't worry. I'll be right back.
-You promised. Okay?
-Yeah.
Yeah, I promise.
You're doing well for yourself.
All the other shops closed down
because they couldn't get the ingredients.
The nightclub managers provide it all.
Where do they get it?
Who knows?
Heck, they charge me too much.
I might as well quit doing this.
They say the ration will be increasing,
so at least I won't starve to death.
Do you happen to know the managers here?
Everyone is a manager here.
Manager Lee, Manager Kim.
It's all bullshit.
Well, this guy doesn't work in this area.
He oversees the accounting
for an organization.
And it seems like
he's close to the people here. Wait.
This man is Manager Im.
I heard he died.
So you know him.
Whenever Father Baek visited,
he'd lecture Im
about becoming a better man.
Bae Jong-su, Manager Lee, Manager Im.
I don't get why those nightclub managers
tried to pay him off.
What were they hoping to get?
Sergeant.
-Please step out of the car.
-Sir!
Sir.
Well, well. Nice to see you here.
What's going on?
Huh?
I'm going on.
Will you be okay?
Yes, thank you. Can you leave now?
Sure.
You should close your window.
There are still mosquitos.
You know someone in the JIU?
He said to call if I needed help.
I can't let you meet him alone.
Close the window.
There are already mosquitoes in here.
Oh, okay.
First,
we should ask him what happened.
See if he admits
to the things we already know.
Take care.
And I'm driving.