END OF THE WORLD
ASTEROID COLLISION IN 200 DAYS
ASTEROID COLLISION IMMINENT
MARTIAL LAW DECLARED
199 DAYS LEFT
CHANCES OF SURVIVAL?
NO INTERNET CONNECTION
198 DAYS LEFT
TOGETHER TO THE END
140 DAYS LEFT
COLLISION CRISIS ALERT
CHEONDONG MIDDLE SCHOOL CLOSED
DO NOT APPROACH
130 DAYS LEFT
SUPERMAN AND WONDERMART
MISSING
BASED ON THE NOVEL SHUMATSU NO FURU
BY KOTARO ISAKA
80 DAYS LATER, OUR ETERNAL LIFE BEGINS
EXPERIENCE THE ETERNAL LIFE
50 DAYS UNTIL THE END
FLOATING BUNKER PRESENTATION
Hey, why isn't your teacher coming?
Did she abandon you?
Stop.
-What are you doing?
-Ms. Jin!
-Speak of the devil.
-Move.
We could use your help. She won't listen.
Ms. Jin, I really wasn't trying
to do anything bad.
Help with what?
She's not paying her maintenance fee.
I know her business is thriving.
I told her we accept ration tickets,
but she won't pay up.
Ration tickets.
Take all you want. This is all I have.
So-min, come here.
Are you okay? You're not hurt?
I'm okay.
Good.
I want that.
Are you sure you're okay?
-Yes.
-You must be scared.
Yes.
-It's okay.
-Hey, lady.
He said you should buy a new bike.
"Just you wait.
I'll make things fun for you."
JUST YOU WAIT
I'LL MAKE THINGS FUN FOR YOU
When the time stands still
You're asleep, I come to you
The world gets in my way
But I end up by your side
My long journey's finally over
And now I go back
Back to you, my home
Again, I'm on my way back home
The world might end tomorrow,
but today I dance!
I'm gonna dance!
Sister! Great moves!
You used to party back in the day!
It's just like a drawer
That keeps opening by itself
You fly high up to the sky
But you always come back to me
Leaving you was never easy
Everything's how we left it
All together now!
You said she'd be right back.
She's on her way. It was nothing serious.
Here's a gift!
A gift?
Thank you!
These are the last two bottles I have,
so my heart is breaking.
Go have fun.
Enjoy the wine somewhere else.
Go. I'll clean up here. Go!
You…
Do you really want to see your mom dead?
Who, you?
I doubt that would happen.
You said you wanted to live!
What was that?
So-min, stop it. Go inside.
My baby.
Ms. Jin, this child is so immature.
Why do I have to be mature? You aren't.
-You brat!
-Hey.
Yeah, your mother is ignorant,
uneducated, and immature.
It must be nice to be smart.
Where was she?
Gye Hyang, it's late. Go inside.
-I'll leave this here.
-Bye.
-Se-kyung, I'm really sorry.
Good night, Gye Hyang.
Se-kyung!
Hey.
Are you okay?
Yeah. The car ran out of gas, that's all.
I dropped the car off at the church
and walked here.
Let's go.
Let's go!
What's wrong? Are you hurt?
-Don't touch me.
-I touched you?
When was the last time
we took a night walk together like this?
I know, right?
It feels like ages ago.
-So you have butterflies?
-What?
That's what you said earlier.
No, I'm just wondering
if Yun-sang is okay.
What about you?
Are you really okay?
Cheers.
This stuff is so good!
I should've drank more of it when I could.
A guy once said
he didn't get drinking wine
because it was distasteful yet expensive.
Now, who was that guy?
-Me?
-That's what you said.
Then you called Sung-jae "pretentious."
What an act of blasphemy.
Truly blasphemous.
I wish we could spend
our last moments like this too.
Did we finish it?
Yeah, it's empty.
We drank it all.
Yes, we did.
Still, it feels good.
When did you get those?
Well-prepared as always.
Congratulations.
Big congratulations in advance!
Save the dance, please.
-Se-kyung.
-Yeah?
You still do soccer these days?
-Sung-jae!
-What?
Those aren't soccer cleats.
They are for mountain biking.
Try to catch up, Father!
Did you say "do soccer"?
Are you trying to sound dumb or what?
Or is that a way of sounding humble?
Drink more.
Someone's gonna get tipsy.
It's getting late.
Let's finish Se-kyung's glass and leave.
No, you should leave when the curfew ends.
-I have more drinks.
-It's okay.
-I have more drinks. Come.
-You do?
-"Go."
-My grandma made it.
Have a taste.
-In-a, you should try it.
-What?
Yeah, let's have a little taste.
What do you say?
Yun-sang, you remember this, right?
She made this
a month before she passed away.
Yeah, I do remember.
But I also remember
that it was made for a different occasion.
She wanted us to keep it
and drink it at our wedding.
When will the four of us
drink together again?
Let's have one more--
-No, we have somewhere to go.
-Just one more drink.
-Come on!
-Shall we?
-Hey.
-We're leaving!
Are soldiers and priests allowed
to break curfew and wander around?
What? No, we are going on a patrol.
Sung-jae, we talked about this.
He's exempt tonight
since he's my assistant.
How admirable!
I opened the lid.
-Thanks for your service.
-In-a.
Have another drink before you go.
-We'll get going.
-We should hurry…
Off you go.
-Bye.
-Good night!
Isn't it a miracle?
Yun-sang and Se-kyung being together
in that warm, loving light.
Seriously, please.
Stop being so sentimental.
This is the Martial Law Command.
-In-a.
-What?
-Capt. Kang.
I'm exempt, right?
Is it really okay for me
to be out during curfew?
It is.
Yeah?
You offered that up so easily.
She made that for our wedding.
You want to have a wedding?
That's the reason I came back.
That's all I have left now.
To give you the best moment of your life.
It still does that.
I find it funny how it goes off randomly.
For now, let's clean up before we sleep.
For now?
Yeah.
Easy.
Why are you trying to carry
all those in one hand?
I don't know why,
but I've always wanted to try this.
-It looks cool, you know.
-Be careful.
Are you okay?
Serves me right.
Don't you think?
I'm sorry.
Se-kyung…
It's okay, Se-kyung.
Wait just a sec.
-I said it's okay.
-No, Yun-sang.
-Let me.
-Se-kyung.
-I'll do it. What's with you today?
-No!
-I'll put the Band-Aid on after I wash it.
-Fine.
Why this neighborhood of all places?
To ensure public safety around here.
And I also remembered that you know
a few people in this part of town.
Hey, I only know a handful of people.
It was Father Baek who had the big shots
in the palm of his hands.
The apocalypse doesn't seem
to affect this place.
Doesn't the curfew start in 30 minutes?
In-a, watch out.
He should not be riding in a narrow alley.
Father! What brings you here at this hour?
Have a seat. I'll make you some noodles.
No, thank you.
My friend here just got a little lost.
There's still no news
on Father Baek, is there?
Unfortunately not.
Oh no! I'm so worried about him!
The thing is, he appeared
in my dream and said, "Stella!"
He called me by my baptismal name.
"Stella, confess your sins!"
Hyeon-sik.
Hey, Kim Hyeon-sik.
You with the long hair, what's your deal?
Come here.
-Come over here, kid.
-Okay.
Hey, this is chicken.
Have it all for yourself.
Thank you, sir.
Sergeant Kim?
-Yes?
-Come here.
-Hey, give me one of those.
-Yes, sir.
This will take you to another world.
No, thanks.
-It's a new product.
-What?
-This stuff is strong.
-I'm okay.
Just take it, kiddo.
I'm just saying you'll end up dead
if you take it all at once, boy.
Thank you.
Go jerk off like crazy.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
When can I go to confess?
I have to confess all of my sins
before the asteroid comes.
What do I do?
-I'll be able to go to heaven, right?
-Yes.
I mean, this is the only way
I can make a living.
The brothel and the gambling house
are connected.
It might look like First Sergeant Park
is running them with discharged soldiers,
but the escaped convicts
are managing everything.
I've sent countless anonymous reports,
but the Joint Investigation Unit
won't budge.
Are you saying the JIU is protecting
the escaped convicts?
I think there's someone above the JIU.
There's a rumor going around
that the money from this area
is being funneled into one place.
By the way, Capt. Kang,
the JIU is still looking for
the missing ammunition.
Will it be okay for you
to take part in this operation?
197 DAYS UNTIL ASTEROID COLLISION
Greetings, citizens of Woongcheon.
This is Deputy Mayor Im Seon-ju.
All supplies are running short,
including daily necessities.
And the city is rampant
with various frauds promising escape.
We declare that Woongcheon City will take
strong action against all crimes.
By joining hands
with the Martial Law Command…
-Yun-sang.
-Oh God!
-Sorry.
-Se-kyung.
I'm taking off.
I wanted to give you a ride.
But I just can't fix this thing.
No, it's okay. I'll see you tonight.
Okay.
-Se-kyung.
-Yeah?
Your bike isn't here.
It's at the city hall.
Bye.
See you tonight.
We were born as men
Of all the things men must do
You and I lived for the honor…
Don't go this way. Go to the coop!
Ma'am, I have something
to discuss with you.
-Captain.
-Yeah?
I'd like you to attend
the completion ceremony.
The completion ceremony?
Yes, it's right this way.
Fall into formation.
Second platoon returning from night shift.
-Okay.
-Ma'am.
Good work.
Sergeant Kim Hyeon-sik,
when are you leaving the army?
-Good work.
-Thank you, ma'am.
All right.
Our first and last fertility project
will be a success no matter what.
To the chief,
and to the rest of the tribe,
salute.
Salute!
As you were.
Now we will proceed
with the ribbon cutting.
Let's go!
You did a good job.
This will last ten years!
We have 198 days left, sir.
It's 197 days.
Give it up!
Where's Pang? Is he off-duty?
-I'm here, sir!
-Right.
Let's go. Please, just go!
That chicken's killing him.
Hey, take it easy!
Thank you, sir.
I was talking to the chicken.
Climb up, please.
Isn't that the hen?
Why can't they tell the difference?
Sergeant.
I want a one-on-one
with every sergeant in each platoon.
-Let's start with the headquarters.
-Yes, ma'am.
Ms. Jin said not to go out and about.
If we pay the collectors,
they give it to the managers.
Who do the managers pay, then?
Any remaining powerful people?
But it's not even in dollars.
The real rich people left a long time ago.
Right at the last moment,
when the government-in-exile leaves Korea,
they'll be issuing national bonds
in exchange for banknotes.
That's what my dad said.
You sound really smart,
but I didn't understand any of that.
Does that mean
the Korean government is moving?
-To where?
-North Korea will move to western China.
It will become an autonomous region.
China's gonna make some room for them.
I don't care about all that.
I want to make a deal with someone
like Sergeant Kim and buy a gun.
Keep it down.
The kids can hear you.
So are you saying
you're going to make a deal with him
by giving him what he wants?
Dirty, homemade videos or whatever?
Ma'am. Sergeant Kim Hyeon-sik reporting.
Hi. Sit down.
I know you worked the night shift.
Sorry to wake you up.
I heard you offered to work overnight
in place of your subordinates.
The command wants us to discharge
all those who apply, regardless of rank.
But you haven't applied yet
when your discharge is way overdue.
They want fewer mouths to feed
'cause supplies are low.
If you ask me, I'd rather
we stay together until the very end,
but… should anyone think it's meaningless
to remain a soldier in this situation,
I will respect their decision.
It's not that I have
no complaints here, but…
If you could enjoy your life in abundance
with like-minded people,
I don't see a reason for you
to maintain your status as a soldier.
I don't really have any plans,
and there's nothing much
I can do out there anyway.
If that's the case, let's try to get along
in the remaining time.
As a member of the army,
if you have any inappropriate connections,
I advise you to cut ties with them.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Come to me if you need help.
I'll be waiting.
Did she fucking see something?
Shit, that was spooky as hell.
Fuck.
Damn it,
are you seriously sleeping right now?
What you gonna do about the bunker?
You scared me. Seriously.
-That's why you're here?
-Aren't you gonna go for it?
Are you just gonna sit here and die?
You can go ahead if you have the money.
For God's sake.
-Why is he always wearing sunglasses?
-Dae-han, is Mi-ryeong here?
-Yun-sang, welcome.
-Hi.
Is that the US guy?
I heard you came from the US.
Yes.
Well,
my daughter, Ha-yul,
used to be Ms. Jin's student,
so I know Ms. Jin very well.
Hi, how are you?
I wish I could say I was good.
So… Watch out!
So I was wondering,
how did you get here?
Excuse me?
If you came here from the US,
you must know a way out of here.
I'd love to hear what you know.
Stop it.
Tell Mi-ryeong that I stopped by.
Don't do it.
-Are you okay?
-He's bleeding a lot.
-Don't cry.
-Poor boy.
Why are you crying?
Did he hurt himself?
He fell while jumping rope.
Hae-chan makes me jump rope all the time.
I don't want to jump rope.
You have to make your legs stronger.
Do as I say.
Woo-chan, here's some water.
Let's put a Baby Shark Band-Aid on it.
Why are you jumping rope so much?
We need strong legs
to run away to a high place.
High place? Where?
I found a place. It's high up.
Hey, do you think you'll survive
if you avoid the tsunami?
Hey, stop.
When the tsunami comes, we'll already be--
Enough, Jeong Ha-yul.
What did I do?
It's okay.
I know all that too.
-All done.
-Let's go.
Don't be mean to the kids.
What? I just told the truth!
-Oh my!
-They're kids.
Why is the house such a mess?
I cleaned up before I left this morning.
But it's such a relief
to see you all here in the house.
You just said we made a mess.
I'd rather you make a mess at home.
Do you know how anxious I get
when you're out of my sight?
You'll all eat before you go, right?
-Yes.
Okay, let's make potato pancakes.
Potato pancakes.
With the temperatures rising,
the unidentified bodies
are decomposing so badly.
And there are so many of them.
We'll need to forgo funerals from now on.
Se-kyung, you do have a bike.
-What?
-But…
You said your bike was totaled.
You got a new one?
No.
Oh wow.
Your taste in bikes is a little unusual,
but this is practically new.
I heard it's tough
to even get secondhand stuff.
-Good for you, Se-kyung.
-Yeah.
-Perfect for grocery shopping!
-Who goes shopping these days?
It'd be perfect
for a nice, breezy ride around here.
NO CALLER ID
But who put this pinwheel here?
Do you like the bike?
I'll give you the key in person.
This is bait, isn't it?
This is the second time.
He used So-min to feel me out yesterday,
and now he's making his move.
He would want to get rid of me
since I'm bad for his business.
You know what?
I can't handle this on my own.
I've been getting threats
since the day Yun-sang got back.
He called me out
during the welcome party too.
I guess he thinks
that I killed Bae Jong-su.
Text him to say you'll meet him.
Okay.
You all right?
I don't think…
Se-kyung will tell me
everything that happened.
She'll keep a few things secret.
We've all been through a lot.
Not the stuff you've all been through.
Here's some more advice.
We all want to enjoy the short time
we have left as best we can.
But to do that, we must resolve the issues
that have piled up in our lives.
The same goes for relationships.
What are you trying to say?
You were wrong from the beginning.
You said you fell for her
because she was cheerful
and generous, right?
But that's just the way you see her.
People are more complicated than that.
All the advice you give me
really seems like good advice
when I listen to it,
but it has no substance.
That's true.
That's my weakness.
Call me Mr. Good Advice.
-Father!
-Yes?
The phones must not be working again.
I tried to call you so many times.
You did?
You should go
and call the bishop's office.
Those old folks keep calling for me
when I don't even know much.
Don't call them old folks.
The Lord won't be happy with that.
I see a couple of slackers here.
This is no time to be playing tennis!
Hey, I'm getting scolded because of you.
Get going!
Okay.
Maybe they want you
to perform a memorial Mass?
What?
No way.
Take this, asteroid!
-Ma'am.
-Hey.
Ma'am.
-Sergeant.
-Yes.
Please handle
the shift inspection tonight.
Okay.
The platoon leader's heading out too.
So?
Understood, ma'am.
Special Missions Unit, begin operation.
Are you going to apply
for discharge this month?
I have nowhere to go,
and there's nothing for me to do.
Hey, you should go out and do
what you wanna do before the world ends.
That's true.
The subway stations will be shelters
when the asteroid hits?
That's freaking hilarious.
Oops, sorry.
I dropped the keys
on the Platform 2 tracks.
They'll be easy to find.
Be careful on your way.
RESTRICTED AREA
WOONGCHEON CITY
SHELTER NO. 3 CONSTRUCTION SITE
Did you think
you were a hero or something?
Look at you,
following orders because of a stupid bike.
Don't worry, Ms. Jin.
I'll take good care of the kids
until the very end.
What the hell?
Bae Jong-su.
Did you kill him?
Walk straight.
Go get it.
Just shoot me.
Just fucking shoot me!
You fucking…
Don't move!
We found the survivors.
Transport the survivors
to the city hospital for now.
Director Ri, please check inside.
Yeah.
Yes, go inside.
Capt. Kang mobilized
her old SMU teammates.
Let me go!
The isolation and safety
of the survivors are our priorities.
Man, this is total chaos.
I know we are short-staffed.
Request emergency volunteer workers.
Go up there and check things out.
-The JIU is here.
-Go with him.
I'll call you back. Yeah!
Hello!
I didn't expect to see you at this hour.
Isn't the Special Missions Unit amazing?
They found out about the depraved activity
that was going on here.
It looks like
everything's been taken care of.
Hey, don't push!
Don't push me!
The JIU will be handling everything,
from the perpetrators to the victims.
What are you talking about?
Just take the perpetrators!
The teenage girls are clearly the victims!
No, they are survivors
under our jurisdiction.
Right, Lieutenant?
Is Capt. Kang behind this?
I'll give her a call.
Capt. Kang did give us the order.
You don't need to call her.
Take the victims to the health center
and return to your unit.
Understood.
Excuse me,
don't just investigate the perps.
Make sure you put them
behind bars this time!
To hell with your nonsense!
Report to Mr. Song.
Keep First Sergeant Park's mouth shut.
Team Bravo, mission accomplished.
People keep coming out.
We are
accomplices now, right?
In-a.
I only performed my duty as a soldier.
A citizen was in danger, so I saved her.
Nothing more.
So you should stop now.
Do you think that gang will give a hoot
about a few dead minions?
Why are you standing there? Let's go.
I'm not sure.
What are you on about? Get it together--
You said you would live to the end.
So why are you putting yourself in danger?
I don't know.
Leave with Yun-sang.
Get over here!
Come on!